[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
>>> HELLO, EVERYONE, WELCOME TO
"AMANPOUR AND COMPANY."
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP.
>> TREMENDOUS NUMBERS DON'T LIE
>> THE PRESIDENT AND THE
POTENTIAL 2020 RIVALS TAKE TO
TEXAS.
THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY,
CONGRESS APPEARS TO COMPROMISE
ON THE KEEPING THE GOVERNMENT
OPENED.
WE GET THE BORDER STORY FROM THE
REPUBLICAN MAYOR OF EL PASO AND
THE HUMANITARIAN FACE OF
IMMIGRATION FROM THOSE CLOSEST
TO HIM.
>>> PLUS, FEARS OF BIG BROTHER
THE FORMER HOMELAND SECURITY ON
THE DANGERS OF GOVERNMENT UNDER
SURVEILLANCE FROM CHINA TO
AMERICA.
WHEN BAE COLEMAN'S CAREER BEGAN,
SHE DIDN'T NOW KNOW HER COOKBOOK
WOULD MAKE IT TO UNIWORLD.
HER CUISINE IS SERVED THROUGH
EUROPE, ASIA, INDIA AND EUROPE,
ACCORDING TO BAE, TO TRAVEL IS
TO EAT.
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,
EVERYONE, I'M CHRISTIANE
AMANPOUR IN LONDON.
PRSIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S NOT
SATISFIED WITH THE CONGRESSIONAL
BREAK THROUGH TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT OPENED.
HOUSE AND SENATE LEADERS ARE
GIVING THE PRESIDENT SOME FUNDS
FOR BORDER BARRIERS, NOT THE
$5.7 BILLION HE IS DEMANDING.
SPEAKING IN THE CABINET ROOM HE
SAID HE DIDN'T EXPECT ANOTHER
SHUTDOWN, ALSO HE SAID THIS.
>> SO I CAN TELL YOU AM I HAPPY
AT FIRST GLANCE?
I JUST GOT TO SEE IT.
THE ANSWER IS, NO, I'M NOT.
I'M NOT HAPPY.
BUT AM I HAPPY WITH WHERE WE'RE
GOING?
I'LL THRILLED.
BECAUSE WE ARE SUPPLEMENTING
THINGS AND MOVING THINGS AROUND
AND WE'RE DOING THINGS THAT ARE
FANTASTIC AND TAKING FROM FAR
LESS REALLY FROM FAR LESS
IMPORTANT AREAS.
>> SO WHILE NEGOTIATORS WERE
WORKING ON THE DEAL IN
WASHINGTON.
THE PRESIDENT WAS IN EL PASO,
TEXAS LAST NIGHT ON THE BODER
RALLYING HIS WALL-LOVING BASE.
HE ALSO HAD ONE EYE ON THE
DEMOCRATS BETO O'ROURKE.
HE RAN FOR SENATE IN 2018 AND
MIGHT RUN FOR PRESIDENT IN 2020.
AS A CONGRESSMAN, HE REPRESENTED
EMPASS SO.
>> THE PRESIDENT DESCRIBES
MEXICAN IMMIGRANTS AS RAPISTS
AND CRIMINALS.
WE HAVE THE CHANCE TO TELL HIM
AND THE COUNTRY, IMMIGRANTS
COMMIT CRIMES, INCLUDING VIOLENT
CRIMES AT A LOWER RATE THAN DO
AMERICANS WHO WERE BORN IN THIS
COUNTRY EL PASO HAS BEEN THE
SAFEST CITY IN THE UNITED STATES
OF AMERICA, NOT INSPITE OF THE
FACT THAT WE ARE A CITY OF
IMMIGRANTS, BUT BECAUSE WE ARE A
CITY OF IMMIGRANTS.
>> EL PASO HAS BECOME A
TOUCHDOWN OF WALL POLITICS.
THE CITY OF MORE THAN 50 MILES
OF FENCING ALONG THE BORDER.
SO WHAT IS THE PROBLEM THERE,
THE MAYOR JOINS ME NOW.
MAYOR, WELL DOCK BA TO THE
PROGRAM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT EL PASO WOULD HAVE BEEN
A TOUCHSTONE AS I SAID IN THIS
WHOLE POLITICAL DRAMA.
BEFORE WE GET TO THAT, CAN I ASK
YOU ABOUT THE NEWS, WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT THE COMPROMISE DEAL
BEING ON BOARD SECURITY TO TRY
TO KEEP THE GOVERNMENT OPENED
AND AFLOAT?
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY SEEN
ANYTHING IN THE HEADLINES ON THE
NEWS ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY OF THE
SPECIFICS.
I'M PROBABLY NOT ALLOWED TO
COMMENT.
FROM MY TIME IN THE LEGISLATURE
I WOULD SAY INCREMENT AM MOVING
UP INCREMENTALLY IS THE WAY TO
DO IT.
ON THE EL PASO PORTRAYERS, THERE
WERE NO WINNERS.
>> YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WE SPENT MANY OF THOSE 35 DAYS
OF GOVERNMENT CLOSURE TALKING TO
SO MANY PEOPLE, FURLOUGHED
FEDERAL WORKERS.
SO MANY PEOPLE WHO HAD SUCH A
HARD TIME GETTING THROUGH AND
SURVIVING THIS SHUTDOWN.
I GUESS YOU ARE SITTING THERE AT
THE NEXUS OF THE GREAT POLITICAL
DRAMA OF OUR TIME.
SO WHEN YOU HAD THE PRESIDENT
AND A POTENTIAL 2020 RIVAL THERE
RALLYING LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
WHAT DID YOU TAKE AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING THAT WAS SAID?
>> I'M NOT SURE THERE WERE ANY
REVELATIONS FROM THE COMMENTS OF
EITHER BETO OR THE PRESIDENT.
I WAS TRYING TO PERSONALLY MEET
WITH THE PRESIDENT BEFOREHAND TO
VISIT WITH HIM.
BECAUSE I'VE SAID FOR MONTHS
THAT IF YOU WANT TO UNDERSTAND
THE BORDER, AND HOW YOU WORK
WITH MEXICO, YOU NEED TO COME TO
THE LARGEST CITY ON THE MEXICO
BORDER THAT HAS BEEN INTERTWINED
FOR ALMOST 400 YEARS, WE
UNDERSTAND IT BETTER, WE'RE THE
PLACE YOU OUGHT TO BE COMING TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> AND YET, DID YOU ACTUALLY MAN
TO SAY THAT TO HIM?
DID YOU MEET HIM?
>> I GOT A HANDSHAKE.
THAT WAS THE EXTENT OF IT.
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD GET MORE
TIME.
THAT WAS TRULY THE EXTENT OF IT.
>> DIFEEL HE WAS NOT TRYING TO
MEET YOU.
HE KNOWS YOU DISAGREE, HAVE YOU
DIFFERENT FACTS AT YOUR DISPOSAL
THAN HE TALKS ABOUT?
I MEAN, DID YOU FEEL IT WAS
DELIBERATE, HE DIDN'T WANT TO
MAKE TIME FOR YOU BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU SAID?
LET'S PLAY WHAT HE'S ACTUALLY
SAID ABOUT YOU.
>> AND THERE IS NO PLACE BETTER
TO TALK ABOUT BORDER SECURITY,
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT,
BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN HEARING A
LOT OF THINGS, OH THE WALL WON'T
MAKE THAT MUCH OF A DIFFERENCE?
YOU KNOW WHERE IT MADE A
DIFFERENCE?
RIGHT HERE IN EL PASO.
I DON'T CARE WHETHER THE SMAR A
REPUBLICAN OR A DEMOCRAT,
THEY'RE NUMBER OF CRAP WHEN THEY
SAY IT HASN'T MADE A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL HEARING THAT?
WHAT WOULD YOU ANSWER BE TO
THAT?
>> I LOVE TO HEAR THAT OVER AND
OVER.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, I'VE NEVER
BEEN AGAINST A PHYSICAL BARRIER
ON THE BORDER.
I THINK THAT'S PART AND PARCEL
TO AN ENTIRE PROCESS.
FROM A STRATEGY STAND POINT IS,
WE'RE IN CONTROL OF THE BORDERS,
WE'RE A SOVEREIGN NATION.
I'VE NEVER DISAGREED WITH THE
PRESIDENT ON THAT, ALL I'VE
TRIED TO DO IS CLARIFY HIS
COMMENTS THAT WE WERE NOT A
LAWLESS COMMUNITY WITH HIGH
CRIME RATES BEFORE THE FENCE
WENT UP UNDER THE BUSH
PRESIDENCY IN 2008.
CERTAINLY IT IS A CONTRIBUTING
FACTOR TOWARDS, TO OUR SAFETY
HERE, BUT IT IS -- IT WAS NOT
THE SOLE PANACEA PRIOR TO,
THAT'S ALL I'VE TRIED TO SAY.
I'VE NOT SPOKEN AGAINST PHYSICAL
BARRIERS OF ANY TYPE.
I THINK THAT'S A PART OF THAT
WHOLE PROCESS.
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER THERE IS
78 MILES OF FENCE IN THE EL PASO
SECTOR FOR THE BORDER CONTROL.
IT'S NOT CONTINUOUS.
A GROUP OF THE FENCING THAT WENT
UP UNDER THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION
IN 2008 WAS PRIMARILY A
REPLACEMENT OF ABOUT TEN MILES
OF CHAIN LINK THAT HAD HOLES IN
IT AND WITH FORESTS.
SO REALLY TO MY KNOWLEDGE, IT
WASN'T EXPANDING THE FENCING.
IT WAS MERELY IMPROVING IT.
>> AND TO YOUR POINT, I DO WANT
TO DIG DOWN, IT IS WORTH
CONSTANTLY PUTTING THE FACTS OUT
THERE ON THE CRIME FIGURES ON
WHAT THE BALL U WALL DID OR
DIDN'T DO AND HOW YOU RESPOND TO
THEM.
IT WAS INTERESTING, BETO
O'ROURKE TALKS ABOUT IT BEING
ONE OF THE SAFEST SECTORS.
IN CALIFORNIA, ALONG THE BORDER,
SORT OF MAKING A POINT THAT
ACTUALLY MANY OF THE CITIES
ALONG THE BORDER ARE SAFER THAN
THOSE FURTHER INLAND.
WOULD YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
>> WELL, FROM OUR STANDPOINT,
YES, FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
EL PASO IS RANKED THE SAFEST
CITY.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO UNIFORM
CRIME STATISTICS REPORTED FROM
THE FBI OR TO THE FBI.
SO A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH
OUR POLICE FORCE AND OUR
COMMUNITY POLICING AND THE
THINGS THAT WE HAVE BEEN DOING
FOR MANY YEARS.
BUT THE ISSUE IS RELATED TO
VIOLENCE WHEN IT CAME TO OUR
REGION HAD TO DO WITH WHAT IS
WITH THE DRUG CARTELS WHEN THEY
WERE FIGHTING IT OUT A FEW YEARS
AGO.
IT NEVER CAME OVER TO EL PASS SO
WE HAVE A SIGNIFICANT LAW
ENFORCEMENT PRESENCE HERE.
PLUS WE HAVE A LARGE MILITARY
PRESENCE.
>> I WANT TO PUT UP THE GRAPH
RIGHT NOW TO TELL PEOPLE WHAT
YOU HAVE BEEN SAYING IN TERMS OF
THE SPIKE IN CRIME AND THE
TROUGH IN CRIME.
SO WE SEE IT WAS VERY HIGH CRIME
RATES IN THE EARLY '90s.
THEN IT STARTED TO DRAMATICALLY
OR DID DRAMATICALLY DROP OFF IN
2006 AND IT STAYED PRETTY LOW
AND THE WALL WAS BUILT AROUND
2008 AND IT WENT UP A BIT.
THE CRIME.
IT PRETTY MUCH STAYED PRETTY
LOW.
SO BASICALLY WHAT YOU ARE SAYING
AND THE GRASS SHOW AND THE FACTS
AND THE NU
EL PASO WAS GETTING SAFER AND
SAFER AND LESS AND LESS CRIME T
PREFER TO USE THE NOMENCLATURE
FENCE, IN CERTAIN NEIGHBORHOODS
FROM AN ANECDOTAL STANDPOINT,
THE RESIDENTS FEEL SAFE BECAUSE
OF THAT.
IT DID THE MOST DRAMATIC DROP IN
OUR CRIME RATE HAD TO OCCUR WITH
AUTOMOBILE THEFTS DURING THAT
TIME FRAME.
SO YOU DON'T HAVE THAT AS A
NUMBER BROKEN OUT.
BUT I'VE SEEN THAT.
BECAUSE WE HAD THE POOREST HOLES
IN THE CHAIN LINK FENCE WERE
COMING OVER, STEALING VEHICLES,
DRIVING THEM BACK TO JUAREZ AND
THAT FENCE HAD A SIGNIFICANT
IMPACT ON THAT SO I'VE SAID FROM
DAY ONE IT HAD AN IMPACT ON
CRIME.
IT HAD AN IMPACT ON THE FEELINGS
OF SECURITY IN CERTAIN
NEIGHBORHOODS.
BUT OVERALL THE CRIME RATE WOULD
NOT DRAMATICALLY DROP.
I FEEL LIKE MY JOB AS A MAYOR IS
TO EXPLAIN TO PEOPLE OUTSIDE
THAT WE WERE NOT LAWLESS CRIME
RIDDEN CITY BEFORE THE FENCE
CAME IN.
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY.
IT'S THE SIXTH LARGEST CITY IN
THE STATE OF TEXAS AND THE 19th
LARGEST CITY IN THE UNITED
STATES.
WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND THE
REST OF THE WORLD NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> SO YOU JUST SAID, I DON'T
KNOW WHETHER YOU TERM IT A PETTY
CRIME OR NON-DRUG-RELATED CRIME
AND NON-VIOLENT CRIME.
YOU TALK ABOUT HOW IT STOPS SOME
AUTO THEFT AND PERHAPS PROPERTY
CRIMES AS WELL, SO THERE WAS
THAT POSITIVE AS PICTURE TO THE
FENCE.
BUT ON THE ISSUES THAT THE
PRESIDENT TALKS ABOUT, WHETHER
IT'S ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION WHETHER
IT'S DRUGS, YOU KNOW, HE'S
CONJURED UP YOU KNOW HOARDS OF
RACISTS AND MURDERS COMING OVER,
IT HAVEN HAD AN EFFECT, RIGHT
THE WALL?
IS THERE THAT CRISIS I GUESS I'M
TRYING TO SAY AT EL PASO AT THE
BORDER.
>>.
>> WELL, LET ME STATE THE
PHYSICAL BARRIERS, ACCORDING TO
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION
AND THE POLICE DO CHANNEL PEOPLE
AND DRUG IN CERTAIN AREAS.
MOST OF THE DRUGS THAT ARE
PICKED UP ILLEGALLY COME THROUGH
OUR PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO A PHYSICAL BARRIER CHANNEL
PEOPLE IN A CERTAIN WAY.
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE TOTAL
RESOLUTION TO BORDER SECURITY.
WHICH NOBODY SEEMS TO FULLY
DEFINE ANYWAY OUT OF WALK.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THE GEOGRAPHY
OF TEXAS FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE, IT'S ALMOST A
PHYSICAL IMPOSSIBILITY TO PUT A
FENCE FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE.
YOU CAN PUT IT IN CERTAIN SPOTS.
BUT THE MAJORITY OF TEXAS IS
PRIVATE LAND.
>> THAT WON'T WORK.
YOU NEED MORE MAN POWER,
TECHNOLOGY, A COMBINATION OF ALL
OF THE ABOVE.
I WOULD RELY ON THE EXPERT THAT
BORDERLAND AND HOMELAND SECURITY
TO TELL US WHAT THEY REALLY
NEED.
>> DO YOU?
YOU SORT OF INTIMATED THAT
PERHAPS THOSE IN WASHINGTON ARE
NOT QUITE CLEAR ABOUT THE
PARAMETERS OF WHAT THEY SEEM TO
BE TALKING ABOUT.
WERE YOU SURPRISED WHEN THE
PRESIDENT, WE UNDERSTAND, DID
OFF SCRIPT AND AD LIBBED ABOUT
LOVING AND WANTING MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION INTO THE UNITED
STATES?
WHEN HE SAID THAT AND WHEN YOU
WERE LISTENING TO THE SPEECH,
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THAT THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
I THINK THAT LOTTERY SYSTEM IS
NOT FUNCTIONING AT ALL.
MY FORMER FIRM WAS TRYING TO
BRING IN AN UNDERWRITER FROM
LOIDS OF LONDON FOR SEVERAL
YEARS AND THE LOTTERY SYSTEM
THEY LOCKED OUT EVERY YEAR FOR
THREE YEARS AND GAVE UP.
BUT WHEN WE'RE BELOW 4%
UNEMPLOYMENT, WE'VE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING MORE ON LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND I'VE ALSO SAID
IF YOU ARE A DACA OR A DREAMER
AND YOU SERVE IN THE MILITARY,
IT OUGHT TO BE AUTOMATIC YOU GET
U.S. CITIZENSHIP IF YOU SO
DESIRE AND FOR THE OTHERS AS
WELL.
IF YOU ARE ALREADY HERE AND THAT
10 TO 12 MILLION GROUP THAT'S
HERE UNDER FALSE SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBERS, BUT EARNING A LIVING
AND RAISING THEIR FAMILY AND NOT
INVOLVED IN ANY CRIMINAL
ACTIVITIES.
YOU BET THOSE PEOPLE AND YOU
GIVE THEM GREEN CARDS, SO THAT
THEY CAN HAVE LEGAL WAYS OF
PAYING TAXES AND FOUGHT JUST
BOGUS SOCIAL SECURED NUMBERS AND
ANYBODY THAT DOESN'T PASS A
CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECK OUGHT
TO BE DEPORTED.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY WE WILL DEAL
WITH THAT I KNOW WE HAVE FOLKS
THAT SAY, OH, THEY'RE HERE
ILLEGALLY, WE CAN'T DEAL WITH
IT.
MY COMMENT IS THE EGG IS ALREADY
BROKEN, DEAL WITH IT.
>> WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID AD
LIBBED DURING THE STATE OF THE
UNION, DO YOU FEEL THAT WAS A
PART OF BE RIGHT BACKING BREAKI
THE EGG, IN OTHER WORDS MOVING
ALONG THE ROAD OF ACCEPTING WHAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT, THAT
THERE NEEDS TO BE MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND PROPER
IMMIGRATION REFORM?
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS A UNIQUE
PERSONALITY WITHIN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
HE'S THE PRESIDENT THAT WE'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE LIKE HIM HIM
I'M NOT SURE WE'LL SEE AFTER
HIM.
BUT HE IS IN A POSITION TO BE
ABLE TO DO SOME THINGS THAT I
THINK OTHERS MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO TO.
SO I WOULD HOPE HE WOULD MOVE
FORWARD WITH THAT.
HE'S INTIMATED ABOUT IMMIGRATION
REFORM AND OUR NATION NEEDS IT.
>> WELL, YOU ARE A POLITICIAN,
MAYOR.
AND YOU'VE ACCURATELY DESCRIBED
THE PRESIDENT.
HE'S A UNIQUE OPERATION IN THE
POLITICAL AFFIRMAMENT, BUT ONE
THAT MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
CERTAIN THINGS DONE.
DO YOU SEE THAT HAPPENING AND
THE POSSIBILITY OF THAT
HAPPENING BY HIS HACKSS, BY HIS
POLIT
POLITICKING, ON IMMIGRATION, FOR
INSTANCE?
AS WE HAVE JUST BEEN DISCUSSING?
IN OTHER WORDS, DO YOU THINK HE
CAN DELIVER AS YOU HAVE
DESCRIBED?
>> I THINK IF HE WANTS TO, HE
CAN DELIVER.
YES.
SO IT'S UP TO HIM TO DETERMINE
THAT.
I WOULD BE HOPEFUL THAT HE
WOULD.
>> RIGHT.
SO LET'S ASK YOU AGAIN TO TALK
ABOUT THE REAL TRAGEDY THAT WE
SEE, WHICH IS A HUMAN TRAGEDY OF
ALL THIS CONFLATION OF ILLEGAL
AND ASYLUM AND THESE CHILDREN
AND FAMILIES BEING SEPARATED AT
THE BORDER AND THIS HORRENDOUS
SITUATION DOES NOT SEEM TO BE
GETTING ANY BETTER.
IN FACT, ESSENTIALLY THE WORSE
EWOULD LIKE TO PLEAS PLAY FOR
YOU THE DETENTION WHEN WE SPOKE
ACTUALLY BACK IN JUNE.
>> WE HAVE BEEN GIVEN NO
INFORMATION REGARDING THE
CHILDREN, WHERE THEY ARE.
ALL WE KNOW IS THEY ARE BEING
DISTRIBUTED THROUGHOUT THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH WAS A
SURPRISE TO COME OF US.
WE HEARD ABOUT THEM BEING PLACED
IN MICHIGAN, NEW YORK, RHODE
ISLAND, ELSEWHERE, THAT'S THE
REASON WE CAME TOGETHER AS A
GROUP OF MAYORS TO SAY ENOUGH IS
ENOUGH.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE ARE ABOUT AS
A NATION.
>> SO, MAYOR, THAT WAS IN JUNE,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER NEAR
WHERE YOU ARE?
BECAUSE THERE ARE REPORTS THAT
ARE VERY, VERY UPSETTING TO
READ.
I WANT TO KNOW IN YOUR LOCATION,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER?
>> THE NUMBERS ARE INCREASING.
WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
3 AND 400 A DAY.
THESE ARE FAMILIES.
THEY'RE NOT BEING SEPARATED.
THE TORNEO SHELTER THAT WAS AT
THE TIME UP FOR UNACCOMPANIED
MINORS THAT I VISITED LAST
SUMMER WAS DISBANDED IF JANUARY.
AND THEY WENT OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
AS I SAID, WE GET, THE WORD I
HAVE PER DAY IS ABOUT 3 TO 400.
THEY'RE PROCESSED THROUGH --
THEY COME INTO EMPASS SO ONCE
DISCHARGED FROM I.C.E. AND OUR
NGO, THE ENUNCIATION HOUSE HAS
APPROXIMATELY 20 SHELTERS IT
COORDINATES AND THEY ARE HERE,
FAMILIES TOGETHER.
THE PARENTS ARE GIVEN ANKLE
BRACELETS IN THE PROCESS AND
THEN THEY GO OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
THEY HAVE BUS FARE, AIR FAIR,
WHATEVER IT IS THAT DOES THAT,
WHATEVER THEY NEED.
THEY'RE HERE USUALLY 24 TO A
MAXIMUM OF 48 HOURS, SOME AS
LONG AS 96 HOURS.
BUT I DON'T KNOW THAT YOUR
VIEWERS FULLY UNDERSTOOD WHEN
CPP, CPP IS A LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCY AND THE WAY IT WAS
STRUCTURED IS THAT HHS WOULD BE
THE ENTITY THAT WOULD BE
EQUIPPED TO TAKE CARE OF THOSE
THAT WERE HELD IN DETENTION AND
THEY'VE FIT DOING THAT.
I THINK THERE WAS A 9th CIRCUIT
COURT DECISION, AS I'M TOLD,
THAT SAYS CAN'T HOLD ANY
IMMIGRANTS THAT ARE SEEKING
ASYLUM LONGER THAN 20 DAYS.
SO THEY'RE PROCESSING THEM,
RELEASING THEM TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
>> SO YOU MENTIONED THE BOARD OF
PROTECTION UNIT AND I CONTRACTOR
AND THE LPG SERVICES.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE AS I LET
YOU GO'S MAYOR OF EL PASO THAT
YOUR CITY IS BEING REALLY A
PUNCHING BACK AND SORT OF IN THE
MIDDLE OF ALL OF THIS VERY, VERY
YOU KNOW HEATED POLITICS AND TO
AN EXTENT FAKE NEWS FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> WELL, I'M DOING MY BEST TO
TRY TO ARTICULATE THE CORRECT
STORY OF WHERE WE ARE AS WELL AS
EXPLAINING THAT WE ARE IN FAVOR
OF A SAFE BORDER AND THAT IS A
SOVEREIGN NATION AND YOU NEED TO
CONTROL OUR BORDERS, BUT THAT
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY, A
CONTRIBUTING COMMUNITY AND HAS A
CLOSE RELATIONSHIP BICULTURALLY
AND BINATIONALLY.
FAMILIES ON BOTH SIDE AND
COMMERCE WITH MEXICO.
I MEAN WE HAVE SIX BRIDGES THAT
HAVE 23,000 ILLEGAL PEDESTRIANS
COMING NORTH EVERY DAY.
I GOT 21 MILLION PRIVATE
PASSENGER VEHICLES THAT COME
NORTH ON AN ANNUAL BASIS.
WE GOT $82 BILLION OF TRADE
IMPORTS AND EXPORTS THAT GO
THROUGH HERE.
I MEAN WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND
VERY MUCH INTERTWINED WITH
MEXICO, IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE
BORDER, COME TO EMPASS SO.
>> ALL RIGHT MAYOR OF EMPASS SO,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE WITH US.
>>> SO, WITH ALL THIS
POLITICKING, THERE ARE REAL
FLESH AND BLOOD PEOPLE WHO ARE
AFFECTED ON A DAILY BASIS.
THE MOST CONTROVERSIAL TRUMP
IMMIGRATION POLICY HAS NOT BEEN
THE WALL, BUT AS I MENTIONED
CHILD SEPARATION, DELIBERATELY
REMOVING MIGRANT CHILDREN FROM
THEIR PARENTS WHO ARE THEN
DETAINED.
A NEW INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT
REVEALS THOUSANDS MORE WERE
SEPARATED FROM THEIR FAMILY
PREVIOUSLY ACKNOWLEDGED.
THE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICE FRS HAD TOO HOUSE
THE CHILDREN AND TESTIFYING ON
CAPITOL HILL RECENTLY COMMANDER
JONATHAN WHITE SAYS HE BELIEVES
THE POLICY HAD CATASTROPHIC
IMPLICATIONS.
>> SO THIS PROBLEM IS NOT OVER
EVEN AFTER THEY UNIFY THE CHILD
WITH THEIR FAMILY.
RIGHT?
>> THE CONSEQUENCES OF
SEPARATION FOR MANY CHILDREN
WILL BE LIFE LONG.
>> LET'S BE CLEAR IS THERE A
NULLIFICATION OF RETRAUMATIZE OR
IS THIS AN ADDITIONAL TRAUM THAT
ADDS ADDITIONAL STRESS AND
ADDITIONAL HARM TO A CHILD AFTER
THEY EXPERIENCE THE DIFFICULTIES
THAT THEY EXPERIENCED IN THEIR
HOME COUNTRY GOING THROUGH THE
LONG TREK?
DID HE ADD ADDITIONAL
RETRAUMIZATION TO THAT CHILD?
>> MANY CHILDREN THAT IS A ABLE
CONSEQUENCE, YES.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TO DIG DOWN
NOW INTO THE HUMANITY OF THAT
FACT AND THE LAW.
ED LAREN DARRAGH REPORTED
EXTENSIVELY ON THE BORDER AND
CHILD SEPARATION.
HE'S JOINING US FROM EL PASO.
MARY BOWER IS A DEPUTY DIRECTOR
FOR THE POVERTY LAW CENTER WHICH
REPRESENTS IMMIGRANTS IN
DETENTION.
SHE TRAVELED ALSO TO THE BORDER.
AND SHE IS JOINING US FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
WELCOME TO YOU BOTH.
I JUST WANT TO ASK YOU, ED,
START OFF WITH SOME STORIES
ACTUALLY FROM BOTH OF YOU.
ED, YOU ARE THERE IN EL PASS SO
YOU JUST HEARD THE MAYOR.
TELL ME WHAT YOU HAVE SEEN AND
WHAT HAVE YOU REPORTED ON THE
HUMAN STORIES THAT IS BEHIND ALL
THESE POLITICS?
>>.
>> I THINK THE IMPORTANT THING
IS HOW FLUID THINGS CLANG ON THE
BORDER.
THE REASON WHY SOME PEOPLE MIGHT
TRY TO MIGRATE INTO THE UNITED
STATES IN 2018 AND 9019 IS BIFF
THAN THREE OR FOUR YEARS AGO.
>> THAT HAS BEEN THE CHALLENGE
WE HAVE SEEN HERE ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER OVER THE
COURSE OF THE LAST MONTH, WHERE
REALLY WE HAVE SEEN THE ARRIVAL
OF FAMILY UNITS, FAMILIES
ARRIVING WITH CHILDREN.
THAT IS A RELATIVELY NEW
PHENOMENON THAT YOU ARE SEEING
HERE ON THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
BECAUSE OF THAT, THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME LAW MAKERS WHO HAVE
CRITICIZED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION FOR NOT ADAPTING
QUICK ENOUGH TO DEALING WITH THE
SPECIFIC TYPE OF PEOPLE WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE AT THE U.S.
SOUTHERN BORDER.
SO THAT'S WHY IT'S LED TO THIS
DRAMATIC INCREASE IN CHILDREN
SEPARATED FROM THEIR PARENTS.
IT WAS A PLAN THE ADMINISTRATION
HOPED A ZERO POLICY WOULD SERVE
AS A DETERRENT TO MIKE GRANTS
COMING MOSTLY FROM CENTRAL
AMERICAN COMPANIES TO DETER THEM
E THEM FROM COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
EVEN THOUGH THE ADMINISTRATION
SAYS THAT POLICY HAS BEEN
STOPPED, WE HEARD THE STORY OVER
HERE OVER THE COURSE OF A
MONTH-AND-A-HALF A YOUNG GIRL
SEPARATED FROM HER FATHER AT THE
END OF DECEMBER.
IT TOOK ALMOST A MONTH FOR THAT
GIRL TO BE REUNITED WITH HER
FAMILY.
THESE STORIES HAVE RAISED
QUESTIONS TO WHAT EXTENT THESE
CHILD SEPARATION CASES ARE STILL
UNFOLDING.
>> LET ME TURN TO YOU, MARY
BOWER, YOU DEAL WITH THIS FROM
YOUR LEGAL PERSPECTIVE.
THERE IS ALSO A HUMANITARIAN
PERSPECTIVE.
DESCRIBE THE EXTENT OF WHAT ARE
YOU SEEING IN.
THE SECRETARY GENERAL SAYS
THOUSANDS MORE HAVE BEEN
SEPARATED THAN EVER HAS BEEN
ACKNOWLEDGED.
IN OTHER WORDS THE PROBLEM IS
WORSE THAN WE THOUGHT IT WAS.
>> IT ABSOLUTELY IS WORSE.
WHAT WE SEE IS FAMILY SEPARATION
HAS EVOLVED.
IT'S TAKEN A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT
FORM.
THERE ARE 10,000 KIDS DETAINED
NOW ACROSS THE UNITED STATES
BECAUSE OF A DELIBERATE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION POLICY AND IT'S
NOT AS THERE ARE THE PREVIOUS
SPEAKER INDICATED, A FAILURE TO
ADAPT.
IT IS A DELIBERATE AND NEFARIOUS
POLICY WHERE THE ADMINISTRATION
DECIDED THAT THEY WERE GOING TO
TAKE ACTIONS THAT WOULD RESULT
IN KIDS BEING DETAINED LONGER
AND IN PARENTS AND SPONSORS
BEING TURNED OVER TO
DEPORTATION.
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING.
WE ARE SEEING MORE THAN 10,000
KIDS LOCKED UP.
MOST WHO DON'T NEED TO BE LOCKED
UP.
>> JUST TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT,
NOW THAT WE KNOW MORE AND THIS
HAS BEEN THE CASE OF GREAT
CONTENTION AND ANGER IN THE
UNITED STATES AND ACTUALLY
AROUND THE WORLD.
ARE YOU ABLE TO DEEM WITH THESE?
ARE YOU ABLE TO HIGHLIGHT THESE
CASES?
IS THE LAW RESPONDING FAST
ENOUGH?
I MEAN, CAN YOU GET THEM
REUNITED WITH THEIR FAMILIES?
WHAT IS THE SITUATION ON THAT
LEVEL, MARY?
>> WELL, WE HAVE BROUGHT A CLASS
ACTION LAWSUIT ON BEHALF OF ALL
KIDS WHO ARE DETAINED ACROSS THE
UNITED STATES.
BUT WE KNOW THAT ANY CHILD WHO
IS LOCKED UP AND SEPARATED FROM
FAMILY IS EXPERIENCING A TRAUM.
WE KNOW THAT.
WE KNOW THESE KIDS WILL
EXPERIENCE LONG-TERM TRAUMA,
BECAUSE THEY ARE SEPARATED FROM
THEIR PARENTS SO WE'RE WORKING
TO REUNITE THEM AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE.
BUT THIS DOES NOT HAVE TO BE.
THIS IS THE RESULT OF
CALCULATED, DELIBERATE
INTENTIONAL ACTS TO SEPARATE
KIDS FROM THEIR PARENTS AND TO
USE THE CHILDREN ESSENTIALLY AS
BAIT TO LURE THEIR PARENTS INTO
THE DEPORTATION SYSTEM AND
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING PLAY
OUT.
>> I'M GOING TO GET BACK TO THE
LEGAL REMEDY TO THIS I WANT TO
FOLLOW UP WITH ED ON YOU KNOW
YOU ARE SEEING EVERY DAY THESE
STORIES.
ED YOU HAVE BEEN SEEING THEM,
TOO, ON A REGULAR BASIS.
YOU HAVE BEEN REPORTING ON THEM.
GIVE ME A SENSE OF WHAT YOU SEE
THE KIDS THE FAMILIES, HOW
THEY'RE BEING AFFECTED THE
TRAUMAS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, I THINK A LOT
OF PEOPLE WHO ARRIVE AND I SPENT
A LOT OF TIME IN SHELTERS ON THE
MEXICAN SIDE OF THE BORDER,
THESE FAMILIES WHO HAVE MADE THE
LONG JOURNEY FROM THEIR CENTRAL
AMERICAN COUNTRY HOMES AND TO
GET THERE.
AND MANY TIMES WHEN I SPEAK TO
THEM, THEY KIND OF SEEM
OBLIVIOUS, NOT AWARE AS TO THE
EXTENT OF HOW MUCH THIS IS BEING
DEBATED HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE AMOUNT OF MISTAKES
INFORMATION THAT THEY'RE GIVEN E
GIVING IN THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
AND ESSENTIALLY LURED BY
CRIMINAL AND ORGANIZED GANGS
THAT BRING THEM THROUGH CENTRAL
AMERICA INTO MEXICO AND TRY TO
GET THEM INTO THE UNITED STATES.
THIS IS HUGE BUSINESS FOR A LOT
OF THESE SMUGGLERS THAT GET THEM
HERE TO THE DOORSTEP OF THE
UNITED STATES AND ESSENTIALLY
WASH THEIR HANDS OF THEM.
THEN IT BECOMES, YOU KNOW ARC
DANGEROUS SITUATION FOR THEM.
SO YOU SEE A LOST CONFUSION AND
BY AND LARGE, I HAVE SPOKEN TO
HUNDREDS, DOZENS OF THESE PEOPLE
OVER THE COURSE OF MY REPORTING
HERE AND ON THE U.S.-SOUTHERN
BORDER FOR YEARS AND ALL OF THEM
REPEATEDLY TELL YOU THAT THEY
COME HERE SIMPLY LOOKING FOR ATE
BER OPPORTUNITY AND IN A CASE
RECENTLY OF THE CENTRAL AMERICAN
MIGRANT, MANY OF THEM TRYING TO
ESCAPE VIOLENCE.
THEY HAVE BEEN DIRECTLY
THREATENED BY GANGS IN THEIR
HOMETOWN.
THEY FEEL LIKE THE ONLY COURSE
OF ACTION THEY HAVE IS TO DROP
EVERYTHING AND RUN NORTH.
>> MARY, FROM A LEGAL POINT OF
VIEW AND THE PERSPECTIVE ON THE
BIG PICTURE, THE PRESIDENT IS
OFTEN GOING TO THE BOARD IR,
GOING TO EL PASO THIS EVENING
AND TALKING ABOUT THE RACISTS
AND THE -- RAPISTS AND CRIMINALS
AND GANGS AND MS-13, ET CETERA.
SORT OF INVOKING YOUNG MEN,
MIDDLE AGED MEN ADOLESCENTS.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, WHO ARE THE
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE COMING OVER?
ARE THEY THAT DEMOGRAPHIC?
AND WHERE ARE MOST OF THE
ILLEGALS?
ARE THEY COMING THROUGH BORDER
THE SOUTHERN BORDER?
WHERE IS THE CENTER OF GRAVITY
ON THIS ISSUE?
>> THEY'RE NOT THE PEOPLE DONALD
TRUMP DESCRIBED, THEY'RE NOT
RAPISTS AND MURDERERS.
THE PEOPLE COMING TO UNITED
STATES WE ARE SEEING DEBORDEER
ARE DESPERATE PEOPLE TERRIFIED
AND FLEEING VIOLENCE.
THEY'RE COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
IN MANY CASES THEY WOULD LIKE TO
APPLY FOR ASYLUM AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY AND THEY CANNOT BECAUSE OF
ADMINISTRATION POLICIES.
WE SEE THAT IN TERMS OF THE
NUMBERS OF UNDOCUMENTED PEOPLE.
THE MAJORITY OF THE UNDOCUMENTED
PEOPLE IN THE UNITED STATES NOW
ARE ACTUALLY COMING IN THROUGH
AIRPORTS, PEOPLE OVERSTAYING
VISAS.
SO ALL OF THE RED RICK FROM
TRUMP ABOUT WHO IMMIGRANTS ARE
AND WHY THEY'RE COMING AND WHAT
THEY'RE SEEKING, IT'S JUST
WRONG.
IT'S JUST DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
WE KNOW THAT WE KNOW IMMIGRANTS
ARE FAR LESS LIKELY TO COMMIT
CRIMES THAN U.S. CITIZENS.
WE KNOW ALL OF THAT.
>> WE HEARD BETO O'ROURKE SAY
THAT THE MAYOR OF EL PASO,
TEXAS, TALKING ABOUT HIS
PRACTICALLY CRIME-FREE LOCATION
THERE IN EL PASO.
CAN YOU JUST SEPARATE FOR US
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A CONSISTENT
CONFLATION OF THE ISSUES?
THERE'S LEGAL.
THEN THERE'S ILLEGAL.
THERE'S ASYLUM SEEKERS.
MARY, JUST TELL US, WHO EACH
GROUP IS AND HOW EACH NEEDS TO
BE DEALT WITH.
>> WELL, I THINK WE HAVE TO ACT
KNOWLEDGE FIRST THAT CONSTANT
RHETORIC ABOUT HOW HE WANTS
PEOPLE TO DO THINGS LEGALLY IS
ALSO DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
RIGHT?
BECAUSE HE'S NOT ALLOWING PEOPLE
TO APPLY AT THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
HE IS PUTTING UP HUGE OBSTACLES
TO ALLOW PEOPLE TO APPLY FOR
ASYLUM TO BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
HE HAS TAKEN BASICALLY A MILLION
PEOPLE WHOARE HERE UNDOCUMENTED
AND TRIED TO MAKE THEM ILLEGAL
BY TRYING TO TERMINATE DACA AND
CPS.
HE HAS UNDERGONE POLICY AFTER
POLICY AFTER POLICY, THAT IS
DESIGNED TO ATTACK PEOPLE WHO
ARE HERE BOTH LAWFULLY AND
UNLAWFULLY AND TO ATTACK THE
SYSTEM OF IMMIGRATION AND ASYLUM
AT ITS ROOTS TO MAKE THAT
UNAVAILABLE TO PEOPLE.
SO WE KNOW THAT RHETORIC ABOUT
HOW PEOPLE NEED TO STAND IN LINE
OR HOW THEY NEED TO DO IT
LEGALLY.
>> THAT IS BELIED BY THE ACTIONS
OF ADMINISTRATION THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
THEY DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO DO
THAT THEY DON'T WANT IMMIGRATION
AT ALL.
THEY HAVE MADE THAT CLEAR
THROUGH THEIR POLICY.
YES, WE NEED TO HAVE AN
IMMIGRATION REFORM THAT LETS 11
MILLION OR SO HERE OUT OF
STATUS.
WE NEED TO HAVE THAT KIND OF
REFORM.
WE HAVE NEEDED THAT FOR WELL
OVER A DECADE OR TWO.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT WE
PUT UP A WALL AND DENY THE
ABILITY TO APPLY ASYLUM TO
PEOPLE WHO ARE DESPERATE AND ON
OUR DOORSTEP.
WE ENACTED THE ASYLUM LAW IN THE
WAKE OF WORLD WAR II EXACTLY SO
THIS WOULD NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
BECAUSE THE WEST WAS ASHAMED, IT
HAD TURNED AWAY JEWS DURING THE
HOLOCAUST.
WE SAID NEVER AGAIN WE DON'T
WANT TO TURN OUR BACK ON
DESPERATE PEOPLE AT OUR
DOORSTEP.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE ASYLUM LAWS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WE ARE SHAMEFULLY, SHAMEFULLY,
IGNORING OUR LEGAL MORAL
RESPONSIBILITY HERE.
>> LET ME ASK YOU TO STAND ON
THAT, YOU SEE IT, YOU REPORT ON
THE PEOPLE.
AND THERE IS THIS POLICY THAT
THE PRESIDENT INPLEMTED CALLED
METERING WHICH LIMITS THE NUMBER
OF ASYLUM SPEAKERS ALLOWED TO
ENTER THE UNITED STATES EACH DAY
AND THEY ARE HELD IN DETENTION
CENTERS OR CENTRES ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
MEANING THEY HAVE TO WAIT MONTH
TO MONTH FOR THEIR CLAIMS ARE
PROCESSED.
WHAT IS THAT DOING AT THE
BOARDER?
THE PRESIDENT CLAIMS A CRISIS AT
THE BORDER.
IS THIS A PART, ED, OF THE
CRISIS?
IS IT MANUFACTURING A CRISIS, IF
YOU LIKE?
>> Reporter: I THINK, MARY
BRINGS UP AN IMPORTANT POINT YOU
GUYS ARE HITTING ON.
THAT'S THE NEWEST ANGLE OF WHAT
WE ARE SEEING IN OUR REPORTING
ALONG THE U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER.
RIGHT NOW MENTIONED THIS
METERING SYSTEM.
SO PEOPLE UNDERSTAND WHAT IT'S
LIKE.
IMAGINE A GROUP, VERY LARGE
GROUPS SHOWING UP IN VARIOUS
SECTION OF THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON TO SEE 200,
300 MIKE GRANTS SHOW UP IN A
BORDER TOWN IN A REMOTE AREA AND
THEY COME TO JUAREZ, FOR
EXAMPLE, THEY'RE AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY, THEN THE U.S. MIGHT HAVE
A SYSTEM IN PLACE, I THINK IT
VARIES BETWEEN WHICH PORT OF
ENTRY YOU COME INTO.
TODAY THEY SAY WE WILL TAKE 15
ASYLUM SEEK ESSER, TODAY 12 THE
DAY BEFORE NINE.
THAT'S NOT LETTING EVERYBODY
COME IN.
THAT'S FORCING PEOPLE TO WHITE
ON THE MEXICAN SIDE OF THE
BORDER AND THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS ALSO FLIRTING
WITH THE IDEA, I THINK THERE IS
A PROGRAM INITIALLY PUT IN PLACE
IN TIJUANA ON THE BORDER OF
CALIFORNIA ESSENTIALLY FORCING
FAMILY UNITS TO WAIT OUT THEIR
ASYLUM CLAIMS ON THE MEMBERS KA
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
THERE IS SOME TALK OF EXPANDING
THAT PROGRAM ON VARIOUS POINTS
OF THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
THIS, THE CRITICS OF THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN WHAT
THEY SEE AS A DETRIMENTAL ISSUE
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO PUT THESE
FAMILIES AND THESE CHILDREN IN
HARM'S WAY.
YOU ARE ESSENTIALLY ASKING
PEOPLE COMING HERE AND ASKING
FOR A LEGAL PROCESS, REQUESTING
ASYLUM AND FORCING THEM TO WAIT
IN THESE COMMUNITIES ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER, WHERE THEY
ARE MUCH MORE, THERE IS MUCH
MORE DANGEROUS SITUATIONS BEING
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF, THREATENED,
THAT SORT OF THING.
>> THAT IS THE CONCERN FOR A LOT
OF ORGANIZATIONS THAT ARE TRYING
TO HELP THESE MIGRANTS WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE IN THESE BORDER
REGIONS.
>> CAN I JUST ASK YOU, MARY, ED,
IF EITHER OF YOU KNOW, THERE
HAVE BEEN REPORTS RECENTLY OF
TWO KIDS THAT DIED IN ONE OF
THESE CENTRES IN MEXICO.
IS IT FACTUALLY CORRECT HOW THAT
HAPPENED?
ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT THE
HAPPENING MORE?
>> IT IS FACTUALLY CORRECT.
WE KNOW THAT THREE CHILDREN WERE
KIDNAPPED IN TIJUANA.
THEY HAD BEEN STAYING AT A YOUTH
SHELTER BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
ALLOWED TO APPLY FOR ASYLUM.
TWO WERE MERD D MURDERED.
ONE WAS ALLOWED TO ESCAPE AND
BRING BACK THE MESSAGE BASICALLY
THAT CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER AND
CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER.
FAMILIES ARE IN DANGER.
THERE IS A DANGEROUS WAY TO
CONDUCT A POLICY.
THIS MEANS THAT PEOPLE ARE
TRAPPED IN BORDER CITIES WHERE
USERS AND GOONGS AND THE FOLKS
THAT PEOPLE ARE FLEEING KNOW
PEOPLE ARE TRAPPED AND SO PEOPLE
ARE IN GRAVE DANGER.
PEOPLE HAVE DIED BECAUSE OF THE
POLICIES.
MORE PEOPLE WILL DIE UNLESS THIS
POLICY IS CHANGED.
WE KNOW THAT THAT IS ON OUR
HANDS.
>> ON THIS SIDE OF THE BORDER,
LET ME PLAY ANOTHER LITTLE CLIP
FROM COMMANDER, THE COMMANDER
WHO WE HEARD, JONATHAN WHITE
FROM HHS.
WE HEARD HIM IN THE LEAD-IN
TALKING ABOUT THE TRAWLER FOR
THE KIDS.
HE TALKED ABOUT THIS POLICY OF
HOUSING SEPARATED CHILDREN, HE
HAD TO ENFORCE IT.
HE NEVER WOULD HAVE ENFORCED
THIS POLICY HIMSELF.
JUST LISTEN TO THIS.
>> THE CONCERN WHICH I EXPRESSED
WERE TWO.
FIRST, THAT THIS WOULD BE
INCONSISTENT WITH OUR LEGAL
REQUIREMENT TO ACT IN THE BEST
INTEREST OF THE CHILD AND WOULD
EXPOSE CHILDREN TO UNNECESSARY
RISK OF HARM.
SECOND, THAT IT WOULD EXCEED THE
CAPACITY OF THE PROGRAM, ISSUES
OF THAT CAPACITY ARE VERY
IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT CONSTITUTES
OUR ABILITY TO PROVIDE A SAFE
AND APPROPRIATE ENVIRONMENT TO
EVERY CHILD.
>> WE'VE ONLY GOT FIRST TIME
SECONDS LEFT, ED LAVANDARA, IN
YOUR REPORTING, HAVE YOU HEARD
SIMILAR MISTAKES GIVINGS FROM
OFFICIALS WHO HAVE TO ENFORCE
SOME OF THIS POLICY?
>> Reporter: THAT TO ME THAT WAS
THE FIRST TIME I HAVE HEARD
PEOPLE IN AN OFFICIAL CAPACITY
SAY THAT THAT WAS MADE THAT
STATEMENT THERE IN THAT
CONGRESSIONAL SETTING SO
STRIKING.
>> WELL, MARY, DO YOU ALWAYS
FIND IT EXTRAORDINARY OR HAVE
YOU HEARD IT BEFORE?
>> NO, THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I
HAVE HEARD THAT.
THAT IS THE CONGRESS AM
STATEMENT OF ATTEMPT THEY ARE
SUPPOSED TO BE ACTING IN THE
BEST ACTION OF CHILDREN.
WHAT WE SEE THAT HAS NOT BEEN
HANG, JUST THE OPPOSITE HAS BEEN
HAPPENING.
>> MARY BOWER, ED LAVANDARA,
THANK YOU FOR JOINING ME THIS
EVENING.
>>> NOW WE DIG INTO AMERICA'S
COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP WITH
DATA AND UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
MICHAEL CHERTOFF WAS PRESIDENT
GEORGE W. BUSH'S HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY.
BUT BEFORE THAT HE MADE A NAME
FOR HIMSELF CO-AUTHORING THE
U.S. PATRIOT ACT IN THE WAKE OF
THE 9/11 ATTACKS.
THE ACT MASSIVELY EXPANDED
GOVERNMENT UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
IT ALLOWED THE DETENTION OF
IMMIGRANTS, SOME THINK THE
SUPREME COURT STRUCK DOWN, NOW
CHERTOFF IS DISCUSSING THE
GROWING THREAT TO PRIVACY AS WE
HAT TOWN IS U DOWN WITH US AND
YES THEY TOUCHED ON THAT BORDER
WALL.
>>?
MICHAEL, LET'S START WITH THINGS
IN THE NEWS NOW AND ABSTRACT UP.
FIRST, IMMIGRATION.
YOU WERE THE SECOND HEAD OF
HOMELAND SECURITY AND SERVED
UNDER PRESIDENT BUSH.
HOW IMPORTANT IS A PHYSICAL
BARRIER THAT'S AT THE CENTER OF
ALL THIS?
>> IT'S A VERY SMALL PIECE OF
WHAT YOU WANT.
WHEN WE WERE IN OFFICE, I THINK
WE BUILT ABOUT 650 MILES OF
BARRIERS ALONG CERTAIN AREAS
WHERE YOU DISTANCE BETWEEN THE
BORDER AND SAY A MAJOR TONY OR A
HIGHWAY WAS VERY SHORT.
AND, THEREFORE, YOU WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO INTERCEPT PEOPLE IF THEY
CROSSED THE BORDER.
YOU COULD PROBABLY BUILD ANOTHER
50 OR SO MILES AND FIND SOME
USEFUL PLACES FOR IT.
BUT IT'S ONLY A VERY SMALL PART
OF WHAT YOU WANT.
WHAT YOU REALLY NEED IS
TECHNOLOGY, BOARD PARE TROLL
PERSONNEL, A DETENTION
FACILITIES FOR PEOPLE WHO WILL
BE DEPORT AND IT HAS TO BE
INTEGRATED INTO A SYSTEM.
SO THE IDEA THAT YOU WANT A WALL
IS A MISTAKES CHARACTERIZATION
FOR WHAT THE REAL REQUIREMENT
IS.
>> IS IT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER?
>> IT'S NOT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER.
THE DISAPPOINTING THING IS IF
YOU ACTUALLY GOT THE
PROFESSIONALS TOEBLG, THEY COULD
MAP OUT PRETTY CLEARLY GIVEN
WHAT THEY KNOW EXACTLY WHERE YOU
WANT PHYSICAL BARRIERS, WHERE
YOU WANT TECHNOLOGY, WHERE YOU
WANT DRONES AND THAT WOULD BE
THE INTELLIGENT WAY TO SPEND THE
MONEY.
IRONICALLY, WHEN THERE IS
COMPLAINING ABOUT DRUGS COMING
THROUGH THE COUNTRY, THE VAST
MAJORITY OF THAT COMES THROUGH
THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO IF YOU HAD EQUIPMENT AT THE
PORTS OF ENTRY THAT WOULD ALLOW
YOU BETTER VISIBILITY TO WHAT IS
CONCEALED IN AN AUTOMOBILE AND
TRUCK, THAT WOULD DO MUCH MORE
TO REDUCE THE IMPLICATION OF
DRUGS AND BARRIERS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DESERT.
BARRIERS REALLY DISCOURAGE A
CERTAIN KIND OF CASUAL CROSSER.
IT DOESN'T DISCOURAGE SOMEONE
WHO IS INVESTING LARGE AMOUNTS
OF MONEY TO MOVE VERY VALUABLE
DRUGS AND THEY WANT VOLUME AND
THEY'RE GOING TO BASICALLY TRY
TO USE EXISTING TRANSPORTATION
SYSTEMS TO COME THROUGH PORTS OF
ENTRY.
>> EVEN IN A NATIONAL EMERGENCY?
>> I WOULDN'T SAY IT'S A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
OBVIOUSLY, BORDER PATROL IS AN
IMPORTANT FEDERAL OBJECTIVE.
ITEMLY THE RATE OF CROSSING
ALTHOUGH FLUCTUATING OVER TIME
HAS GENERALLY GONE DOWN.
WHAT'S REALLY DRIVING IT NOW IS
LARGELY CONDITIONS IN PARTS OF
CENTRAL AMERICA WHERE YOU HAVE,
NOT ONLY ECONOMIC ISSUES BUT
HAVE YOU GANG VIOLENCE, HAVE YOU
LACK OF RULE OF LAW AND PEOPLE
ARE FLEEING BECAUSE THEY'RE
AFRAID FOR THEIR LIVES THE BEST
WAY TO STOP THAT IS TO WORK WITH
THE CENTRAL AMERICAN GOVERNMENTS
TO REINSTITUTE THE RULE OF LAW
TO BUILD THE ECONOMY AND KEEP
THE WORLD HAPPY TO STAY IN THEIR
HOMES.
>> ANOTHER REASON, THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE LAID OUT
AN INDICTMENT AGAINST HAUWEI.
IF UNITED STATES HAS BEEN
PRESSURING OR LEVERAGE COUNTRIES
AROUND THE WORLD TO FOUGHT USE
EQUIPMENT FROM THIS TELECOM
COMPANY AS THE WORLD UPGRADES TO
35G.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT IT THAT'S
IMPORTANT?
>> THIS IS ACTUALLY NOT NEW.
THE ISSUE OF CHINESE TECHNOLOGY
HAS POTENTIALLY CREATING AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR THE CHINESE TO
EXIT ACTS OF ESPIONAGE OR ACTS
OF SABOTAGE HAS BEEN DISCUSSED
AMONG SECURITY PEOPLE FOR THE
LAST TEN YEARS OR SO WE SAW
EARLIER THIS YEAR AN INDICTMENT
OF HAUWEI FOR STEALING
TECHNOLOGICAL SECRETS FROM
T-MOBILE.
THAT'S HAPPENED IN THE PAST THAT
WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN.
BUT BEYOND THAT I THINK THERE IS
A CONCERN THAT YOU ARE
POTENTIALLY PUTTING THE NEXT
GENERATION OF CRITICAL
TECHNOLOGY IN THE HANDS OF A
COUNTRIES WHICH MAY BE AN
ADVERSARY IF CERTAIN RESPECTS.
WE'VE PUBLISHED A REPORT CALLED
FREEDOM ON THE NET AND IN THE
REPORT, WE DETAIL HOW THE
CHINESE ARE USING THE EXPLOITS
OF I.T. TECHNOLOGY TO EMBED
THEMSELVES AROUND THE WORLD IN
ASIA AND AFRICA AND THEY'RE
ACTUALLY TEACHING SOME OF THE
LOCAL GOVERNMENTS THERE HOW TO
USE TECHNOLOGY TO BETTER CONTROL
THE POPULOUS AND TO SUPPRESS
FREE SPEECH.
SO WE'RE IN A SITUATION NOW
WHERE IF YOU HAVE CHINESE
COMPANIES THAT ARE IN CRITICAL
NODES AROUND THE WORLD, ARE YOU
ESSENTIALLY, PROGRAMS, ENABLING
THE EXPORT AUTHORITARIANISM TO
PARTS OF THE WORLD THAT ARE
FREE.
>> HOW DO THE WEST COUNTER THAT?
IS FROM A WAY THAT YOU CAN GET
THE WORLD TO AGREE ON THE RULES
OF THE ROAD?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THERE ARE
THINGS THAT WE CAN DO, EASTERN
USING MULTI-STAKE HOLDER
APPROACH.
THEY'RE UNDER WAY RIGHT NOW.
FOR EXAMPLE, I THINK MANY OF THE
WESTERN COUNTRIES DO HAVE A MORE
OR LESS A COMMON SET OF VALUES
AND COULD REASONABLY REALLY
REACH AGREEMENTS ON SOME OF THE
THINGS WE ARE TALKING ABOUT AND
BECAUSE OF THE FACT THAT THESE
COUNTRIES ARE STILL
CORRECTIVELY, BY FAR, THE MOST
POWERFUL ECONOMIC ACTORS ON THE
GLOBE, IN THE END IF WE DO HAVE
A RESET OF VALUES AND AGREED
APPROACH, I THINK THAT CAN DRIVE
THE CHINESE TO ACCOMMODATE TO
THAT AS WELL.
AND I'M ON A GLOBAL COMMISSION
FOR STABILITY NOW WHICH HAS
DRAWN PEOPLE FOCUSING ON CYBER
ISSUES TO TRY TO COME UP WITH
SOME NORMS THAT CAN BE GLOBALLY
ACCEPTED TO HAVE AN OPEN
INTERNET, A FREE INTERNET AND AN
INTERNET THAT IS NOT FRAGMENTED
BUT RATHER IS TRULY GLOBAL IN
IT.
>> YOU WROTE A BOOK RECENTLY
TALKING ABOUT THE DATA EXPLOSION
AND HAVE YOU KIND OF A SIMPLE
IDEA IN DATA 1.0, 2.0, 3.0,
BREAK THAT DOWN FOR US?
>> I WROTE THE BOOK BECAUSE I
THOUGHT PEOPLE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE MATTER IN WHICH DATA IS
BEING CHECKED AND HOW WE'RE
USING NEWS NOW AND HOW IT WILL
TRANSFORM THE WAY WE LIVE.
SO I LOOK BACK HISTORICALLY.
IF YOU LOOK AT MOST OF HUMAN
HISTORY, DATA WAS BASICALLY WHAT
YOU SAID WHAT YOU HEARD, WHAT
WAS WRITTEN DOWN, WHAT WAS
PUBLISHED AND WE WERE MAINLY
CONCERNED ABOUT PROTECTING OUR
PRIVACY IN THE SENSE OF OUR
PROPERTY.
IT WAS AN EXPRESSION HEARING.
EVERY MAN'S HOME IS HIS CASTLE.
IT GOES BACK A FEW HUNDRED YEARS
AND THE IDEA WAS YOUR PRIVACY IS
BACK TO YOUR PROPERTY.
NO ONE CAN ENTER THROUGH YOUR
HOUSE WITHOUT A WARRANT.
WHEN YOU GOT TO LESSEN, ALL OF A
SUDDEN PROPERTY WAS NOT THE
ISSUE ANYMORE.
IT WAS CONFIDENTIALITY.
COULD I KEEP MY CONVERSATIONS
PRIVATE?
COULD I KEEP MY IMAGE PRIVATE?
AND THEREFORE THE LAW STARTED TO
CHANGE, TO RECOGNIZE WE HAVE TO
FOCUS ON PROPERTY AND NOW WE
HAVE TO FOCUS CONFIDENTIALITY.
MY POINT NOW IS, GIVEN THE
AMOUNT OF DATA THAT IS BEING
GENERATED, NOT ONLY WHAT WE
VOLUNTARILY GENERATE BUT WHAT IS
GENERATED ABOUT US.
THE FACT THAT IT IS NOW STORED
INDEFINITELY.
IT CAN BE PUBLISHED ALL OVER THE
WORLD.
SHOULD WE TRY TO KEEP THINGS
HIDDEN OR SECRET?
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
NOW WE TALK ABOUT WHO CONTROLS
THE DATA?
WHAT IS YOUR RIGHT EVEN WHEN THE
DATA IS COLLECTED TO BE ABLE TO
SAY YES OR NO TO HOW IT'S BEING
USED?
>> THEY'RE ISSUING AUTONOMY.
>> EXACTLY.
IT'S ABOUT FREEDOM AND CHINA,
CHINA ARE WORKING ON A SOCIAL
CREDITOR, WHERE EVERYTHING THAT
YOU DO WILL BE COMPILED AND YOU
ESSENTIALLY GET A RATING AS TO
WHETHER YOU ARE A GOOD OR A BAD
THING.
IF YOU ARE GOOD, YOU GET
PREFERENCE AND ALL KIND OF
THINGS LIKE JOBS AND EDUCATION.
AND IF NOT, YOU COULD BE SHUT
OUT OF THINGS.
NOW IMAGINE THAT IN A WESTERN
SOCIETY, AND IT MIGHT BE
PRIVATE, WHERE YOUR ABILITY TO
GET A JOB OR GET INSURANCE OR
FIND A PLACE TO LIVE WOULD BE
AFFECTED BY WHETHER AN ALGORITHM
LOOKS AT EVERYTHING YOU DO,
THAT'S RECORDING IN SOME FORM OR
FAX OF DATA AND MAKES A JUDGMENT
OF WHETHER YOU ARE DESIRABLE OR
NOT A DESIRABLE PERSON.
>> ISN'T THAT STARTING TO HAPPEN
ALREADY?
IF A HEALTH INSURER HAD ACCESS
TO MY SHOPPING LIST, IT COULD
CHANGE MY RATES.
BEING REALLY HEALTHY AND MAYBE
EQUALS OUT PUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE A GYM
MEMBERSHIP LOCKING IN FIVE TIMES
A WEEK.
OKAY.
HE'S NOT GOING TO DIE, VERSUS A
BAG OF M AND AND Ms, NETFLIX
BINGEING.
>> BUT THAT'S HAPPENING NOW,
EVEN I PUBLISHED A BOOK ABOUT
SIX MONTHS AGO AND THERE ARE
MORE STORIES ABOUT INSURANCE
COMPANIES SAYING, WE WANT TO SEE
YOUR FitBit.
HOW MUCH EXERCISE ARE YOU
GETTING?
AND THEY'RE ALSO LOOKING AT
THINGS LIKE, EXACTLY WHAT FOODS
DO YOU EAT WHEN YOU GO TO A
RESTAURANT?
WHAT DO YOU EAT AT A RESTAURANT.
HOW WAS YOUR SLEEP PATTERN?
IMAGINE ALL OF THIS BEING
COLLECTED AND PRETTY SOON YOUR
FREEDOM TO DECIDE WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO WILL ALWAYS BE SUBJECT TO
A NAGGING FEAR THAT YOU ARE
GOING TO BE PUNISHED.
THERE WAS A BBC THAT WAS ON THAT
ACTUALLY TOOK THIS, I'D LIKE TO
SAY TO AN EXTREME, NOT THAT
EXTREME ABOUT A WORLD IN WHICH
LITERALLY EVERYBODY IS BEING
RAIDED UP AND DOWN MINUTE BY
MINUTE AND IT MAKES 1984,
GEORGERWELL'S DISTOPIAN NOVEL
LOOK LIKE A KINDER GAT INNER'S
DREAM THERE THIS IS THE GUY THAT
HELPED WRITE THE PATRIOT ACT.
AT THE TIME YOU WERE NOT IN THAT
DATA CLIMATE WE ARE IN TODAY.
THERE WASN'T AMAZON NEARLY AS
POWERFUL AND ALL KNOWING WHAT IT
IS.
WHAT IS THE BALANCE BETWEEN
GIVING THE GOVERNMENT THE
OPPORTUNITIES TO CHASE DOWN AND
GET AS MUCH INFORMATION, PREVENT
ATTACKS, ET CETERA?
AND THAT SENSE OF AUTONOMY THAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT WHERE I
STILL FEEL LIKE I HAVE SOME
LEVEL OF CONTROL OVER WHAT I
CHOOSE TO SHARE WITH ESPECIALLY
THE BODY GOVERNING ME?
>> WELL, WE ARE RIGHT TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT
AS WELL AS THE PRIVATE SECTOR.
WHAT IS INTERESTING IS THAT THE
GOVERNMENT OPERATES ON MUCH MORE
CONSTRAINTS THAN A PRIVATE
SECTOR.
THE GOVERNMENT DOESN'T EVEN
DREAM OF COLLECTING DIVINE
INFORMATION THAT'S COLLECTED IN
THE PRIME SECTOR AND BEFORE THE
GOVERNMENT USES IT, THERE ARE
ALL KIND OF DATES THEY HAVE TO
GO THROUGH, AT LEAST IN THE
UNITED STATES AND OTHER
COUNTRIES ARE ACTUALLY
DIFFERENT.
SO, FOR EXAMPLE, TO COLLECT
CONTENT OF INFORMATION E-MAILS
ARE BEING DISCUSSED OVER THE
TELEPHONE, EITHER ONE.
NOW THERE IS A MOVEMENT I THINK
FOR CORRECTLY TO REQUIRE A
WARRANT, EVEN FOR OLDER, NOT
JUST CURRENT E-MAILS, TO USE THE
INFORMATION, YOU HAVE TO GO
THROUGH VARIOUS KIND OF HOOPS TO
GET PERMISSION.
SO I DO THINK THAT THE
GOVERNMENT, ALTHOUGH YOU CAN
ALWAYS ARGUE ABOUT WHAT THEY
OUGHT TO DO, IT DOES OPERATE
UNDER A REGIME WHERE THEY ARE
CONTROLLED.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN SO MANY
EXAMPLES WHERE EVEN IF THOSE
PERMISSION SYSTEMS HAVE EXISTED,
THERE HAS BEEN SUCH A LACK OF
TRANSPARENCY THAT IT SHAKES OUR
FOUNDATIONAL TRUST IN THE
GOVERNMENT SAYING, HEY, IF THE
NSA HAS THIS PROGRAM, WHETHER
THEY WERE AUTHORIZED OR NOT, IT
SEEMS SHADY, IT'S ONE MORE THING
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU, I THINK
TRANSPARENTSCY WILL BE
IMPORTANT.
ONE OF THE MISTAKES TAKES THE
GOVERNMENT MADE OVER A PERIOD OF
TIME, FOR EXAMPLE THE COURT OF
OPINION OF THE KOIRT THAT
SUPERVISORS UNDER SURVEILLANCE
IT'S KEPT CLASSIFIED.
AFTER SNOWDEN YOU KNOW DID HIS
RELEASE OF CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION, THE GOVERNMENT
STARTED TO DECLASSIFY THE
OPINIONS.
I THINK WHAT WAS PUT OUT, A, WAS
FOUGHT PARTICULARLY DAMAGING TO
NATIONAL SECURITY.
BUT FOR THE FIRST TIME PEOPLE
COULD SEE, WOW THE JUDGES ARE
REALLY DIGGING INTO THIS.
THEY COULD SEE THE REASONING OF
THE COURT AND, FRANKLY, I THINK
THE GOVERNMENT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BETTER SERVED HAD THEY PUT THIS
OUT BEFORE ANY OF THIS BUSINESS
HAPPENED.
I AGREE, I THINK A LESSON FOR
THE GOVERNMENT THE YOU HAVE TO
ASK YOURSELF IS THIS SECRECY
REALLY NECESSARY OR WILL WE
ACTUALLY GET MORE VALUE BY AT
LEAST IN A GENERALIZED WAY,
MAKING PUBLIC WHAT WE'RE DOING
TO WHAT THE RULES ARE.
>> A CORE QUESTION HERE IS THE
4th AMENDMENT.
RIGHT?
WHAT IS UNREASONABLE SEARCH AND
CEASE E SEIZURE IN THIS NEW ERA
THAT WE ARE GOING INTO?
IS MY HEART RATE INFORMATION AND
MY SLEEP HABITS, SITTING IN THE
SERVERS OF THE THIRD PARTY.
DO I HAVE CONTROL OF THAT
INFORMATION AND WHO SHOULD BE
ABLE TO TRANSACT THAT?
>> I WOULD GUESS EXACTLY THE
ISSUE WE ARE FACING.
HOW WE ARE CREATING SO MUCH
DIFFERENT DATA, WE HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND WHO GOVERNS IT.
WHAT ARE THE RULES THAT APPLY TO
THE ISSUE OF ACCESS AND THAT'S
ALREADY BEGINNING TO CHANGE.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
YEARS AGO, MANY YEARS AGO,
ADOPTING BORDER SEARCHES, WE
WERE PROMULGATED BY THE SUPREME
COURT.
WHICH CROSS THE BORDER TO COME
INTO THE U.S., BORDER OFFICIALS
ARE ABLE SEARCH ANYTHING YOU
CARRY WITH YOU.
YOU HAVE A LIMIT TO WHAT YOU CAN
PURCHASE REPORT INTO THE U.S.
THAT WAS APPLIED TO LAPTOPS AND
OTHER REPOSITORY DATA, BECAUSE
YOU ARE BRINGING IT INTO THE
UNDERSTAND K. NOW VERY RECENTLY
THE ISSUE WAS RAISED WHAT DO YOU
DO, FOR EXAMPLE, THE SMART HOME
WHICH IS CONNECTED TO THE CLOUD.
SO IF YOU ARE ABLE OPEN UP THE
PHONE AND SEARCH THE PHONE, YOU
ARET NOT ONLY GETTING ON THE
PHONE, ARE GETTING WHAT MAY BE
SITTING ON AMAZON SERVERS
SOMEWHERE IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT WOULD BE AS IF I SEARCHED YOU
WHEN YOU CAME INTO COUNTRY.
AND THE SUPREME COURT CAN
ACCOUNT FOR THE SHEER VOLUME OF
MATERIAL THAT IS NOW AVAILABLE
ON A PHONE OR A LOOPTOP.
>> I WANT TO ASK ALSO ABOUT
UPCOMING ELECTIONS, ARE THERE IS
TWO LEVELS.
ARE STATE SYSTEMS IN THE UNITED
STATES SECURE ENOUGH?
>> TWO LEVELS, THE
INFRASTRUCTURE, THAT IS THE
VOTING MACHINES AN VOTER
REGISTRATION ROLLS AND
TABULATION.
I THINK IT'S VERY UNEASY,
CONGRESS IS TRYING TO GET MORE
MONEY, THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY IS WORKING
WITH SOME OF THE STATES THAT
UPGRADE THEIR SECURITY OF THE
INFRASTRUCTURE.
AND THERE ARE SOME THINGS THAT I
HAVE BEEN INVOLVED IN THE
COMMISSION ON ELECTION INTEGRITY
WHERE WE ARE TRYING TO PROMOTE
THAT.
THE LARGER ISSUE, THOUGH, IS
WHAT THEY CALL INFORMATION
OPERATIONS.
IT'S THE USE BY FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS, LIKE THE RUSSIANS
OR EVEN FRANKLY BY PEOPLE IN OUR
OWN COUNTRY OF TOOLS DESIGNED TO
MANIPULATE PUBLIC OPINION AND
CREATE THERE UNITY AND EVEN
SUPPRESS VOTING BY PROPAGATING
STORIES OR MAGNIIFYING
DISTURBING STORIES, ALL TO PLAY
WITH EMOTIONS.
THERE ARE SOME THINGS YOU CAN DO
TO MITIGATE THAT, PARTICULARLY
WHEN HAVE YOU FOREIGN GOVERNMENT
INVOLVED.
BUT AGAIN, SOME OF THIS IS GOING
TO REQUIRE THE HARD WORK AND THE
EDUCATION OF THE PEOPLE ABOUT
HOW TO BE CRITICAL THINKERS.
THIS IS ABOUT TO GET MORE
CHALLENGING, BECAUSE WE ARE NOW
ON THE VERGE OF WHAT THEY CALL
FAKES.
WHICH IS THE ABILITY TO CREATE
AUDIO AND VIDEO THAT IS
COMPLETELY FABRICATED THAT MAKES
IT SEEM LIKE A REAL PERSON IS
SAYING SMCHLTH AND IF THAT
STARTS TO GET USED AGAINST
CANDIDATES, FOR EXAMPLE, WILL
YOU REALLY HAVE STRESS ON THE
NOTION OF DETERMINING WHAT THE
TRUTH IS.
>> WHAT HAPPENS TO OUR
PROFESSION?
>> WELL, A BIG PIECE OF THIS IS
ACTUALLY BEING PUT ON
JOURNALISM.
HOW DO YOU MEASURE AND DETEBT
WHETHER SOMETHING IS PALS?
HOW DO YOU MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
GET CAUGHT UP IN THE --
>> ON THE COMPETITION FOR AGAIN
ZSA?
>> THE COMPETITION FOR CLIFFS
WHICH DRIVES THE BEHAVIOR YOU
ARE TRYING TO FIGHT AGAINST.
REINJECTING AN ELEMENT OF
PROFESSIONALISM AND JUDGMENT IN
THE WAY EDITORIAL DECISIONS ARE
MADE.
I THINK THERE IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF PRESERVING OUR
DEMOCRACY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> A DIFFICULT CHALLENGE AHEAD.
BEFORE WE GO, REMEMBER TO TUNE
IN TOMORROW WHEN WE WILL HAVE A
SPECIAL PROGRAM ON HUMANITY'S
BIGGEST TRIAL, THAT IS CLIMATE
CHANGE.
I WILL SPEAK WITH THE WASHINGTON
GOVERNOR, MAKING IT THE CENTER
OF A POSSIBLE PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN AND I'LL TALK TO THE
FLAFR GAMES BALOG, WHO HAS
DEVOTED HIS LIFE, HE HAS A NEW
FILM TO HUMAN ELEMENTS.
THANK YOU U THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AMANPOUR AND COMPANY ON
PBS AND JOIN US AGAIN NEXT TIME.
♪♪
-PNC Bank values the importance
of publipr