>>> HELLO, EVERYONE.
AND WELCOME TO AMANPOUR AND
COMPANY.
BEFORE COLBERT, STUART THERE WAS
DICK CAVETT WHO FOUND HUMOR IN
SOME OF AMERICA'S MOST TROUBLED
EAST TIMES.
>>> THEN RICHARD E. GRANT.
THE SURPRISE DARLING OF THIS
YEAR'S AWARD SEASON.
>>> AND A COLLEGE COUNSELOR WHO
TAKES ON CONTROVERSIAL CLIENTS,
YOUNG MEN WHO WERE DISCIPLINED
FOR SEXUAL ASSAULT.
>>> THE UNIWORLD IS A PROUD
SPONSOR OF AMANPOUR AND COMPANY.
BECAUSE ACCORDING TO BEE, TO
TRAVEL IS TO EAT.
BOOKINGS AVAILABLE THROUGH YOUR
TRAVEL ADVISER.
FOR MORE INFORMATION VISIT
UNIWORLD.COM.
>>> ADDITIONAL SUPPORT IS
PROVIDED BY --
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,
EVERYONE.
I'M CHRISTIANE AMANPOUR IN
LONDON WHERE WE'RE BRINGING YOU
UP TO DATE WITH SOME OF OUR
IMPORTANT RECENT STORIES AND WE
BEGIN WITH DICK CAVETT THE
BRILLIANT COMIC MIND WHO LATE UP
LATE NIGHT TELEVISION WITH HIS
QUICK WIT AND INCITEFUL
INTERVIEWS.
FOR DECADES AMERICAN STAYED UP
PAST THEIR BED TIMES AT CAVETT
HOSTED AN UNPRECEDENTED STRING
OF MUST-SEE INTERVIEWS GOING
HEAD TO HEAD WITH GUESTS RANGING
FROM MARLON BRANDO TO KATHERINE
HELP BURN.
NOW THAT ITS AWARD SEASON, WE'RE
LOOKING AT HOW THE MASTER OF
CELEBRITY INTERVIEWED CORRAL ALL
THOSE FAMOUS NAMES AND HAD SO
MUCH FUN DRAWING THEM OUT.
DICK CAVETT, WELCOME TO MY
PROGRAM.
>> I'M GLAD TO BE HERE BECAUSE I
SIT YELLING AT THE SCREEN WHEN
YOU'RE ON YELLING WHEN AM I
GOING TO BE ON.
>> WELL, HERE YOU ARE.
I DO INTERVIEWING FOR A LIVING,
BUT IT'S ALMOST EMBARRASSING FOR
ME TO SAY THAT TALKING TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU ARE THE KING OF
INTERVIEWERS.
>> I'LL BE THE JUDGE OF THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHEN YOU CAME ON TO THE STAGE,
HOW DID YOU GET YOUR BREAK?
HOW DID A YOUNG BOY FROM
NEBRASKA BY WAY OF YALE
UNIVERSITY BECOME DICK CAVETT,
GET THE DICK CAVETT SHOW?
>>, IN FACT, IT WAS VERY, VERY
STRANGE.
I BECAME A COPY BOY AT "TIME"
MAGAZINE MAKING THE $60 A WEEK
SO JACK PAR WORRIES ABOUT HIS
MONOLOGUE.
I WAS A HUGE PAR FOUND.
I WENT HOME AND TYPED A
MONOLOGUE, TOOK IT ON THE SUBWAY
DOWN TO THE RCA BUILDING, NEW
WHAT FLOOR JACK'S SHOW WAS ON
AND HERE HE CAME DOWN THE HALL
AS IN A TOO CONTRIVED SITUATION
AND I PUT IT IN A T"TIME"
ENVELOPE AND IT CAUGHT HIS EYE
AND SAID I'VE WRITTEN SOME STUFF
FOR YOU MR. PAR.
HE AND HE SAID, OKAY, KID.
I SAT IN THE AUDIENCE.
HE CAME OUT AND TOOK SOME PAPERS
OUT.
AND LISTEN TO THIS ROUTINE ABOUT
MOTHERS-IN-LAW AND I SAID OH,
NO.
IT'S NOT MY STUFF.
IT SOMEBODY'S ELSE'S.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE SHOW HE DID
WONDERFUL AD LIBBED THAT WERE
FROM MY MATERIAL I HAD GIVEN
HIM, LIKE FIRST SHIP HIJACKING
WAS IN AND HE HAD A HAND MIKE IN
THE AUDIENCE AND HE SAID TO HER,
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS
PIRATE SHIP?
AND HE USED THAT PHRASE A COUPLE
TIMES AND JACK SAID, IT MUST
HAVE BEEN A SURPRISE TO THE
PEOPLE HEARING A VOICE COME OVER
SAYING, ATTENTION, PLEASE.
THIS IS YOUR PIRATE SPEAKING.
WELL THAT GOT A BIG LAUGH.
HE USED ANOTHER ONE OF MY LINES
IN AN ELEVATOR LATER AND HE
SAID, YOU WANT TO WRITE, DON'T
YOU KID?
I SAID YEAH.
HE SAID COME BACK IN A WEEK AND
HERE WE ARE.
>> HERE WE ARE.
>> EVERYTHING FOLLOWED FROM
THAT --
>> AND JACK PAR WAS THE BIGGEST
AND THE MOST SUCCESSFUL HOST,
RIGHT?
>> HE WAS MR. TONIGHT SHOW.
STEVE ALLEN HAD DONE ONE BEFORE
BUT JACK SURPRISINGLY THE IMPACT
HE HAD ON THE NATION, HE WAS
ONLY ON IT FIVE YEARS.
>> IT IS PRETTY AMAZING?
>> JOHNNY 30SOME.
>> AND JOHNNY CARSON WAS A BIG
RIVAL OF YOURS, RIGHT?
>> BEING TWO NEBRASKAENS WHO
CAME TO NEW YORK DEWIED EYE, HE
CAME DEWIED EYE TEN YEARS BEFORE
I DID.
WE WERE VERY, VERY GOOD FRIENDS.
>> I JUST WANT TO QUICKLY READ
PART OF THE INCREDIBLE ROSTER.
MARLO BRANDON, BET DAVIS, JOHN
LENNON.
THAT'S NOT BAD.
THAT IS NOT BAD AT ALL.
THAT'S JUST FOR STARTER.
>> THOSE ARE THE LITTLE FOLKS.
>> BUT HERE'S THE ADVICE THAT
JACK PAR GAVE YOU, HE SAID TO
YOU, HEY, KID, WHEN YOU DO YOUR
SHOW, DON'T DO INTERVIEWS.
>> THAT KNOCKED ME OVER.
I PICKED UP THE PHONE.
THE VOICE SAID IT WAS JACK PAR
AND I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT BECAUSE
HE DIDN'T CALL ME.
HEY, KID, THIS IS JACK.
LET ME GIVE YOU SOME ADVICE.
PLEASE DON'T DO INTERVIEWS.
I SAID WHAT, DO I DO SING OR
TALK TO THE GUESTS IN POETRY.
HE SAID NO INTERVIEW Q&A AND
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE THIS OR
THAT.
DAVID FROST FALLING ASLEEP ON
HIS CLIPBOARD AND JUST MAKE IT A
CONVERSATION.
>> SO HE WAS -- DON'T DO
INTERVIEWS, HAVE CONVERSATION.
>> CONVERSATION IS BEST.
WHEN IT BECOMES SPONTANEOUS AND
YOU'RE ROLLING ALONG AND YOU CAN
THROW YOUR NOTES AWAY.
A FRIEND OF MINE POINTED MY
FAULT AT, YOU STUCK TO MY NOTES
AND I'D GO TO THIS ONE AND THIS
ONE WHATEVER HAD JUST BEEN SAID.
>> YOU WEREN'T LISTENING.
>> IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN, RIGHT?
>> NOT LISTENING, YES.
>> SO, LOOK, I JUST READ THIS
INCREDIBLE LIST, JUST FOR
STARTERS BUT IT WOULD BE ON
ANYBODY'S DREAM LIST TO HAVE
MARLON BRANDO.
YOU WERE DEBATING HIS PREMISE
THAT EACH OF YOU WERE, IN FACT,
ACTORS AND TO PROVE HIS POINT,
HE DISSECTED YOUR PERFORMANCE AS
A TALK SHOW HOST.
HERE'S A CLIP.
>> OH, GREAT.
>> YOU'RE THINKING OF 60 THINGS
AT ONCE, HOW IS IT GOING?
IS HE UPSET AND DISTRESSED AND
ARTICULATE?
IS HE -- IS HE BORED, IS HE
OFFENDED?
HERE'S A GOOD TIME FOR A JOKE.
WE HAVEN'T GOT MUCH TIME IS, BUT
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT 9 MILLION
THINGS AND REACTING TO WHAT I
SAY AND HOW'S THAT GOING TO BE
AND IS THAT GOING TO BE
OFFENSIVE?
SO YOU'RE DOING THIS -- THIS
EDITING AT AN INSANE RATE AND
YOU HAVE TO DO THAT AND THAT'S
YOUR JOB AND YOU HAVE THIS
DEMEANOR OF LEVITY AND LIGHTNESS
AND AMUSEMENT AND ZEST AND IT'S
EASY TO ASK IF FINALLY WHAT GOES
ON YOUR MUND.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE ALL MY
CLOTHES HAVE BEEN TAKEN OFF.
>> YOU FELT LIKE YOU'D BEEN
STRIPPED BARE THERE AND THEN.
>> HERE I AM LITTLE DICKIE
CAVETT AND MARLON BRANDO WAS
TALKING ABOUT ME WHO IS ALSO
FROM NEBRASKA.
>> NO.
THAT DOES SURPRISE ME.
>> HERE IS ONE THAT WOULD KNOCK
YOUR HEAD OFF, FRED ASTAIRE A
NEBRASKAEN, THE EUROPEANS WON'T
BELIEVE IT.
>> DID YOU INTERVIEW HIM TOO?
>> HE DID MY SHOW TWICE.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK OF MARLON
BRANDO?
HE'S A PRETTY INTIMIDATING GUY.
>> HE HAD COME UP TO MY DRESSING
ROOM BEFORE THE SHOW AND I WAS
IN AWE, BUT EASY TO TALK TO.
HE'S SO BRILLIANT AND AFTERWARDS
HE SAID, NO, NO, NO.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR FOR YEARS.
SO WE WENT --
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU JUST
SAID.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO DOWN TO
CHINATOWN?
WE WENT DOWN.
I'LL MAKE IT QUICK.
THE PAP RATSI FOLLOWED US.
EVERYTHING WAS CLOSED.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I SAID THAT THAT ONE RIGHT
THERE, THE OTHER GUY THERE,
LET'S KEEP THE SAME EXPRESSION
ON YOUR FACE AND HE'LL GET TIRED
OF TAKING THE SAME PICTURE.
HE DID NOT GET TIRED OF TAKING
IT.
WE ALL KNOW MARLON HAS A TEMPER
AND HE LEANED IN AND SAID, YOU
WANT TO TAKE THOSE SUNGLASSES
OFF MARLON AND MARLON TOOK THEM
OFF AND WHAM.
A SHOT THAT CAME UP FROM THE
SIDEWALK, BROKE GALELO'S JAW AS
HE FELL FACE FORWARD ON THE
FRONT OF A CAR.
>> THAT WAS MARLON BRANDO.
>> THIS IS SO THRILLING AND ONE
OF THE STUPIDIEST THINGS I'VE
EVER SEEN.
>> YOU ARE KNOWN MNUAMONGst YOU
FRIENDS AS INCREDIBLY LITERATE.
YOUR LATE WIFE ONCE SAID HE'S A
GENUINELY WITTY NAME.
HE'S A QUESTIONER, REALLY.
HE EMPLOYS THE SOW CRATTIC
METHOD FOR 45 MINUTES AND IT
DRIVES ME ABSOLUTELY CRAZY.
IS THAT PART OF YOUR SECRET?
WHAT MAKES YOU A GREAT
INTERVIEWER?
DO YOU RECALL -- WHAT IS IT YOU
THOUGHT OF?
YOU IT DO INTERVIEWS FOR MORE
THAN AN HOUR OR SO AND THAT WAS
COMMERCIAL TELEVISION.
THAT IS IT NOT HAPPEN THAT MUCH
THESE DAYS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I NEVER HAD ANY EXPERIENCE DOING
IT BEFORE AND BUT I FOUND THAT
WHEN I GOT OUT THERE AND THOUGHT
OF JACK'S TALK TO THE PEOPLE,
DON'T READ -- WHAT IS YOUR
FAVORITE MOUNTAIN OR SOMETHING,
THAT IT JUST SEEMED TO FLOW.
>> WAS SOMEBODY LIKE DAVID BOWIE
A NATURAL FOR YOU?
I'M A GREAT DAVID BOWIE FAN.
HE WAS PARTICULARLY CUTTING EDGE
ON ALL THE GENDER FLUIDITY AND
HIS MUSIC WAS CUTTING EDGE AND
HIS PERSONA.
>> HE'S DYNAMIC AND YOU CAN FEEL
IT SITTING THERE.
>> WHICH YOU DID.
>> AND A FEW PEOPLE IN OUR
BUSINESS WHO SOMETHING REALLY
EMANATES FROM THEM AND YOU CAN
FEEL IT, YEAH.
>> I'M GOING TO PLAY A CLIP.
>> OTHER THAN THAT, WE HAD A
GOOD TIME.
>> LET ME PLAY A CLIP.
>> I DECIDED THAT I PREFER TO
ENACT A LOT OF THE MATERIAL I
WAS WRITING RATHER THAN PERFORM
IT MYSELF.
I WILL CONTINUE TO IN THE FUTURE
AFTER I FOUND WHAT I WISHED TO
DO AT THE MOMENT.
I DON'T CARE WHAT ANYBODY SAYS.
I LIKE DOING IT AND IT'S WHAT
ISH CONTINUE TO DO.
>> >> NOBODY STOPPING YOU AND
EVERYBODY LAUGHED AT THAT.
HE WAS -- DID YOU GET HIM THEN?
DID YOU GET HOW REVOLUTIONARY HE
WAS IN THIS INDUSTRY AND HOW --
>> PROBABLY NOT.
MY ANTENNA WAS WHIMABLY AND
LAME.
AS I WATCHED HIM, GARBO DIDN'T
SEEM VERY INTERESTING IN THE
STUDIO WHEN THEY WERE SHOOTING
BUT WHEN YOU SAW IT ON SCREEN,
SAW ALL KINDS OF THINGS GOING
ON.
THAT WAS BOWIE.
>> TALKING ABOUT HUGE STARS.
YOU DID TWO PROGRAMS WITH
KATHERINE HEPBURN.
HOW MANY HOURS?
>> I HAD WANTED HER FOR YEARS,
FINALLY SHE HAD SAID SOMETHING
TO SOMEBODY.
>> HOW DID YOU GET HER TO AGREE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT DID IT.
I THINK A COUPLE OF OTHER
FRIENDS SAID YOU SHOULD DO IT
WITH HIM, HE'S THE ONE YOU
SHOULD DO IT WITH.
SHE'D NEVER DONE THAT AND SHE'S
THE KIND OF WOMAN IF SHE'S NEVER
PICKED UP A SNAKE, SHE WILL PICK
ONE UP JUST SO SHE'S DONE THAT
AND SHE DECIDED TO DO A TALK
SHOW.
>> SHE WAS PRETTY CANTANKEROUS
IN THE ACTUAL INTERVIEW.
>> SHE WAS AT TIME.
>> HERE'S A CLIP.
WATCH THIS CLIP.
>> YOU KEEP INTERRUPTING THE
LONG STORY OF MY LIFE, IF YOU'D
JUST SHUT UP, I'D BE ABLE TO --
>> I WON'T SPEAK AGAIN FOR THE
NEXT HOUR.
>> THAT'LL BE THE DAY.
THAT'LL BE THE NIGHT.
>> I MEAN, NO PUNCHES PULLED
THERE.
>> MY FAVORITE MOMENT ON THAT
SHOW WAS WHEN I CORNERED HER, I
GOT HAVING FUN WITH HER AND I
SAID, WE WORKED TOGETHER, THE
SUMMER AT STRATFORD I WAS AN
EXTRA IN THE MERCHANT AT VENUS
WITH YOU, YOU WEREN'T ON STAGE I
SAID WHAT LINE.
SHE ASKED THE LINE AND I TOLD
HER THE LINE AND SHE SAID, IS
THAT HOW YOU SAID IT?
>> THAT IS PRETTY GOOD.
IN 1971, YOU, IN FACT, HAD THE
FIRST TELEVISION INTERVIEW WITH
JOHN LENNON AND YOECO ONO AND IT
WAS AT THE TIME WHEN THE BEATLES
HAD BROKEN UP AND YOU WERE
ASKING JOHN WHAT MADE THEM BREAK
UP.
>> WE DON'T WANT TO BE THE CRAZY
GANG WHICH IS BRITISH OR THE
MARX BROTHERS WHICH HAVE BEEN
DRAGGED ON STAGE SINGING SHE
LOVES YOU WHEN WE'VE GOT ASTHMA
AND TUBERCULOSIS AND WHEN
THEY'RE 50.
A LONG TIME AGO I SAID -- I
DIDN'T WANT TO BE SINGING SHE
LOVED YOU WHEN I WAS 30.
I SAID THAT WHEN I WAS 25.
WHEN I WAS 30 LAST OCTOBER AND
THAT'S ABOUT WHEN MY LIFE
CHANGED, REALLY.
>> HE WAS SO APPROACHABLE, SO
AVAILABLE.
WHEN YOU MET HIM IT WAS THAT
FEELING OF I'VE KNOWN HIM A LONG
TIME AS THOUGH YOU HAD NOT AND
WE HAD FUN ON THE SHOW.
>> THIS WAS A VERY DIFFICULT
TIME.
HE WAS CHOOSING YOKO OVER THE
BEATLES.
>> YES, YES.
I DID MAYBE ONE OF THE FEW GOOD
THINGS, WHICH WAS WENT DOWN AS
HE HAD ASKED ME IF I WOULD AND
PROTESTED THE FACT THAT OUR
GREAT UNINDICTED CO-CONSPIRATOR
OF THAT TIME RICHARD MILLHOUSE
NIXON WANTED JOHN OUT OF THE
COUNTRY AND UNFORTUNATELY, LATER
GOT HIMSELF OUT OF THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> OUT OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> I THOUGHT THEY'D HAVE TO CUT
HIS HANDS OFF AT THE WRIST TO
GET HIM OUT OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> WE FORGET THAT JOHN WAS PUT
ON A BLACK LIST.
NIXON SICKED THE FBI ON HIM.
>> OH, YEAH.
I HELPED HIM.
IT WAS A GOOD FEELING.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> ANYTHING I COULD DO FOR JOHN
AND AGAINST NIXON, I WOULD JUMP
AT.
>> AND WHAT IT YOU DO FOR HIM?
>> I JUST WENT DOWN AND TALKED
ABOUT HOW HE SHOULD NOT BE
THROWN OUT AND NOW, IF YOU GO TO
YOUTUBE AND -- NOT WHILE WE'RE
ON AND PUT IN CAVETT/NIXON YOU
CAN SEE HIM IN THE OVAL OFFICE
AND THE WORDS ARE UP HERE, IT
BEGINS WITH, WHAT IS CAVETT ANY
WAY HE SAYS TO HIS HR ALDERMAN.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING WE CAN
DO TO SCREW HIM.
>> YOU TOOK THE WORDS OUT OF MY
MOUTH.
ON THE WHITE HOUSE TAPES.
>> YOU NEVER HEARD YOU TALK LIKE
THAT.
>> YOU WERE ONE OF THE FIRST TO
DELVE INTO COVERING WATERGATE.
YOU SPOKE A LOT ON YOUR SHOW
ABOUT WATERGATE.
YOU DEBATED ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
YOU DIDN'T SHY AWAY FROM THOSE
ACTUAL TOPICS.
>> I DID NOT, NO.
IT WAS SO DAMN INTERESTING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH CREDIT I
DESERVED FOR IT.
YOU WOKE UP EVERY MORNING AND
YOU HAD TO HAVE YOUR WATERGATE
FIX.
IT WAS JUST THRILLING.
>> AGAIN, YOU HAD AN
EXTRAORDINARY CONVERSATION WITH
HENRY KISSINGER.
IT WAS AFTER WATERGATE YOU
DISCUSSED NIXON'S FINAL DAYS AND
YOU ASKED HIM HIS MENTAL HEALTH
AND KISSINGER SAID IT WAS A
SCARY PERIOD BECAUSE HE SAID WE
WERE LIVING IN A NUCLEAR WORLD.
WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN HE SAID
THAT?
>> KISSINGER, WHO I LIKED EVEN
THOUGH I OFFENDED HIM ONCE OR
TWICE, HOW WOULD YOU DESCRIBE
NIXON OR WHAT WAS NIXON AND HE
SAID, JUST ABOUT ANYTHING YOU
WOULD SAY ABOUT HIM WOULD BE
TRUE.
>> THAT IS WONDERFUL.
CAN I MAKE A VERY, VERY HARD
TURN AND A QUITE DIFFICULT HARD
TURN?
>> DO YOUR WORSE.
>> BECAUSE -- WELL MAYBE PAINFUL
HARD TURN.
THERE ARE A LOT OF GREAT
CREATIVES ACROSS THE WHOLE
SPECTRUM OF HUMAN ENDEAVOR.
>> YEAH.
>> WHO SUFFER FROM SOME KIND OF
DEPRESSION IN ALL SORTS OF
DEGREES.
YOU DID YOURSELF.
>> IT'S NOT HARD TO FIND THE
LATEST.
YEAH, AND THERE'S NOTHING GOOD
ABOUT DEPRESSION.
SOMEBODY CALLED IT THE WORST
AGONY DEVISED FOR MAN AND IT
SORT OF IS.
PEOPLE ARE FAMILIAR WITH THE
FACT THAT YOU LOSE INTEREST IN
EVERYTHING.
ALL THE COLOR GOES OUT OF YOUR
LIFE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
AND IT'S HATEFUL AND YOU ALSO
FEEL THAT IT'S ALWAYS GOING TO
BE THAT WAY.
THE THING WITH GREAT FORCE TELLS
YOU THIS IS PERMANENT.
THIS IS HERE FOR GOOD.
TELL YOUR DEPRESSIVE VICTIM OR
CHILD OR WIFE OR FRIEND, IT WILL
PASS.
THAT DOESN'T DO YOU MUCH GOOD
WHILE YOU'RE DOING IT AND IF
ANYBODY SAYS TO YOUR WIFE,
DAUGHTER OR YOU WHILE YOU'RE
SUFFERING FROM IT, WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT TO BE DEPRESSED ABOUT?
YOU'VE GOT MONEY AND A HOUSE AND
A DAUGHTER AND -- YOU CAN PUNCH
THOSE PEOPLE WITHOUT A SENSE OF
GUILT BECAUSE IT'S -- IT'S A
DISEASE.
>> I WANT TO END WITH A REALLY
NICE EXCHANGE BETWEEN YOU AND
THE GREAT JANICE JOPLIN BACK IN
1970.
>> OH, DEAR, JANICE, MY GOD.
>> YOU EVER GET BACK TO PORT
ARTHUR, TEXAS.
>> I'M GOING BACK IN TEXAS.
>> IT'S MY TENTH ANNUAL HIGH
SCHOOL REUNION.
>> TAKE MOVIES AND BRING THEM
BACK HERE AND SHOW.
>> WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO?
>> I DON'T HAVE THAT MANY
FRIENDS IN YOUR HIGH SCHOOL
CLASS.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> OR MINE FOR THAT MATTER.
>> OH, BOY.
SHE LOVED COMING ON THE SHOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF SHE WOULD.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHO SHE WAS THE
FIRST TIME I SAW HER AT FILLMORE
ON STAGE.
SOMEBODY DRAGGED ME DOWN.
SHE WAS TERRIFIC.
I SAID WHO WAS THAT GIRL IN THE
GREEN PANTS AND THEY TOLD ME HER
NAME AND LITTLE DID I KNOW -- I
THINK SHE MUST HAVE BEEN ON SIX
OR EIGHT TIMES.
>> YOU HAD A GREAT CONNECTION.
YOU HAD A GREAT CONNECTION WITH
ALL YOUR GUESTS.
>> NOT SPIRO AGNEW.
>> MAYBE NOT SOME OF THEM.
>> HE WAS THE DULLEST GUEST,
RUNNER UP.
>> DICK CAVETT, THANK YOU SO
MUCH INDEED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
DON'T MENTION IT.
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
>>> AND NOW WE TURN FROM A YOUNG
MAN WHO CAME OUT OF NEBRASKA TO
TAKE THE TV WORLD BY STORM TO A
YOUNG MAN WHO CAME OUT OF SWAZI
LAND TO TAKE THE MOVIE WORLD BY
STORM.
HE IS RICHARD E. GRANT AND HE IS
HAVING HIS MOMENT.
AFTER 40 YEARS AND MORE THAN 100
FILMS, THE MUCH LOVED ACTOR IS
GETTING SERIOUS AWARD SHOW LOVE
INCLUDING HIS FIRST EVER OSCAR
NOMINATION FOR HIS UNLIKELY ROLE
ALONGSIDE MELISSA McCARTHY IN
"CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?"
.
HERE'S A CLIP.
>> THIS IS QUITE SOMETHING.
>> THESE ARE WONDERFUL.
>> I THOUGHT SO TOO.
>> NAME YOUR PRICE.
>> YOU WERE LOOKING AT ONE
MONTH'S RENT.
>> GAMBLE, SHOP, DRINK.
>> WE HAVE A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS
REGARDING THE LIFE LETTER I
PURCHASED.
>> JACK HAWK IS ONE OF A SERIES
OF MEMORABLE ALCOHOLICS ON
GRANT'S RESUME GOING ALL THE WAY
BACK TO HIS BREAK-THROUGH ROLE
IN THE INDY CLASSIC AND THOUGH
HE IS, IN FACT, A TEE TOLLER OFF
SCREEN, GRANT'S FATHER WAS AN
ALCOHOLIC AND THAT WAS A MAJOR
FACTOR IN HIS COMPLICATED AND
SOMETIMES VIOLENT CHILDHOOD IN
SOUTHERN AFRICA.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT ALL OF THAT
WHEN WE SPOKE AGAINST A BACKDROP
OF BREXIT BASED UPHEAVAL HERE IN
LONDON.
RICHARD E. GRANT, WELCOME TO THE
PROGRAM.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> WE JUST HAD THIS ROBUST
DISCUSSION ABOUT BREXIT.
YOU CAN SEE THAT NOBODY KNOWS
WHICH IS THE WAY FORWARD.
WE HEARD FROM THE EUROPEANS AND
BRITISH MPs.
ARE YOU POLITICAL?
YOU'RE AN ACTOR.
>> HUGELY.
>> ARE YOU?
>> I FEEL PASSIONATE ABOUT IT
BUT I THINK THAT WHAT'S HAPPENED
NOW IS SO -- PUT IT THIS WAY, I
THINK THERE'S SOMETHING ON THE
ONE HAND IN THE DNA OF THE
BRITISH PEOPLE AND ON THE OTHER
HAND FAIR MINDED AND THOSE TWO
THINGS HAVE ABSOLUTELY REVEALED
THEMSELVES TODAY IN WHAT'S GONE
ON.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE TOLD WHAT
TO DO BY EUROPE AND WE'RE NOT
GOING TO BE TOLD TO TAKE THIS
DEAL THAT THE MAJORITY OF THE
PEOPLE IN PARLIAMENT DON'T SEEM
TO AGREE WITH.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE AN
ALICE IN WONDERLAND.
>> CAN YOU SEE IT BEING FODDER
FOR MORE FILMS OR TV SERIES, ONE
OF YOUR BRITISH COLLEAGUES HAS
DONE BREXIT, THE FILM AND ITS
ENDLESS INTERESTING AS
CHARACTERS, RIGHT?
>> I THINK SO.
I ALSO THINK THAT PEOPLE ARE
SICK TO THE BACK TEETH OF ALL
THIS, YOU KNOW, TURMOIL THAT'S
GOING ON.
THEY DON'T WANT TO KNOW ABOUT
IT.
I WOULD BE VERY SURPRISED IF
THAT GETS THE VIEWING FIGURES
THAT THEY CLEARLY ANTICIPATE
THEY WILL GET.
>> THAT TURMOIL PRESUMABLY YOU
FELT WHEN YOU WERE IN THE UNITED
STATES SHOOTING THIS LATEST
FILM, "CAN YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?"
>> I WAS THERE FOR THE
INAUGURATION OF DONALD TRUMP AND
PEOPLE WERE SO DEPRESSED ON THAT
FRIDAY AND ON THE SATURDAY
MORNING, THERE WAS THIS HUGE
MARCHES ALL ACROSS AMERICA AND
HUGE WOMEN'S MARCH, ALMOST 1
MILLION PEOPLE IN CENTRAL PARK.
>> ALL THESE YEARS LATER INTO
HIS SECOND YEAR, WE'VE GOT
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN HERE,
PARALYSIS OF THE GOVERNMENT
HERE.
LET'S MOVE ON AND TALK ABOUT
YOUR FILM, THE BREAKTHROUGH,
THIS SORTED REALITY.
LET ME SAY THE "NEW YORK TIMES"
QUOTED ABOUT THE BOOK THAT YOU
MADE THE FILM, IT'S A SLENDER
SORTED AND PRETTY DAMNED
FABULOUS BOOK ABOUT HER
MISADVENTURES.
IT'S BASED ON THE AUTHOR LEE
ISRAEL.
GIVE US THE PREMISE.
>> LEE ISRAEL WAS A SUCCESSFUL
BEST SELLING BIOGRAPHER IN
NEW YORK IN THE 1980s AND SHE
THEN FELL ON HARD TIMES.
HER BOOK ABOUT ESTEE LAUDER
FAILED TO
NOBODY WANTED TO DO A BOOK ABOUT
FANNY PRICE.
SO SHE SCHENN ADDED A POST
SCRIPT TO A LESSER AND SOLD IT
TO A COLLECTOR AND REALIZED
THERE WAS MONEY TO BE MADE IN
BEING A VENTRILOQUIST LIKE
FORGER.
SHE WAS VERY SUCCESSFUL AT IT.
I PLAY A GUY, A CLEPT TOE MANIAC
HIV DRUG ADDICT ALCOHOLIC WHO
WORKED IN COLLUSION WITH HER.
SHE'S AN UNAPOLOGETIC, MISAN
THROPPIC GRUMP PLAYED BY
MULTIPLE SCLEROSIS McCARTHY OF
THE -- MS. McCARTHY.
>> WITH THAT IN MIND HERE'S WHEN
YOU FIRST MEET.
>> JACK HAWK.
LAST TIME I SAW YOU WE WERE BOTH
PRESENTLY PISSED AT SOME
HORRIBLE BOOK PARTY, AM I RIGHT?
>> IT'S FLOODING BACK TO ME.
YOU'RE FRIEND WITH JULIA
SOMEBODY.
>> SHE'S NOT AN AGENT ANY MORE.
SHE DIED.
>> SHE DID.
THAT'S YOUNG.
>> MAYBE SHE DIDN'T DIE.
MAYBE SHE JUST MOVED BACK TO THE
SUBURBS.
I ALWAYS CONFUSE THOSE TWO.
SHE GOT MARRIED AND HAD TWINS.
>> BETTER SHE TO HAVE DIED.
>> IT'S FUNNY.
YOU BOTH PLAY GAY CHARACTERS.
SHE'S AN ALCOHOLIC AND YOU'RE AN
ALCOHOLIC.
YOU END UP HIV POSITIVE.
WHAT DREW YOU TO THIS FILM AND
ALSO, WHAT WAS IT LIKE WORKING
WITH THIS IRREPRESSABLE MELISSA
McCARTHY?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS CURIOUS
ABOUT.
WHEN I GOT THE SCRIPT AND SAW IT
WAS A TRUE STORY, I WONDERED
WHETHER THIS WAS GOING TO BE A
VEHICLE FOR THE COMIC PERSONA
THAT WE KNOW AND LOVE HER MS.
McCARTHY.
I MET HER ON A FRIDAY LAST YEAR,
JANUARY.
SHE WAS WEARING A GRAY WIG
SHOWING THE GRAY ROOTS AND VERY,
VERY DOWDY CLOTHES.
HER CENTER OF GRAVITY SEEMED TO
HAVE SHIFTED.
HER VOICE WAS LOWERED AND I KNEW
THAT SHE WAS 5,000% COMMITTED TO
PLAYING THIS CHARACTER WITHOUT A
SCINTILLA OF SENTIMENT ALT AND
TO PLAY HER FOR ALL HER
CANTANKEROUS.
FOR A COMEDY ACTRESS TO TAKE
THAT ON IN A MOVIE WAS A BOLD
CHOICE AND SHE DOES IT
ABSOLUTELY BRILLIANTLY.
>> YOU HAVE A GREAT RAPPORT IN
THE FILM.
>> YOU HOPE FOR THAT.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE -- I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE RECENTLY SINGLED, YOU
KNOW THAT WHEN YOU MEET SOMEBODY
YOU HOPE YOU'LL HAVE A
CONNECTION WITH THEM.
ON PAPER THERE'S THIS, BUT AS I
SAID, WE KNEW WE WOULD PLAY ALL
THESE -- AND IT FELT LIKE
LIGHTNING IN A BOTTLE.
I KNEW WE'D BE FRIENDS FOREVER
AND WE ARE.
>> IT IS AWARD SEASON AND YOU
HAVE BEEN NOMINATED AND THE
FILM'S BEEN REALLY CRITICALLY
WELL REVIEWED.
DID YOU IMAGINE THAT THIS WEIRD
UNDER THE RADAR --
>> I'M 61 YEARS OLD.
I'VE NEVER BEEN NOMINATED FOR
ANYTHING IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
I'VE NOW GOT 20 OF THEM ON
MYSELF -- IT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
FOR SOMETHING THAT TOOK ME 20
DAYS TO SHOOT AND THE REST OF
THE MOVIE IS 26 DAYS IN TOTAL,
THIS SHOULD BE -- THIS SHOULD
HAVE HAPPENED IS EXTRAORDINARY.
WE KEEP MEETING PEOPLE THAT SAID
THIS MOVIE MADE US FEEL
SOMETHING.
>> BECAUSE LONELINESS IS ALSO --
OBVIOUSLY THE SORT OF FORGERY
AND ALL OF THAT, BUT LONELINESS
IS REALLY I THINK THE THEME OF
IT AND HOW YOU BOTH TRY TO
COMFORT EACH OTHER.
>> THE LONELY AND THEIR
FAILURES.
WHO WANTS TO SPEND AN EVENING
WITH TWO PEOPLE DOING THAT BUT
THEY HAVE RESPONDED VERY
POSITIVELY.
>> YOU'RE ON A GOOD RUN.
SO YOU ALSO HAVE AN AMAZING BACK
STORY.
YOU GREW UP IN SWAZI LAND.
YOUR FATHER WAS A MAJOR
PERSONALITY IN THE EDUCATION
SYSTEM THERE.
BUT HE WAS ALSO AN ALCOHOLIC AND
YOU'RE NOT EMBARRASSED OR SHY
ABOUT TALKING ABOUT IT.
YOU'VE TALKED QUITE A LOT ABOUT
HOW DIFFICULT IT WAS GROWING UP
IN THAT KIND OF ENVIRONMENT AND,
OF COURSE, YOU PLAY AN ALCOHOLIC
IN THIS CHARACTER.
>> I'M ALLERGIC TO ALCOHOL.
I CANNOT KEEP ALCOHOL DOWN
WHATSOEVER, BUT I THINK THAT'S
WHAT I SAW THE TOXIC PRICE THAT
MY FATHER PAID AND WE PAID AS A
FAMILY BY KEEPING ALL THAT
SECRET AND SO I MADE A MOVIE
ABOUT IT 14 YEARS AGO.
SO I FEEL VERY, VERY STRONGLY
THAT SECRETS LIKE THAT ARE
ULTIMATELY TOXIC.
IN TALKING ABOUT THEM, YOU KNOW,
PROBLEMS IS PROBLEMS SHARED.
I BELIEVE IN THAT.
IT'S SAVED ME AND IT'S CONNECTED
ME WITH OTHER PEOPLE WHO WERE IN
THE SAME SITUATION.
>> NOW THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE
AND PEOPLE ARE MORE AND MORE
OPEN ABOUT IT WHETHER IT'S ABOUT
OPIOIDS OR WHETHER IT'S ANY KIND
OF ADDICTION AND THAT'S PRETTY
GOOD IN TERMS OF PROGRESS IN
TRYING TO GET HELP BUT AT THE
TIME YOU WERE A KID AND
QUOTE/UNQUOTE, IN A FOREIGN
LAND.
YOU GREW UP THERE, BUT
NONETHELESS IT WAS JUST A
STRANGE ENVIRONMENT AND YOU TALK
ABOUT YOUR FATHER EVEN POINTING
A GUN AT YOU.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW --
>> AND FIRING THE GUN.
>> I WAS 15.
I WAS VERY, VERY ANGRY AND HE
WAS VERY DRUNK AND VIOLENT AND
SO I EMPTIED A CRATE OF HIS
SCOTCH DOWN THE SINK.
IN THE DELUDED HOPE I COULD STOP
HIM DRINKING BY DOING THAT, BY
REMOVING THE SOURCE MATERIAL.
>> THAT'S A VERY NATURAL
IMPULSE.
>> AND HE HAD A GUN AND HE CAME
AT ME AND CALLED AT ME IN THE
GARDEN AND HAD THE GUN AT MY
TEMPLE.
I SAID BLOW MY BRAINS OUT.
GET IT OVER AND DONE WITH.
HE PULLED THE TRIGGER BUT
BECAUSE HE WAS SO DRUNK, HE
LURCHED.
I LIVED TO TELL THE TALE.
THE THING IS WITH ALL ADDICTION
I'M SURE YOU'VE EXPERIENCED WITH
PEOPLE THAT YOU'VE INTERVIEWED
BEFORE, THE PERSON THAT I LOVED
AND ADORED WHO'S MY FATHER WAS
VERY VERY QUICK WITTED AND
WELL-EDUCATED AND INCREDIBLY
CHARMING PERSON.
BY 9:00 AT NIGHT THIS JEKYLL AND
HYDE CHARACTER WOULD COME OUT
AND THAT WASN'T THE PERSON I
KNEW HIM TO BE.
IT WAS VERY CLEAR TO ME THAT OUR
LIVES WERE IN TWO HALVES.
>> BUT IT IS ACTUALLY
EXTRAORDINARY TO HEAR THAT HE
ACTUALLY PULLED THE TRIGGER.
YOU KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF
THREATENING BEHAVIOR THAT CAN
HAPPEN LIKE PUTTING A GUN TO
YOUR TEMPLE BUT HE PULLED THE
TRIGGER.
>> YEAH.
AND I RAN.
WHEN HE MISSED, I THEN RAN AWAY
FROM HOME FOR A WEEK.
I FELT MY LIFE WAS REALLY IN
DANGER.
>> AND GIVEN THE TITLE OF THIS
LATEST FILM, YOU KNOW, "CAN YOU
EVER FORGIVE ME?"
CAN YOU FORGIVE HIM?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HE BLACKED OUT AND DIDN'T
REMEMBER THIS HAD HAPPENED.
THAT'S THE WEIRD THING ABOUT IF
YOU'RE -- YOU FORGIVE YOUR
PARENTS ALMOST ANYTHING BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE THE PEOPLE
THAT YOU LOVE AND HE WASN'T LIKE
THAT ALL THE TIME.
DURING THE DAY HE WAS SOBER.
>> IT MUST BE SO DIFFICULT FOR A
KID.
YOUR MOTHER ALSO YOU CAUGHT HER
HAVING AN AFFAIR.
>> WHEN I WAS 10 YEARS OLD.
>> AND HOW DID THAT AFFECT YOU?
>> I STARTED KEEPING A DIARY,
WHICH I'VE KEPT EVER SINCE SINCE
I WAS 10 YEARS OLD.
I TRIED GOD AND GOT NO RESPONSE.
I HAVE NO FAITH OR RELIGION
ALTHOUGH I LIVE BY THE TEN
COMMANDMENTS.
I COULDN'T TELL MY FRIEND OR
FAMILY.
BY KEEPING A DIARY THIS MAKES IT
REAL.
IN THE SAME WAY THAT I'VE JUST
BEEN ON THE HUGE PRESS JUNKET IN
LOS ANGELES AND NEW YORK AND SAN
FRANCISCO FOR THIS FILM THAT
WHEN I MEET PEOPLE I NEVER
THOUGHT THAT I'D POSSIBLY MEET
MY WHOLE LIFE, WRITING ABOUT IT
IS A WAY OF MAKING IT REAL.
THAT'S A LIFELONG HABIT.
>> DID YOU EVER CONFRONT YOUR
MOM?
>> OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
>> WAS IT BECAUSE YOUR DAD WAS A
DRUNKYARD?
>> NO, NO.
SHE FELL IN LOVE WITH SOMEBODY
ELSE.
>> YOU THINK HE BECAME A DRUNK
BECAUSE OF THAT?
>> I KNOW HE DID.
AND SO HE SUFFERED, YOU KNOW,
UNREQUITED LOVE FOR HER AND
BASICALLY DRANK HIMSELF TO DEATH
AT THE AGE OF 53.
AFTER THREE DECADES OF
ESTRANGEMENT AFTER I HAD REALLY
GOOD PSYCHO ANALYSIS WITH AN
ABSOLUTELY BRILLIANT MAN IN
LONDON, I THEN HAD -- WITH MY
MOTHER.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
I SKYPED WITH HER TODAY.
I SKYPED WITH HER TODAY AND I
SPEAK TO HER ONCE A WEEK.
>> THAT REALLY IS WONDERFUL,
ACTUALLY, TO SEE --
>> OH, IT SAVED MY LIFE.
>> AND COME OUT OF THESE LIFE
ALTERING EXPERIENCES.
BUT I AM INTERESTED THAT YOU SAY
YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO ALCOHOL AND
YET YOUR BREAKOUT FILM YOU PLAY,
WHAT, AN ALCOHOLIC?
>> YOU PLAYED MORE ALCOHOLIC,
DRUG ADDICTS, COCAINE HEADS MORE
THAN ANYTHING ELSE IN MY CAREER.
>> THERE MUST BE A REASON.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'M GOING TO PLAY A LITTLE
CLIP JUST TO SHOW WHAT YOU LOOK
LIKE DRUNK.
>> THESE AREN'T MINE THEY BELONG
TO HIM.
>> YOU'RE DRUNK.
>> I ASSURE YOU I'M NOT OFFICER.
I'VE ONLY HAD A FEW ALES.
>> I PLAY A GOOD DRUNK.
THE NIGHT BEFORE THE FINAL DAY
OF REHEARSALS BECAUSE THE
DIRECTOR WHO'S A LIFELONG FRIEND
NOW, HE SAID THAT I HAD TO HAVE
A CHEMICAL MEMORY HE CALLED IT
OF WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO BE
COMPLETELY -- SO I DID AND I'VE
NEVER DONE IT SENSE.
I PASSED OUT.
>> HERE YOU ARE AS YOU SAID AT
THE AGE OF 61 AND 3/4 SUDDENLY
RECEIVING AWARDS NEVER HAD DONE
BEFORE AND YOU'RE IN THE PRIME
OF YOUR LIFE.
HOW HAPPY DO YOU FEEL?
>> I AM ASTONISHED BECAUSE I'M
VERY, VERY KIND AND CONSIDERATE
ACTOR RONNIE McDOWELL, I MET HIM
WHEN I WAS RESEARCHING A NOVEL
WHEN I WAS 40 AND HE SAID HOW DO
YOU SEE OLD AGE?
I SAID, I HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT
IT.
DO YOU GO -- I'M THE LUCKIEST
PERSON TO HAVE WORKED WITH, TO
HAVE MET WITH TO EARN THIS, SO
THE WISDOM OF THAT HAS REALLY
STAYED WITH ME.
IF YOU TOLD ME 41 YEARS AGO THAT
I'D BE IN THE FINAL "STAR WARS"
FILM THAT I'VE JUST BEEN
SHOOTING, I WOULD HAVE SAID
YOU'RE COMPLETELY INSANE.
THE FACT THAT I'VE HAD THIS UP
SURGE AT THE AGE I AM NOW IS
BEYOND ALL -- IT'S LIKE WHAT
JOHN LENNON SAID BEFORE HE WAS
SHOT THAT LIFE IS WHAT HAPPENS
IN BETWEEN MAKING YOUR PLANS AND
THAT REALLY IS WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO ME SO I'M INCREDIBLY
GRATEFUL.
>> RICHARD E. GRANT, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH INDEED.
>>> IT'S GREAT THAT HE'S GETTING
ALL THIS RECOGNITION FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN OVER 60 YEARS OLD
BUT NOW WE TURN TO COLLEGE AND A
COLLEGE ADMISSIONS COUNSELOR WHO
DEAD INDICATES HER CAREER TO
HELPING STRUGGLING STUDENTS.
HANNA STOTLAND SPECIALIZES IN
WHAT SHE CALLS THE KRYPTONITE
CASES, KIDS WITH A RECORD OF
SUBSTANCE ABUSE, LEGAL TROUBLES
OR BEHAVIORAL ISSUES THAT MIGHT
BLOCK THEIR PATH TO A COLLEGE
EDUCATION.
BUT ONE ASPECT OF STOTLAND'S
PRACTICE IS PARTICULARLY
CONTROVERSIAL.
SHE'S THE GO-TO EXPERT FOR
STUDENTS WHO ARE DISCIPLINED FOR
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT AT A TIME OF
WHITE HOT CONTROVERSY OVER HOW
COLLEGES HANDLE ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS, STOTLAND BELIEVES
THAT EVERYONE DESERVES A SECOND
CHANCE AS SHE'S BEEN TELLING OUR
MICHELLE MARTIN.
>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR TALKING TO
US.
>> THANK YOU.
I'M GLAD TO BE HERE.
>> YOU GOT YOUR G.E.D. AND THEN
YOU ACTUALLY TRANSFERRED TO
HARVARD.
TELL ME HOW ALL THAT HAPPENED.
>> SO I FLUNKED OUT OF HIGH
SCHOOL.
I HAD STRAIGHT Fs MY LAST THREE
SEMESTERS AND I DIDN'T THINK I
WAS COLLEGE MATERIAL.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS GOING TO
GO.
I GOT A JOB.
MY PARENTS SAID IF YOU'RE GOING
TO LIVE IN THE HOUSE YOU NEED TO
HAVE A JOB, SO I STARTED WORKING
FULL TIME ON MY 18th BIRTHDAY.
AFTER A COUPLE OF YEARS I
THOUGHT I WANTED TO GO TO
COLLEGE BUT I HAD NO IDEA, IF
ANY, FOUR YEAR COLLEGE WOULD
TAKE ME ON THE STRENGTH OF MY
TEST SCORES.
I GOT INTO A SMALL WOMEN'S
COLLEGE.
DID REALLY WELL FOR TWO YEARS
AND WAS ABLE TO TRANSFER AND
ENDED UP GOING TO HARVARD.
>> HOW DID YOU GET INTO
EDUCATIONAL CONSULTING?
>> THIS IS SOMETHING THAT CAME
TO ME.
AFTER I TRANSFERRED, I GOT A JOB
AS A TOUR GUIDE IN THE
ADMISSIONS OFFICE AND, YOU KNOW,
I WOULD BE GIVING A TOUR AND
THERE'S A SPOT IN THE TOUR
SCRIPT AND YOU SAY THIS IS WHAT
BROUGHT ME TO HARVARD AND I SAID
I HAD THREE Fs MY LAST SEMESTERS
OF HIGH SCHOOL, I GOT MY GED AND
I GOT HERE WHEN I WAS 22.
AFTER EVERY TOUR, SOME FAMILY
WOULD TALK TO ME.
>> DID THAT FREAK YOU OUT OR DID
YOU THINK -- DID YOU DO IT?
DID YOU CALL THESE PEOPLE'S
NEPHEW OR WHATEVER?
>> I WOULD GIVE THEM A CARD AND
I WOULD SAY, HERE'S MY EMAIL
DRESS AND IF YOU WANT TO GET IN
TOUCH WITH ME AND THOSE THAT DID
I WAS HAPPY TO TALK TO.
THEY WANTED TO KNOW, CAN YOU
RETAKE THE S.A.T. WHEN YOU'RE
20?
YES.
I HAD TO DO THAT.
QUESTIONS LIKE THAT AND SO IT
GREW FROM THERE AND I STARTED
LEARNING FROM MY CLIENTS.
>> YOU SAID IN ONE INTERVIEW
THAT I READ WITH YOU TO OTHER
FOLKS IN THE FIELD, YOU SAID
SEND ME YOUR CONVICTED, YOUR
EXPELLED, YOUR EATING DISORDER,
YOUR KRYPTONITE CASES IF YOU
WILL.
DID YOU MEAN THAT?
WHY DID YOU SAY THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY I MEANT IT.
I THINK THESE ARE -- THESE KIDS
CAN BENEFIT FROM EDUCATION TOO
AND IT'S REALLY HARD FOR THEM TO
GET IT, BUT I KNOW HOW TO HELP
THEM DO.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU SAID
YOU'RE DOING A LOT OF EATING
DISORDERS, KIDS WHO HAD TO TAKE
HEALTH BREAKS FROM SCHOOL AND
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
BACK IN, WHEN DID IT BECOME
ABOUT SEXUAL MISCONDUCT?
>> I GOT MY FIRST TWO CALLS FROM
STUDENTS WHO HAD BEEN ACCUSED OF
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT IN JANUARY
2014 AND THEY ASKED, CAN YOU
HELP ME IN THIS SITUATION AND I
SAID, I HAVE NO IDEA.
LET'S FIND OUT.
BUT AFTER I HAD A FEW SUCCESSFUL
CLIENTS, THE NEXT THING I KNEW I
HAD DOZENS.
>> WHY JANUARY 2014?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN THAT
STARTED TO STIMULATE THESE
PARTICULAR CASES?
>> I'M NOT SURE.
I THINK IT WAS PROBABLY A
DELAYED IMPACT OF THE 2011 OBAMA
ERA DEAR COLLEAGUE LETTER FROM
THE DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION THAT
REVISED THE STANDARDS THAT
UNIVERSITIES HAD TO FOLLOW IN
ADJUDICATING SEXUAL MISCONDUCT
CASES.
>> COULD YOU JUST BRIEFLY
DESCRIBE FOR PEOPLE WHO DON'T
FOLLOW THIS FIELD LIKE WHAT THE
SHIFT WAS?
>> THE SHIFT WAS DESIGNED TO
PUSH BACK AGAINST A SYSTEM THAT
WAS I THINK CORRECTLY PERCEIVED
AS SILENCING VICTIMS,
PARTICULARLY WOMEN, AND IT WAS
PERCEIVED AS NOT RESULTING IN
REAL CONSEQUENCES FOR FOLKS WHO
HAD COMMITTED HARASSMENT OR
ASSAULT AND SO IT WAS AN ATTEMPT
TO MAKE THE SYSTEM MORE
STRINGENT SO THAT THERE WOULD BE
STRICTER ENFORCEMENT OF TITLE 9,
THE LAW THAT MANDATES EQUALITY
OF THE SEXES IN HIGHER
EDUCATION.
>> IS THERE A TYPICAL SCENARIO
THAT BRINGS SOMEONE TO YOU?
>> SO ABOUT TWO-THIRDS OF MY
CASES STEM FROM I WOULD BROADLY
SAY A DRUNKEN HOOK-UP, ABOUT
ONE-THIRD OF THE CASES THE
ACCUSATION HAPPENED THE BREAK-UP
OF IN COLLEGE TERMS A LONG-TERM
RELATIONSHIP.
>> AND SO ARE THESE MOSTLY MEN,
YOUNG MEN?
>> THEY ARE MOSTLY YOUNG MEN WHO
ARE ACCUSED.
>> BY WOMEN?
>> BUT THAT'S -- THAT'S A MIX.
I SEE BOTH MEN AND WOMEN
ACCUSING MEN.
I HAVE A TINY HANDFUL OF WOMEN
WHO HAVE BEEN ACCUSED EITHER BY
MEN OR WOMEN.
>> AND WHAT DO YOU DO FOR THEM?
>> THE MAIN THING I DO FOR THEM
IS HELP THEM MAKE A PLAN FOR HOW
TO CONTINUE THEIR EDUCATION
AFTER THIS INTERRUPTION AND HELP
THEM TALK ABOUT THE PROBLEM ON
THEIR RECORD IN A WAY THAT GIVES
THEM A SHOT AT A SECOND CHANCE.
>> DO YOU ASK THEM WHAT HAPPENED
HERE?
>> YES.
>> IF YOU'RE REPRESENTING
SOMEBODY IN A CRIMINAL
PROCEEDING, I THINK THE QUESTION
WOULD BE, WHAT DO THEY SAY
HAPPENED?
>> I NEED BOTH.
IF I'M GOING TO HELP YOU WRITE
AN EXPLANATION OF WHAT HAPPENED,
I NEED TO UNDERSTAND AND YOU
NEED TO TALK ABOUT BOTH THE BEST
WAY OF LOOKING AT THE FACTS AND
THE WORSE WAY OF LOOKING AT THE
FACTS.
>> TALK TO ME MORE IF YOU WOULD
ABOUT HOW YOU GO ABOUT THIS.
>> I WANT TO TAKE THE COUNSELING
EQUIVALENT OF A SEARCHING
MEDICAL HISTORY, YOU WANT TO
KNOW BOTH FROM THE POINT OF VIEW
OF YOU AS A STUDENT, WHAT MAJOR
DO I WANT, WHAT'S MY CAREER PLAN
AND THEN ALSO WHAT HAPPENED HERE
IN THE INCIDENT IN QUESTION AND
ALSO IN THE PROCESS THAT LED YOU
OUT OF THAT SCHOOL.
>> DO YOU LOOK FOR REMORSE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WHAT IF IT'S NOT FORTHCOMING?
>> THERE'S OFTEN DISAGREEMENT
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED AND I DON'T
TRY TO EVALUATE, YOU KNOW, WHO'S
VERSION OF EVENTS WOULD MATCH A
VIDEO TAPE IF THERE HAD BEEN A
VIDEO TAPE.
IT'S NOT MY AREA OF EXPERTISE,
IT'S NOT MY JOB, BUT IT IS
ESSENTIAL TO MAKING THE ARGUMENT
THAT YOU NEED A SECOND CHANCE,
THAT THIS WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
IF THIS WAS JUST A LIGHTNING
STRIKE THAT COULD HAVE HAPPENED
TO ANYONE, THEN YOU HAVE NO --
NO LEG TO STAND ON SAYING I'M
GOING TO PREVENT THIS FROM
HAPPENING AGAIN IN MY LIFE.
EVEN IF YOU FEEL YOU DIDN'T
COMMIT ASSAULT WHICH MAYBE YOU
DIDN'T, I WASN'T THERE, YOU
BETTER FIND OTHER CHOICES THAT
YOU MADE THAT YOU WOULD MAKE
DIFFERENTLY NOW OF THE MAYBE YOU
WEREN'T AS KIND AS YOU COULD
HAVE BEEN.
MAYBE YOU WERE DRINKING UNDER
AGE, MAYBE YOU WERE HOOKING
UNDER SOMEONE WHO WAS DRINKING
OR USING DRUG AND NOW YOU THINK
THAT WASN'T SMART.
YOU NEED TO LOOK AT WHAT YOUR
FAILURES OF JUDGMENT, OF
KINDNESS, OF ANY STANDARD THAT
YOU WANT TO LIVE UP TO IN THE
FUTURE, LOOK AT THOSE FAILURES
AND TALK ABOUT HOW YOU'VE
CHANGED THEM.
>> AND HOW DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE
NOT INTRODUCING SOMEBODY
DANGEROUS BACK INTO AN
ENVIRONMENT WHERE THEY'RE JUST
GOING TO DO SOMETHING ELSE
BECAUSE GUESS WHAT, THEY GOT
AWAY WITH IT?
>> IT'S ALWAYS POSSIBLE THAT
SOMEONE WHO'S DONE SOMETHING
WRONG IN THE PAST WILL REPEAT
THAT BEHAVIOR.
THERE'S A COUPLE OF ASSUMPTIONS
THAT I WANT TO UNPACK.
ONE IS -- THESE KIDS WILL BE IN
THE COMMUNITY SOME WHERE.
THESE ARE NOT STUDENTS WHO ARE
TYPICALLY CHARGED WITH ANYTHING
CRIMINALLY AND SO THEY CAN BE IN
THE COMMUNITY AS STUDENTS OR
THEY CAN BE IN THE COMMUNITY AS
WORKERS OR VOLUNTEERS.
IF INDEED SOMEONE IS A HABITUAL
PREDATOR, THEY CAN AND WILL BE
THAT WHEREVER THEY MAY BE, YOU
KNOW, UNLESS THEY'RE IN A CELL
WHICH IS USUALLY NOT ON THE
TABLE.
>> CAN YOU GIVE US AN EXAMPLE
WITHOUT -- TO THE DEGREE THAT
YOU CAN WITHOUT VIOLATING YOUR
VOW OF CONFIDENTIALITY TO YOUR
CLIENT?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN YOU JUST GIVE ME MORE
DETAIL ABOUT A SCENARIO?
>> SO, THERE'S A FEW TYPICAL
SCENARIOS.
ONE IS TWO PEOPLE MEET AT A
PARTY, THEY GO OFF AND HOOK UP.
BOTH HAVE BEEN DRINKING.
FOLLOWING THE HOOK-UP IN SOME
DAYS OR MONTHS LATER, ONE OF THE
PARTIES ALLEGES THAT THEY WERE
TOO DRUNK TO CONSENT TO THE
HOOK-UP.
IN THAT CASE, FREQUENTLY THE
PERSON WHO DIDN'T MAKE THE
ALLEGATION IS GOING TO BE
EXPELLED OR SUSPENDED EVEN IF
THEY WERE EQUALLY OR MORE
INEBRIATED AND THE WHOLE
QUESTION THAT THE CASE WOULD
TURN ON IS WERE THEY INTOXICATED
OR WERE THEY INCAPACITATED.
>> WHICH PARTY?
THE CLAIMANT OR BOTH?
>> THE CLAIMANT.
SO THAT IS PROBABLY THE MOST
SINGLE MOST COMMON SCENARIO I
SEE WHERE YOU HAVE TWO
INTOXICATED PEOPLE AND EVERYONE
AGREES THAT THE -- THAT THE
ENCOUNTER WAS -- APPEARED
CONSENSUAL AT THE TIME.
THAT, YES, THERE WAS
PARTICIPATION.
THERE WASN'T NO, BUT THE
CONSENT -- THE APPARENT CONSENT
WAS NO GOOD BECAUSE OF THE LEVEL
OF INTOXICATION AND SO THAT'S
THE -- THAT'S THE CORE OF THE
DISPUTE USUALLY THAT DETERMINES
WHETHER SOMEONE GETS EXPELLED OR
NOT IS HOW DRUNK DO WE THINK THE
ACCUSER WAS AT THAT MOMENT.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT THE
BULK OF YOUR CASELOAD IS
AMBIGUOUS CONSENT?
>> THE BULK OF MY CASELOAD IS
AMBIGUOUS.
>> THERE'S NO FORCE INVOLVED IN
YOUR VIEW.
>> THERE'S A MEANINGFUL MINORITY
OF MY CASES WHERE FORCE IS
ALLEGED AND THERE'S USUALLY
MIXED EVIDENCE ON THAT QUESTION.
THE MAJORITY OF MY CASES DON'T
INVOLVE AN ALLEGATION OF FORCE.
>> WHAT IS THIS ABOUT IN YOUR
VIEW?
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
SAYING, TIMES UP, RIGHT?
ENOUGH.
WOMEN HAVE BEEN MANIPULATED FOR
TOO LONG, HAVE BE COERCED AND
HAVE HAD IT AND THEY'RE SPEAKING
UP NOW.
THAT'S WHAT SOME PEOPLE SAY IS
HAPPENING.
I TAKE IT YOU SAY IT'S ACTUALLY
DIFFERENT THAN THAT.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
I THINK THAT IS HAPPENING AND I
THINK THERE ARE A WHOLE LOT MORE
ACCUSATIONS.
PEOPLE ARE SPEAKING UP.
BOTH IN CASES WHERE -- WHERE THE
EVIDENCE IS UNAMBIGUOUS IN
SUPPORTING THE ALLEGATION AND
CASES WHERE IT'S AMBIGUOUS OR
EVEN RUNS CONTRARY TO THE
ALLEGATION, BUT IT IS ABSOLUTELY
TRUE THAT THE PATRIARCHY HAS
BEEN SILENCING OF VICTIMS FOR
SEXUAL VIOLENCE FOR MILL LENNA.
WE OUGHT TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
THAT AND THAT IN GENERAL THE
FACT THAT YOU HAVE A LOT OF
COMPLAINTS IS NOT A BAD THING.
>> YOU ARE A LAWYER BUT YOU
DON'T REPRESENT PEOPLE IN COURT,
DO YOU?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> CRIMINAL DEFENSE LAWYERS
OFTEN GET THIS QUESTION, RIGHT,
WHICH IS HOW CAN YOU DEFEND THAT
PERSON?
AND TYPICALLY WHAT THEY SAY IS,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S IN THE CONSTITUTION.
YOU HAVE A RIGHT TO A DEFENSE
AND HAVE A RIGHT TO BE
REPRESENTED BY COUNSEL AND THAT
I THINK A LOT OF THEM WOULD SAY
PARTICULARLY PEOPLE WHO TAKE
CASES THAT OTHER PEOPLE WON'T F
THE SYSTEM DOESN'T WORK FOR
EVERYBODY, IT DOESN'T WORK FOR
ANYBODY, OKAY?
BUT GOING TO A FOUR YEAR
COLLEGE, A PRIVATE COLLEGE,
THAT'S NOT IN THE CONSTITUTION
AND I REMEMBER IN ONE OF THE
INTERVIEWS YOU SAID THAT THERE
WAS A CLIENT YOU HELPED TO
BECAUSE HE WAS SUPER HAPPY
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T HAVE TO GO TO
COMMUNITY COLLEGE AND THE
QUESTION A LOT OF PEOPLE MIGHT
HAVE IS, WHY ARE THEY ENTITLED
TO GO TO A PRIVATE FOUR YEAR
COLLEGE, WHY IS THAT SOMETHING
THAT THEY HAVE TO HAVE?
>> THEY DON'T HAVE TO HAVE IT
AND THEY AREN'T ENTITLED TO IT.
THEY MAY EARN IT.
MY STUDENTS, AGAIN -- THE ONLY
REASON TO WORK WITH ME IS TO
TELL YOUR WHOLE STORY AND GIVE
EACH INSTITUTION AN OPPORTUNITY
TO MAKE THEIR OWN DECISION AND
FOR A TYPICAL CLIENT OF MINE
WHO'S BEEN EXPELLED FROM UNDER
GRAD, I WOULD ENCOURAGE THEM TO
APPLY TO ABOUT 30 UNIVERSITIES
AND I WOULD EXPECT THEM TO GET
INTO THREE TO FIVE.
THAT'S OFTEN A VERY GOOD OUTCOME
FOR ONE OF MY STUDENTS.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF COLLEGES
THAT HAVE NO TROUBLE SAYING NO,
BUT IF WHAT I'M HELPING THE
STUDENT DO IS MAKE THEIR CASE
FOR WHY ONE OF THE SPOTS IN THE
CLASS -- AND THEY'RE NOT HIGHLY
SELECTIVE COLLEGES, BUT WHY ONE
OF THE SPOTS IN CLASS WOULD BE
WELL SERVED WITH ME.
>> AND TELL ME WHY.
YOU SAY YOU THINK YOU'RE MAKING
THE SYSTEM MORE FAIR, TELL ME
WHY.
>> I THINK WE ABSOLUTELY SHOULD
BELIEVE WOMEN AND ACCUSERS IN
GENERAL, WHEN WE ARE THEIR
FRIENDS, THEIR DOCTORS, THEIR
PROFESSORS, THEIR FAMILY
MEMBERS, WHEN YOU'RE STUDENT OR
PATIENT OR FRIEND OR LOVED ONE
COMES TO YOU AND SAYS I WAS
ASSAULTED, BELIEVE THEM.
ABSOLUTELY BELIEVE THEM.
IF YOU ARE A JUDGE, A JUROR, A
JOURNALIST OR A DECISION MAKER
AT A COLLEGE, THERE'S NO ONE YOU
SHOULD AUTOMATICALLY BELIEVE.
IN THE FIRST INSTANCE, YOUR JOB
IS TO PROVIDE SUPPORT AND CARE
FOR THE PERSON IN YOUR LIFE AND
IN THE SECOND MUCH SMALLER GROUP
AND MANY PEOPLE ARE IN BOTH
GROUPS AT DIFFERENT TIMES, BUT
IN THE SECOND MUCH SMALLER GROUP
YOUR JOB IS TO SEEK THE TRUTH.
>> THERE ARE STILL THOSE THAT
WOULD ARGUE THAT THE SCALES HAVE
BEEN TIPPED ON ONE SIDE FOR SO
LONG THAT ANYTHING YOU DO ON THE
OTHER SIDE IS HELPING THE
PATRIARCHY TO FELT BACK AND IT
IS UNDENIABLE THAT MOST OF THE
PEOPLE THAT RETAIN YOU
WELL-HEALED, OVERWHELMINGLY
MALE, OVERWHELMINGLY WHITE, THIS
IS A GROUP THAT CONTROLS MOST OF
THE ASSETS IN THE COUNTRY, SO
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY TO THOSE AND
I'M NOT SAYING IT'S FAIR, WHAT
WOULD YOU SAY TO THOSE THAT SAY
WHY IS THAT FAIR?
THE SCALES ARE ALWAYS ON THIS
GROUP'S SIDE, WHY ARE YOU
HELPING HIM?
>> I'M HELPING THEM BECAUSE THIS
IS ABOUT INDIVIDUAL JUSTICE.
I THINK IF IF I'M EXAMINING U.S.
SOCIETY FROM 30,000 FEET, I
MIGHT MAKE DIFFERENT CHOICES
THAN IF I'M LOOKING AT IT ONE
STUDENT AT A TIME.
I THINK OUR JUSTICE SYSTEM AND
THE TITLE 9 ENFORCEMENT SYSTEM
IS LIKE THE JUSTICE SYSTEM, FOR
GOOD AND FOR ILL, FOR ILL IN
THAT IT'S RACIST JUST LIKE EVERY
OTHER SYSTEM IN THE U.S., FOR
ILL THAT IT FAVORS THOSE WITH
GREATER RESOURCES JUST LIKE
EVERY OTHER SYSTEM IN THE U.S.,
BUT FOR GOOD IN THAT WE DON'T
JUDGE PEOPLE BY, OKAY, WELL
YOU'RE A WHITE MALE, THAT MEANS
YOU ARE A RACIST.
WE TRY AND DETERMINE, ALL RIGHT,
THE ALLEGATION IS ABOUT YOU AND
SARAH IN DRAKE HALL ON THE 19th
AND WHAT HAPPENED THERE AND I
THINK THAT'S HOW WE OUGHT TO DO
JUSTICE WHETHER IT'S CRIMINAL
JUSTICE OR IN THIS CASE SCHOOL
DISCIPLINE JUSTICE, WE SHOULD BE
SAYING, WHAT HAPPENED IN THIS
CASE BETWEEN THESE INDIVIDUALS.
>> I CANNOT HELP BUT WONDER WHAT
YOUR REACTION WAS TO THE
KAVANAUGH HEARINGS.
>> I'VE NOW WORKED WITH MANY
DOZENS OF YOUNG MEN AND I'M
CERTAIN THAT IN MY POPULATION
I'M SEEING BOTH PEOPLE WHO ARE
WRONGLY ACCUSED AND PEOPLE WHO
ARE CORRECTLY ACCUSED.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHO IS WHO.
I'VE NEVER SEEN AN ACCUSED YOUNG
MAN RAGE, CRY AND BLAME IN MY
ENTIRE CAREER THE WAY JUSTICE
KAVANAUGH DID IN FRONT OF THE
U.S. SENATE AND I'M THEIR
COUNSELOR.
I WOULDN'T JUDGE THEM IF THEY
DID DO THAT.
YOU WOULD TAKE THEM AS I'VE FIND
IT, I'VE --
>> WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THAT?
>> I CAN'T DECIDE WHETHER IT'S
MORE DISQUALIFYING THAT HE
UNCONTROLLABLY HAD AN EMOTIONAL
OUTBURST AND TALKED BACK TO THE
U.S. SENATE AND EVERYTHING ELSE
OR WHETHER THAT WAS ALL A
PLANNED, CAREFUL CYNICAL
POLITICAL ACT.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH OF THOSE
WOULD BE MORE DISQUALIFYING FOR
THE SUPREME COURT BUT THEY'RE
BOTH POSSIBILITIES ARE
DISQUALIFYING IN MY BOOK.
>> CAN WE JUST TAKE A STEP BACK
AND TAKE THAT 30,000 FOOT VIEW
OF RELATIONSHIPS RIGHT NOW,
RELATIONSHIPS ON CAMPUS AND WHAT
SHOULD HAPPEN?
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU CAN TELL
US BY WHAT YOU'RE SEEING ON
CAMPUS?
>> A BIG PART OF WHAT I'M SEEING
IS THAT A WHOLE LOT OF STUDENTS
WOULD BE A LOT BETTER OFF IF
THERE WERE LESS ALCOHOL ABUSE.
THAT'S THE ALMOST -- I HESITATE
TO SAY THIS, ALMOST THE EASY
PART.
THERE WILL ABSOLUTELY STILL
CONTINUE TO BE SEXUAL ASSAULT IN
A SOCIETY THAT DOESN'T HAVE SUCH
RAMPANT ALCOHOL ABUSE, BUT IT'S
PLAYING AN ENORMOUS ROLE IN THE
LARGE MAJORITY OF MY CASES.
I'D LOVE TO SEE A LOT MORE
PUBLIC HEALTH RESEARCH ABOUT
PREVENTION IN GENERAL AND ABOUT
ALCOHOL RESPONSIBILITY IN
PARTICULAR.
THE CONFLATION OF GETTING WASTED
ALL THE TIME AND GETTING THE
MOST OUT OF COLLEGE IS A WHITE
MIDDLE CLASS IDEA.
WE ALREADY DON'T SEE IT AT
NEARLY THE SAME WAY WITH FIRST
GENERATION STUDENTS, WE DON'T
SEE IT WITH NONWHITE STUDENTS.
THAT IS A REALLY POISONOUS IDEA
THAT'S HURTING A LOT OF
STUDENTS.
>> I'M TRYING TO HEAR OUR
CONVERSATION THROUGH THE EARS OF
PEOPLE WHO MIGHT HAVE OTHER
EXPERIENCES AND THERE ARE GOING
TO BE PEOPLE WHO ARE GOING TO
HEAR WHAT YOU SAID AND SAY,
YOU'RE BLAMING THE VICTIM, LIKE
A WOMAN HAS A RIGHT TO BE ALONE
WITH A MAN AND HAS A RIGHT TO
HAVE HAD A COUPLE DRINKS AND NOT
BE RAPED OR ASSAULTED OR HAD SEX
AGAINST HER WILL AND TO THAT YOU
WOULD SAY?
>> YOU HAVE ALL THE RIGHTS IN
THE WORLD.
YOU HAVE RIGHTS TO DO LOTS OF
THINGS AND THE WORLD HAS A LOT
OF BAD PEOPLE IN IT AND THAT
HASN'T BEEN SOMETHING THAT ANY
PROPHET OR KING OR ANYONE HAS
BEEN ABLE TO SOLVE AND I'M
INTERESTED IN HARM REDUCTION.
I WANT PEOPLE TO GO OUT THERE
AND LEARN, DISCOVER WHAT HELPS
REDUCE ALL OF THIS HARM TO THESE
YOUNG PEOPLE THAT'S SO
UNNECESSARY.
>> HANNA STOTLAND, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR TALKING WITH US.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING
ME.
>>> IT'S A COMPLICATED QUESTION
ESPECIALLY IN THIS TIMES UP
MOMENT.
DO THESE YOUNG MEN DESERVE A
SECOND CHANCE.
STOTLAND, OF COURSE, BELIEVES
THEY DO AND THAT IS IT FOR OUR
PROGRAM TONIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING AMANPOUR
AND COMPANY ON PBS AND JOIN US
AGAIN TOMORROW NIGHT.