Captioning sponsored by CBS
>> O'Donnell: BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT: DEADLOCKED.
THE COURTROOM BOMBSHELL.
JURORS AT HARVEY WEINSTEIN'S
RAPE TRIAL ASKING WHAT TO DO IF
THEY CAN'T REACH A VERDICT ON
ALL OF THE CHARGES.
COULD THE TRIAL END WITH A HUNG
JURY?
THE BREAKING NEWS FROM THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
AFTER THAT BRUTAL DEBATE,
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG HAS A CHANGE
OF HEART.
WHAT HE'S NOW SAYING ABOUT THOSE
SECRET AGREEMENTS HE MADE WITH
WOMEN YEARS AGO.
PLUS, WHO'S IN THE LEAD ON THE
EVE OF THE NEVADA CAUCUSES.
UNDER ARREST: THE IDAHO MOM WHO
WENT ON VACATION AFTER HER
CHILDREN DISAPPEARED IS BEHIND
BARS TONIGHT.
WHY DID POLICE FINALLY MOVE IN
MONTHS AFTER HER KIDS WENT
MISSING?
THE GROWING ANGER OVER
CORONAVIRUS.
PROTESTERS ATTACK BUSES FILLED
WITH PEOPLE EVACUATED FROM CHINA
AS FEAR OVER THE DEADLY VIRUS
SPREADS.
PLUS, THE NEW WARNING TONIGHT
FROM THE C.D.C.
INTELLIGENCE FALLOUT: THE
PRESIDENT LASHES OUT, BLASTING
INTEL FROM HIS OWN GOVERNMENT
AFTER OFFICIALS TELL CONGRESS
THAT RUSSIA IS INTERFERING IN
THIS YEAR'S ELECTION.
WHAT CBS NEWS IS LEARNING ABOUT
THAT CLOSED DOOR BRIEFING.
ROYAL NAME CHANGE: THE BIG
ANNOUNCEMENT FROM P PRINCE HARRY
AND MEGHAN.
WHAT THEY NOW WON'T EWON'T BE
CALLING THEMSELVES.
HAILED AS A HERO: SHE RAN INTO
AN INFERNO TO RESCUE A DYING MAN
JUST DAYS AFTER SHE GAVE BIRTH.
>> IF I CAN DO ANYTHING TO SAVE
THAT LIFE, I'M GOING TO.
>> O'Donnell: AND STEVE
HARTMAN GOES "ON THE ROAD" WITH
A BOY WHO SHARES A SPECIAL BOND
WITH THE PETS NO ONE ELSE WANTS.
>> THIS IS THE "CBS EVENING
NEWS" WITH NORAH O'DONNELL
REPORTING FROM THE NATION'S
CAPITAL.
>> O'Donnell: GOOD EVENING.
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
WE'RE GOING TO BEGIN TONIGHT
WITH BREAKING NEWS FROM HARVEY
WEINSTEIN'S RAPE TRIAL.
LATE TODAY, JURORS SUGGESTED
THEY MAY BE DEADLOCKED ON TWO OF
THE MOST SERIOUS CHARGES AGAINST
THE MOVIE MOGUL.
IN A NOTE TO THE JUDGE
OVERD IF THEY HAD TO
REACH A UNANIMOUS VERDICT ON ALL
OF THE COUNTS AGAINST THE FORMER
HOLLYWOOD PRODUCER.
THE ALLEGATIONS AGAINST
WEINSTEIN LAUNCHED THE "ME TOO"
MOVEMENT PROMPTING WOMEN ACROSS
THE COUNTRY TO SPEAK OUT AND
REVEAL ACCUSATIONS AGAINST
POWERFUL MEN.
JERICKA DUNCAN LEADS OFF OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT FROM OUTSIDE
THE COURTHOUSE.
>> Reporter: HARVEY WEINSTEIN
LEFT COURT TODAY, HIS FATE STILL
IN THE HANDS OF THE JURY.
AFTER FOUR DAYS OF DELIBERATING,
JURORS INDICATED THIS AFTERNOON
THEY COULD BE CLOSE TO REACHING
A VERDICT.
IN THEIR 11th NOTE TO THE
JUDGE, THEY HAD A QUESTION
REGARDING THE FIVE FELONY COUNTS
WEINSTEIN IS FACING.
"CAN WE BE HUNG ON ONE AND/OR
THREE AND UNANIMOUS ON THE OTHER
CHARGES?"
CHARGES ONE AND THREE ARE THE
MOST SERIOUS-- PREDATORY SEXUAL
ASSAULT-- AND CARRY UP TO LIFE
IN PRISON.
THE DEFENSE AND PROSECUTION
COULD NOT AGREE ON ACCEPTING A
PARTIAL VERDICT, SO JUDGE JAMES
BURKE TOLD THE JURY TO KEEP AT
IT.
"IT IS NOT UNCOMMON FOR A JURY
TO BELIEVE THAT THEY WILL NEVER
BE ABLE TO REACH A UNANIMOUS
VERDICT.
BUT AFTER FURTHER DELIBERATIONS,
MOST JURORS," HE SAID, "ARE ABLE
TO REACH A UNANIMOUS VERDICT."
CBS NEWS LEGAL ANALYST RICKY CLI
MAN:
>> IF HARVEY WEINSTEIN IS
CONVICTED OF ANY OF THE THREE
COUNTS, HE IS FACING REALLY
SERIOUS TIME IN PRISON BECAUSE
THESE ARE SERIOUS FELONIES.
>> Reporter: WEINSTEIN IS
ACCUSED OF SEXUALLY ASSAULTING
HIS FORMER PRODUCTION ASSISTANT,
MIRIAM HALEY, IN 2006.
HE IS ALSO CHARGED WITH RAPING
ASPIRING ACTRESS JESSICA MANN IN
2013.
DELIBERATIONS WILL CONTINUE ON
MONDAY MORNING FOR A FIFTH DAY.
NOW, WEINSTEIN HAS MAINTAINED
ALL ALONG THAT HE SAYS THE
RELATIONSHIPS HE'S HAD WITH HIS
ACCUSERS ARE CONSENSUAL AND,
NORAH, NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
HERE IN MANHATTAN, HARVEY
WEINSTEIN STILL FACES SEXUAL
ASSAULT CHARGES IN LOS ANGELES.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT,
JERICKA, THANK YOU.
NOW TO THE 2020 CAMPAIGN ON THE
EVE OF TOMORROW'S NEVADA CAUCUS,
A NEW POLL SHOWS BERNIE SAND
WERS A BIG LEAD OVER HIS
DEMOCRATIC RIVALS IN THE SILVER
STATE.
AND TONIGHT MICHAEL BLOOMBERG IS
SCRAMBLING TO EXPLAIN
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXIST COMMENTS
TOWARDS WOMEN WHO HAVE WORKED,
FOR HIM.
>> Reporter: UNDER INTENSE
PRESSURE TO REE
EMPLOYEES FROM NONDISCLOSURE
AGREEMENTS...
>> WHAT WE NEED TO KNOW IS
EXACTLY WHAT'S LURK OUT THERE.
>> Reporter: ...MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG ANNOUNCED TODAY HIS
COMPANY IDENTIFIED THREE WOMEN
WHO SIGNED N.D.A. AND THEY WOULD
BE ABLE TO TALK ABOUT THEIR
ALLEGATIONS.
HE ADDED:
THE FORMER NEW YORK MAYOR
CONTINUES TO TAKE FIRE FROM ALL
SIDES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP, SPEAKING HERE
IN LAS VEGAS AND HOPING TO
MUDDLE THE DEMOCRATIC MESSAGE,
MOCKED BLOOMBERG'S LAST DEBATE
PERFORMANCE, WHICH WAS WIDELY
PANNED.
>> MINI-MIKE.
HE WAS A BEAUTY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Reporter: BERNIE SANDERS
ALSO TOOK EXCEPTION WITH
BLOOMBERG.
>> DO YOU SEE MICHAEL BLOOMBERG
BEING ABLE TO BUILD A MOVEMENT?
>> YOU'RE NOT ASKING THAT IN A
SERIOUS-- YES, I THINK HE WILL
HAVE A VERY STRONG MOVEMENT OF
THE BILLIONAIRES RALLYING AROUND
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG.
BEYOND THAT, NOT SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: MEANWHILE, MUCH
OF THE REST OF THE DEMOCRATIC
FIELD IS WORRIY SANDERS, WHO
ALSO LEADS IN NATIONAL POLLS,
COULD SOON BECOME UNSTOPPABLE.
>> WE COULD BE JUST A WEAK
EXPAEF WAY FROM BERNIE SANDERS
HAVING A DOMINATING LEAD IN THIS
PROCESS.
AND EVEN THOUGH HE'S GOT A A
VERY STRONG BASE OF SUPPORT,
THAT'S CLEARLY NOT WHAT MOST
DEMOCRATS WANT.
>> Reporter: ALREADY, 75,000
PEOPLE HAVE VOTED EARLY HERE IN
NEVADA, NEARLY AS MANY AS
CAUCUSED FOUR YEARS AGO.
BUT BECAUSE THEY'LL BE USING
IPADS TO TABULATE VOTE TOTALS
TOMORROW, THERE'S A CHANCE FOR
THE SAME MATH AND TECHNOLOGY
PROBLEMS THAT PLAGUEDLY THE IOWA
CAUCUS JUST A FEW WEEKS AGO.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT, ED,
THANK YOU.
AND THIS PROGRAMMING NOTE.
GAYLE KING AND I WILL MODERATE
THE NEXT PRESIDENTIAL DEMOCRATIC
DEBATE FROM CHARLESTON, SOUTH
CAROLINA, TUESDAY NIGHT AT 8:00
EASTERN TIME.
AND WE'RE INTERESTED IN YOUR
QUESTIONS FOR THE CANDIDATE.
YOU CAN USE THE HASHTAG
#DEMDEBATE.
TONIGHT, PROSECUTORS IN HAWAII
ARE CALLING THE MOTHER OF TWO
MISSING CHILDREN A FLIGHT RISK.
LORI VALLOW JUST MADE HER FIRST
COURT APPEARANCE AFTER BEING
ARRESTED ON FELONY CHARGES IN
THIS BIZARRE CASE.
IT BEGAN IN IDAHO AND SPANS
MULTIPLE STATES OVER SEVERAL
MONTHS, AND INCLUDES THREE
MYSTERIOUS DEATHS OF FAMILY
MEMBERS.
JONATHAN VIGLIOTTI REPORTS
TONIGHT FROM KAUAI.
>> Reporter: LORI VALLOW IS
SPENDING TONIGHT IN A KAUAI JAIL
CELL, HER BAIL ACCEPT THE AT $5
MILLION.
FOR MONTHS, VALLOW HAS BEEN
LIVING IN HAWAII WITH HER NEW
HUSBAND, CHAD DAYBELL, WHO WAS
ALSO QUESTIONED BY POLICE.
HE WAS NOT ARRESTED.
POLICE HAVE SAID VALLOW AND
DAYBELL HAVE LIED ABOUT THE
CHILDREN'S WHEREABOUTSS.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHERE J.J. AND
TYLEE ARE AND WHATEVER THEY HAVE
TO DO TO GIVE US AS FAMILY
MEMBERS THAT CLOSURE.
>> Reporter: JARED KUSHNER IS
TYLEE RYAN'S AUNT.
>> HOPEFULLY, SHE WILL COME TO
THE CONCLUSION THAT JUST COMING
CLEAN WILL BE THE BEST PATH FOR
HER BECAUSE LAURIE IS ONLY GOING
TO ACT IN THE BEST INTEREST OF
LORI.
>> Reporter: VALLOW FACES
SEVERAL SERIOUS CHARGES:
DESERTING HER CHILDREN AND
DELAYING LEGAL ATTEMPTS TO
LOCATE THEM, EACH COUNT CARRYING
A POSSIBLE 14 YEARS IN PRISON.
ANOTHER CHARGE, CONTEMPT OF
COURT, FOR NOT PHYSICALLY
PRODUCING HER CHILDREN TO
AUTHORITIES IN IDAHO AS ORDERED.
AUTHORITIES ARE ALSO
INVESTIGATING THREE SUSPICIOUS
DEATHS CONNECTED TO THE COUPLE:
DAYBELL'S WIFE, TOOMEY; VALLOW'S
ESTRANGED HUSBAND, CHARLES;  AND
VALLOW'S BROTHER, ALEX COX, WHO
KILLED CHARLES AND LATER DIED OF
UNKNOWN CAUSES HIMSELF.
BUT FOR CUSHING THE CHILDREN
COME FIRST.
>> WE STILL, POTENTIALLY, HAVE A
LONG ROAD AHEAD OF US.
BUT WE ARE HOPEFULLY ONE STEP
CLOSER TO FINDING TYLEE AND J.J.
>> Reporter: AND CBS NEWS HAS
JUST LEARNED MORE FROM
INVESTIGATORS ABOUT WHAT LED UP
TO LORI VALLOW'S ARREST.
HER FINANCIAL RECORDS REVEAL NOT
A PENNY HAS BEEN SPENT ON CHILD
CARE SINCE THEY DISAPPEARED IN
SEPTEMBER.
PRESCRIPTIONS FOR J.J.'S AUTISM
MEDICATION HAVE ALSO GONE
UNFILLED.
LORI VALLOW IS FIGHTING THIS
EXTRADITION.
HER NEXT COURT APPEARANCE IS SET
FOR MARCH 2.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: SO MANY MORE
DETAILS TO BE LEARNED IN THIS
INVESTIGATION.
JONATHON, THANK YOU.
TONIGHT, THE C.D.C. IS CALLING
THE CORONAVIRUS A TREMENDOUS
HEALTH THREAT.
IT'S NOW WORKING WITH STATE AND
LOCAL HEALTH OFFICIALS TO MAKE
SURE THAT HOSPITALS, PHARMACIES,
AND MEDICAL SUPPLY COMPANIES CAN
MEET THE DEMANDS OF A POTENTIAL
PANDEMIC.
THE VIRUS HAS KILLED MORE THAN
2200 PEOPLE AND INFECTED NEARLY
77,000 WORLDWIDE.
CARTER EVANS HAS MORE ON THE
GROWING THREAT.
>> Reporter: PROTESTERS SET
FIRES IN THE STREETS OF UKRAINE
TO BLOCK BUSES CARRYING EVACUEES
FROM CHINA.
FEAR AND THE CORONAVIRUS HFL IS
SPREADING RAPIDLY AROUND THE
WORLD WITH INFECTIONS NOW IN
MORE THAN 30 COUNTRIES.
AUTHORITIES ARE DISINFECTING
STREETS IN SOUTH KOREA, WHERE
CONFIRMED CASES DOUBLED
OVERNIGHT.
AT A MASS WEDDING IN THE
PHILIPPINES, MORE THAN 200
COUPLES EXCHANGED VOWS, ALL
WEARING MASKS.
BACK IN THE U.S., INFECTED
EVACUEES ARE BEING TRANSFERRED
TO SPECIALIZED BIOCONTAINMENT
HOSPITALS, THIS AS THE NUMBER OF
CONFIRMED CASES JUMPS TO 34.
AND TODAY, FOR THE FIRST TIME,
C.D.C. DOCTORSAID IN A TELEPHONE
BRIEFING THEY'RE BRACING FOR THE
POSSIBILITY OF THE VIRUS
SPREADING ACROSS THE U.S.
>> Reporter: AND NOW, AN
URGENT NEW WARNING FROM THE
STATE DEPARTMENT: AVOID
TRAVELING BY CRUISE SHIP AROUND
ASIA.
THE C.D.C. SAYS ALL AMERICAN
EVACUEES FROM THE "DIAMOND
PRINCESS" ARE AT HIGH RISK, AND
THEY EXPECT MORE TO TEST
POSITIVE.
SO FAR, THERE HAVE ONLY BEEN TWO
PERSON-TO-PERSON TRANSMISSIONS
OF THE VIRUS HERE IN THE U.S.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT,
CARTER, THANK YOU.
AMERICAN INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
HAVE BEEN CLEAR, VLADIMIR
PUTIN'S GOVERNMENT IS STILL
TRIED TRYGGVASON TO MEDDLE IN
AMERICAN ELECTIONS.  TONIGHT,
CBS NEWS HAS LEARNED BERNIE
SANDERS' CAMPAIGN WAS TOLD THE
RUSSIANS HAVE BEEN WORKING TO
HELP HIS CAMPAIGN.
BUT IT'S THIS CLOSED DOOR
BRIEFING TO UPDATE MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS THAT HAS IGNITED A
FIRESTORM, WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
PUBLICLY QUESTIONING THE
JUDGMENT OF THE TRADITIONALLY
INDEPENDENT INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY.
PAULA REID REPORTS TONIGHT FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
TODAY BLASTED ASSESSMENTS BY HIS
OWN INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS THAT
RUSSIA WANTS TO SEE HIM
RE-ELECTED.
>> HERE WE GO AGAIN.
DID YOU SEE IT?
>> Reporter: OFFICIALS FROM
SEVERAL AGENCIES BRIEFED THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
LAST WEEK.
>> THIS WAS A BROAD, MULTIAGENCY
BRIEFING IN WHICH U.S. OFFICIALS
TOLD LAWMAKERS THAT RUSSIA WAS
CONTINUING TO INTERFERE IN THE
U.S. ELECTIONS, AND THAT IT HAS
ESTABLISHED A PREFERENCE FOR
DONALD TRUMP.
>> Reporter: SOURCES SAY
LAWMAKERS PUSHED BACK AND WANTED
TO SEE THE UNDERLYING
INTELLIGENCE.
AND PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS FURIOUS
WHEN HE FOUND OUT ABOUT THE
BRIEFING.
>> I WAS TOLD IT WAS HAPPENING.
I WAS TOLD A WEEK AGO.
THEY SAID,UN," THEY'RE TRYING TO
START A RUMOR.
IT'S DISINFORMATION."
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
THIS WEEK OUSTED NAVY VETERAN
JOSEPH MAGUIRE AS ACTING
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, REPLACING HIM WITH
U.S. AMBASSADOR TO GERMANY
RICHARD GRENELL, A VOCAL TRUMP
SUPPORTER, WITH NO PREVIOUS
INTELLIGENCE EXPERIENCE.
GRENELL'S NEW DEPUTY IS ANOTHER
TRUMP LOYALIST, CASH PATEL, WHO
HAS BEEN TOLD TO CLEAN HOUSE.
JUST TODAY, THE FIFTH TOP
OFFICIAL SINCE AUGUST ANNOUNCED
HE WAS LEAVING.
>> IF YOU HAVE SOMEBODY AT THE
TOP WHO IS OVERLY RESPONSE TOIFT
PRESIDENT, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
GET THAT KIND OF UNBIASED
INFORMATION, AND IT'S VERY,
VERY, VERY DANGEROUS FOR
NATIONAL SECURITY.
>> Reporter: TODAY, BERNIE
SANDERS REVEALED THAT HE HAS
BEEN BRIEFED ON RUSSIAN EFFORTS
TO BOOST HIS CAMPAIGN, AND THIS
IS NOTHING NEW.
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION FOUND
THAT THE RUSSIANS ALSO WORKED
BACK IN 2016 TO BOOST THE
SANDERS CAMPAIGN AND THE
CAMPAIGN OF THEN-CANDIDATE
TRUMP.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT,
PAULA, THANK YOU.
THERE'S A BIG ANNOUNCEMENT
TONIGHT FROM PRINCE HARRY AND
HIS WIFE, MEGHAN.
AFTER LONG DISCUSSIONS WITH THE
QUEEN, THE COUPLE HAS GIVEN UP
ON PLANS TO USE THE TERM "SUSSEX
ROYAL" WHEN THEY PROMOTE
THEMSELVESES ON INSTAGRAM AND
THE WEBSITE.
HARRY AND MEGHAN FORMALLY
STEPPED DOWN AS SENIOR MEMBERS
OF THE ROYAL NAMELY AT THE END
OF NEXT MONTH.
TONIGHT, PROSECUTORS IN NEW YORK
CITY ARE TAKING A FRESH LOOK AT
THE ASSASSINATION OF MALCOLM X,
WHICH TOOK PLACE EXACTLY 55
YEARS AGO.
NEW EVIDENCE FROM A NETFLIX
DOCUMENTARY IS RAISING QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHETHER TWO MEN WERE SENT
TO PRISON FOR A MURDER THEY DID
NOT COMMIT.
MAURICE DuBOIS TAKES A LOOK.
>> Reporter: THE SIX-PART
DOCUMENTARY PRESENTS NEW FACTS
ABOUT MALCOLM X'S ASSASSINATION
AND CLAIMS THE POLICE BOTCHED
THE INVESTIGATION.
>> THE OFFICIAL COUNT OF WHO
KILLED MALCOLM X, IT'S NOT TRUE.
>> Reporter: MALCOLM X,
ALIENATED FROM THE NATION OF
ISLAM, WAS KILLED IN A BARRAGE
OF BULLETS AS HE WAS ABOUT TO
GIVE A SPEECH IN HARL ONLY THIS
VERY DAY IN 1965.
>> PANDEMONIUM BROKE OUT AMONG
THE NEARLY 400 PEOPLE GATHERED
INSIDE THE AUDUBON BALLROOM.
THE CHAOS SPILLED OUT ON TO THE
SIDEWALK, WHERE ONE SUSPECT,
TALMADGE HAYER, HAD TO BE SAVED
BY NEW YORK CITY POLICE
OFFICERS.
TWO OTHER MEN WERE LATER
ARRESTED, AND ALL THREE WERE
CONVICTED IN MALCOLM'S DEATH.
PHIL BERTELSEN AND NAILAH SIMS
PRODUCED THE DOCUMENTARY.
>> THE F.B.I. HAD EYEWITNESS
TESTIMONY FROM, PRESUMABLY, THE
NINE INFORMANT THAT WERE IN THE
ROOM THAT DAY ABOUT WHO DID THE
CRIME.
>> Reporter: TALMADGE HAYER
CONFESSED, BUT THE OTHER MEN,
THOMAS JOHNSON, AND NORMAN
BUTLER, WHO CHANGED HIS NAME TO
MUHAMMAD AZIZ, MAINTAINED THEIR
INNOCENCE.
AZIZ, NOW 81, SPENT 20 YEARS IN
PRISON.
>> IF I WANTED TO DO TI COULDN'T
HAVE DONE IT.
SO THAT MEANS THEY KNEW WHAT
THEY WERE DOING WHEN THEY PUT ME
IN JAIL.
>> Reporter: THE MANHATTAN
D.A.'S OFFICE RECENTLY ANNOUNCED
IT'S OPENED A PRELIMINARY REVIEW
OF THE MURDER.
WHAT DO YOU HOPE HAPPENS HERE
FOR HIM?
>> I HOPE HE GETS EXONERATED.
>> I HOPE HE GETS A FIGHTING
CHANCE AT CLEARING HIS NAME ONCE
AND FOR ALL.
>> Reporter: A FIGHTING CHANCE
TO SET RECORD STRAIGHT AND
REWRITE HISTORY.
MAURICE DuBOIS, CBS NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> O'Donnell: AND THERE S
STILL MUCH MORE NEWS AHEAD ON
TONIGHT'S "CBS EVENING NEWS."
DRAMATIC NEW BODY CAM FOOTAGE AS
POLICE OPENED FIRE TO STOP A
TERROR ATTACK.
DAYS AFTER GIVING BIRTH, THIS
MOM IS CREDITED WITH SAVING THE
LIFE OF A STRANGER.
LATER, "ON THE ROAD," WHY A
YOUNG BOY HAS A SPECIAL
CONNECTION WITH THE OLDEST,
SCRUFFIEST DOGS IN THE POUND.
Wherever we want to go,
Autosave your way
there with Chase.
Chase.
Make More Of What's Yours.
Saturdays Happen.
Pain Happens.
Aleve It.
Aleve is proven stronger
and longer on pain
than Tylenol.
When pain happens, Aleve It.
All Day Strong.
Discover a new world
♪
Discover what's good -
Pantene Nutrient Blends
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN MAKE ME SHOW UP
TOO EARLY... OR TOO LATE.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.
(Fozzie)
Wow!
Hey Portal, call Kermit.
(Kermit)
Fozzie!
(Fozzie)
Kermit!
(Kermit)
I sent everyone a Portal so we
can be together
no matter where we are!
(Animal)
Ala lala lala lala!
(Floyd)
Look, it's going where you go!
(Janice)
I think it's got like a Smart
Camera.
(Ma Bear)
How's Chicago?
(Fozzie)
Ah, great city! But the winters
are unbearable!
(Fozzie and Ma Bear)
Ahhhh!
(Kermit)
Piggy, it's good to see you.
(Piggy)
You too, Kermie. You, too.
(Fozzie VO)
Portal from Facebook.
Managing lipids like very high
triglycerides, can be tough.
You diet. Exercise.
But if you're also taking
fish oil supplements...
You should know...
they are not FDA approved...
they may have saturated fat and
may even raise bad cholesterol.
To treat very high
triglycerides,
discover the science
of prescription VASCEPA.
Proven in multiple
clinical trials,
VASCEPA, along with diet is the
only prescription EPA treatment,
approved by the FDA to lower
very high triglycerides by 33%,
without raising bad cholesterol.
Look. It's clear, there's only
one prescription EPA VASCEPA.
Vascepa is not right
for everyone.
Do not take Vascepa if you are
allergic to icosapent ethyl
or any inactive ingredient
in Vascepa.
Tell your doctor if you are
allergic to fish or shellfish,
have liver problems
or other medical conditions
and about any medications
you take,
especially those that may affect
blood clotting.
2.3% of patients
reported joint pain.
Prescription power.
Proven to work.
Now with a new indication.
Ask your doctor about VASCEPA.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> O'Donnell: TONIGHT, NEWLY
RELEASED BODY CAM VIDEO SHOWS AN
INTENSE SHOOT-OUT LAST DECEMBER.
( GUNFIRE )
THIS WAS THE CHAOTIC SCENE
OFFICERS FIRING MULTIPLE ROUNDS
AT TWO SUSPECTS WHOA KILLED A
POLICE DETECTIVE BEFORE
TARGETING A KOSHER MARKET IN
UNUSUAL, KILLING THREE PEOPLE.
THE ATTACKERS WERE KILLED IN THE
GUN BATTLE.
TONIGHT AIR, 59-YEAR-OLD TRUCK
DRIVER IS IT IN CRITICAL
CONDITION AFTER A FIERY WRECK IN
INDIANA.
ADRIANA DIAZ MET TODAY WITH THE
HERO HOOSIER WHO GIVES PROOF TO
THE SAYING, "THE STRENGTH OF A
MOTHER IS SECOND TO NONE."
>> Reporter: WHEN HOLLY
McNALLY SAW THE WALL OF
FLAMES, SHE RAN TOWARD IT.
>> I SAW HIM COMING OUT OF THE
HUGE PLUME OF SMOKE WITH FIRE
COMING OFF OF HIS HEAD AND HIS
BACK.
HE HAD NOTHING LEFT ON BUT HIS
BOOTS.
>> Reporter: THE FIRE HAD
BURNED HIS CLOTHES OFF.
>> EVERYTHING.
AND I SAID, "WHAT'S HITTING MY
FEET?"
AND HE SAID, "JET FUEL."
AND AT THAT POINT I SAID, "OH,
MY GOSH, YOU GUYS, WE HAVE GOT
TO HUSTLE BECAUSE IF THIER IS
GOING TO FOLLOW US."
>> Reporter: WHAT MADE YOU RUN
TOWARDS DANGER?
EVERYBODY ELSE IS STAYING BACK.
>> A MATERNAL INSTINCT.
>> Reporter: McNALLY HAD
JUST GIVEN BIRTH TO HER FOURTH
CHILD FIVE DAYS AGO, A SON NAMED
CONNER.
TROOPER CHRIS HANSON ARRIVED AS
McNALLY AND TWO OTHER GOOD
SAMARITANS WERE DRAGGING THE
DRIVER AWAY JUST BEFORE A SECOND
EXPLOSION.
>> THREE SELFLESS PEOPLE TOOK
THE INITIATIVE TO SAY, "NOT
TODAY.
NOT ON OUR WATCH."
>> Reporter: WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO TELL YOUR BABY BOY WHEN
HE GROWS UP?
>> THAT MOMMY WAS TOUGH THAT DAY
AND HE WAS MY DRIVING FORCE TO
SAVE A LIFE PLUS GET BACK TO
HIM.
>> TELL HIM HIS MOMMY WAS A
HERO.
THAT'S WHAT I'LL TELL HIM
MYSELF, I SAID IT, TO BE PROUD.
>> Reporter: PROUD, BECAUSE
SHE RISKED HER LIFE TO SAVE A
STRANGER.
ADRIANA DIAZ, CBS NEWS,
INDIANAPOLIS.
>> O'Donnell: MOMMY IS TOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S FRIDAY, SO STEVE
HARTMAN IS NEXT WITH THE STORY
BEHIND THIS REMARKABLE PICTURE.
WHY A LITTLE BOY IS SO DEVOTED
TO PETS OTHERS DIDN'T WANT.
(Beep)
The ups and downs
of frequent mood swings
can plummet you
to extreme lows.
(Crying)
Lift you to intense highs.
(Muffled arguing)
Or, make you feel
both at once.
Overwhelmed by
bipolar I symptoms?
Ask about VRAYLAR.
Some medications only treat
the lows or the highs.
VRAYLAR effectively
treats depression,
acute manic and mixed
episodes of bipolar I.
Full-spectrum relief
of all symptoms.
With just one pill,
once a day.
Elderly patients with
dementia-related psychosis
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor
about unusual changes
in behavior or
suicidal thoughts.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in children and young adults.
Report fever, stiff
muscles, or confusion,
which may mean
a life-threatening reaction,
or uncontrollable
muscle movements,
may be permanent.
Side effects may not appear
for several weeks.
Metabolic changes may occur.
Movement dysfunction,
restlessness, sleepiness,
stomach issues are
common side effects.
When bipolar I overwhelms,
VRAYLAR helps smooth
the ups and downs.
Introducing even more value
from Fidelity.
Fidelity now has
zero commissions
for online U.S. equity trades
and ETFs.
And Fidelity also offers
zero account fees
for brokerage accounts,
plus zero minimums
to open an account.
And only Fidelity offers four
zero expense ratio index funds
directly to investors.
With all of those zeros,
there are zero reasons
to invest anywhere else.
Fidelity.
♪ So maybe I'll win ♪
♪ Saved by zero ♪
Yes. The first word
to any adventure.
But when allergies
and congestion strike,
take Allegra-D...
a non-drowsy antihistamine
plus a powerful decongestant.
So you can always say “yes”
to putting your true colors
on display.
Say “yes” to Allegra-D.
to putting your true colors
on display.
♪ Yes I'm stuck in
the middle with you, ♪
No one likes to feel stuck,
boxed in, or held back.
Especially by something
Like your cloud.
It's a problem.
But the IBM Cloud is different.
It's the most open and secure
public cloud for business.
It can manage all your apps
and data from anywhere.
So it can help take on anything,
from rebooking
flights, on the fly
to restocking shelves on demand.
Without getting in your way.
♪ ♪ ♪
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
I'm your Mother in Law.
And I like to question your
every move.
Like this left turn.
It's the next one.
You always drive this slow?
How did you make someone I love?
That must be why you're always
so late.
I do not speed.
And that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
My son, he did say that you were
the safe option.
And that's the nicest thing you
ever said to me.
So get Allstate.
Stop bossing.
Where good drivers save 40% for
avoiding mayhem, like me.
This is my son's favorite color,
you should try it.
[Mayhem] You always drive like
an old lady?
[Tina] You're an old lady.
>> O'Donnell: ASK ANY KID WHAT
THEY WANT FOR THEIR BIRTHDAY,
AND CHANCES ARE THEY'LL SAY A
PUPPY.
WELL, NOT THE KID YOU'RE ABOUT
TO MEET.
HE'S DRAWN TO THE PETS THAT ARE
FRGOTTEN BY OTHERS.
HERE'S STEVE HARTMAN "ON THE
ROAD."
>> Reporter: EIGHT-YEAR-OLD
ROBBIE GAY LOVES AN UNDERDOG.
>> HEY!
>> Reporter: BRING HIM TO THE
FLAGLER COUNTY HUMANE SOCIETY IN
PALM COAST, FLORIDA, AS WE DID,
AND ASK HIM TO FIND A FAVORITE,
HE WILL SEEK OUT THE OLDEST,
MANGIEST, LEAST-ADOPTABLE MUTT
OF THE LOT.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THOSE
DOGS THEY JUST LIKE.
>> Reporter: DO YOU SEE
YOURSELF IN THESE DOGS?
>> YSIR.
>> HE KNOWS WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
NOT TO BE LOVED AND CARED FOR
HELP HE'S THE MOST HOPEFUL,
OPTIMISTIC, AND GENUINELY CARING
KID WHO HAS ABSOLUTELY NO REASON
TO BE THAT WAY.
>> Reporter: ROBE'S ADOPTIVE
MOM, MARIA, SAYS BEFORE HE
ENTERED THE FOSTER SYSTEM,
ROBBIE WAS A HOLY TERROR, SO
BADLY ABUSED, HE WAS TWICE
HOSPITALIZED WITH BRAIN
INJURIES.
THEN, TWO YEARS AGO, MARIA AND
HER HUSBAND, CHARLES, ADOPTED
HIM.
>> IT WAS JUST A GOOD DAY.
>> Reporter: WHAT DID THAT DAY
MEAN TO YOU?
>> EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: HE HAS COME A
LONG WAY, EXCEPT IN THIS ONE
RESPECT: MARIA SAYS HE COULD NOT
CRY.
DESPITE THE HORRORS OF HIS PAST
OR MAYBE BECAUSE OF THEM, THE
KID WAS A STONE.
UNTIL EARLIER THITH.
ONE OF ROBBIE'S OLD DOGS, BUFFY,
D
HE WANTED TO HOLD HER TILL THE
VERY END, AND INSISTED HIS MOM
TAKE PICTURES OF THE PROCESS.
PERHAPS BECAUSE HE KNEW WHAT WAS
ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
AFTER ROBBIE FINALLY LET GO, HE
TOLD HIS MOM, "I KNOW HOW IT
FEELS NOT TO BE LOVED OR CARED
FOR.
>> AND DON'T WANT ANY ANIMAL OF
MINE TO FEEL THAT WAY."
NOR DOES HE WANT ANY FOSTER KID
TO FEEL THAT WAY.
>> PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO ORDER
PEOPLE AND ORDER DOGS.
THEY ONLY WANT BABIES.
>> HE IS SO AWARE THAT IT COULD
HAVE GONE TOTALLY DIFFERENTLY
FOR HIM.
AND IN THESE OLDER DOGS,
ROBBIE'S FOUND A PLACE TO
PRACTICE COMPASSION.
>> Reporter: SOME DAY, ROBBIE
WANTS TO ADOPT OLDER FOSTER
CHILDREN HIMSELF.
>> GO UP AND KNOCK ON THE DOOR.
>> Reporter: BUT UNTIL THEN,
TO SHOW HIS COMMITMENT AND DO
WHAT HE CHE HAS VOWED TO ADOPT
AS MANY OLD DOGS AS HIS PARENTS
WILL ALLOW.
>> DO YOU LOVE HER?
>> Reporter: TODAY, IT'S A
LAME, SNAGLE-TOOTHED SHIH TZU
NAMED MOLLY.
MOLLY'S OWNER HAD TO GO INTO
ASSISTED LIVING, BUT NOW MOLE
HAS A NEW HOME, THANKS TO THE
SWEET LITTLE BOY WHO SEES HIS
REFLECTION IN THE EYES OF THE
SUFFERING.
STEVE HARTMAN, "ON THE ROAD,"
NEAR PALM COAST, FLORIDA.
>> O'Donnell: PRACTICING
COMPASSION.
I'M GOING TO WATCH THAT ONE A
COUPLE MORE TIMES.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
With more farm-fresh taste,
more vitamins,
and 25% less saturated fat?
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste, better
nutrition, better eggs.
Is this where
our family is from?
What about here?
Here?
Daddy, is that
where we're from?
Well, actually...
we're from a lot of places.
You see we're from here
and there and here...
Turn questions you've
always had into stories
you can't wait to share;
with Ancestry.
Turn questions you've
always had into stories
♪ ♪ ♪
Wherever we want to go,
Autosave your way
there with Chase.
Chase.
Make More Of What's Yours.
>> O'Donnell: NEXT WEEK ON THE
CBS, EVENING NEWS, WE'LL BE IN
SOUTH CAROLINA FOR OUR CBS NEWS
DEMOCRATIC DEBATE TAKING A LOOK
AT AN INNOVATIVE WAY TO BRING
HEALTH CARE TO THOSE WHO NEED
IT.
AND IF YOU CAN'T WATCH LIVE,
DON'T FORGET TO SET YOUR DVR, SO
YOU CAN WATCH US LATER.
AND THAT IS TONIGHT'S "CBS
EVENING NEWS."
I'M NO