Captioning sponsored by CBS
>> O'Donnell: BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT, HARVEY WEINSTEIN GUILTY
OF RAPE.
THE MOVIE MOGUL WHO SET OFF THE
"ME TOO" MOVEMENT CONVICTED ON
TWO COUNTS OF SEXUALLY
ASSAULTING WOMEN, HANDCUFFED AND
TAKE ON THE JAIL.
WHAT HIS VICTIMS ARE SAYING
TONIGHT.
MORE BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT.
STOCK MARKET MELTDOWN.
THE DOW PLUMMET, WIPING OUT ALL
OF 2020'S GAINS.
THE FEAR NOW INFECTING THE
FINANCIAL MARKETS AS CASES OF
THE CORONAVIRUS IN THE U.S. AND
OVERSEAS SKYROCKET.
SHOWDOWN IN SOUTH CAROLINA ON
THE EVE OF OUR CBS NEWS
DEMOCRATIC DEBATE.
OUR EXCLUSIVE NEW POLL.
THE NEW FRONT-RUNNER IN THE
PALMETTO STATE AND WHAT BERNIE
SANDERS JUST SAID ABOUT A
DICTATOR THAT HAS MEMBERS OF HIS
OWN PARTY NERVOUS.
>> IT'S UNFAIR TO SIMPLY SAY
EVERYTHING IS BAD.
♪
>> O'Donnell: FAREWELL TO A
LEGEND.
THE STAR-STUDDED MEMORIAL TO
BASKETBALL GREAT KOBE BRYANT.
THE TRY BOUTS AND TEARS AS
CELEBRITIES AND BRYANT'S WIFE
HONOR KOBE AND HIS DAUGHTER.
>> YOU TAKE CARE OF OUR GIGI.
>> O'Donnell: "EMPIRE" STAR IN
COURT.
ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT MOBBED AT
A CHICAGO COURTHOUSE AS HE FACES
NEW CHARGES OF STAGING A RACIST
ATTACK ON HIMSELF.
WHAT HE'S NOW SAYING TO A JUDGE.
ROAD TO RECOVERY.
AFTER THIS DRAMATIC CRASH AT THE
DAYTONA 500, NASCAR DRIVER RYAN
NEWMAN SPEAKING OUT.
THE INJURY HE'S STILL SUFFERING
AND WILL HE RACE AGAIN?
AND REMEMBERING A PIONEER.
SHE GOT AMERICANS TO THE MOON
WITH NOTHING MORE THAN A PENCIL
AND HER MIND.
TONIGHT WE PAY TRIBUTE TO ONE OF
THE SPACE PROGRAM'S REAL LIVE
HIDDEN FIGURES.
>> THIS IS THE "CBS EVENING
NEWS" WITH NORAH O'DONNELL
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM
CHARLESTON, SOUTH CAROLINA.
>> O'Donnell: GOOD EVENING,
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
WE ARE IN CHARLESTON AHEAD OF
TOMORROW'S PIVOTAL DEMOCRATIC
DEBATE.
WE'VE GOT SOME BIG NEWS ON THAT
IN JUST A MOMENT, BUT WE WANT TO
BEGIN TONIGHT WITH THIS BREAKING
NEWS.
HARVEY WEINSTEIN, THE MOVIE
MOGUL BEHIND SOME OF HOLLYWOOD'S
BIGGEST HITS, IS BEHIND BARS
TONIGHT.
HE WAS CONVICTED BY A NEW YORK
JURY TODAY OF RAPE AND
COMMITTING A CRIMINAL SEXUAL ACT
AFTER A MONTH-LONG TRIAL
FEATURING TESTIMONY FROM
MULTIPLE WOMEN WHO SAID HE
ASSAULTED THEM.
WHILE HE WAS ACQUITTED OF THREE
OTHER CHARGE, THE 67-YEAR-OLD
COULD STILL FACE DECADES IN
PRISON.
TODAY'S VERDICT WAS THE END OF A
STUNNING FALL FROM GRACE FOR ONE
OF THE MOVIE INDUSTRY'S MOST
POWERFUL MEN, AND IT REPRESENTS
A MILESTONE IN THE "ME TOO"
MOVEMENT.
JERICKA DUNCAN LEADS OFF OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THE PLAN ONCE
REFERRED TO AS A GOD IN
HOLLYWOOD IS NOW A CONVICTED
RAPIST.
AFTER FIVE DAYS OF DELIBERATION,
THE JURY FOUND HARVEY WEINSTEIN
GUILTY OF A CRIMINAL SEXUAL ACT
AND THIRD-DEGREE RAPE, WHICH
COULD BRING A McMUM SENTENCE
OF 29 YEARS.
>> THESE SURVIVORS WEREN'T JUST
BRAVE, THEY WERE HEROIC.
>> Reporter: MANHATTAN
DISTRICT ATTORNEY CY VANCE DID
NOT GET A CONVICTIONON THE MOST
SERIOUS CHARGE, PREDATORY SEXUAL
ASSAULT, WHICH CARRIED UP TO A
LIFE SENTENCE.
>> WELL, I'M CERTAINLY NOT
DISSATISFIED BY THE VERDICT.
I THINK THIS WAS A VERY
DIFFICULT CASE THAT REALLY MOVED
OUR UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT SEXUAL
ASSAULT IS.
>> Reporter: THE 67-YEAR-OLD
WEINSTEIN WAS LED AWAY IN
HANDCUFFS AFTER THE VERDICT WAS
READ.
WAS HE UPSET IN
>> HE'S BEEN FIGHTING THIS CASE
FOR TWO YEARS.
I THINK YOU COME TO SOME
REALIZATION THAT SOMETHING LIKE
THIS COULD HAPPEN.
I THINK HE UNDERSTOOD IT WAS A
POSSIBILITY.
>> Reporter: CBS LEGAL ANALYST
RIKKI KLIEMAN SAYS EVEN THE
MINIMUM SENTENCE COULD BE HARD
ON WEINSTEIN.
>> FIVE YEARS FOR HARVEY
WEINSTEIN AT THIS STAGE IS
CERTAINLY GOING TO BE A
DIFFICULT TIME FOR HIM, AND I'D
EXPECT THE JUDGE TO BE MORE
HARSH THAN FIVE YEARS.
>> Reporter: DURING THE
MONTH-LONG TRIAL, JURORS HEARD
FROM SIX WOMEN WHO DESCRIBED IN
DETAIL HOW WEINSTEIN ALLEGEDLY
SEXUALLY ABUSED THEM.
THE CASE CENTERED AROUND TWO
WOMEN, FORMER PRODUCTION
ASSISTANT MIMI HALEY, WHO SAID
WEINSTEIN FORCED ORAL SEX ON HER
IN 2006, AN ASPIRING ACTRESS
JESSICA MANN, WHO TESTIFIED THAT
WEINSTEIN RAPED HER IN 2013.
MORE THAN 80 WOMEN HAVE ACCUSED
THE MOVIE MOGUL OF SEXUAL ABUSE,
HARASSMENT, AND THREATS.
AMONG THEM, MODEL AMBER
GUTTIEREZ, WHO WAS OUTSIDE THE
COURTHOUSE TODAY.
>> IT MEANS A LOT.
IT'S A START.
>> Reporter: THAT SENTIMENTS
WAS ECHOED ON A CONFERENCE CALL
WITH ACTRESS ROSE McGOWAN.
>> TODAY IS NOT A REFERENDUM ON
"ME TOO."
THIS IS TAKING OUT THE TRASH.
>> Reporter: FORMER "SEW PLAN
PLAN -- "SOPRANOS" ACTRESS
ANNABELLA SCIORRA, WHO
TESTIFIED, SAYS SHE HAS NO
REGRETS BREAKING HER SILENCE,
SAYING, "IN SPEAKING TRUTH TO
POWER, WE PAVE THE WAY TO A MORE
JUST CULTURE."
SHORTLY AFTER THE VERDICT WAS
READ, HARVEY WEINSTEIN WAS TAKEN
AWAY IN AN AMBULANCE TO JAIL.
NORAH, THAT IS WHERE HE WILL
SPEND TIME UNTIL HIS SENTENCING,
WHICH IS ON MARCH 11th.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT.
JERICKA, THANK YOU.
CORONAVIRUS FEARS WIPED OUT ALL
OF THIS YEAR'S STOCK MARKET
GAINS.
THE DOW LOST MORE THAN 1,000
POINTS TODAY.
THAT'S MORE THAN 3.5%.
THE NASDAQ AND S&P 500 ALSO
TANKED.
THE NUMBER OF CASES HERE IN THE
U.S. SHOT UP TO 53 OVER THE
WEEKEND, AND DOZENS OF SICK
PASSENGERS RETURNED FROM THAT
CRUISE SHIP IN JAPAN.
THE DEADLY VIRUS IS EXPLODING
OUTSIDE CHINA.
AS MARK PHILLIPS REPORTS, THE
GLOBAL ECONOMY IS STARTING TO
GASP AND WHEEZE.
>> Reporter: THE CORONAVIRUS
IS NOT JUST AFFECTING THE HEALTH
OF PEOPLE, IT'S HITTING THE
HEALTH OF THE ECONOMY.
THE NEW YORK STOCK MARKET WIPED
OUT ALL ITS GAINS OF THIS YEAR.
>> IF YOU'RE A TRADER, YOU NEED
TO BE NIMBLE.
IF YOU'RE A LONG-TERM INVESTOR,
DON'T LOOK AT YOUR PORTFOLIO.
>> Reporter: THE VIRUS'S
EFFECTS HAVE HIT EUROPE.
THIS IS NORMALLY CARNIVAL TIME
IN VENICE, BUT THE PARTY IS OVER
AND THE MASKS HAVE CHANGED.
AS THE CORONA CLUSTER HIT
NORTHERN ITALY, THE CARNIVAL HAS
BEEN CANCELED AND TOURISTS ARE
GREG OUT OF TOWN.
POLICE ROADBLOCKS HAVE BEEN SET
UP ISOLATING TWO AREAS NEAR
VENICE AND MILAN WHERE THE
NUMBER OF CASES HAS RISEN ABOVE
200, BY FAR THE BIGGEST OUTBREAK
IN EUROPE.
AROUND 50,000 PEOPLE ARE BEING
CONTAINED IN THE RED ZONE.
THE VIRUS HAS A FIRMER FOOTHOLD
IN THE FAR EAST.
IN DAEGU, KOREA, THE NUMBER OF
CASES QUADRUPLED OVER THE
WEEKEND, A WORRY FOR ITS 2.5
MILLION RESIDENTS AND FOR THE
2,500 U.S. SERVICEMEN STATIONED
THERE.
>> OUR POPULATION IS NOT
VULNERABLE.
STILL, THOUGH, WE'RE ALL NERVOUS
ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE NERVOUS,
TOO, IN COSTA MESA, CALIFORNIA,
WHERE THE CITY IS TRYING TO GET
A RESTRAINING ORDER AGAINST
PLANS TO HOUSE UP TO 50 PEOPLE
WHO HAVE TESTED POSITIVE FOR THE
VIRUS IN A LOCAL HOSPITAL.
>> WE ARE NOT GOING TO CONTINUE
TO BE THE PLACE WHERE EVERYBODY
DROPS OFF THEIR CRISES.
>> Reporter: WITH A CLUSTER OF
MORE THAN 200 CASES NOW HERE IN
ITALY, THERE IS PLENTY OF
NERVOUSNESS TO GO AROUND.
ITALIAN HEALTH AUTHORITIES,
NORAH, SAY THE NEXT FEW DAYS
WILL BE CRITICAL TO SEE WHETHER
THEY'VE CONTAINED IT.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT, MARK.
THANK YOU.
WE TURN NOW TO THE 2020
CAMPAIGN.
OUR NEWS CBS NEWS BATTLEGROUND
POLL HAS JOE BIDEN LEADING THE
PACK HERE IN SOUTH CAROLINA
AHEAD OF SATURDAY'S PRIMARY.
BUT BERNIE SANDERS IS CLOSING IN
FAST, AND HIS CONVINCING WIN IN
THE NEVADA CAUCUS OVER THE
WEEKEND ALONG WITH A NEW DEFENSE
OF A NOTORIOUS DICTATOR HAS SOME
DEMOCRATS GROWING DESPERATE TO
FIND A WAY TO STOP HIM.
AND IT MAY HAPPEN AT TOMORROW
NIGHT'S DEBATE.
HERE'S ED O'KEEFE.
>> Reporter: BERNIE SANDERS
HAS A LEAD IN TOTAL VOTES AND
DELEGATES, BUT IT'S COMMENTS HE
MADE SUNDAY NIGHT ON "60
MINUTES" THAT IS CAUSING FRESH
PANIC FOR SOME DEMOCRATS.
HE WAS ASKED TO EXPLAIN THE
POLICIES OF FIDEL CASTRO
>> WE'RE OPPOSED TO THE NATURE
OF CUBA, BUT IT'S UNFAIR TO SAY
EVERYTHING THE S BAD.
WHEN FIDEL CASTRO CAME INTO
OFFICE, HE HAD MASSIVE LITERACY
PROGRAM.
IS THAT A BAD THING?
EVEN THOUGH FIDEL CASTRO DID IT.
>> A LOT OF DISDEBITS IN
PRISON --.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE CONDEMN THAT.
>> Reporter: HIS RESPONSE
INFURIATED DEMOCRATIC VOTERS IN
SOUTH FLORIDA.
>> HE MADE MORE THAN A MISTAKE.
IT'S WHAT HE BELIEVES, AND IT'S
UNACCEPTABLE TO OUR COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: THE BLOWBACK IS
EMBLEMATIC OF BROADER
UNCERTAINTY ABOUT HOW NOMINATING
A DEMOCRATIC SOCIALIST COULD
IMPACT DEMOCRATS' CHANCES IN THE
ELECTION.
SANDERS CONTINUES TO OUTLINE
PROGRAMS FOR EXPANSIVE NEW
PROGRAMS.
TODAY HE UNVEILED THE UNIVERSAL
CHILDCARE POLICY WITH A $1.5
TRILLION OVER TEN YEARS, BUT HI
HAS STRUGGLED TO EXPLAIN HOW HE
WOULD PAY FOR HIS IDEAS.
>> WE HAVE DONE IN PAYING FOR
THEM ON ISSUE AFTER ISSUE.
>> Reporter: POLLS SHOW JOE
BIDEN LEADS IN SOUTH CAROLINA
AND MAY BE THE ONLY CANDIDATE
WHO CAN SLOW SANDERS' MOMENTUM.
INFLUENTIAL SOUTH CAROLINA
CONGRESSMAN JIM CLYBURN IS
EXPECTED TO ENDORSE BIDEN LATER
THIS WEEK.
>> I THINK WE'RE GOING TO DO
FINE.
>> DO YOU THINK BERNIE SANDERS
IS THE FRONT-RUNNER IN THIS RACE
RIGHT NOW?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO -- LOOK, YOU
ALL CAN -- THE ANSWER IS I'M
GOING TO DO WELL HERE.
>> O'Donnell: ED JOINS US
OUTSIDE THE DEBATE HALL WHERE I
UNDERSTAND THAT MAYOR BLOOMBERG
PLANS TO TAKE THE GLOVES OFF
AGAINST BERNIE SANDERS.
WHAT'S HIS STRATEGY?
>> YEAH, HE RELEASED A NEW
ATTACK AD TODAY CALLING OUT THE
SENATOR'S SUPPORT FOR LESS
RESTRICTIVE GUN POLICY AND
CALLING HIM AN ALLY OF THE
N.R.A.
THE SENATOR'S VIEWS HAVE
CHANGED.
HE POINTS OUT HE'S A SENATOR
FROM A RURAL STATE WITH A GUN
CULTURE, BUT THE MAYOR IS URGING
OTHER DEMOCRATS TO KEEP THE
FOCUS TOMORROW NIGHT ON THE
SENATOR INSTEAD OF HIM.
WE'LL SEE IF IT HAPPENS.
>> O'Donnell: WOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE A PIVOTAL
DEBATE
>> IT SURE WILL.
>> O'Donnell: THANK YOU, ED.
REMEMBER, GAYLE KING AND I WILL
MODERATE THAT DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE RIGHT HERE
IN CHARLESTON.
THAT'S AT 8:00 EASTERN.
YOU CAN SUBMIT QUESTIONS FOR THE
CANDIDATES ON TWITTER BY USING
THE HASHTAG DEM DEBATE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ONCE NAMED A
CASINO AFTER THE TAJ MAHAL.
TODAY THE PRESIDENT AND THE
FIRST LADY HAD A CHANCE TO VISIT
THE REAL ONE ON A TRIP NO INDIA.
THE PRESIDENT MET WITH THE PRIME
MINISTER OF INTHAT AND ADDRESSED
A CROWD OF 100,000 IN WHAT WAS
CALLED A NAMASTE TRUMP RALLY.
THERE THE PRESIDENT ANNOUNCED A
$3 BILLION DEAL TO SELL INDIA
HELICOPTERS.
>>> KOBE'S WIDOW FILED A
WRONGFUL-DEATH SUIT AGAINST THE
COMPANY THAT OPERATED THE
HELICOPTER IN THAT CRASH THAT
KILLED HER HUSBAND AND DAUGHTER
GIANNA AND SEVEN OTHERS.
VANESSA BRYANT ALSO TOOK CENTER
STAGE WHAT WHAT WAS CALLED A
CELEBRATION OF LIFE MEMORIAL AT
THE STAPLES CENTER.
DANA JACOBSON WAS THERE FOR THE
EMOTIONAL OUTPOURING.
>> Reporter: IN THE HOUSE THAT
KOBE BUILT, THE CITY THAT LOVED
HIM LIKE NO OTHER PAID TRIBUTE
TO KOBE BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER
GIANNA.
FAMILY, BASKETBALL LEGENDS, AND
THE CITY'S BIGGEST STARS UNITED
IN A CELEBRATION OF LIFE.
FAMILY FRIEND AND MUSIC ICON
BEYONCE SET THE TONE.
♪ BABY I CAN SEE YOUR HALO ♪
VANESSA BRYANT SHOWED STRENGTH,
SPEAKING LIKELY FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE HER HUSBAND,
13-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER, AND SEVEN
OTHERS DIED IN A HELICOPTER
CRASH LAST MONTH.
SHE FOUGHT BACK TEARS AND N
TALKING ABOUT HER GIGI.
>> I'LL NEVER GET TO SEE MY BABY
GIRL WALK DOWN THE AISLE, HAVE A
FATHER/DAUGHTER DANCE WITH HER
DADDY, DANCE ON THE DANCE FLOOR
WITH ME OR HAVE BABIES OF HER
OWN.
>> Reporter: AND SPOKE OF THE
MAN ONLY HER FAMILY KNEW.
>> HE WAS A DOTING FATHER, A
FATHER THAT WAS HANDS ON AND
PRESENT.
BABE, YOU TAKE CARE OF OUR GIGI.
>> KOBE WAS MY DEAR FRIEND.
HE WAS LIKE A LITTLE BROTHER.
>> Reporter: OVERCOME WITH
EMOTION, MICHAEL JORDAN RECALLED
THEIR FRIENDSHIP THAT BEGAN WHEN
KOBE BRYANT ENTERED THE NBA AT
17 YEARS OLD.
>> EVERYONE ALWAYS WANTED TO
TALK ABOUT THE COMPARISONS
BETWEEN HE AND I.
I JUST WANTED TO TALK ABOUT
KOBE.
WHEN KOBE BRYANT DIED, A PIECE
OF ME DIED.
>> Reporter: AND THEN THERE
WAS BRYANT'S LAKER TEAMMATE,
SHAQUILLE O'NEAL.
>> I'LL BE SURE TO TEACH
NATALIA, BIANCA, AND BABY CAPRI
ALL YOUR MOVES, AND I PROMISELY
NOT TEACH THEM MY FREE THROW
TECHNIQUES.
KOBE, YOU'RE HEAVEN'S M.V.P.
I LOVE YOU, MY MAN, UNTIL WE
MEET AGAIN.
REST IN PEACE, KOBE.
>> Reporter: THERE WERE 20,000
INSIDE FOR THE MEMORIAL, BUT IT
FELT INTIMATE.
WHEN VANESSA BRYANT AND HER
FAMILY WALKED IN, THE PLACE
ERUPTED, BUT NOT WITH THE CHEERS
THAT WE'RE USED TO.
AS FORMER LAKER JOHN SALLEY TOLD
US, IT WAS AN OVERFLOW OF HUMAN
EMOTION, NORAH.
HE SAID IT WAS LIKE THE CROWD
WAS GIVING THE FAMILY A HUG.
>> O'Donnell: DANA, THANK YOU.
TONIGHT ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS
AGAIN ON THE DEFENSE, FIGHTING
OFF SIX NEW CHARGES THAT HE LIED
TO POLICE AND STAGED A BOGUS
ATTACK THAT.
GOT HIM KICKED OFF THE TV SHOW
"EMPIRE."
DEAN REYNOLDS HAS MORE TONIGHT
FROM CHICAGO.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THESE
NEW CHARGES?
>> Reporter: SMOLLETT'S PLEA
OF NOT GUILTY CAME ALMOST A YEAR
AFTER HE WAS ORIGINALLY BOOKED
FOR FABRICATING THE STORY OF AN
ATTACK ON HIM BY HOMOPHOBIC
TRUMP SUPPORTERS.
THOSE ORIGINAL CHARGES WERE
ABRUPTLY DROPPED WITHOUT MUCH OF
A REASON.
A JUDGE APPOINTED A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR TO TAKE ANOTHER LOOK.
THROUGH IT ALL, SMOLLETT HAS
INSISTED HE WAS A VICTIM AND HIS
LAWYERS HAVE ACCUSED BROTHERS OF
BEATING HIM UP ON THAT SUBZERO
JANUARY NIGHT LAST YEAR.
THE BROTHERS ADMIT INVOLVEMENT,
BUT ONLY IN A PATTY-CAKE
PUBLICITY STUNT CONCOCTED BY
SMOLLETT WHICH POLICE SAY WAS
DONE TO GET THE ACTOR A RAISE.
>> THEY HAVE BEEN TRUTHFUL SINCE
DAY ONE.
>> Reporter: THE FORMER
"EMPIRE" STAR'S LAWYER TINA
GLANDIAN WANTS THE CASE
DISMISSED.
>> HE'S OBVIOUSLY FRUSTRATED TO
BE DRAGGED THROUGH THIS PROCESS
AGAIN.
>> Reporter: AS ARE MANY IN
CHICAGO WHO, LIKE MAYOR LORI
LIGHTFOOT, BELIEVE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT SHOULD BE PUNISHED.
DEAN REYNOLDS, CBS NEWS,
CHICAGO.
>> O'Donnell: WE'VE BEEN
SPEAKING WITH A LOT OF VOTERS
HERE IN SOUTH CAROLINA ABOUT
WHICH ISSUES THEY WANT THE
CANDIDATES TO TALK ABOUT.
OUR CBS NEWS BATTLEGROUND
TRACKER, 42% SAID HEALTHCARE.
IT WAS NUMBER ONE BY FAR.
MANY SOUTH CAROLINA COUNTIES,
HOSPITALS ARE FEW AND FAR
BETWEEN, SO A DOCTOR FOUND A WAY
TO TAKE HER SERVICES TO THE
COMMUNITY.
NIKOLE KILLION CONTINUES OUR
SERIES "EVERY STATE HAS A
STORY."
>> Reporter: ALLEN DEALG SITS
ON THE EDGE -- ALLENDALE SITS ON
THE EDGE OF SOUTH CAROLINA'S LOW
COUNTY.
IT'S ONE OF THE SMALLEST AND
POOREST COUNTIES IN THE STATE.
>> THE PURPOSE OF THE MOBILE
UNIT IS TO PROVIDE FOR UNINSURED
AND UNDERINSURED.
>> Reporter: WHICH IS WHY
DR. YOLANDA GIBBS THOUGHT IT WAS
THE PERFECT PLACE THE LAUNCH
PALMETTO PALACE.
THE MOBILE HEALTH UNIT OFFERS
EVERYTHING FROM PREVENTIVE
HEALTH SCREENINGS TO DENTAL CARE
AT NO COST.
>> IF YOU NO LONGER HAVE YOUR
LOCAL HOSPITAL, THAT MEANS THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TRAVEL
TO ANOTHER TOWN.
THIS UNIT IS ABLE TO DRIVE INTO
THESE COMMUNITIES TO PROVIDE
THIS SERVICE.
>> Reporter: LISA FERNANDEZ
AND HER FATHER SAMUEL GOT THEIR
TEETH CLEANED FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN YEARS.
>> IT'S THE MONEY SITUATION,
GOING TO THE DENTIST, IT'S A
LUXURY, YOU KNOW?
>> Reporter: WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT WHAT WHEN YOU HEAR YOUR
DAD SAY GOING TO THE DENTIST IS
A LUXURY?
>> IT'S REALLY SAD.
I HOPE THE RIGHT PEOPLE ARE
LISTENING.
>> Reporter: ORE THAN 100,000
PEOPLE CENTRAL INTO THE
SO-CALLED COVERAGE GAP IN SOUTH
CAROLINA, ONE OF SEVERAL STATES
THAT DID NOT EXPAND MEDICAID
UNDER THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT.
WITH THE DEMOCRATIC FIELD
DIVIDED OVER GOVERNMENT-RUN
PROPOSALS LIKE MEDICARE FOR ALL,
DR. GIBBS IS TEMPERING HER
EXPECTATIONS.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M LOOKING
FOR ANYTHING FROM THEM, TO BE
HONEST.
>> Reporter: DR. GIBBS TOLD ME
SHE ISN'T SURE ANY OF THE
CANDIDATES' PLANS CAN FIX THE
CURRENT HEALTHCARE SYSTEM.
SHE REALLY BELIEVES THAT
PROVIDERS HAVE TO BE PART OF THE
SOLUTION.
AND SHE SEEMS TO BE DOING HER
PARTED, BECAUSE SHE ALREADY HAS
A WAIT LIST OF MORE THAN 100
APPLICANTS.
NORAH
>> O'Donnell: INTERESTING TO
HEAR VOTERS DESCRIBING IT AS A
LUXURY.
NIKOLE, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS STILL MONEY MORE NEWS
AHEAD TONIGHT HERE ON THE "CBS
EVENING NEWS."
NE RESEARCH SAYS YOUR SMART
SPEAKER MAY WILL -- BE LISTENING
IN A LOT MORE THAN YOU THINK.
A NEW STATEMENT FROM NASCAR
DRIVER RYAN NEWMAN AFTER THIS
TERRIBLE CRASH.
WILL HE RACE AGAIN?
LATER, REMEMBERING KATHERINE
JOHNSON, WHO PUT AMERICANS ON
THE MOON AND INSPIRED "HIDDEN
FIGURES."
.
Whether it's a year old
or a few years old,
we want to buy your car.
So go to Carvana
and enter your license plate,
answer a few questions,
and our techno-wizardry
calculates your car's value
and gives you a real offer
in seconds.
When you're ready,
we'll come to you,
pay you on the spot,
and pick up your car.
That's it.
So ditch the old way
of selling your car,
and say hello to the new way--
at Carvana.
Breathe freely fast, with Vicks
Sinex.
My congestion's gone.
I can breathe again! Ahhhh!
I can breathe again! Ughh!
Vicks Sinex.
Breathe On.
♪♪
There's my career,...
my cause,...
my choir.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes...
into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO
is for adults
who are starting HIV-1 treatment
and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines
dolutegravir or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2...
medicines in...
1 pill to help you reach
and then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines...
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day,...
with food...
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if
you're allergic to any of its...
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become
harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening...
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO...
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,...
liver problems,
and liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash
and other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,...
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,...
including hepatitis B or C.
One of the ingredients in DOVATO
may harm your...
unborn baby.
Your doctor may prescribe
a different medicine...
than DOVATO. Your doctor should
do a pregnancy test...
before starting...
DOVATO. Use effective
birth control...
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache, diarrhea, nausea,
trouble sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am...
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment with DOVATO
is right for you.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment with DOVATO
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> O'Donnell: WELCOME BACK.
YOUR SMART SPEAKER MAY BE
LISTENING IN MORE THAN YOU
THINK.
RESEARCHERS AT NORTHEASTERN
UNIVERSITY PUT SERIES,
AELECTION, YEAH AND SEVERAL
OTHER SYSTEMS TO THE TEST,
EXPOSING THE DEVICES TO 125
HOURS OF NETFLIX SHOWS.
RANDOM WORDS ACTIVATED THE
SPEAKERS TO LISTEN IN UP TO 19
TIMES A DAY FOR AS LONG AS 43
SECONDS.
NASCAR DRIVER RYAN NEWMAN WAS
REVEALED THAT HE HAS SUFFERED A
BRAIN INJURY IN THAT HOR HORRIFC
CRASH LAST WEEK AT THE DAYTONA
500.
IN STATEMENT NEWMAN SAYS HE WAS
LUCKY TO ESCAPE WITH NO BROKEN
BONES OR INTERNAL ORGAN DAMAGE.
HE SAYS HE'S LOOKING FORWARD TO
GETTING BEHIND THE WHEEL AGAIN,
BUT THERE IS NO TIMETABLE FOR
HIS RETURN TO RACING.
COMING UP NEXT, JOHN GLENN
TRUSTED HER NUMBERS MORE THAN
THE COMPUTERS.
SO WE'RE GOING TO REMEMBER THE
GREAT KATHERINE JOHNSON.
♪♪
If you have moderate
to severe psoriasis...
or psoriatic arthritis,
little things, can
become your big moment.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an
injection or a cream...
...it's a pill that
treats differently.
For psoriasis, 75% clearer
skin is achievable...
...with reduced
redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis,
...Otezla is proven....
to reduce joint swelling,
tenderness, and pain.
And the Otezla prescribing
information
has no requirement for
routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe
diarrhea, nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an...
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if
you have a history
of depression or
suicidal thoughts....
...or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor
your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory
tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Otezla.
Show more of you.
It took plenty of work
to get here.
But it's still important to be
prepared for what's next.
At Fidelity,
we can help you build
a clear plan for retirement
without the unnecessary fees
you might expect
from so many financial firms.
We'll make sure
you can cover the essentials,
as well as all the things
you want to do.
Because when you have
a retirement partner
who gives you clarity
at every step,
there's nothing to stop you
from moving forward.
♪ Here's wishing you
the bluest sky ♪
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
there's nothing to stop you
from moving forward.
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to provide
complete, balanced nutrition...
For strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
Great-tasting Ensure.
With nine grams
of protein
and twenty-seven
vitamins and
minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
The good news?
Our protection lasts all day.
The bad news?
Your patience might not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
>> O'Donnell: KATHERINE
JOHNSON DIED THIS MORNING AT 101
YEARS OLD.
WHILE SHE WAS INDISPENSABLE
UNTIL THE U.S. SPACE PROGRAM,
UNTIL JUST A FEW YEARS AGO HER
CONTRIBUTIONS WERE INVISIBLE
NOSE.
HERE'S JAN CRAWFORD.
>> WE HAVE LIFTOFF.
>> Reporter: IN THE RACE TO
PUT MAN ON THE MOON, THERE WAS A
WOMAN WHOSE MATHEMATICAL GENIUS
MADE THE DIFFERENCE.
>> I COUNTED EVERYTHING.
I COUNTED THE DISHES WHEN I
WASHED THEM.
>> Reporter: KATHERINE JOHNSON
BROKE BARRIERS.
AT NASA SHE CALCULATED THE
TRAJECTORY OF ALAN SHEPARD'S
FACE FLIGHTS.
HER PROJECTIONS HELPED THE
APOLLO MISSION LAND ON THE MOON.
AS RECOUNTED IN THE MOVIE
"HIDDN FIGURES," WHICH TOLL THE
STORY OF JOHNSON AND OTHER
PIONEERING AFRICAN AMERICAN
WOMEN AT NASA, ASTRONAUT JOHN
GLENN WOULD FLY ONLY AFTER SHE
VERIFIED THE NUMBERS.
>> IF SHE SAYS THEY'RE GOOD, I'M
READY TO GO.
>> Reporter: AT A TIME WHEN
ONLY 2% OF AFRICAN AMERICAN
WOMEN HAD COLLEGE DEGREES,
JOHNSON GRADUATED AT 18 IN THE
JIM CROW SEGREGATED SOUTH.
>> THERE ARE NO COLORED
BATHROOMS IN THIS BUILDING.
>> Reporter: IN 2015,
PRESIDENT OBAMA AWARDED HER THE
PRESIDENTIAL MEDAL OF FREEDOM.
SHE TOLD US ON HER 98th
BIRTHDAY HER FATHER'S MOTTO
ALWAYS DIVIDED HER.
>> YOU'RE AS GOOD AS ANYBODY
HERE.
>> Reporter: AND YOU TOOK THAT
TO HEART.
>> YEAH.
AND YOU'RE NO WORSE.
YOU'RE NO BETTER.
>> Reporter: KATHERINE JOHNSON
MADE AMERICA BETTER.
JAN CRAWFORD, CBS NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> O'Donnell: AN AMERICAN HERO
WHOSE LEGACY WILL NOT BE
FORGOTTEN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ci
You can find it in the vitamin
aisle in stores everywhere.
Prevagen. Healthier brain.
Better life.
Alice loves the scent of Gain so
much,
she wished there was a way to
make it last longer.
Say hello to your fairy
godmother Alice.
and long-lasting Gain Scent
Beads.
Part of the irresistible scent
collection from Gain!
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you have fast-acting
power over pain,
So the whole world
looks different.
The unbeatable strength
and speed of Advil Liqui-Gels.
What Pain?
I'm your Mother in Law.
And I like to question your
every move.
Like this left turn.
It's the next one.
You always drive this slow?
How did you make someone I love?
That must be why you're always
so late.
I do not speed.
And that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
My son, he did say that you were
the safe option.
And that's the nicest thing you
ever said to me.
So get Allstate.
Stop bossing.
Where good drivers save 40% for
avoiding mayhem, like me.
This is my son's favorite color,
you should try it.
[Mayhem] You always drive like
an old lady?
[Tina] You're an old lady.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
>> O'Donnell: SO MUCH MORE
AHEAD.
ON TOMORROW'S "CBS EVENING
NEWS," WE'LL PRESTREW DEMOCRATIC
DEBATE HERE IN CHARLESTON, AND I
CAN'T WAIT TO INTRODUCE YOU TO A
COFFEE SHOP OWNER WHO MAKES A
POINT OF HIRING WORKERS WHOSE
SKILLS ARE OFTEN OVERLOOKED BY
OTHERS.
AND IF YOU CAN'T WATCH LIVE,
DON'T FORGET TO SET YOUR DVR SO
YOU CAN WATCH US LAT
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Hills, you crush them...
kind of.
Black freedom and Black labor.
Kale, you eat it
for breakfast...
sometimes.
You go far to eliminate
stubborn fat.
But sometimes life
gets in the way.
Coolsculpting takes you further.
A non-surgical
treatment that targets,
freezes, and eliminates
treated fat cells for good.
Discuss Coolsculpting
with your doctor.
Some common side-effects
include temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Don't imagine results,
see them.
Coolsculpting,
take yourself further.
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.