>>> GOOD MORNING.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING AND WELCOME
TO "CBS THIS MORNING."
I'M MICHELLE MILLER WITH DAVID
BEGNAUD AND JERICKA DUNCAN.
GAYLE KING, ANTHONY MASON, AND
TONY DOKOUPIL ARE OFF.
>>> WEATHER MAYHEM.
STRONG WINDS THREATEN TO GROUND
NEW YORK CITY'S PARADE BALLOONS
AS A POWERFUL STORM BRINGING
SNOW AND ICE SLAMS THE MIDWEST
AND CONTINUES TO MOVE EAST.
>>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT, NORTH
KOREA REPORTEDLY LAUNCHES TWO
MORE MISSILES TOWARD JAPAN WHILE
CHINA ANGRILY PROTESTS PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S DECISION TO BACK THE
DEMOCRACY MOVEMENT IN HONG KONG.
>>> BURSTING BUBBLES.
CLIMATE CHANGE THREATENS ONE OF
THE MOST FAMOUS SPARKLING WINES.
>>> PLUS, BUZZER BEATER
BLESSING.
HEAR FROM THE COLLEGE BASKETBALL
PLAYER WHO SCORED A GIANT UPSET
AND WINS BIG FOR HIS FAMILY
STRUGGLING TO RECOVER AFTER A
HURRICANE.
>> THAT'S A WITHDROW.
>>> IT'S THURSDAY, NOVEMBER
28TH, 2019.
HERE YOURS EYE E"EYE OPENER," Y
WORLD IN 90 SECONDS.
>> 24 BALLOONS, NEARLY 1,000
CLOWNS, 26 FLOATS.
>> ALL EYES ON THE MACY'S PARADE
BALLOONS.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S THE COOLEST
PART SO FAR?
>> WATCHING THEM BLOW UP.
>>> MONSTER STORMS HAVE BEEN
SWEEPING ACROSS THE COUNTRY,
CANCELING FLIGHTS AND SHUTTING
DOWN HIGHWAYS.
>> HEADING INTO SUNDAY AS ALL OF
US TRY TO GET HOME, WE HAVE A
BIG STORM ACROSS THE EAST.
>>> THE NOO"THE NEW YORK TIMES"
REPORTING THAT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT INTERPERSPECTIVE
GENERAL DIDN'T -- INSPECTOR
GENERAL DIDN'T FIND ANY
EVIDENCE.
>> IT'S A WORTHLESS
INVESTIGATION TAKING PLACE.
>>> THE MASSIVE EXPLOSION AT A
CHEMICAL PLANTS HAVE ROCKED THE
NEIGHBORHOOD IN SOUTHEAST TEXAS.
>> THE FIRE STILL BURNING
OVERNIGHT.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHAT GETTING
BLOWN OUT OF BED MEANS NOW.
>> Reporter: ANGRY REACTION FROM
CHINA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SIGNED A PAIR OF
BILLS THAT SHOWED SUPPORT FOR
PRO-DEMOCRACY PROTESTERS IN HONG
KONG.
>> Reporter: FORMER PRESIDENT
JIMMY CARTER IS BACK HOME IN
TIME FOR THANKSGIVING.
HE WAS RELEASED FROM THE
HOSPITAL YESTERDAY.
>>> ALL THAT --
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETING THIS
PHOTO OF HIS HEAD ON ROCKY
BALBOA'S BODY.
>> THE FIRST THING THEY DO IS
THEY TAKE OFF YOUR, SHOW US THAT
GORGEOUS CHEST.
>>> ALL THAT MATTERS.
>> I LOVE DOING THIS EVER YEAR.
YOU OPEN IT UP, POKE A HOLE IN
THE BOTTOM --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> CHEF JOSE ANDREAS TRIED TO
TEACH STEPHEN COLBERT HOW TO
TOOK FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
>> DON'T COME TO THANKSGIVING AT
MY HOUSE.
>>> ON "CBS THIS MORNING."
>> THANKSGIVING CELEBRATIONS ARE
CHANGING ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
ACCORDING TO NEW RESEARCH, 70%
OF YOUNG AMERICANS PREFER
CELEBRATING FRIENDS-GIVING OVER
A TRADITIONAL THANKSGIVING WITH
FAMILY.
AND DEPENDING ON WHAT KIND OF
FAMILY YOU HAVE, YOU MIGHT ALSO
OPT FOR FRIENDS-OWEEN,
FRIENDS-MAS, AND IN FEBRUARY,
FRIENDS-DAY.
>>> THIS "EYE OPENER" PRESENTED
BY BROUGHT TO YOU BY TOYOTA --
LET'S GO PLACES.
.
>> WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG THAT'S
WHERE IT'S AT.
>> FRIENDS-GIVING.
>> GLAD TO BE WITH YOU.
>> DITTO.
>> AND THE CREW.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WELCOME TO "CBS THIS MORNING."
AND HAPPY THANKSGIVING,
EVERYBODY.
CONCERNS ABOUT THE WEATHER MAY
LEAVE AMERICANS WITHOUT ONE OF
THE MOST FAMILIAR SITES OF THIS
HOLIDAY.
THERE ARE HIGH WIND ALERTS
ACROSS THE NORTHEAST THIS
MORNING.
SOME AREAS EXPECT GUSTS OF UP TO
50 MILES AN HOUR.
THAT COULD FORCE THE MACY'S
THIRD PARADE HERE IN NEW YORK TO
GROUND ITS FAMOUS BIG BALLOONS.
>> THE ROUTE RUNS FOR 46 BLOCKS
TO MANHATTAN'S 34th STREET.
IF THE WIND BLOWS STEADILY AT
MORE THAN 23 MILES PER HOUR, THE
BALLOONS WILL STAY ON THE
GROUND.
IT WOULD BE THE FIRST TIME SINCE
1971.
E-RON BARNETT IS AT THE -- ERROL
BARNETT IS AT THE STARTING POINT
ALONG CENTRAL PARK.
WHEN TO WE FIND OUT IF THE
BALLOONS ARE GOING TO GO?
>> Reporter: WELL, GOOD MORNING,
GUYS.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING, EVERYONE.
LOOK, THIS IS A SPECIAL DAY, I'M
EXCITED TO SEE THESE BALLOONS
GET UP AS MY FIRST THANKSGIVING
PARADE HERE IN NEW YORK CITY.
WE DON'T KNOW YET.
A DECISION, DAVID, EXPECTED
BETWEEN 8:30 A.M. AND 9:00 A.M.
WHEN THE PARADE BEGINS.
AT THE MOMENT THERE ARE NO
CREDIBLE SECURITY THREATS.
YOU DO HAVE MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
HERE ANXIOUS JUST LIKE ME TO SEE
THE BALLOONS THAT MAKE TODAY SO
SPECIAL.
>> IT'S JUST MAGICAL FOR THEM TO
SEE THEM GO FROM THE GROUND ALL
THE WAY UP INTO THE AIR.
>> I THINK THIS IS BETTER THAN
SCHOOL, AND I CAME HERE BECAUSE
I WANTED TO SEE THE BALLOONS.
>> Reporter: MILLIONS OF FANS
ARE LINING THE STREETS OF NEW
YORK CITY TO SEE THE ICONIC
PARADE BALLOONS FLY HIGH IN THE
SKY.
>> GOING TO BE A GAME DAY
DECISION.
IT ALL DEPENDS ON THE STRENGTH
OF THE WINDS.
>> Reporter: THE NYPD'S CHIEF OF
PATROL, RODNEY HARRISON, SAYS
PARADE OFFICIALS ARE CLOSELY
WATCHING THE THREAT OF HIGH
WINDS.
YOU GET A SENSE OF HOW HUGE
THESE BALLOONS ARE WITH FOLKS
NEXT TO THEM STILL FILLING THEM
WITH HELIUM.
EACH WILL HAVE ITS OWN POLICE
SERGEANT ASSIGNED TO IT TO MAKE
SURE IT IS SAFE AND SECURE ALONG
THE ENTIRE ROUTE.
HISTORY SHOWS THE WEATHER
AGAINST THESE MASSIVE BALLOONS
COULD BE VERY DANGEROUS.
>> IT SNAPPED OFF AND CAME
AROUND AND HIT THE PEOPLE.
IT WAS A HUGE PIECE OF METAL.
>> Reporter: IN 1997, FOUR
PEOPLE WERE HURT INCLUDING A
WOMAN WHO SPENT A MONTH IN A
COMA, AFTER STRONG WINDS BLEW
THE CAT IN THE HAT BALLOON INTO
A METAL POLE.
IN 2005, AN M&M BALLOON KNOCKED
OFF A STREET LAMP AND LEFT TWO
PEOPLE WITH CUTS AND BRUISES.
STRONG WINDS ARE ONLY ONE FACTOR
FOR THE LARGEST POLICE FORCE.
>> WE'LL HAVE LONG GUNS, WE'LL
HAVE ROOFTOP COVERAGE.
>> Reporter: ABOUT 12,000 POLICE
OFFICERS ARE LINING THE
2.5-MILE-LONG ROUTE ALONG ABOUT
35 EXPLOSIVE-DETECTION K-9s.
THAT'S IN ADDITION TO MORE THAN
135 CAMERAS AND DETECTION DRONES
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE ROUTE.
>> WE JUST NEED EVERYONE TO HAVE
THEIR EYES AND EARS OUT AND
SHARE ANYTHING THAT LOOKS
SUSPICIOUS.
>> Reporter: THE NYPD HAS PATROL
VEHICLES BLOCKING OFF THE ROUTE.
SAND-FILLED TRUCKS, AS WELL.
BEHIND ME, YOU CAN SEE THE
ICONIC BALLOONS READY TO GO.
YOU CAN MAKE OUT SNOOPY IN A
BRAND-NEW SPACE SUIT AS WELL AS
SOME OTHER BALLOONS.
AND EVEN IF THEY DO GET TO HIT
THE AIR AT THE BEGINNING OF THIS
PARADE, THEY COULD BE TAKEN DOWN
AT ANY MINUTE IF THE WINDS AND
GUSTS DO PICK UP.
A LOT OF FAMILIES OUT HERE, AS
WELL.
THE NYPD, OF COURSE, WANTS TO
KEEP EVERYBODY SAFE AND HAPPY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S KEEP OUR FINGERS CROSSED.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING, ERROL.
>> Reporter: HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> THE SYSTEM IN THE NORTHEAST
IS BRINGING SNOW TO NORTHERN NEW
ENGLAND.
IN THE WEST ANOTHER BIG STORM IS
MOVING INTO THE SOUTHERN ROCKIES
AND THE GREAT PLAINS.
CBS NEWS CLIMATE AND WEATHER
CONTRIBUTOR JEFF BERARDELLI IS
WITH US.
WHAT ARE THE BIG ISSUES RIGHT
NOW, AND WHERE ARE THESE STORMS
HEADED?
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE'RE MOST CONCERNED ABOUT
IS THE BIG WIND IN THE EAST AND
WHETHER OR NOT THESE BALLOONS
WILL TAKE FLIGHT.
LET ME SHOW YOU THE BIG PICTURE.
LITERALLY IT'S GOING TO BE DOWN
TO THE WIRE.
THERE'S A STORM DEVELOPING OFF
THE EAST COAST.
LOOK AT THE WINDS AT 8:00 A.M.
JUST BELOW THE 34 MILE-AN-HOUR
THRESHOLD AT 33.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM -- AS THE SUN
RISE, THE WIND COMES UP.
BY 9:00, 10:00, 11:00, OUR WINDS
ARE OVER THE THRESHOLD IN
CENTRAL PARK AT AROUND 37, 38
MILE-PER-HOUR WIND GUSTS.
THAT IS THE FORECAST.
AND YOU CAN UNDERSTAND THESE ARE
LARGE BALLOONS HERE.
THEY CAN GET BLOWN AROUND REALLY
EASILY.
OTHERWISE, IT'S LOOKING GOOD
WITH LOTS OF SUN AND
TEMPERATURES AROUND 45.
DOUBLE JET STREAM STRUCTURE,
THIS WAS A MEGA STORM THAT
SLAMMED THE WEST COAST WITH
GUSTS OVER 100 MILES PER HOUR A
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
NOW IT'S A MAJOR RAIN AND SNOW
PRODUCER WITH A TON OF MOISTURE
MOVING IN.
DAY BY DAY, THIS WILL LITERALLY
GO COAST TO COAST.
TOMORROW, FRESH POWDER IN THE
WEST.
IF YOU'RE A SKIER, YOU'RE GOING
TO LOVE IT.
FLOODING AROUND PHOENIX.
THEN THE STORM BECOMES A
BLIZZARD.
RAPID CITY AND FARGO.
LOOK AT THIS, BEGINS TO TRANSFER
ITS ENERGY TO THE EAST COAST.
COULD BE AN ICE STORM INTERIOR
PARTS OF NEW ENGLAND ON SUNDAY.
THEN MAYBE A SNOWSTORM, A
NOR'EASTER POSSIBLE BY MONDAY
MORNING.
NOT GOING TO BE GREAT FOR
TRAVELERS, UNFORTUNATELY.
>> DOES NOT LOOK LIKE IT.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>>> THE BAD WEATHER COULD MAKE
FOR TREACHEROUS DRIVING
CONDITIONS FOR MANY DRIVERS.
IT REMAINS BRUTAL IN PARTS OF
THE WEST BECAUSE OF A POWERFUL
STORM THAT LEFT PEOPLE STRANDED
FOR MANY HOURS NEAR THE
OREGON-CALIFORNIA BORDER EARLIER
THIS WEEK.
THIS MORNING, THE MAIN HIGHWAY
THERE, INTERSTATE 5, HAS FULLY
REOPENED.
TRANSPORTATION CORRESPONDENT
KRIS VAN CLEAVE HAS BEEN
TRACKING THE HOLIDAY RUSH.
>> Reporter: AS TRAVELERS MADE
THEIR WAY CLOSER TO THANKSGIVING
MEALS, THEY FACED HARSH WEATHER
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
TWO STORMS DUMPED HEAVY SNOW IN
THE WEST AND BROUGHT WINDS AND
RAIN TO THE EAST WEDNESDAY.
>> PEOPLE ARE IN A RUSH.
YOU GOT TO TAKE IT EASY.
>> Reporter: MANY DRIVERS IN
MINNESOTA SPENT THE DAY DIGGING
OUT.
CRASHES AND SPINOUTS TIED UP
TRAFFIC FOR MILES.
THE WEATHER ALSO CAUSED DELAYS
AT AIRPORTS WHERE NEARLY 4.5
MILLION AMERICANS WERE EXPECTED
TO FLY THIS THANKSGIVING
HOLIDAY.
>> I WAKE UP AT 4:00 A.M., GET
HERE AN HOUR EARLY.
>> Reporter: AMTRAK HAS MORE
TRAINS OPERATING AT ITS MAJOR
HUBS.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO FIND EXTRA
STAFFING STATIONS, EXTRA TRAINS,
EXTRA CAPACITY.
>> Reporter: MOST AMERICANS ARE
HITTING THE ROADS LIKE WE DID.
WE ARE ON THE MOVE FROM DOWNTOWN
BOSTON.
AN EARLY START DID NOT SAVE US
FROM RUNNING INTO HOLIDAY
TRAFFIC ON INTERSTATE 95 ON OUR
TREK TO D.C.
NOT EVEN GOING 20 MILES PER HOUR
RIGHT NOW.
AND WE WERE NOT ALONE.
A TRIP THAT SHOULD HAVE TAKEN AN
HOUR TOOK 2, 2 1/2 HOURS.
>> Reporter: WE FINALLY MADE IT.
DRIVING FROM BOSTON TO
WASHINGTON ON A GOOD DAY TAKES
ABOUT EIGHT HOURS.
IT'S AROUND 440 MILES.
THIS WAS NOT A GOOD DAY.
THIS WAS THE DAY BEFORE
THANKSGIVING.
AND IT TOOK MORE THAN 11 HOURS.
BUT WE HAVE JUST NOW FINALLY
CROSSED INTO WASHINGTON.
FOR "CBS THIS MORNING," KRIS VAN
CLEAVE, WASHINGTON.
>>> BREAKING NEWS FROM SOUTH
KOREA.
SOUTH KOREA'S MILITARY SAYS THAT
NORTH KOREA LAUNCHED TWO
SHORT-RANGE MISSILES TOWARD
JAPAN.
THEY WERE REPORTEDLY FIRED FROM
NORTH KOREA'S EASTERN REGION
RIGHT INTO THE SEA OF JAPAN.
NOW JAPAN'S PRIME MINISTER IS
CALLING IT A THREAT TO JAPAN AND
SAYING IT'S ALSO A THREAT TO THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY.
RAMY INOCENCIO IS IN SOUTH KOREA
RIGHT NOW.
HE HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: THIS COUNTS AS THE
13th PROJECTILE LAUNCH BY NORTH
KOREA THIS YEAR.
SEOUL'S JOINT CHIEFS OF STAFF
SAID THE PROJECTILES WERE
LAUNCHED FROM A PROVINCE ON THE
NORTHEAST COAST.
THE MOVE APPEARS TO BE AN
ATTEMPT BY THE NORTH TO PRESSURE
THE WHITE HOUSE TO MAKE
CONCESSIONS IN NUCLEAR TALKS
WHICH HAVE BEEN IN A DEEP
FREEZE.
SOUTH KOREA'S MILITARY TOGETHER
WITH THE UNITED STATES IS
MONITORING THE AREA FOR MORE
LAUNCHES.
MEANWHILE, NORTH KOREAN ALLY
CHINA IS REACTING FURIOUSLY TO A
MOVE BY U.S. PRESIDENT TRUMP.
IN HONG KONG, ANTI-GOVERNMENT
PROTESTERS ARE CELEBRATING WHAT
THEY CALL A MORAL VICTORY AFTER
THE PRESIDENT SIGNED THE HONG
KONG HUMAN RIGHTS AND DEMOCRACY
ACT.
THAT LAW PASSED WITH A
VETO-PROOF BIPARTISAN MAJORITIES
IN BOTH THE HOUSE AND SENATE,
ALLOWS THE WHITE HOUSE TO
SANCTION CHINESE AND HONG KONG
OFFICIALS AND ORGANIZATIONS
BASED ON THE FORMER BRITISH
COLONY IF CIVIL LIBERTIES ARE
VIOLATED.
THE HONG KONG GOVERNMENT HAS
CALLED IT UNWARRANTED.
BEIJING HAS CALLED THE ACT HEDGE
MOONIC AND DOOMED TO FAIL.
THIS MORNING CHINA SUMMONED THE
U.S. AMBASSADOR TO PROTEST THAT
MOVE.
FOR "CBS THIS MORNING," RACY
SEN --
RAMY INOCENCIO, SEOUL.
>>> A FIRE IS BURNING IN TEXAS
AFTER AN EXPLOSION AT A CHEMICAL
PLANT.
A SECOND BLAST RATTLED THE CITY
OF PORT NECHES YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON.
THE INITIAL EXPLOSION HIT EARLY
YESTERDAY MORNING AND WAS FELT
UP TO 30 MILES AWAY.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE HAVE
OPIN
BEEN TOLD TO EVACUATE.
OMAR VILLAFRANCA HAS A LOOK AT
THE DEVASTATION.
>> Reporter: A WALL OF FLAMES
ERUPTED FROM THE TPC PLANT IN
PORT NECHES, TEXAS.
JUST HOURS AFTER A MASSIVE BLAST
TORE THROUGH THE REFINERY EARLY
WEDNESDAY MORNING.
THE NEW EXPLOSION FORCED A
MANDATORY EVACUATION OF ABOUT
60,000 PEOPLE WITHIN A FOUR-MILE
RADIUS OF THE PLANT.
PUTTING MANY RESIDENTS'
THANKSGIVING PLANS ON HOLD.
>> I HAD DRESSING MADE IN THE
FREEZER.
READY TO COOK.
I HAD A TURKEY IN THE OVEN.
>> JUST LIT UP THE ENTIRE SKY.
HADN'T SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THAT
BEFORE.
>> Reporter: THE FIRST BLAST
HAPPENED JUST AFTER MIDNIGHT IN
AN AREA OF THE PLANT THAT
PRODUCES A HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CHEMICAL USED TO MAKE SYNTHETIC
RUBBER AND OTHER PRODUCTS.
OFFICIALS SAY IT WAS FELT UP TO
30 MILES AWAY AND BLEW OUT
WINDOWS AND DOORS OF NEARBY
HOMES.
THREE WORKERS WERE HURT DURING
THE EXPLOSION.
ALL HAVE BEEN TREATED AND
RELEASED.
STATE AUTHORITIES SAY A SERIES
OF SMALLER EXPLOSIONS OCCURRED
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
>> IT PUTS A LOT OF FEAR IN A
LOT OF FAMILIES BECAUSE THEIR
HUSBANDS AND WIVES AND CHILDREN
WORK IN THESE REFINERIES.
>> Reporter: TEXAS HAS ALREADY
SEEN MASSIVE FIRES IN AT LEAST
FIVE CHEMICAL PLANTS THIS YEAR.
IN APRIL, A FIRE AT A PLANT IN
CROSBY, NORTHEAST OF HOUSTON,
KILLED ONE PERSON AND SERIOUSLY
INJURED TWO.
A LOSS OF POWER IS PREVENTING
INVESTIGATORS FROM ESTIMATING
HOW LONG THE FIRE WILL LAST.
>> IT'S HORRIFIC WHEN YOU
REALIZE WHAT FORCE TOOK THE
FRONT DOOR AND PUT IT IN YOUR
LIVING ROOM.
WE'RE THANKFUL WE'RE SAFE.
WE HAVE A LOT TO BE THANKFUL FOR
THIS THANKSGIVING.
>> Reporter: FOR "CBS THIS
MORNING," I'M OMAR VILLAFRANCA.
>>> TO POLITICS NOW.
IN THE IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY,
SOURCES ARE TELLING CBS NEWS
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LIKELY TO
REJECT THE DEMOCRATS' OFFER TO
APPEAR WHEN THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE STARTS HEARINGS NEXT
WEEK.
NEW REPORTS SAY THE PRESIDENT'S
PERSONAL ATTORNEY, RUDY
GIULIANI, DISCUSSED LUCRATIVE
BUSINESS DEALS WITH UKRAINIAN
OFFICIALS WHILE HE WAS WORKING
WITH THEM TO INVESTIGATE FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN AND HIS
SON, HUNTER.
WEIJIA JIANG IS TRAVELING WITH
THE PRESIDENT IN FLORIDA.
HE IS CELEBRATING THANKSGIVING
AT HIS MAR-A-LAGO RESORT.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
DAVID, AND GOOD MORNING,
EVERYONE.
YOU KNOW, RUDY GIULIANI'S
PURSUITS IN UKRAINE AND HOW MUCH
OF THEM UNFOLDED WITH THE
PRESIDENT'S KNOWLEDGE ARE
CENTRAL TO THE HOUSE IMPEACHMENT
INQUIRY INTO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
AND MANY WITNESSES HAVE ALREADY
TESTIFIED UNDER CONGRESS THAT IT
WAS GIULIANI WHO WAS LEADING THE
ADMINISTRATION'S CAMPAIGN TO
PRESSURE UKRAINE TO ANNOUNCE
INVESTIGATIONS INTO THE
PRESIDENT'S POLITICAL RIVALS.
RUDY GIULIANI HAS DENIED THAT HE
TRIED TO RAKE IN HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS FROM
PRIVATE BUSINESS DEALS WITH
UKRAINIAN OFFICIALS.
>> I HAVE NO BUSINESS INTERESTS
IN UKRAINE.
>> Reporter: BUT HE'S
ACKNOWLEDGING THAT HE DID
CONSIDER WORKING FOR ONE
COMPANY.
IN A STATEMENT WEDNESDAY, HIS
LAWYER SAID, "BOTTOM LINE IS HE
DID NOT SEEK ANY BUSINESS AND
TURN DOWN THE BUSINESS THAT
SOUGHT HIM."
GIULIANI'S CONVERSATIONS WITH
UKRAINIAN OFFICIALS CAME WHILE
HE WAS PURSUING DAMAGING
INFORMATION ABOUT THE BIDENS.
IN RECENT DAYS, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS DEFENDED GIULIANI'S ROLE IN
LOOKING INTO UKRAINIAN
CORRUPTION.
>> RUDY IS A GREAT CRIMEFIGHTER,
CORRUPTION FIGHTER.
>> Reporter: WHILE CLAIMINGLY
DID NOT SEND GIULIANI --CLAIM
ING HE DID NOT SEND GIULIANI TO
UKRAINE.
>> HE POSSIBLY SAW SOMETHING.
>> Reporter: EU AMBASSADOR
GORDON SONDLAND IS ONE OF
SEVERAL WITNESSES IN THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY TO DESCRIBE
GIULIANI AS THE MASTERMIND OF
PRESSURING UKRAINE TO
INVESTIGATE THE BIDENS.
>> I FOLLOWED THE DIRECTIONS OF
THE PRESIDENT.
WE WORKED WITH MR. GIULIANI
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT DIRECTED
US TO DO SO.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE HOUSE IS
ALSO RESPONDING TO A REPORT THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP FOUND OUT ABOUT
THE WHISTLE-BLOWER'S COMPLAINT
IN LATE AUGUST.
BEFORE HE RELEASED U.S. MILITARY
AID TO UKRAINE, A SOURCE CLOSE
TO THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT
REPORT SHOWS THAT THE AID
RELEASE WAS NOT CONNECTED TO THE
WHISTLE-BLOWER COMPLAINT BECAUSE
HE WAITED AT LEAST 11 DAYS.
DEMOCRATS SAY IT SHOWS THE
OPPOSITE.
>> A LOT OF SCRAMBLING WENT ON
AFTER THE FACT TO TRY TO COVER
THEIR TRACKS.
INCLUDING THE ULTIMATE
RESUMPTION OF AID ITSELF.
>> Reporter: SO FAR WE HAVE NOT
SEEN PRESIDENT TRUMP DURING HIS
BREAK DOWN HERE IN FLORIDA, BUT
HE DOES HAVE ONE PUBLIC ITEM ON
HIS SCHEDULE TODAY -- A TEST
CONFERENCE WITH MEMBERS --
TELECONFERENCE WITH MEMBERS OF
THE MILITARY.
LAST YEAR THE SAME EVENT TURN
INTO A FREE-WHEELING NEWS
CONFERENCE.
MICHELLE, YOU NEVER KNOW, HE
MIGHT JUST CHIME IN ON GIULIANI,
IMPEACHMENT, AND WHATEVER ELSE
HE FEELS LIKE TALKING ABOUT.
>> THIS IS TRUE.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
THANK YOU.
>>> THREE NAVY S.E.A.L.s LINKED
TO THE WAR CRIMES CASE OF EDWARD
GALLAGHER WILL KEEP THEIR
TRIDENT PINS.
GALLAGHER WAS CONVICTED OF
POSING WITH A CORPSE WHILE IN
IRAQ.
THE NAVY DEMOTED HIM, BUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP ORDERED HIS RANK
BE RESTORED.
THE NEW ACTING SECRETARY OF THE
NAVY CANCELED REVIEW BOARDS FOR
THE THREE S.E.A.L.s WHO WERE
GALLAGHER'S SUPERIOR OFFICERS SO
THEY COULD KEEP THEIR TRIDENT
PINS.
THOSE PINS IDENTIFY THEM AS NAVY
S.E.A.L.s.
FORMER NAVY SECRETARY RICHARD
SPENCER, WHO WAS FIRED OVER HIS
REFUSAL TO STOP AN INVESTIGATION
INTO GALLAGHER, WRITES IN A NEW
"WASHINGTON POST" OP-ED, QUOTE,
THE PRESIDENT HAS VERY LITTLE
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE IN THE MILITARY, TO FIGHT
ETHICALLY OR TO BE GOVERNED BY A
UNIFORM SET OF RULES AND
PRACTICES.
>
>>> FORMER PRESIDENT JIMMY
CARTER IS SPENDING THANKSGIVING
AT HOME AFTER A HOSPITAL STAY.
THE 39th PRESIDENT WAS RELEASED
FROM AN ATLANTA HOSPITAL AFTER
SURGERY FOR BLEEDING AROUND HIS
BRAIN.
A SPOKESWOMAN SAYS HE WILL
CONTINUE TO RECOVER AT HOME IN
PLAINS, GEORGIA.
MR. CARTER WAS INJURED THREE
TIMES THIS YEAR AFTER FALLING.
AT AGE 95, HE IS THE OLDEST
LIVING FORMER PRESIDENT IN U.S.
HISTORY.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING, MR.
PRESIDENT.
>>> ONE OF THE WORLD'S MOST
POPULAR SPARKLING WINES IS BEING
THREATENED BY CLIMATE CHANGE.
WE WILL TAKE YOU TO ITALY TO SEE
HOW SCIENTISTS AND WINE MAKERS
ARE TEAMING UP TO LOOK FOR WAYS
TO LESSEN THE
PEETE.
>>> WE HAVE MUCH MORE NEWS
AHEAD.
THE PLAYER WHO BEAT THE BUZZER
TO UPSET DUKE TALKS ABOUT
WINNING MASSIVE SUPPORT TO HELP
REBUILD HIS HURRICANE-RAVAGED
HOME.
>>> PLUS, MEET SOME OF THE
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE WHO GATHER
TO CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS MOVIES
HALLMARK STYLE.
>>> RIGHT NOW WE'RE KEEPING AN
EYE ON THE BIGGEST THANKSGIVING
DAY PARADE.
WILL THE BALLOONS FLY?
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>>> WE'LL PREVIEW THE NFL ACTION
THAT FOLLOWS THE SHOW.
GOOD FOOTBALL TODAY.
YOU'RE WATCHING "CTM."
It's tough to quit smoking
cold turkey.
So CHANTIX can help you quit
slow turkey.
Along with support, CHANTIX
is proven to help you quit.
With CHANTIX you can keep
smoking at first
and ease into quitting.
CHANTIX reduces the urge
so when the day arrives,
you'll be more ready to kiss
cigarettes goodbye.
When you try to quit smoking,
with or without CHANTIX,
you may have nicotine
withdrawal symptoms.
Stop CHANTIX and
get help right away
if you have changes
in behavior or thinking,
aggression, hostility,
depressed mood,
suicidal thoughts or actions,
seizures,
new or worse heart or blood
vessel problems, sleepwalking,
or life-threatening allergic
and skin reactions.
Decrease alcohol use.
Use caution driving
or operating machinery.
Tell your doctor if you've had
mental health problems.
The most common side effect
is nausea.
Quit smoking slow turkey.
Talk to your doctor
about CHANTIX.
Well, here's to first dates!
You look amazing.
And you look amazingly
comfortable.
When your V-Neck looks more
like a U-Neck...
That's when you know, it's
Half-Washed.
Try Downy Fabric Conditioner.
Unlike detergent alone, Downy
helps prevent stretching
by conditioning and smoothing
fibers,
so clothes look newer, longer.
Downy and it's done.
(VO) At Pro Plan,
we believe nutrition is full of
possibilities to improve
your pet's life.
We're redefining
what nutrition can do.
Because the possibility
of a longer life
and a healthy life
is the greatest
possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan.
Nutrition that Performs.
♪
Hey! Your science project.
Thanks, Dad.
Toyota. Let's go places.
If your gums bleed
when you brush,
you may have gingivitis.
And the clock could be
ticking towards bad breath,
receding gums, and possibly...
tooth loss.
Help turn back the clock
on gingivitis
with Parodontax.
Leave bleeding gums behind.
Parodontax.
♪
>>> AHEAD IN OUR "A MORE PERFECT
UNION" SERIES, MEET A WOMAN WHO
STARTED HER OWN FOOD PANTRY
THAT'S FREE TO ANYONE IN HER
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> PLUS, THE MISTAKE THAT LED
TO A THANKSGIVING TRADITION
BETWEEN TOTAL STRANGERS.
YOUR LOCAL NEWS IS NEXT.
To the outside world,
you look good,
but you don't feel good.
With polycythemia vera,
PV, symptoms can change
so slowly over time
you might not notice.
But new or changing symptoms
can mean your PV is changing.
Let's change the way we see PV.
You track and discuss blood
counts with your doctor.
But it's just as vital
to discuss
changing symptoms as well.
Take notice and take action.
Discuss counts and symptoms
with your doctor.
Visit TakeActionPV.com
Discuss counts and symptoms
with your doctor.
♪  ♪
Lowe's helps you
do hosting right
with the best
prices of the year
on appliances to help you
handle anything and everything.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING ON "CBS
THIS MORNING."
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING!
>> MILLIONS TURN OUT IN NEW YORK
CITY FOR THE MACY'S THANKSGIVING
DAY PARADE.
>> I ABSOLUTELY LOVE IT.
EVERY YEAR WE'RE HERE.
WHEN THE KIDS DIDN'T WANT TO
COME, MY HUSBAND AND I CAME BY
OURSELVES.
>> I THINK THIS IS BETTER THAN
SCHOOL.
>>> RAIN, SNOW, AND HEAVY
TRAFFIC SLOW THANKSGIVING TRAVEL
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
>> THE DRIVERS OUT THERE, THEY
DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA HOW TO
DRIVE.
>> IF YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO
OUTSIDE, DON'T GO.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LIKELY TO
SKIP THE NEXT IMPEACHMENT
INQUIRY WHILE RUDY GIULIANI'S
UKRAINE TIES GET NEW ATTENTION.
>> RUDY IS A GREAT CRIME
FIGHTER, CORRUPTION FIGHTER.
>>> YES!
>> PLUS, MEET THE PLAYER WHOSE
GAME-WINNING SHOT AGAINST DUKE
TURNED INTO A GAUGE CHANGER FOR
HIS FAMILY.
>>> WE ENJOY THE GOOD FEEL THEY
GIVE YOU AND THE JOY AND
HAPPINESS THAT IT BRINGS.
>>> WE'LL GO TO THE FIRST-EVER
CHRISTMAS COM WITH THE HEART
THERE'S DROT OF HOLIDAY MOVIES,
JONATHAN BENNETT.
>> THIS GUY LOVES HALLMARK
CHRISTMAS MOVIES.
>> YES, I DO.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "CBS THIS
MORNING."
I'M DAVID BEG FLAWED WITH
MICHELLE MILLER AND JERICKA
DUNCAN.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
AND TO YOU LADIES, TOO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE APPRECIATE THAT.
>>> CLIMATE CHANGE IS CREATING
NEW CHALLENGES FOR THE GLOBAL
WINE INDUSTRY.
THIS MORNING IN OUR "EYE ON
EARTH" SERIES, WE'RE GOING TO
EXPLORE HOW THE CHANGING
ENVIRONMENT IS ACTUALLY
AFFECTING THE PRODUCTION OF THE
POPULAR SPARKLING WINE PROSECCO.
SETH DOANE WENT TO MANWAY,
OUTSIDE OF ITALY, TO SEE HOW
THEY'RE WORKING TO MAKE SURE
THAT WARMER TEMPERATURES DON'T
END UP ALTERING THE TASTE AND
P
PUN GENESEE.
>> Reporter: CLIMATE CHANGE IS
THREATENING CENTURIES OF ITALIAN
TRADITION IN THIS REGION KNOWN
FOR PROSECCO.
PAOLA TOMASELLA SAYS EXTREME
WEATHER IS POSING CHALLENGES TO
HIS VINEYARD, TENUTE TOMASELLA.
>> IT POSES A PROBLEM WHEN IT'S
HOTTER, WHEN IT'S RAINING, IT
RAINS VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: PROSECCO, HE
EXPLAINED, SHOULD HAVE LOW
ALCOHOL AND HIGH ACIDITY.
HIGH TEMPERATURES AND EARLIER
RIPENING PRODUCE THE OPPOSITE
EFFECT.
>> IT'S OUR PROSECCO.
IT IS OUT OF OUR FORT.
>> Reporter: SO HE IS TESTING
NEW TECHNIQUES AND LETTING
ITALIAN GOVERNMENT SCIENTISTS
USE THE VINEYARD AS A SORT OF
LABORATORY.
>> THE CLIMATE CHANGE IS MAKING
EFFECT ON THE ACIDITY BECAUSE
MORE TEMPERATURE MEANS ALSO LOW
ACIDITY.
>> Reporter: HE SHOWED US GRAPES
THAT HAVE BURNED ON THE VINE.
WINE MAKERS ARE SOMETIMES FORCED
TO HARVEST WEEKS EARLIER IN THE
HOTTEST MONTHS WHICH CAN PRODUCE
DIFFERENT AROMAS AND FLAVORS.
>> THE VINE IS LIKE A
THERMOMETER.
IT'S VERY SENSITIVE TO
TEMPERATURE.
>> Reporter: AT ITALY'S RESEARCH
CENTER, THEY'RE HEARING FROM
WINEMAKERS WHO ARE PLANTING AT
HIGHER ELEVATIONS AND HAVE
DISCOVERED THE TIMING BETWEEN
GROWING STAGES IS NOW SHORTER.
WHY DO YOU BLAME CLIMATE CHANGE?
>> BECAUSE OF COURSE THE SOIL IS
MORE OR LESS THE SAME.
THE VARIETY MORE OR LESS OF THE
SAME.
AND SO EVERYTHING THAT WE ARE
DISCOVERING NOW DEPENDS ON THE
CLIMATE.
>> Reporter: WHICH MEANS MAKING
ADJUSTMENTS LIKE CUTTING BACK
FOLIAGE TO STOP PHOTOSYNTHESIS,
A WAY TO REDUCE THE AMOUNT OF
ALCOHOL THAT COMES FROM THE
GRAPES, AND PIPING NITROGEN INTO
THE WATER TO BOOST ACIDITY.
GROWERS COULD PLANT NEW VINES
BETTER SUITED IS ON CHANGING
CLIMACTIC CONDITIONS, BUT NEW
VINES TAKE YEARS TO PRODUCE AND
ULTIMATELY CHANGE THE CHARACTER
OF A WINE AND A PLACE.
AS CLIMATE CHANGE CREEPS IN TO
YET ANOTHER ASPECT OF LIFE.
FOR "CBS THIS MORNING," SETH
DOANE, MANSWAY, ITALY.
>> WOW.
WHO KNEW?
IT TAKES SO MUCH WORK --
>> I DIDN'T KNOW PROSECCO HAD
SUCH A HIGH ACIDITY.
>> THE IMPACTS OF CLIMATE CHANGE
KEEP BEARING OUT.
>> GOOD TO KNOW.
>>> A HUGE NUMBER OF CHRISTMAS
MOVIES ARE BEING RELEASED THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
AHEAD WE VISIT A CHRISTMAS MOVIE
CONVENTION TO FIND OUT WHY THESE
MOVIES ARE BECOMING EVEN MORE
POPULAR.
>>> AND IF YOU'RE ON THE GO,
SUBSCRIBE TO OUR PODCAST.
HEAR THE DAY'S TOP STORIES IN
LESS THAN 20 MINUTES.
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING "CBS THIS
MORNING."
[Alarm bell rings]
♪ Bang bang, there
goes my bang bang, ♪
♪ I want my bang bang,
I want my bang bang ♪
♪ Go bang bang ♪
♪ there goes my bang bang, ♪
♪ Go bang bang,
there goes my bazooka ♪
♪
♪ Go bang bang, there
goes my bang bang, ♪
♪ I want my mind blown,
I want my mind blown ♪
♪ Go bang bang, there
goes my bazooka ♪
Thanks to Move Free Ultra
I keep up with this little one.
See the world with this guy.
And hit the town with these
girls.
In a clinical study,
4 out of 5 users felt
better joint comfort.
Move Free.
Find our coupon in
Sunday's paper.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle Repair's
derm-proven Retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week to reveal
younger looking skin.
Making wrinkles look
so last week.
Rapid Wrinkle Repair®
Pair with retinol oil for 2x
the wrinkle fighting power.
Neutrogena®
Donald Trump failed as a
businessman.
He borrowed billions
and left a trail of bankruptcy
and broken promises.
He hasn't changed.
I started a tiny investment
business,
and over 27 years,
grew it successfully to 36
billion dollars.
I'm Tom Steyer and I approve
this message.
I'm running for president
because unlike other candidates,
I can go head to head with
Donald Trump on the economy,
and expose him fo what he is:
a fraud and a failure.
If your mouth is made to amaze,
Let Philips Sonicare
give its care a raise.
Get healthier gums
in 2 weeks guaranteed.
Give it Philips Sonicare.
Next level clean,
next level care.
There's always a way
to make life better.
Philips Sonicare
Forget about vacuuming
for months.
The Roomba i7+ with cleany
base automatic dirt disposal
And AllergenLock™ bags
that trap 99% of allergens,
so they don't escape
back into the air.
If it's not from iRobot, it's
not a Roomba™
♪
♪ ♪
Nothing feels like connecting
with the people that matter.
Holiday Inn.
Holiday Inn Express.
We're there.
So you can be too.
>>> DEFINITELY IN THE HOLIDAY
SPIRIT WITH THAT SONG.
♪
THE UNOFFICIAL KICKOFF TO THE
HOLIDAY MOVIE SEASON.
BUT FOR DIEHARD FANS IT STARTED
EVEN EARLIER.
LIFETIME AND HALLMARK BEGAN
PREMIERING CHRISTMAS MOVIES BACK
IN OCTOBER.
BETWEEN THE TWO NETWORKS, THERE
WILL BE 70 NEW HOLIDAY MOVIES
OUT BY NEW YEAR'S DAY.
NIKKI BATTISTE LOOKS AT WHAT'S
BEHIND THE BOYFRIENDS MOVIES --
THE MOVIES' GROWING POPULARITY.
YOU WENT TO A CHRISTMAS MOVIE
CONVENTION?
I'M JEALOUS.
>> GOOD MORNING.
THIS WAS A REALLY TOUGH
ASSIGNMENT.
EARLIER THIS MONTH, WE ATTENDED
CHRISTMAS CON IN EDISON, NEW
JERSEY, SPONSORED BY HALLMARK.
9,000 TICKETS WERE SOLD FOR THIS
NOW ANNUAL GATHERING OF
CHRISTMAS MOVIE FANS.
SOME SAID THEY PAID HUNDREDS OF
DOLLARS TO BE THERE, AND WE
WANTED TO KNOW WHY.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE COOLEST
EXPERIENCES I'VE EVER BEEN TO.
>> Reporter: IF YOU WANT TO BE
THE ENVY OF THOUSANDS OF WOMEN
--
LOOK AT ALL THESE LADIES, OH, MY
GOSH!
JUST WALK THROUGH CHRISTMAS CON
WITH THE HEARTTHROB KING OF
HOLIDAY MOVIES --
>> BE A CHRISTMAS AMBASSADOR --
>> Reporter: JONATHAN BENNETT.
[ CHEERS ]
AND IF BENNETT IS THE KING --
>> I THINK PEOPLE LOVE HALLMARK
MOVIES BECAUSE THEY MAKE THEM
FEEL GOOD.
>> Reporter: THEN LACY CHABERT
IS THE QUEEN.
>> LIKE THE PERFECT BLEND OF
BRIOCHE AND COTTON CANDY.
>> Reporter: YOU AND LACEY ARE
THE HALL MARKS --
>> ARE WE ROYALS?
>> THAT'S WHY YOU WANTED TO JOIN
THE MATHLETES.
>> MATHLETES?
YOU HATE MATH.
>> Reporter: BENNETT AND CHABERT
STARRED IN THE HIT "MEAN GIRLS,"
BUT THESE DAYS FOUND A HOME IN
HOLIDAY MOVIES.
>> IS IT TOO WEIRD?
>> IT'S SLIGHTLY WEIRD.
>> Reporter: AND BE THERE
FESTIVE FANS CAME TO EDISON, NEW
JERSEY, FOR THE FIRST-EVER
CHRISTMAS CON TO SEE THEM AND
MORE THAN A DOZEN OTHER STARS.
TICKETS FOR CHRISTMAS CON SOLD
OUT IN A FLASH.
PASSES FOR ALL THREE DAYS COST
$75.
THAT DOESN'T INCLUDE THE PRICE
OF A PHOTO WITH THE CELEBRITY.
THIS GUY LOVES HALLMARK
CHRISTMAS MOVIES.
>> YES, I DO.
>> Reporter: JIM DeANGELO SAYS
WATCHING THE MOVIES IS PART OF
HIS HOLIDAY SEASON ROUTINE.
>> IT'S RELAXING BECAUSE THEY'RE
ENTERTAINING, AND YOU KNOW, NO
VIOLENCE.
IT'S -- IT'S GOOD.
>> Reporter: THERE IS NO DENYING
THE GROWING POPULARITY OF
CHRISTMAS MOVIES.
SINCE ITS HOLIDAY SEASON LAUNCH
ON OCTOBER 25th, HALLMARK SAYS
IT'S REACHED MORE THAN 40
MILLION TOTAL VIEWERS, MAKING IT
THE HIGHEST RATED AND
MOST-WATCHED CHANNEL ON KIEBL.
HALLMARK -- CABLE.
HALLMARK IS PUTTING OUT A RECORD
LIFETIME IS ALSO PREMIERING 30
NEW HOLIDAY MOVIES AND NETFLIX,
SIX.
>> HEY --
>> Reporter: THE MERRY MOVIES
SEEM TO FIT A FORMULA.
A WOMAN FALLS IN LOVE WITH A
HANDSOME SMALL TOWN MAN, AND
EVEN WITH SOME BUMPS ALONG THE
WAY, THEY END UP TOGETHER.
BUT FANS WE SPOKE TO SAID IT'S
NOT ABOUT THE PLOT.
>> WE ENJOY THE GOOD FEEL THAT
IT GIVES YOU AND THE JOY AND THE
HAPPINESS THAT IT BRINGS.
>> Reporter: THIS
MOTHER-DAUGHTER DUO CAME FROM
KENTUCKY AND SAY THEY WATCH
AROUND 100 CHRISTMAS MOVIES A
YEAR.
THEY EVEN TRAVELED TO A TOWN IN
GEORGIA WHERE ONE OF THE MOVIES
WAS FILMED.
>> RETRACED THE STEPS OF THE
COUPLE IN THE MOVIE.
>> Reporter: THE MOVIES ARE NOT
ALWAYS REFLECTIVE OF EVERYONE.
LIFETIME SAYS FOUR OF ITS MOVIES
THIS YEAR FEATURE LGBTQ COUPLES
IN PROMINENT ROLES.
AND HALLMARK DECLINED TO PROVIDE
CBS NEWS WITH A SPECIFIC NUMBER.
SIX HALLMARK MOVIES THIS YEAR
FEATURE LEADS OF COLOR COMPARED
TO NEARLY HALF OF THE NEW
LIFETIME AND NETFLIX MOVIES.
HOLLY ROBINSON PEETE HAS TWO
HALLMARK CHRISTMAS MOVIES COMING
OUT THIS SEASON.
>> WE ALL CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS.
WE COME IN DIFFERENT SHAPES,
COLORS, SIZES.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR THE
MOVIES AND THE CONTENT TO
REFLECT THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
WATCHING.
>> THERE ARE REALLY SORT OF
ENCOURAGING STEPS BEING TAKEN.
>> Reporter: "VARIETY" SENIOR
FILM WRITER MATT DONNELLY SAYS
AS DIVERSITY BEHIND THE CAMERA
INCREASES, HE EXPECTS IT TO BE
REFLECTED ON SCREEN, AS WELL.
>> CHRISTMAS IS NOT JUSTICE
ABOUT RELIGION.
IT'S AN AMERICAN PASTIME.
THERE'S SOMETHING REALLY
IRRESISTIBLE ABOUT A HAPPY
ENDING AND A CHRISTMAS TREE.
>> Reporter: MELISSA JOAN HART
IS THE LEAD IN SEVERAL CHRISTMAS
MOVIES.
>> OKAY, YOU GOT ME.
I WANTED TO SEE IF YOU HAD
CHANGED --
I THINK THE CHRISTMAS MOVIES DO
WHAT SHIRLEY TEMPLE DID IN THE
DAYS OF THE DEPRESSION.
LIKE GIVE YOU AN ESCAPISM, GIVE
YOU SOMEWHERE TO GO.
>> Reporter: IF A BREAK FROM
REALITY THIS HOLIDAY SEASON IS
YOUR CUP OF COCOA --
>> SAY HI, GAYLE KING.
>> Reporter: THEN JONATHAN
BENNETT MAY BE THE PERFECT
TEMPERATURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I GUESS THERE'S NO NOTHING
LEFT TO SAY BUT --
♪ WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS
WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS
AND A HAPPY NEW YEAR ♪
>> DID I JUST SING IS ON
NATIONAL TV?
I DID.
MY MOM SHAKING HER HEAD.
THE CHRISTMAS-CON FOUNDERS SAY
THEY'LL BE BACK IN NEW JERSEY
NEXT YEAR AND IN LOS ANGELES.
LIFETIME TOLD US DIVERSITY AND
INCLUSION ARE OF THE UTMOST
IMPORTANCE, AND HALLMARK SAID
IT'S COMMITTED TO TELLING
STORIES AND DEVELOPING
CHARACTERS FROM A DIVERSE RANGE
OF LIFESTYLES AND BACKGROUNDS.
>> GOOD NEWS.
>> CAN'T GET ENOUGH --
>> I KNOW HOW IT'S GOING TO END.
I GOT TO KEEP WATCHING.
IT'S SO AUSTIN-ESQUE.
IT STEALS FROM THE FORMULA IN MY
HUMBLE BEEN.
THESE GO BACK TO JULY.
THERE'S A JULY, CHRISTMAS IN
JULY WHOLE SCENARIO.
>> YES, THEY FILM THE MOVIES IN
THE SUMMER.
THEY SAID IT'S SO HOT.
FUN FACT, THEY USE CHIPPED ICE
THAT YOU WOULD SEE IN A FISH
MARKET, TO DO THE SNOW.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
>> I'M THE ODD MAN OUT.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN --
>> I HADN'T, NOW I'M ADDICTED.
EVEN MY HUSBAND SAID LET'S TURN
ON HALLMARK CHRISTMAS.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>>> AHEAD IN "WHAT TO WATCH,"
HOW TOM HANKS IS TRYING TO MAKE
SOCIAL MEDIA LITTLE BIT NICER.
>> AWW.
>> CAN WE DO THAT?
>>> THIS PORTION OF "CBS THIS
MORNING" SORRY TOED BY --
(VO) Imagine a visibly
healthier pet
in 28 days.
Purina ONE.
Natural ingredients
in powerful combinations.
For radiant coats,
sparkling eyes.
Purina ONE.
ONE visibly
healthy pet.
Try New Digestive Health with
probiotics for dogs.
Why do wrinkles happen at the
worst times?
Showing up here
Here
And even here?
With new Bounce Rapid Touch Up
Spray,
you can fight wrinkles anywhere.
Spray
Smooth
And you're fresh and ready to go
wherever you are.
New Bounce Rapid Touch Up Spray.
Bounce out wrinkles anywhere.
♪ Life is Better With You
by Michael Franti ♪
♪ Life is better with you ♪
♪ Whoa whoa ♪
♪
♪ I know just one thing
is true... ♪
♪ Life is better with you ♪
♪
Skin Sin #17...
Too many after-parties.
New Neutrogena® Bright Boost
with dullness-fighting
Neoglucosamine.
Boosts cell turnover by 10 times
for instantly brighter skin.
Bright Boost Neutrogena®.
♪ ♪
Oh, ho!
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
You... You got me.
Uh, what do you want?
I've got uh, AI robots,
I've got VR goggles.
I want your sled, please.
No.
[ chuckles ]
Timmy.
It'd be a shame if
this went viral.
For those who never compromise.
The Mercedes-Benz Winter Event.
Whoa.
He was pretty
good this year.
>>> ALL RIGHT, GET THOSE TURKEYS
IN THE OVEN.
VLAD DUTHIERS IS BRINGING THE
HEAT.
>> WHOA.
>> GEEZ.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING, FAM.
>> YOU, TOO.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HERE ARE STORIES WE THINK YOU'LL
BE TALKING ABOUT TODAY -- SINCE
JANUARY, I.C.E. HAS ARRESTED
ABOUT 250 FOREIGN STUDENTS AT A
FAKE UNIVERSITY IN MICHIGAN.
IT'S PART OF A STING OPERATION
BY FERDERAL AGENTS.
THE UNIVERSITY OF FARMINGTON WAS
OPENED IN 2015 AS A GUISE BY
I.C.E. OFFICIALS.
IT ENTICED FOREIGN-BORN STUDENTS
MOSTLY FROM INDIA WHO HAD
ARRIVED LEGALLY IN THE UNITED
STATES ON LEGITIMATE STUDENT
VISAS.
BUT THE GOVERNMENT SAYS THE
PHONY UNIVERSITY WAS A
PAY-TO-PLAY SCHEME THE STUDENTS
USE TODAY TO REMAIN IN THE
UNITED STATES UNDER A STUDENT
VISA.
SOME OF THE STUDENTS WERE
ARRESTED AND DEPORTED WHILE
OTHERS AWAIT TRIAL IN THE UNITED
STATES.
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE CRITICIZED
I.C.E. BECAUSE OF THEIR GROWING
POWER.
THE GOVERNMENT SAYS THE STUDENTS
SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT THIS WAS
NOT A REAL UNIVERSITY.
THAT THEY WERE JUST USING IT TO
HAVE A STUDENT VISA TO STAY IN
UNITED STATES.
>> THAT'S HOW A LOT OF STUDENTS
COME IN.
THE STUDENT VISA.
>>> WE KNOW TWITTER CAN BE
NASTY.
THOSE OF US IN THE NEWS BUSINESS
KNOW IT CAN BE NASTY PLACE.
OSCAR WINNER TOM HANKS WHO PLAYS
MR. ROGERS IN HIS LATEST MOVIE
IS MAKING IT A WHOLE LOT NICER.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
>> I'M GOING TO READ SOME OF THE
NICEST TWEETS ON THE INTERNET.
I WORKED AT McDONALD'S FOR 2 1/2
YEARS, AND I PUT 11 NUGGETS IN
ALMOST EVERY TEN-PIECE I MADE.
THAT IS A MAN WHO'S NOT ONLY
BEING NICE, BUT HE'S FEEDING THE
WORLD.
AN OLD LADY TOOK A PHOTO OF MY
CAT CHIPS, WENT TO THE TROUBLE
OF GETTING IT DEVELOPED AND PUT
THEM IN OUR LETTER BOX THIS
MORNING.
FOR YOU, YOUR LOVELY CAT, I
ALWAYS LOOK FOR HIM, JEAN.
OH, MY LORD.
WHO DOESN'T LOVE CATS?
>> THIS IS -- THIS HAS RACKED UP
3.8 MILLION VIEWS.
>> OH, MY.
>> PEOPLE LOVE IT.
>> HE'S PLAYING MR. ROGERS, SO
YOU KNOW --
>> SOMETHING ABOUT PETS, THOUGH.
ANY TIME PEOPLE TALK ABOUT PETS
ON SOCIAL MEDIA, IT'S THE NICEST
YOU'VE SEEN.
>> IT IS.
WHAT'S THE NAME.
YOUR DOG?
>> PADDINGTON --
>> THAT'S THE GREATEST NAME.
I WANT TO READ THAT NEXT WEEK.
>> HE'S GOING TO BE HERE IN
ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
>> SNAP.
CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT.
MAYBE HE CAN DO "WHAT TO WATCH."
A DOG'S LIFE.
>>> MORE NOW THANKSGIVING FOR
YOU.
A FRIENDSHIP FORGED OVER A WRONG
TEXT MESSAGE YEARS AGO IS STILL
GOING STRONG.
SO IT HAPPENED BACK IN 2016
AFTER A GRANDMA IN ARIZONA
INVITED A THEN-STRANGER TO
THANKSGIVING DINNER.
HER NAME IS WANDA DENCH.
SHE MEANT TO SEND IT TO HER
GRANDSON.
INSTEAD, JAMAL HINTON GOT THE
MESSAGE.
HE THEN ASKED, WE HAVE THE TWEET
UP, ASKED CAN I STILL GET A
PLATE, THOUGH?
SHE SAID, OF COURSE.
AND THE PAIR HIT IT OFF.
AND FOR THE PAST THREE YEARS,
THEY HAVE SPENT EVERY
THANKSGIVING TOGETHER.
THE PAIR SAYS IT HAS TAUGHT THEM
TO BE GRATEFUL FOR THE
UNEXPECTED.
DENCH AND HINTON ARE
COMMEMORATING THEIR FOURTH
THANKSGIVING DINNER TOGETHER.
AND THIS YEAR HINTON INVITED
DENCH AND HER HUSBAND TO
CELEBRATE WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND'S
FAMILY.
>> I LOVE THAT.
LIKE THE "A MORE PERFECT UNION"
STUFF THAT YOU DO --
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
>>> AHEAD, WE'LL TALK WITH THE
HOST OF THE CBS THIS MORNING
PARADE COVERAGE.
STAY WITH US.
en 2PM Thursday.
Save on boots...Keurig®...
diamond jewelry...plus 40% off
Levi's® jeans
for him and her!
Sale ends Saturday!
JCPenney!
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately to
severely active Crohn's disease,
Sale ends Saturday!
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed relief
and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house needs
or recently had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how Janssen can help
you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start with
STELARA®.
Fact! Coffee stains teeth.
Unlike ordinary whitening
toothpaste,
Colgate Optic White has hydrogen
peroxide
that goes below the tooth's
surface
for a smile that's 4 shades
visibly whiter.
Colgate Optic White. Whitening
that works.
It's time to make
mopping history.
Introducing the new
Braava jet m6 robot mop.
With an adjustable precision jet
spray and advanced pad system
Braava jet breaks up messes
and gets deep in corners.
Braava jet.
Only from iRobot.
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
I'm your Mother in Law.
And I like to question your
every move.
Like this left turn.
It's the next one.
You always drive this slow?
How did you make someone I love?
That must be why you're always
so late.
I do not speed.
And that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
My son, he did say that you were
the safe option.
And that's the nicest thing you
ever said to me.
So get Allstate.
Stop bossing.
Where good drivers save 40% for
avoiding mayhem, like me.
This is my son's favorite color,
you should try it.
[Mayhem] You always drive like
an old lady?
[Tina] You're an old lady.
He could've just been the middle
class kid who made good.
But Mike Bloomberg became the
guy who did good.
After building a business that
created thousands of jobs
he took charge of a city still
reeling from 9/11
a three-term mayor who helped
bring it back from the ashes
bringing jobs and thousands of
affordable housing
units with it.
After witnessing the terrible
toll of gun violence...
he helped create a movement
to protect
families across America.
And stood up to the coal
lobby and this administration
to protect this planet from
climate change.
And now, he's taking on...
him. To rebuild a country
and restore faith in the
dream that defines us.
Where the wealthy will
pay more in taxes
and the middle class get
their fair share.
Everyone without health
insurance can get it
and everyone who likes
theirs keep it.
And where jobs won't just help
you get by, but get ahead.
And on all those things
Mike Blomberg intends to make
good.
Jobs Creator. Leader.
Problem Solver.
Mike Bloomberg for President.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
>>> IT'S THANKSGIVING DAY DAY,
THURSDAY, NOVEMBER 28TH, 2019.
WELCOME BACK TO "CBS THIS
MORNING".
GAYLE, TONY, AND ANTHONY ALL OF
THEM OFF.
I'M MICHELLE MILLER.
AHEAD, THE LATEST FROM THE
MACY'S THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE
WHERE THE WIND WILL DECIDE WHAT
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE SEE.
>>> GOOD MORNING TO, YOU I'M
DIFFERENT BEGNAUD.
SEE HOW THIS GAME-WINNING BASKET
IS HELPING A FAMILY DEVASTATED
BY THE HURRICANE IN THE BAHAMAS.
>>> AND I'M JERICKA DUNCAN.
BILL HCOWHER WILL BE HERE WITH
THE LATEST ACTION.
>>> FIRST, THIS MORNING'S "EYE
OPENER."
>> CONCERNS ABOUT THE WEATHER
MAY LEAVE AMERICANS WITHOUT ONE
OF THE MOST FAMILIAR SITES OF
THIS HOLIDAY.
>> THIS IS A SPECIAL DAY, I'M
EXCITED TO SEE THESE BALLOONS
GET UP AS MY FIRST THANKSGIVING
PARADE HERE IN NEW YORK CITY.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
THESE ARE LARGE BALLOONS RIGHT
HERE.
THEY CAN GET BALLOON AROUND
EASILY.
OTHERWISE, IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
>> Reporter: THIS COUNTS AS THE
13th PROJECTILE LAUNCH BY FLAE
THIS YEAR.
SEOUL -- NORTH KOREA THIS YEAR.
SEW SAID THE PROJECTILES WERE
LAUNCHED FROM A PROVINCE ON THE
NORTHEAST COAST.
>> Reporter: A MASSIVE FIRE IS
STILL BURNING IN SOUTHERN TEXAS
AFTER AN EXPLOSION AT A CHEMICAL
PLANT.
A SECOND BLAST RATTLED THE CITY
OF PORT NECHES YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON.
>> LIT UP THE ENTIRE SKY.
>> Reporter: GIULIANI'S PURSUITS
IN UKRAINE AND HOW MUCH OF THEM
UNFOLDED WITH THE PRESIDENT'S
KNOWLEDGE ARE CENTRAL TO THE
HOUSE IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY INTO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>>> I'M BRITISH, WE DON'T DO
THANKSGIVING.
THIS IS ALL FAIRLY NEW TO ME.
BRITS GIVE THANKS THE SAME WAY
WE EXPRESS LOVE -- BY SIPPING
TEA AND AVOIDING EYE CONTACT.
>>> THIS MORNING'S "EYE OPENER"
IS PRESENTED BY BROUGHT TO YOU
BY TOYOTA -- LET'S GO PLACES.
>>> LET'S GO.
WELCOME BACK, AND HAPPY
THANKSGIVING TO ALL OF YOU.
AS AMERICANS GET READY FOR
TURKEY DAY DINNERS, LUNCHES,
MANY OF US WILL NOT BE GIVING
THANKS TO THE WEATHER.
ANOTHER POWERFUL SYSTEM BRINGING
HEAVY SNOW AND STRONG WINDS TO
MUCH OF THE WESTERN U.S.
THAT STORM WILL TRAVEL COAST TO
COAST THROUGHOUT THE WEEKEND,
AFFECTING THE ROCKIES, PLAINS,
GREAT LAKES, AND FINALLY THE
EAST COAST.
THAT SHOULD BE BY SUNDAY.
>> THERE ARE -- THERE ARE SOME
STRONG GUSTY WINDS IN THE EAST
TODAY.
THEY COULD AFFECT THE MACY'S
THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
CBS NEWS CLIMATE AND WEATHER
CONTRIBUTOR, JEFF BERARDELLI,
JOINS US WITH A LOOK AT THE
HOLIDAY FORECAST.
JEFF, HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING TO YOU AND
TO ALL OF YOU AT HOME.
SO THE GOOD NEWS IN THE EAST AT
LEAST IS THAT THE STORM IS
BEGINNING TO WIND DOWN.
A LITTLE SNOW AND RAIN WAY UP
NORTH.
THE WIND IS THE BIGGEST STORY IF
YOU'RE FLYING TODAY.
COULD BE ON THE BUMPY SIDE.
REALLY THE BIGGEST STORY IS A
HUGE STORM, THIS WAS A BOMB
CYCLONE, RAMMED INTO THE OREGON
COAST WITH WINDS OF 110 MILES
PER HOUR.
TROPICAL MOISTURE IS PRODUCING A
TON OF RAIN AND SNOW.
LOOK AT ALL THIS POWDER FOR
SKIERS.
ONE, TWO, THREE FEET OF SNOW,
AND A VERY JEALOUS WEATHERMAN
THAT I'M NOT OUT THERE RIGHT
NOW.
SO DAY BY DAY, THIS IS THE
SITUATION TODAY.
WATCH WHAT HAPPENS TOMORROW.
LOOK AT ALL THAT SNOW IN THE
WEST.
FLOODING DOWN SOUTH, THE DEEP
SOUTHWEST.
AND ALL-OUT BLIZZARD, RAPID
CITY, FARGO, EVENTUALLY TURNS TO
SNOW IN MINNEAPOLIS.
IT BECOMES AN ICE STORM, AN ICE
STORM IN THE EAST AS WE HEAD
INTO SUNDAY.
THEN MAYBE A NOR'EASTER WITH
HEAVY INLAND SNOW AS WE HEAD
INTO MONDAY.
SO IT'S GOING TO KEEP ME BUSY AS
A WEATHERMAN.
FOR EVERYBODY TRAVELING ACROSS
THE COUNTRY, THIS IS GOING TO BE
A TOUGH COUPLE OF DAYS AHEAD.
>> SURE IS.
JEFF, THANK YOU.
>>> AN ESTIMATED 3.5 MILLION
SPECTATORS WILL BE ALONG THE
ROUTE OF TODAY'S 93rd MACY'S
THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE IF
THEY'LL GET TO SEE THE
WORLD-FAMOUS BALLOONS, BUT SO
FAR THINGS ARE GOING AS PLANNED.
THE PARADE BEGINS ALONG THE WEST
SIDE OF CENTRAL PARK AND HEADS
DOWNTOWN, ENDING AT 34th STREET
IN HAROLD SQUARE.
ERROL BARNETT IS AT THE
BEGINNING OF THE 2.5-MILE ROUTE.
ERROL, HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
I KNOW IT'S YOUR FIRST.
>> Reporter: IT IS MY FIRST
THANKSGIVING HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY, MICHELLE.
I CAN TELL YOU, BRITISH FOLKS
ENJOY THANKSGIVING HERE IN THE
U.S. JUST FINE.
AND THERE IS PLENTY OF
EXCITEMENT IN THE AIR BEHIND ME.
YOU SEE A MARCHING BAND FROM
BALTIMORE, MARYLAND.
AND EVERYONE IS READY FOR THIS
TO GET GOING.
THE THOUGHT ON EVERYONE'S MIND,
THOUGH, IS WILL THE WORLD-FAMOUS
BALLOONS FLY?
THEY WERE INFLATED LAST NIGHT.
AS OF NOW, THEY ARE SCHEDULED TO
FLY.
THE NYPD, THOUGH, CAN STILL CALL
THEM OFF IF WIND GUSTS DO GET
ABOVE 34 MILES PER HOUR OR IF
THEY DETECT SUSTAINED WINDS
ABOVE 23 MILES PER HOUR.
NOW AMONG THE AMAZING SIGHTS AND
SOUNDS DURING THE PARADE ARE 11
MARCHING BANDS FROM ACROSS THE
COUNTRY, ALSO 34 FLOATS
INCLUDING A NEW LEGO FLOAT, VERY
CLOSE TO MY HEART.
THAT IS AMONG FIVE OF THE NEW
FLOATS THIS YEAR.
AND THERE ARE ALSO 16 GIANT
CHARACTER BALLOONS READY TO
ROLL.
AND GET THIS -- ONE OF THE
CHIEF, THE CHIEF OF PATROL TOLD
ME YESTERDAY HIS FAVORITE WILL
BE THE TRIUMPHANT RETURN OF
SNOOPY DRESSED AS AN ASTRONAUT.
THAT IS TO COMMEMORATE THE 50th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE MOON LANDING.
AND ON A MORE SERIOUS NOTE, THE
NYPD SAYS THERE ARE NO KNOWN
SERIOUS THREATS AT THIS MOMENT.
BUT OF COURSE, WE'VE GOT
THOUSANDS OF OFFICERS ALL ALONG
THE PARADE ROUTE READY TO ACT
SHOULD SOMETHING TAKE PLACE.
AND AS FOR THE PARADE ITSELF, IT
WILL FEATURE A FAMOUS TRADITION
WITH SANTA CLAUS TOWARD THE END.
SO YOU'LL WANT TO GET THE KIDS
NEAR THE TV AND READY TO SEE
SANTA FOR THE FIRST TIME THIS
SEASON.
>> ERROL, WE LOVE THAT BAND
BEHIND YOU.
IT'S NOT TOO COLD OUT THERE, IS
IT?
>> Reporter: NO, IT'S NOT TOO
BAD.
IT'S PRETTY MODERATE.
THESE GUYS WERE JAMMING MOMENTS
AGO.
THERE'S SO MUCH TALENT AND
ENTHUSIASM UP AND DOWN THIS
PARADE ROUTE.
QUITE SPECIAL FOR ME TO BE HERE,
FOLKS.
>> THANK YOU, MY FRIEND.
>> Reporter: I'LL TAKE VIDEOS
AND CLIPS FOR YOU GUYS.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
CBS HAS BROADCAST THE PARADE FOR
59 YEARS.
YOU CAN SEE THE THANKSGIVING DAY
DAY PARADE ON CBS RIGHT AFTER
"CBS THIS MORNING."
YOU'LL BE IN GOOD HANDS.
KEVIN FRAZIER AND KELTIE KNIGHT
ARE BACK HOSTING THE BROADCAST.
AND I WILL SEE THEM A LITTLE BIT
LATER WHEN I APPEAR ON THEIR
SHOW.
THEY JOIN US FROM THE PARADE
ROUTE RIGHT NOW.
GUYS, WHERE ARE YOU EXACTLY
ALONG THE ROUTE?
>> WE'RE AT 6th AVENUE AND 53rd,
RIGHT ACROSS FROM THE HILTON.
YOU CAN SEE THE HILTON IN THE
BACKGROUND.
I MEAN, WE HAVE A BEAUTIFUL
SPOT.
WE KNOW YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY.
WE'RE WAITING ON YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING TO HOLD UP
THE PARADE IF YOU DON'T GET HERE
SOON.
MICHELLE CAN HANDLE EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE GO WAY BACK.
>> WAY BACK.
>> YEAH, WE DO.
>> TELL US ALL ABOUT THAT.
>> WHAT YOU GOT PLANNED?
>> Reporter: GUYS, WELL, MIRANDA
LAMBERT IS COMING BY TO PERFORM.
THAT WILL BE ONE OF THE THINGS.
THAT'S GOING TO BE EXCITING.
A COUPLE OF THE BROADWAY SHOWS
--
>> THE BROADWAY CAST OF "MEAN
GIRLS" WILL BE PERFORMING.
AND WE ARE JUST SO EXCITED.
50 MILLION PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
BE TUNING IN TO WATCH AROUND THE
WORLD.
3.5 MILLION FANS LINING THE
STREETS.
WE WERE DOWN EARLY THIS MORNING,
WE HAD PEOPLE FROM FLORIDA, FROM
DETROIT.
EVERYONE'S BRAVING THE COLD.
>> HAWAII.
>> VERY, VERY COOL.
THE PARADE IS IN ITS 93rd YEAR
THIS YEAR.
IT'S JUST SUCH A SPECIAL HOLIDAY
TRADITION.
IT REALLY KICKS OFF THE HOLIDAY
SEASON.
AND I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
THERE IS SO FESTIVE, YOU KNOW.
>> LISTEN, HERE'S THE DEAL, GUYS
-- ALL THESE PEOPLE COME OUT
HERE EARLY IN THE MORNING, THEY
GET A PRIME SPOT.
THEY WANT TO SEE THE BALLOONS
FLY.
WE HOPE THEY ARE FLYING TODAY,
AND THAT'S THE BIG, BIG THING.
YOU HAVE FOLKS FROM AROUND THE
WORLD, EVERY ONE OF THE 50
STATES.
BY THE WAY, FOR YOU AT HOME,
JUST SIT TIGHT.
CURL UP WITH A BLANKET.
STAY IN YOUR PAJAMAS.
BUT PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE SE
SENSENDS
-- SEND A MESSAGE USING TDAYCBS,
AND MAYBE YOU'LL MAKE THE BR
BROADCAST.
>> I WANT TO SEE BABIES WITH
FUNNY HATS, DOGS WITH COSTUMES,
AND LOTS OF FOOD.
KEVIN LIKES THE FOOD.
I LIKE THE DOGS IN FUNNY
COSTUMES.
>> AS SOMEONE WHO'S BEEN THERE
WATCHING LIVE AND IN PERSON, I
HAVE TO TELL YOU THE BEST SEAT
IN THE HOUSE IS IN FRONT OF YOUR
TV SET.
RIGHT THERE.
>> TOUCHE.
>> YOU KNOW WE'RE GOING TO ASK
--
>> OR RIGHT HERE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO YOU ASK, IT'S
THANKSGIVING, WHAT ARE YOU
THANKFUL FOR?
>> SURE.
>> KEVIN --
>> LISTEN, FIRST OF ALL, ALWAYS
THANKFUL FOR MY FAMILY AND
GETTING TO SPEND THIS TIME WITH
MY ENTIRE FAMILY WHO'S HERE
TODAY.
BUT JUST BEING HERE.
RY LOVE DOING THIS.
>> IT'S A REALLY SPECIAL THING.
I'M THANKFUL FOR KINEVIN FRAZIE.
>> WE WORK CLOSELY, LIKE A
LITTLE FAMILY.
IF WE COULD TURN THE CAMERA
AROUND, YOU WOULD SEE EVERY--
>> THE WHOLE CREW.
>> SAME CREW EACH AND EVERY
YEAR.
>> AND TO GET TO SPEND
THANKSGIVING WITH THIS CREW.
IT'S COOL.
>> KEVIN SAY HI TO YASMINE FOR
ME.
>> SAVE US SOME FOOD.
>> I WILL.
COME ON DOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SHOUT OUT TO YOUR CREW AND
OUR CREW.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
WE WILL SEE YOU SOON ON THE
ROUTE.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> GET DOWN HERE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AGAIN, YOU CAN WATCH THE
THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE HERE ON
CBS JUST AFTER "CTM."
>>> IT'S BEING CALLED ONE OF THE
BIGGEST UPSETS EVER IN COLLEGE
BASKETBALL.
AHEAD HOW THE WINNING BASKET IS
NOW HELPING A PLAYER'S FAMILY
REBUILD THEIR HOME DESTROYED IN
A HURRIC
>>> THERE'S MUCH MORE AHEAD.
THANKSGIVING IT ALWAYS MEANS
FOOTBALL.
SO BILL COWHER OF CBS SPORTS
WILL PREVIEW THE NFL ACTION.
PLUS, THE BEST THINGS TO BUY ON
BLACK FRIDAY AND THE EXTRA
ADVANTAGE OF SHOPPING ON LINE
AFTER THANKSGIVING.
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING "CBS THIS
MORNING."
TREMFYA® helps adults with
moderate to severe
plaque psoriasis uncover
clearer skin that can last.
In fact, TREMFYA® was proven
superior to Humira®
in providing significantly
clearer skin.
TREMFYA® may increase your
risk of infections
and lower your ability
to fight them.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or symptoms or if you had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
TREMFYA®. Uncover clearer skin
that can last.
Janssen can help you explore
cost support options.
♪ ♪
Only Roomba i7+ uses two
multi-surface rubber brushes.
And picks up more pet hair
than other robot vacuums.
And the filter captures 99%
of dog and cat allergens.
If it's not from iRobot,
it's not a Roomba™.
TOM STEYER: Wall Street Banks
took advantage
of millions of Americans during
the recession.
So, my wife Kat and I took
action.
We started a non-profit
community bank
with a simple theory -
give people a fair deal and real
economic power.
Invest in the community,
in businesses owned by women and
people of color,
in affordable housing.
The difference between words
and actions matters.
That's a lesson politicians
in Washington could
use right now.
I'm Tom Steyer, and I
approve this message.
Mucinex Cold & Flu All-In-One.
Fights...
Oh no. No-no-no.
Did you really need the caps
lock?
Mucinex Cold and Flu All-In-One.
♪
Good lunch?
Amazin'!
Toyota. Let's go places.
>>> SPORTS FANS ARE STILL
BUZZING ABOUT ONE OF THE BIGGEST
UPSETS IN COLLEGE BASKETBALL
HISTORY.
THIS GAME-WINNING SHOT GAVE
STEPHEN F.-AUSTIN STATE
UNIVERSITY VICTORY OVER
NUMBER-ONE RANKED DUKE ON THEIR
COURT THIS WEEK.
STEPHEN F.-AUSTIN WAS RANKED
264th ACCORDING TO ONE WIDELY
WATCHED RANKING.
NATHAN BAIN, THE PLAYER WHO
SCORED THE WINNING BASKET, WON
BIG FOR MORE THAN JUST HIS TEAM.
>> THEY GOT IT -- THEY DON'T USE
IT -- BAIN!
YES!
THE LUMBERJACKS HAVE DONE IT!
>> Reporter: NATHAN BAIN'S
BREAKAWAY LAY-UP WITH .1 SECONDS
LEFT IN OVERTIME WAS A SHOCKER
TO END ALL SHOCKERS.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE THE
BIGGEST WIN IN PROGRAM HISTORY!
>> Reporter: THE STEPHEN
F.-AUSTIN UNIVERSITY LUMBERJACKS
FROM NACOGDOCHES, TEXAS, WENT
INTO THE GAME AS THE UNDERDOG.
THEY UPSET DUKE IN NORTH
CAROLINA, SNAPPING THE BLUE
DEVILS' 150-GAME HOME COURT WIN
STREAK AGAINST NONCONFERENCE
OPPONENTS.
>> NATHAN BAIN, THIS IS YOUR
LIFE!
>> Reporter: THAT BUZZER BEATER
WAS TRULY HISTORY IN THE MAKING.
>> JUST FELT LIKE IT WAS IN SLOW
MOTION.
I MEAN, BY THE TIME I PUT IT UP,
THE BUZZER WENT OFF.
>> Reporter: TO TEAMMATES, THE
WIN WAS A POINT OF PRIDE.
TO HIS FAMILY IT WAS A MIRACLE.
>> THINGS CHANGED FROM THE
HURRICANE.
>> Reporter: THEY LOST ALMOST
EVERYTHING WHEN HURRICANE DORIAN
HIT THE BAHAMAS IN SEPTEMBER
DESTROYING THEIR HOME AND HIS
FATHER'S CHURCH.
>> THEY'RE STILL UP, THEY'RE
GIVING PRAYERS TO GOD.
>> Reporter: THE UNIVERSITY SAID
UP A GOFUNDME PAGE TO HELP WITH
RECOVERY.
BEFORE THE GAME, THERE WERE
ABOUT $2,000 IN DONATIONS.
>> CAME TO BASICALLY A COMPLETE
STOP, YOU KNOW.
SO, YOU KNOW, GOT DISCOURAGED.
REGIME AFTER THE LAY-UP AND
BAIN'S NEWFOUND FAME, THE SITE
RAISED MORE THAN DOUBLE THE
ORIGINAL $50,000 GOAL.
MONEY THAT WILL HELP BAIN'S
FAMILY REBUILD.
>> NOT WALNONCE DID I CORRELATE
WINNING THE GAME WOULD HELP THE
GOFUNDME.
IT'S ANOTHER BLESSING WITH
WINNING.
>> Reporter: THE GOFUNDME
DONATIONS WILL GO TOWARD THE
CHURCH AND THE SCHOOL THAT HIS
FAMILY RUNS IN THE BAHAMAS WHICH
MANY PEOPLE DEPEND ON.
HIS TEAM'S INCREDIBLE WIN HAS
PUT THE SPOTLIGHT ON THE
POST-DORIAN RELIEF EFFORTS.
AS OF LATE OCTOBER, THERE WAS A
TOTAL OF $3.4 BILLION IN LOSSES
FOR THE BAHAMAS.
SO THE HOPE IS, YOU KNOW --
>> THE ATTENTION THERE, TOO.
THERE IT IS.
>> I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE,
NUMBER 23 IN THAT MOMENT --
MICHAEL JORDAN, YOU KNOW.
HE HAD NUMBER 23.
>> WOW.
>> I'M THINKING --
>> GO TO SEE THAT.
I CHECKED THE GOFUNDME PAGE IT
HAS $113,000 --
>> $2,000 TO $113,000.
SOMEBODY'S THANKFUL.
>>> FOOTBALL WILL BE AT THE
CENTER OF MANY FAMILY GATHERINGS
THIS THANKSGIVING.
GO, SAINTS, GO, SAINTS.
>> GO, SAINTS!
>> CALM DOWN WITH ALL THAT.
>> CBS SPORTS ANALYST BILL
COWHER IS HERE WITH A PREVIEW OF
THE MATCHUPS AND WHAT
THANKSGIVING MEANS FOR THE
PLAYERS AND COACHES.
YOU'RE WATCHING "CBS THIS
MORNING."
COME ON BACK.
>>> THIS IS COLONEL ANDER,
COMMAND SERGEANT MAJOR HILL.
>> THIS IS THE 1118 TSV HERE IN
BEAUTIFUL KUWAIT.
>> WE WANT TO TAKE A MOMENT TO
PAUSE TO SAY THANK YOU.
>> THIS HOLIDAY SEASON, WE WISH
YOU GUEST OF HEALTH.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING!
>>> MANY FAMILIES WILL BE
FOCUSED ON THANKSGIVING FOOTBALL
TODAY AS WELL AS TURKEY.
THE BUFFALO BILLS AND DALLAS
COWBOYS WILL FACE OFF IN A
CRUCIAL GAME.
YOU CAN SEE IT RIGHT HERE ON
CBS.
FORMER PITTSBURGH STEELERS HEAD
COACH AND CBS SPORTS NFL ANALYST
BILL COWHER JOINS US RIGHT HERE
AT THE TABLE WITH WHAT WE CAN
EXPECT.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING, MICHELLE,
DAVID, JERICKA.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YEAH.
>> BIG GAME HERE BETWEEN DALLAS
AND THE BILLS.
BILLS --
>> YEAH --
>> FANS HERE.
>> YOU GOT TO GIVE IT TO THE
BILLS.
TH PLAYOFFS STARTED .
HEEY WOULD BE THE NUER-ONE.YOU R
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE TEAM
THAT'S 9-2, MAYBE A HISTORICAL
PACE, MICHAEL THOMAS IS IT AS A
RECEIVER.
WE'LL AWE KNOW DREW BREES IS
THERE.
IT WOULD BE IDEAL TO SEE A DREW
BREES-TOM BRADY MATCH-UP.
>> I'D LOVE IT.
>> BUT THERE'S A COUPLE OF
THINGS TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE SAN FRANCISCO AND
BALTIMORE.
LAMAR JACKSON, THE KIND OF YEAR
HE IS HAVING.
GREAT STORY LINES THROUGHOUT THE
NFL.
>> ALL EYES WERE ON THE REFS
LAST YEAR.
THEY REALLY HAVE TO CRUNCH IT
DOWN.
MAKE THE RIGHT CALLS.
>> I THINK OFFICIATING IS ALWAYS
GOING TO BE A PART OF THE GAME.
AGAIN, IT'S SUCH -- IT'S A
CONTACT GAME.
IT'S A LOT OF TIMES, IT'S SO
QUICK.
WE SLOW IT DOWN TO FRAME TO
FRAME, WHAT WE SEE FROM THAT
STANDPOINT.
THESE OFFICIALS ARE OUT IN GAME
SPEED, I THINK OVERALL THEY DO A
PRETTY GOOD JOB.
>> THEY'RIZE I EASY TO BEAT UP.
YOU SPENT THE LAST 40 YEARS,
STARTING THANKSGIVING EVERY DAY
WITH FOOTBALL.
>> FOOTBALL.
THERE'S FOOTBALL AND FAMILY.
A LOT OF TIMES IT WAS THE FAMILY
I WAS WORKING WITH.
WHETHER IT WAS A FOOTBALL TEAM
IN THE LAST 13 YEARS WITH THE
CBS FAMILY THAT WE HAVE HERE, SO
YOU KNOW, FAMILY HAS BEEN IN THE
FOREFRONT AS LONG AS FOOTBALL
WAS THERE.
AND YOU KNOW, YOU THINK ABOUT
THANKSGIVING, YOU KNOW, DAVID, I
ALWAYS THINK ABOUT THE ABILITY
TO PUT THINGS BACK INTO
PERSPECTIVE.
AND YOU KNOW COULD YOU THINK
ABOUT FAMILY.
I ALWAYS ENCOURAGE THE PLAYER
WHEN I WAS COACHING JUST TO TAKE
SOME TIME TO GIVE THANKS TO THE
PEOPLE THAT HAVE HELPED YOU BE
HERE, SITTING IN THIS CHAIR.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES WE TAKE IT
FOR GRANTED.
BUT IT'S THE PEOPLE ALONG THE
WAY THAT GAVE US OUR CHANCE,
GAVE US THE OPPORTUNITY.
>> BELIEVED IN US.
>> YEAH.
AND SO I THINK IT'S ABOUT
PERSPECTIVE WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
THANKSGIVING.
>> YEAH.
>> SO COACH, FOR THE
NON-FOOTBALL FANS WHO ARE --
>> YEAH --
>> I'M NOT A NON-FOOTBALL FAN.
BUT WHAT DO YOU TELL THEM?
WHO SHOULD THEY ROOT FOR?
I WOULD SAY THE BILLS.
I WOULD SAY THE BILLS --
>> WE WOULD SAY THE SAME.
>> I THINK WHEN YOU WATCH THE
GAME, TRADITIONALLY IT GOES BACK
SO FAR.
EVERYONE HAS THEIR OWN TEAM.
WHETHER IT BE THE SAINTS,
WHETHER IT BE THE BILLS.
DALLAS HAS CALLED THEMSELVES
AMERICA'S TEAM FOR SO MANY
YEARS.
I'VE PLAYED IN THIS GAME BEFORE.
WE PLAYED THE DETROIT LIONS.
AGAIN, I THINK WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT, IT'S ABOUT JUST, YOU
KNOW, STAY WITH YOUR TEAM.
YOU KNOW, SUPPORT YOUR TEAM.
>> BE LOYAL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I'M SO EXCITED FOR THE BILLS.
FOUR SUPER BOWLS, AND THEY NEVER
WON.
NOW THEY'RE 8-3.
>> HER BILLS RIGHT HERE --
>> JOSH ALLEN IS HAVING A VERY,
VERY GOOD YEAR RIGHT NOW.
>> HE IS.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
COACH, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BILL COWHER AND THE NFL
TEAMMATES WILL KICK OFF COVERAGE
THIS AFTERNOON FOLLOWED BY THE
BILLS-COWBOYS GAME RIGHT HERE ON
CBS.
>>> AHEAD, HOW TO FIND THE BEST
HOLIDAY SHOPPING DEALS AND WHEN
TO BUY.
YOUR LOCAL NEWS IS NEXT.
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
To the outside world,
you look good,
but you don't feel good.
With polycythemia vera,
PV, symptoms can change
so slowly over time
you might not notice.
But new or changing symptoms
can mean your PV is changing.
Let's change the way we see PV.
You track and discuss blood
counts with your doctor.
But it's just as vital
to discuss
changing symptoms as well.
Take notice and take action.
Discuss counts and symptoms
with your doctor.
Visit TakeActionPV.com
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "CBS THIS
MORNING."
IT'S TIME TO BRING YOU SOME OF
THE STORIES THAT ARE THE "TALK
OF THE TABLE" THIS MORNING.
THIS IS WHERE WE EACH PICK A
STORY WE'D LIKE TO SHARE WITH
EACH OTHER AND ALL OF YOU, OF
COURSE.
AND JERICKA, SHE'S GOING TO
START US OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS PRETTY INTERESTING.
YOU KNOW, AMAZON'S VOICE
ASSISTANT ALEXA IS ACTUALLY
SOUNDING MORE HUMAN THAN EVER
BEFORE.
ALEXA IS NOW ABLE TO RESPOND
WITH AN EXCITED TONE WHICH COULD
BE USED WHEN YOU ANSWER A TRIVIA
QUESTION CORRECTLY.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I'M PLAYING A SINGLE HAND IN
WHAT LOOKS LIKE A LOSING GAME.
>> OR ALEXA CAN USE A
DISAPPOINTED TONE FOR THOSE
TIMES WHEN YOUR FAVORITE SPORTS
TEAM LOSES.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> I'M PLAYING A SINGLE HAND IN
WHAT LOOKS LIKE A LOSING GAME.
>> IT'S THE FIRST TIME AMAZON IS
ADDING A LAYER OF FEELINGS TO
ALEXA.
TESTS SHOW THAT PEOPLE LIKE THE
NEW SPEAKING STYLE MORE THAN HER
STANDARD MONOTONE VOICE.
EXPERTS SAY IT WILL ALSO HELP
SPEED UP HOW FAST PEOPLE ADOPT
ALEXA IN THEIR DAILY ROUTINES.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT I WANT HER
HAVING EMOTION.
I FEEL LIKE SHE'S TALKING BACK
TO ME.
>> YEAH.
KIND OF SPOOKY.
>> A LITTLE SASSY.
YOU?
>> I DON'T HAVE -- I DON'T EVEN
USE THOSE.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN THAT STUFF
BECAUSE I'M LIKE, I DON'T -- BIG
BROTHER.
BIG BROTHER.
I THINK IT IS PRETTY COOL.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> I'M WITH YOU --
>> SHE SOUNDS ROBOTIC RIGHT NOW.
WHAT YOU GOT?
>> I LIKE HER THAT WAY.
>>> ASTRONOMERS -- GET THIS --
IN CHINA MADE A BIG SURPRISING
DISCOVERY.
A MASSIVE BLACK HOLE IN OUR
GALAXY.
THIS IS KIND OF SPOOKY TO ME.
>> OKAY.
>> IT'S BEING CALLED LB LIVE 1.
TH
-- LB-1.
70 TIMES OF THE MASS OF THE SUN.
THE FIRST TIME IT'S DETECTED IN
THE MILKY WAY.
HOW IT WAS FORMED IS A MYSTERY.
SOME FOLKS SAY TWO BLACK HOLES
MAY HAVE MERGED.
ASTRONOMERS SAY THE MILKY WAY
CONTAINS UP TO 100 MILLION BLACK
HOLES.
I BECAME FASCINATED WITH BLACK
HOLES BACK IN 1980, A MOVIE
CALLED "THE BLACK HOLE," DISNEY
PRODUCED IT.
IT WAS WITH ANTHONY PERKINS.
THE WHOLE NOTION OF THIS -- THIS
MASS OUT THERE, COULD GOBBLE UP
THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE, FREAKED ME
OUT.
SO THIS NOT GOOD NEWS FOR ME.
HATE TO BE THE DEBBIE DOWN OR
THIS THANKSGIVING.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> WE'RE THANK WE'RE STILL HERE.
>> WHAT CAN I SAY?
>> MAKES HUMAN BEINGS FEEL
HUMBLE WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT THE
GALAXY.
>> THE WAY WE KNOW IT, IT
SHOULDN'T EVEN BE POSSIBLE.
NOW IT IS.
WE HAVE TO CHANGE THE WAY WE
LOOK AT THESE THINGS.
>> FASCINATING.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S WHAT I HAVE -- ON
THANKSGIVING, WE WANT TO GIVE
THANKS TO THOSE WHO GIVE.
AWARD-WINNING CHEF JOSE ANDREAS
IS THE FOUNDER OF THE CHARITY
GROUP WORLD CENTRAL KITCHEN.
THEY DELIVER MEALS TO THOSE IN
NEED AROUND THE WORLD.
TODAY THE CHARITY HOPES TO SERVE
9,000 MEALS IN THE BAHAMAS WHICH
IS STILL RECOVERING FROM
HURRICANE DORIAN.
BACK IN SEPTEMBER, WE MET THE
CHEF IN THE BAHAMAS.
HE WAS DELIVERING MEALS RIGHT
AFTER DORIAN DEVASTATED THE
ISLAND.
LAST NIGHT HE APPEARED ON "THE
LATE SHOW WITH STEPHEN COLBERT"
TO TALK ABOUT HIS PHILANTHROPY.
>> I ALWAYS SAY THAT WE DON'T
PLAN, YOU KNOW, WHEN SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAPPENS IN BAHAMAS,
NOBODY HAD FOOD AND NOBODY HAD
WATER.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO PLAN?
START COOKING, START BRINGING
WATER, START DELIVERING AS QUICK
AND AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
>> HE IS JUST A REMARKABLE HUMAN
BEING.
>> HE IS.
>> HE ASSEMBLES PEOPLE FROM -- I
LOVE THAT HE PULLS FROM THE
LOCAL CHEFS, RIGHT.
IF YOU LAND IN NORTHERN
CALIFORNIA, YOU FIND THE LOCAL
CHEFS, AND THEY SET UP THIS
KITCHEN, AND THEY GIVE.
AND HE ALWAYS TALKS AT THE FACT
THAT HE'S AN IMMIGRANT, AND HE
CAME TO THERE COUNTRY AND --
CAME TO THIS COUNTRY AND FOUND
OPPORTUNITY AND IS GIVING BACK.
>> A LOT OF IMMIGRANTS DO THAT.
A LOT.
THANK YOU, CHEF.
>>> TURKEY ISN'T THE ONLY THING
ON PEOPLE'S MINDS THIS
THANKSGIVING MORNING.
MANY AMERICANS WILL BE SEARCHING
FOR THE BEST HOLIDAY DEALS AS WE
APPROACH BLACK FRIDAY.
THIS HOLIDAY SEASON, ONLINE
SALES ARE EXPECTED TO INCREASE.
A NEW RECORD OF MORE THAN, GET
THIS, $143 BILLION, WITH A "B."
ACCORDING TO ADOBE WHICH TRACKS
INTERNET RETAILERS, THAT'S A
MORE THAN 14% INCREASE FROM
2018.
SO HOW DO YOU KNOW IF YOU'RE
GETTING THE BEST DEALS?
SHARON PROFIS, EXECUTIVE EDITOR
AND DIRECTOR OF "THE CONTENT"
FROM OUR PARTNERS AT CNET JOINS
US NOW.
I THINK WHAT PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW
IS WHERE AND HOW DO YOU GET THE
BEST DEALS ON BLACK FRIDAY?
>> SO THE BEST DEALS ARE
ACTUALLY HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
I SAY YOU DON'T HAVE TO SHOP ON
BLACK FRIDAY.
YOU CAN DO YOUR SHOPPING THIS
MORNING ON THANKSGIVING AND THEN
GET BACK TO COOKING YOUR TURKEY.
>> YEAH.
THE REAL DEAL, THOUGH, IS TO GET
SOMEONE IN THE STORES TO TELL
YOU WHAT'S HAPPENING ON BLACK
FRIDAY OUR THANKSGIVING.
HAVING THAT INSIDER'S KNOWLEDGE.
>> YEAH.
SO WHERE IS THE BEST PLACE TO DO
THE SHOPPING?
IN THE STORE OR ON LINE?
>> THIS YEAR, ESPECIALLY, ON
LINE IS BECOMING THE BEST PLACE
TO DO THE BEST SHOPPING.
>> FOR CONVENIENCE OR BECAUSE
IT'S ACTUALLY CHEAPER?
>> A LITTLE BIT OF BOTH.
SO IT USED TO BE THAT YOU HAD TO
GO INTO THE STORE TO GET THE
BEST DEALS.
WE'RE SEEING RETARLGS REPLICATE
THE -- RETAILERS REPLICATE THE
SAME DEALS IN NOR AND ON LINE.
THE BEST PART ABOUT SHOPPING AT
HOME IS YOU CAN DO THE
COMPARISON SHOPPING.
YOU GO INTO THE STORE, YOU'RE
STUCK IN THAT STORE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A LOT OF OPTIONS,
AND IF YOU CAME FOR A DOOR
BUSTER DEAL, THERE'S A GOOD
CHANCE THAT THEY HAVE A VERY --
YOU KNOW, SMALL AMOUNT OF
INVENTORY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AND THEN YOU'RE STUCK WITH
WHATEVER THEY HAVE LEFT.
>> BIG-TICKET ITEM, AIR PODS AND
APPLE WATCHES.
WHAT'S THE BEST DEAL?
WHERE CAN WE FIND THEM?
>> YEAH.
WE'RE SEEING STEEP DISCOUNTS ON
APPLE PRODUCTS WHICH, BY THE
WAY, NEVER HAPPEN.
>> NEVER.
SO WE'RE SEEING GRAELGS ON THE
APPLE WATCH -- GREAT DEALS ON
THE APPLE WATCH.
ESPECIALLY FOR AS MUCH AS $200
OFF RIGHT NOW.
A GREAT GIFT.
AIR PODS WE'VE SEEN AS LOW AS
$129.
NOT FOR THE PRO BUT FOR THE
SECOND MODEL.
SO TODAY'S A GREAT DAY TO BUY
APPLE PRODUCTS.
>> WHY ARE THEY DISCOUNTED?
>> WELL, THEY'RE -- THEY'RE
DISCOUNTED BECAUSE OTHER
RETAILERS ARE DISCOUNTING THEM.
IN THIS CASE, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT WALMART'S DISCOUNTS IN
PARTICULAR.
>> WOW.
>> WE KNOW THAT 50% OF HOLIDAY
SHOPPING GROWTH WILL BE BECAUSE
OF SMARTPHONE SHOPPING.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY ABOUT WHERE
WE'RE GOING IN TERMS OF NOT JUST
USING THE COMPUTER BUT DOING
EVERYTHING ON OUR PHONES?
>> YEAH.
CONSUMERS ARE BECOMING WAY MORE
COMFORTABLE WITH SHOPPING ON
THEIR PHONES.
I THINK A BIG PART IS THAT IT'S
ACTUALLY BECOMING MORE OF A
STREAMLINED, SEAMLESS
EXPERIENCE.
AND WHAT WE'RE SEEING IS
RETAILERS ARE RESPONDING TO THIS
NEW BEHAVIOR BY OFFERING WAYS TO
BRIDGE THE GAP BETWEEN SHOPPING
ON YOUR PHONE AND GOING INTO THE
STORE.
AN INCREASE IN BUY ON LINE, PICK
UP IN STORE IS HAPPENING.
TARGET HAS A NEW DRIVEUP OPTION.
SO YOU BUY IT ON YOUR PHONE,
DRIVE YOUR CAR INTO A SPECIFIC
PARKING STALL, AND THEY'LL BRING
THE PRODUCT OUT TO YOU.
SO IT'S KIND OF THE BEST OF BOTH
WORLDS.
>> A LOT OF SKAMCAMS OUT THERE.
RELIABILITY IS KEY.
HOW DO YOU MAKE SURE YOU'RE
GETTING THE REAL DEAL?
>> YEAH.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE TOOLS IS
CAMEL, CAMEL, CAMEL.
FUNNY NAME.
BUT YOU CAN'T FORGET IT.
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
DISCOUNT THAT YOU'RE SEEING IS A
SPECIAL AND A RARE DISCOUNT.
YOU GO TO CAMEL, CAMEL, KAPPC C
YOU SEE WHAT THE PRICE HAS BEEN,
MAYBE IT'S DROPPED A FEW TIMES
THIS YEAR.
THE OTHER THING TO LOOK OUT FOR
IS FAKE REVIEWS.
WE'VE SEEN AN INCREASE IN FAKE
REVIEWS THIS YEAR IN THE FTC
JUMPING ON IT.
>> HERE'S MY QUESTION -- HOW DO
I KNOW A REVIEW IS FAKE?
IT SAYS VERIFIED, YOU GOT THE
FIVE STARS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT IT'S FAKE?
>> YEAH.
IT'S -- I ALWAYS RECOMMENDS
BEING SKEPTICAL OF ALL REVIEWS.
AND USE A TOOL CALLED FAKESP
FAKESPOT.COM TO FIND OUT HOW
RELIABLE THE REVIEWS ARE.
YOU ENTER THE URL OF THE PRODUCT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR.
THEY HAVE AN ALGORITHM THAT
HELPS SUSS HOW OUT ACCURATE THEY
ARE.
>> FAKESPOT.COM.
>> WHEN DID YOU START SHOPPING?
>> I STARTED SHOPPING ON MONDAY.
BLACK FRIDAY IS REALLY BLACK
FRIDAY WEEK NOW.
YOU CAN START SHOPPING VERY
EARLY AND NOT WORRY ABOUT
STRESSING ON THANKSGIVING.
>> I STARTED LAST BLACK FRIDAY.
>> OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SHARON PROFIS, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
>>> AHEAD IN OUR SERIES "A MORE
PERFECT UNION," HOW NEIGHBORS
ARE WORKING TOGETHER TO HELP
FAMILIES STRUGGLING TO AFFORD
FOOD.
>>> WE DON'T GET PAID FOR
ANOTHER THREE DAYS, SO WE ARE AT
THE PANTRY TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE CAN FEED THE KIDS SINCE
THEY'RE OUT OF SCHOOL.
>> Reporter: WHAT ARE YOU HOPING
TO GET HERE TODAY?
>> SOME BREAKFAST AND SOMETHING
THAT WE CAN MAKE SO THEY CAN
WARM UP WHEN I'M AT WORK.
>> HOW ONE WOMAN FOUND A WAY TO
HELP AND IS GOING THE EXTRA MILE
THIS
You know the time is right
to get the tools you trust.
Lowe's is here with
more of the tools
and accessories that pros want.
At our lowest
prices of the year.
You're doing your part to save
energy.
We're doing ours to make it
cleaner.
At Dominion Energy, we've cut
our carbon emissions in half.
That's like taking 6 million
cars off the road.
That's just the start.
Leading the way to a cleaner
planet.
Our future...
is counting on it.
♪
>>> OUR SERIES, "A MORE PERFECT
UNION," AIMS TO SHOW THAT WHOA
UNITES US AS AMERICANS IS FAR
GREATER THAN WHAT DIVIDES US.
IN COMMUNITIES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY PEOPLE ARE GETTING
CREATIVE TO MAKE SURE THEIR
NEIGHBORS DO NOT GO HUNGRY.
ROUGHLY 40 MILLION AMERICANS ARE
FOOD INSECURE, MEANING THEY
CAN'T ALWAYS AFFORD FOOD.
ADRIANA DIAZ VISITED A
NEIGHBORHOOD WHERE AN IDEA FOR A
FOOD PANTRY IS HELPING FAMILIES
IN NEED THERE.
>> Reporter: EVERY DAY WHEN
JAMIE HENDRICKS GETS HOME, SHE
GETS TO WORK CHECKING HER PANTRY
AND FILLING IT UP.
SO WHAT NEEDS TO BE RESTOCKED
TODAY?
>> SO TODAY WE NEED TO RESTOCK
SOME MORE OF THE VEGETABLES AND
SOME MORE OF THE MACARONI TYPE
OF ITEMS.
>> Reporter: THIS FOOD ISN'T FOR
HER FAMILY.
IT'S FOR HER COMMUNITY IN ST.
PAUL, MINNESOTA.
WHAT ARE YOU GRABBING NOW FOR
THE PANTRY?
>> TOILET PAPER.
>> Reporter: OKAY.
THE SUPPLIES ARE HEADED TO HER
FRONT YARD WHERE SHE PLANTED THE
NORTH END FREE PANTRY.
SHE GOT THE IDEA FROM LITTLE
FREE LIBRARIES WHERE NEIGHBORS
LEND AND BORROW BOOKS.
SHE'S REPLACED BOOKS WITH FOOD.
SO MANY PEOPLE TOOK THE FREE
FOOD, SHE HAD TO REPLACE HER
2.5-FOOT CABINET WITH A
SEVEN-FOOT ONE.
>> THAT TOLD ME THAT WE HAVE A
MUCH BIGGER PROBLEM, MUCH BIGGER
NEED IN OUR COMMUNITY THAN WHAT
I HAD EVEN THOUGHT.
EVERY DAY WHEN I COME HOME AND I
CHECK IT, THERE'S USUALLY
SOMETHING'S GONE.
>> Reporter: WHEN PEOPLE ARE A
FEW DAYS AWAY FROM PAYDAY.
>> RIGHT BEFORE RENT.
RIGHT AFTER THEY'VE PAID THEIR
RENT.
>> Reporter: 20% OF PEOPLE IN
ST. PAUL LIVE BELOW THE POVERTY
LINE.
THAT'S MORE THAN 8% ABOVE THE
NATIONAL POVERTY RATE.
ANGELIQUE RUSH KNOWS WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO HAVE TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
PAYING BILLS AND BUYING
GROCERIES FOR HER HUSBAND AND
FOUR KIDS.
>> NOW WE DON'T GET PAID FOR
ANOTHER THREE DAYS.
SO WE ARE AT THE PANTRY TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT WE CAN FEED
THE KIDS SINCE THEY'RE OUT OF
SCHOOL.
>> Reporter: WHAT ARE YOU HOPE
TO GET HERE TODAY?
>> SOME BREAKFAST AND SOMETHING
THAT WE CAN MAKE SO THEY CAN
WARM UP WHEN I'M AT WORK.
>> Reporter: RIGHT.
RUSH LEARNED ABOUT THE PANTRY ON
FACEBOOK.
SHE'S GONE TO FOOD BANKS, BUT
THEY HAVE LIMITED HOURS, AND
SOME REQUIRE PROOF OF INCOME.
SHE SAYS SHE AND HER HUSBAND
MAKE $75 TOO MUCH TO QUALIFY FOR
FOOD STAMPS.
>> HAVING THE PANTRY AND IT
BEING ANONYMOUS, IT HELPS A LOT.
IT MAKES IT SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO
ANSWER TO ANYBODY OR FEEL
SHAMEFUL.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN ONLY
HAVING SOME THINGS TO FEED YOUR
KIDS AND NOT HAVING WHAT THEY
WANT TO EAT.
AS A MOM IT MAKES YOU FEEL
REALLY SAD THAT THEY DON'T WANT
TO EAT RAMEN NOODLES OR THEY
DON'T WANT TO EAT THE SOUP YOU
GOT, BUT THEY HAVE TO BECAUSE
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING ELSE TO
FEED THEM.
IT'S REALLY HARD.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO CRY.
>> Reporter: IT'S OKAY.
I'M SURE THERE'S NOTHING HARDER
THAN TO HEAR THEM SAY THEY'RE
HUNGRY.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD.
>> Reporter: YEAH.
HAS YOUR LIFE EXPERIENCE PUSHED
YOU TO DO THIS FOR OTHERS?
>> WHEN WE GREW UP WE DIDN'T
HAVE A LOT OF MONEY.
THAT WAS THE SAME WITH WHEN MY
DAUGHTERS WERE YOUNG.
BUT WE ALWAYS FOUND A WAY TO BE
ABLE TO MAKE IT AND TO BE ABLE
TO HELP OTHER PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: FREE FOOD PANTRIES
HAVE POPPED UP NATIONWIDE.
MORE THAN 700 ARE LISTED IN THIS
ONLINE DIRECTORY.
HENDRICKS' NEIGHBOR ROSIE TOOL
SEES THE IMPACT.
HOW OFTEN DO PEOPLE COME AND
TAKE FOOD?
>> ALMOST EVERY DAY.
IT'S NOT THAT THEY'RE TAKING,
BUT PEOPLE ALMOST TWO, THREE
TIMES A WEEK BRINGING STUFF.
>> IT KIND OF PROVIDES A LITTLE
BIT OF HOPE FOR PEOPLE AND NOT
JUST IN THE SENSE THAT THERE'S
SOMETHING THERE, BUT THAT OTHER
PEOPLE CARE.
AND SO THAT IN AND OF ITSELF I
THINK MAKES A BIG DIFFERENCE.
>> Reporter: IF EVERYONE DID A
SMALL THING LIKE THIS FOR THE
COMMUNITY, WHAT KIND OF WORLD DO
YOU THINK THIS WOULD BE?
>> A NON-HUNGRY WORLD, THAT'S
FOR SURE.
IT WOULD MAKE IT EASIER FOR
PEOPLE TO SURVIVE.
>> Reporter: FOR "CBS THIS
MORNING," ADRIANA DIAZ, ST.
PAUL, MINNESOTA.
>> WOW.
>> AND WE HAVE AN UPDATE.
JAMIE HENDRICKS WITH THE HELP OF
GENEROUS NEIGHBORS, THEY PUT
TOGETHER A THANKSGIVING MEAL
PACKAGE.
IT'S FOR PEOPLE WHO WANT TO
CELEBRATE BUT CAN'T AFFORD THE
TRIMMINGS.
INCLUDES CORN, MASHED POTATOES,
STUFFING, AND TURKEY.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY AND DO
SOMETHING SIMILAR AT CHRISTMAS.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
SUCH A REMINDER -- WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT THE AMOUNT OF FOOD
THAT WE WASTE IN THIS COUNTRY --
>> THAT'S WHY I ALWAYS HAVE A
CLEAN PLATE.
>> I FEEL LIKE GIVING IS
INFECTIOUS.
LIKE SHE SAID, PEOPLE ARE TAKING
FROM IT, BUT PEOPLE ARE SHOWING
UP TO GIVE, TOO.
>> TO GIVE TO IT.
>> YOU ALWAYS FEEL BETTER WHEN
YOU GIVE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> FAR BETTER TO GIVE THAN TO
RECEIVE.
>>> ON TODAY'S "CBS THIS
MORNING" PODCAST, THE STORY WHEN
KENNETH DAVIS SHARES THE HISTORY
OF THANKSGIVING.
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED AT THE
FIRST THANKSGIVING AND WHY
DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS HELD
SEPARATE THANKSGIVING HOLIDAYS
IN 1939, AND -- I KNOW, RIGHT --
HOW FOOTBALL BECAME SUCH A LARGE
PART OF THE DAY.
>>> BEFORE WE GO, A HEARTWARMING
HOMECOMING FOR THOUSANDS OF
SAILORS AND MARINES JUST IN TIME
FOR THE HOLIDAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
AT HAVERTYS, WE KNOW
IT'S TIME TO GET
YOUR HOUSE
HOLIDAY READY.
BECAUSE THE GUESTS...
THEY ARE COMING.
THOSE DECORATIONS ARE
ONLY AS PRETTY AS
THE ROOM
YOU'RE DECORATING.
YOU MAY NEED A PEACEFUL
SPOT TO LAY DOWN THE
LAW WITH YOUR
MOTHER-IN-LAW.
AND WHEN IT'S TIME TO
PLOP DOWN IN FRONT
OF THE GAME, THEY ALL
NEED A PLACE TO PLOP.
HAVERTYS BLACK FRIDAY
SALE IS HERE TO HELP!
RIGHT NOW,
GET FREE DELIVERY.
PLUS SAVE UP TO $1000!
READY, SET, HOLIDAY!
HAVERTYS
LIFE LOOKS GOOD
He could've just been the middle
class kid who made good.
But Mike Bloomberg became the
guy who did good.
After building a business that
created thousands of jobs
he took charge of a city still
reeling from 9/11
a three-term mayor who helped
bring it back from the ashes
bringing jobs and thousands of
affordable housing
units with it.
After witnessing the terrible
toll of gun violence...
he helped create a movement
to protect
families across America.
And stood up to the coal
lobby and this administration
to protect this planet from
climate change.
And now, he's taking on...
him. To rebuild a country
and restore faith in the
dream that defines us.
Where the wealthy will
pay more in taxes
and the middle class get
their fair share.
Everyone without health
insurance can get it
and everyone who likes
theirs keep it.
And where jobs won't just help
you get by, but get ahead.
And on all those things
Mike Blomberg intends to make
good.
Jobs Creator. Leader.
Problem Solver.
Mike Bloomberg for President.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
Cancer won't wait for
appointments to open up,
test results to come back,
or treatment plans to start.
At Cancer Treatment Centers of
America,
we make time for cancer
patients.
Time to answer questions,
relieve worries,
and turn indecision into good
decisions.
Because cancer won't wait,
and we don't think you should
either.
Call or go online anytime
to set up an appointment with
our team of cancer experts.
Cancer Treatment Centers of
America.
Appointments available now.
>>> BEFORE WE GO, THOUSANDS OF
SAILORS AND MARINES HAVE BEEN
REUNITED WITH THEIR LOVED ONES
THIS TIME FOR THANKSGIVING.
MORE THAN 4,5 HIT-AND-RUN
SERVICE MEMBERS IN THE "USS
BOXER" AMPHIBIOUS GROUP RETURNED
TO SAN DIEGO YESTERDAY.
THE SARPS ILORS AND MARINES WER
A SEVEN-MONTH DEPLOYMENT IN THE
MIDDLE EAST.
LOVED ONES WELCOMED THEM WITH
SIGNS, AMERICAN FLAGS, AND TEARS
OF JOY.
ONE SAILOR EVEN MET HIS BABY
DAUGHTER IN PERSON FOR THE FIRST
TIME OUR SAN DIEGO AFFILIATE
KFNB SPOKE WITH A WOMAN WHO WAS
EXCITED TO SEE HER SON AFTER HIS
FINALLY DID EMPLOYMENT.
>> I WOULDN'T WAIT UNTIL HE COME
HOME TO BE WITH HIS SON.
THIS IS HIS ONLY CHILD.
SO IT WAS HARD.
IT WAS HARD LEAVING HIS SON
BEHINDS FOR ALL THEM DIFFERENT
DEPLOYMENTS.
THANK GOD TODAY IS HIS LAST
DEPLOYMENT.
>> AND THAT SAILOR SON IS
EXCITED.
HE SAID HIS DAD HAS BEEN IN THE
MILITARY SINCE THE DAY HE WAS
BORN.
>> OH.
BEAUTIFUL.
>> SWEET KID.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING, ALL.
>> HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
YOU HAVE A BIG DAY AHEAD.
A LOT OF FOLKS DO.
THAT, OF COURSE, DOES IT FOR US.
BE SURE TO TUNE IN TO THE "CBS
EVENING NEWS" TONIGHT.
This Black Friday weekend,
Verizon is giving you more
holiday magic with our best
offer ever.
Switch to any Fios home internet
plan
starting at $39.99 per month
and get a year of Disney+ on us.
Stream all your Disney favorites
and new originals all on the
100% fiber-optic network.
But, the magic doesn't end
there.
This weekend only, you'll get a
$100 Visa Prepaid Card when you
switch.
Plus, an additional $100
Visa Prepaid Card
when you upgrade to our fastest
internet.
But, hurry! Offer ends
Cyber Monday.
Get more from Verizon.