Captioning sponsored by CBS
TONIGHT:, THE BIG DEBATE.
THE FINAL SHOWDOWN BEFORE THE
BIGGEST PRIMARIES.
BERNIE SANDERS IN THE LEAD BUT
ON THE DEFENSE ABOUT THE PRICE
OF HIS PROPOSALS.
JOE BIDEN FIGHTING FOR A WIN.
PLUS, CAN MICHAEL BLOOMBERG
REBOUND AFTER HIS LAST
PERFORMANCE?
WE'RE WITH THE CANDIDATES AHEAD
OF TONIGHT'S FACE-OFF.
THE OTHER BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT,
THE DIRE GOVERNMENT WARNINGS,
AMERICANS TOLD TO PREPARE FOR
THE CORONAVIRUS TO SPREAD HERE.
SAN FRANCISCO DECLARES A STATE
OF EMERGENCY, AND WITH THE STOCK
MARKET IN FREE-FALL, THE
CRITICAL SHORTAGE TONIGHT OF A
KEY MEDICAL SUPPLY.
WORSENING CRISIS: OVERSEAS, MORE
PANIC AS THE CORONAVIRUS
EMERGENCY KEEPS GROWING WITH
CASES IN ITALY SKYROCKETING.
IS THE VIRUS NOW SWEEPING ACROSS
EUROPE?
SPEAKING OUT: HARVEY WEINSTEIN
UNDER GUARD AT A NEW YORK
HOSPITAL.
WHY HE'S BEING TREATED ONE DAY
AFTER BEING CONVICTED OF RAPE
AND WHAT HIS ACCUSERS ARE SAYING
TONIGHT.
SIX-YEAR-OLD ARRESTED: NEWLY
RELEASED POLICE VIDEO RAISING
QUESTIONS TONIGHT.
WHY DID POLICE TIE A LITTLE
GIRL'S ARMS BEHIND HER BACK AND
TAKE HER FROM HER SCHOOL?
HOW YOUNG IS TOO YOUNG TO BE
UNDER ARREST?
THE SEARCH WIDENS.
POLICE EXPAND THE INVESTIGATION
FOR THOSE MISSING CHILDREN FROM
IDAHO ACROSS FIVE STATES WITH
THEIR MOTHER BEHIND BARS IN
HAWAII.
THE NEW CLUE POLICE SAY COULD BE
THE KEY TO FINDING THEM.
DISNEY'S C.E.O. OUT.
BOB IGER, THE LONGTIME HEAD OF
ONE OF THE WORLD'S BIGGEST
ENTERTAINMENT COMPANIES REPLACED
TONIGHT.
THE NEW DETAILS ARE JUST COMING
IN.
AND POURING IT FORWARD-- THE
UNIQUE COFFEE SHOP RIGHT HERE IN
CHARLESTON CHANGING LIVES BY
HIRING THOSE WHOSE SKILLS ARE
OFTEN OVERLOOKED.
>> THIS IS THE "CBS EVENING
NEWS" WITH NORAH O'DONNELL
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM THE
DEMOCRATIC DEBATE IN CHARLESTON,
SOUTH CAROLINA.
>> O'Donnell: GOOD EVENING,
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US TONED AS THE SEVEN
CANDIDATES FOR THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL NOMINATION WILL
FIGHT IT OUT RIGHT HERE ON THIS
STAGE.
THIS DEBATE MAY BE THE MOST
IMPORTANT, COMING JUST FOUR DAYS
BEFORE THE SOUTH CAROLINA
PRIMARY AND ONE WEEK BEFORE THE
14-STATE EXTRAVAGANZA KNOWN AS
SUPER TUESDAY.
OUR LATEST CBS NEWS POLL SHOWS
JOE BIDEN WITH A SLIM LEAD HERE
IN SOUTH CAROLINA OVER THE
NATIONAL FRONTRUNNER, BERNIE
SANDERS.
BILLIONAIRE TOM STEYER IS
POLLING THIRD.
TODAY, THE CANDIDATES TOOK TURNS
WALKING THROUGH THE DEBATE HALL,
AND THE BIGGEST QUESTION IS
WHETHER ANYONE CAN SLOW DOWN
BERNIE SANDERS, WHO COULD BE ON
TRACK TO TAKE A SIGNIFICANT LEAD
IN DELEGATES.
THE OTHERS HAVE ALREADY STEPPED
UP THEIR ATTACKS.
IN NEW ADS, JOE BIDEN ACCUSES
SANDERS OF TRYING TO IMPEDE
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S 2012
RE-ELECTION.
PETE BUTTIGEIG ATTACKED SANDERS'
MEDICARE FOR ALL HEALTH CARE
PLAN.
AND MIKE BLOOMBERG IS TAKE AIM
AT SANDERS' GUN CONTROL RECORD.
NO SHORTAGE OF PLOT LINES FOR
TONIGHT'S DEBATE HERE, AND SO
ED O'KEEFE LEADS OFF OUR
COVERAGE.
>> Reporter: JUST HOURS FROM
NOW, CANDIDATES WILL TAKE THIS
STAGE FOR THE FINAL DEBATE
BEFORE SATURDAY'S SOUTH CAROLINA
PRIMARY AND NEXT WEEK'S SUPER
TUESDAY, WHEN VOTERS IN 14
STATES CAST BALLOTS.
AT CENTER STAGE TONIGHT, SENATOR
BERNIE SANDERS, THE FRONTRUNNER,
WHOSE LIKELY TO FACE FRESH
ATTACKS FROM MORE MODERATE
OPPONENTS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME, THE SANDERS
CAMPAIGN IS PROVIDING WHAT IT
SAYS IS A DETAILED PLAN TO PAY
FOR SOME OF THE SENATOR'S
MOST-AMBITIOUS IDEAS, LIKE
MEDICARE FOR ALL, UNIVERSAL
CHILDCARE, AND FREE PUBLIC
COLLEGE.
>> THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH!
>> Reporter: HIS COMPETITORS
SAY THE MATH DOESN'T AWPPED, AND
IT'S THOSE KINDS OF PROPOSALS
THAT WORRY CONGRESSIONAL
DEMOCRATS, LIKE VIRGINIA'S
DONALD McEACHIN, A SUPPORTER
OF FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE
BIDEN.
>> YOU KNOW, HE'S A DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALIST.
HE'S AN INDEPENDENT.
HE'S WHATEVER HE WANTS TO BE,
UNTIL IT'S TIME TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
NOW HE WANTS TO BE A DEMOCRAT.
THAT DOG DOESN'T HUNT IN
VIRGINIA.
>> Reporter: MICHAEL BLOOMBERG
HAS ALSO SIGNALED HE PLANS TO GO
AFTER SANDERS.
HE SPENT LAST FEW DAYS HOLED UP
WITH HIS TEAM IN FLORIDA.
AIDES SAY HE'S AWARE HOW ANSWERS
TO HIS LAST DEBATE ABOUT
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS TREATMENT OF
WOMEN.
AFTER THAT DIMINISH BLOOMBERG
RELEASED THREE WOMEN WHO ACCUSED
HIM OF INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR
FROM NONDICLOSURE AGREEMENTS.
HIS LONGTIME PARTNER, DIANA
TAYLOR, DEFENDED THE USE OF
NONDICLOSURE AGREEMENTS.
>> HE ISST WAS NOT ACCUSED OF
DOING ANYTHING OR SAYING
SOMETHING NEWSCAST TOW WOMEN.
THAT'S NOT WHO HE IS.
>> Reporter: A BLOOMBERG
CAMPAIGN SPOKESPERSON SAID IT IS
NOT THE.
TAKE A RECENT CBS NEWS POLL THAT
FOUND UP TO 63% OF LIKELY SOUTH
CAROLINA LIKELY DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARY VOTERS COULD STILL
CHANGE THEIR MIND BEFORE
SATURDAY.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT, ED,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AND AS WANT AUDITORIUM BEGINS TO
FILL UP HERE, LET'S BRING IN
MAJOR GARRETT, WHO WILL BE
JOINING GAYLE KING AND ME IN
TERMS OF MODERATING THIS DEBATE.
UN, MAJOR, THIS IS A KEY DEBATE,
BECAUSE NOT ONLY IS IT THE LAST
DEBATE BEFORE THE SOUTH CAROLINA
PRIMARY, BUT ALSO SUPER TUESDAY.
IT'S MAKE OR BREAK FOR THESE
CANDIDATES TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AND IT'S THE LAST
OPPORTUNITY ANYONE NOT NAMED
BERNIE SANDERS HAS TO SLOW HIS
MOMENTUM.
BERNIE SANDERS' MOMENTUM IS
REAL.
IT'S NOT AN ABSTRACTION.
AND EVERY OTHER DEMOCRAT ON THE
STAGE TONIGHT KNOWS THAT.
AND, NORAH, YOU AND I HAVE
COVERED PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGNS.
YOU KNOW OPPOSITION RESEARCH IS
PART AND PARCEL OF THAT.
MOST OF THAT HAS BEEN KEPT IN
THE VAULT AGAINST BERNIE SANDERS
THINKING HE WOULDN'T GET OFF TO
THIS FAST START.
NOW THAT HE HAS ALL THE
CAMPAIGNS ARE SIGNALING TO ME
TODAY THAT VAULT IS GOING TO BE
OPENED AND SPILL OUT ON TO THE
STAGE.
>> O'Donnell: IT IS ALSO A BIG
STAGE FOR JOE BIDEN.
HE HAS CALLED THIS FATE STATEHIS
FIREWALL.
>> Reporter: JOE BIDEN HAS
UNDERPERFORMED THREE TIMES.
HE CANNOT UNDERPERFORM HERE.
HE MUST WIN CONVINCINGLY.
WHY I DO SAY THAT?
EVEN HIS CAMPAIGN RECOGNIZES A
NARROW VICTORY HERE IS NOT
ENOUGH TO SAY I'M THE BERNIE
SANDERS ALTERNATIVE.
JOE BIDEN IS FIGHTING FOR THE
VERY LAST TIME TO BE THAT IEFLT.
IF HE MISSES IT HERE, HE MISSES
IT FOREVER.
>> O'Donnell: MAYOR BLOOMBERG
ADNITS HE DID NOT HAVE A GREAT
DEBATE LAST TIME.
>> Reporter: HE BLEW IT THE
FIRST TIME.
BUT HE IS GOING AFTER BERNIE
SANDERS SAYING HE'S UNELECTABLE,
THAT FOR A CONSERVATIVE OR
CENTRIST DEMOCRATS IN HOUSE AND
SENATE RACES HE'S TOXIC AND THAT
HE'S REALLY BAD ON GUNS.
EXPECT THAT ISSUE TO COME UP
TONIGHT.
>> O'Donnell: AND SUPERED IT,
THE 14 STATES WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT, BLOOMBERG IS OUTSPENDING
EVERYBODY BY OVER $100 MILLION.
>> Reporter: HE'S OUTSPENDING
BUT WHAT HE MEANS ON SUPPER
SUICIDE IS WINS OR DELEGATES.
HE HAS NEITHER RIGHT NOW.
HE NEEDS SHOW UP BIG TIME AND
MAKE THE MONEY WORTH SOMETHING
ON SUPER TUESDAY.
>> Ninan: CAN'T THINK OF A
MORE PIVOTAL NIGHT THAN TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN FEEL THE
ELECTRICITY.
>> O'Donnell: AND A REMINDER
GAYLE AND I WILL MODERATE THE
DEBATE BEGINNING AT 8:00 P.M.
EASTERN TIME RIGHT HERE ON CBS,
AND WE WELCOME YOU TO SUBMIT
YOUR OWN QUESTIONS FOR THE
CANDIDATES.
IT IS NOT TOO LATE, ON TWITTER
BY USING THE HASHTAG #DEMDEBATE.
WE WANT TO GO NOW TO THE OTHER
BIG STORY TONIGHT: A DIRE
WARNING FROM THE C.D.C. THAT AN
OUTBREAK OF CORONAVIRUS IS
COMING HERE TO THE U.S.
IT COULD BE SEVERE, AND
AMERICANS NEED TO PREPARE NOW.
THERE IS ALSO WORD THAT THIS
COUNTRY DOESN'T HAVE ENOUGH FACE
MASKS TO CONTAIN AN OUTBREAK.
THE NEWS SENT THE STOCK MARKET
RELING AGAIN.
THE DOW HAS DROPPED MORE THAN
1900 POINTS IN TWO DAYS.
THAT'S A LOSS OF NEARLY 7%.
HEALTH OFFICIALS WARN THE U.S.
COULD SOON SEE MORE CASES AS THE
VIRUS SPREADS OUTSIDE CHINA.
WE HAVE TWO REPORTS TONIGHT,
BEGINNING WITH KRIS VAN CLEAVE
IN WASHINGTON.
AND I UNDERSTAND,KRIS, YOU HAVE
SOME BREAKING NEWS.
>> Reporter: NORAH,
SAN FRANCISCO HAS JUST DECLARED
A STATE OF EMERGENCY, THE FIRST
MAJOR AMERICAN CITY TO DO SO
BECAUSE OF CORONAVIRUS, EVEN
THOUGH SAN FRANCISCO HAS ZERO
CASES SO FAR.
BUT THE C.D.C. IS SAYING IT'S NO
LONGER A MATTER OF IF BUT WHEN
THE VIRUS STARTS SPREADING HERE.
THE C.D.C. IS SOUNDING THE ALARM
TONIGHT, WARNING AMERICANS THE
CORONAVIRUS IS COMING.
>> Reporter: OF.
>> Reporter: THE C.D.C.'S
NANCY MESSIONER SAID SHE TOLD
HER OWN CHILDREN TO PREPARE FOR
A SIGNIFICANT DISRUPTION AND
PARENTS SHOULD ASK THEIR SCHOOLS
ABOUT PLANS FOR DISMISSAL IF THE
ILLNESS BECOMES SERIOUS IN THEIR
COMMUNITIES.
( BELL RINGING )
>> Reporter: FEARS THE
OUTBREAK COULD CRIPPLE THE
GLOBAL ECONOMY SENT STOCKS
TUMBLING FOR THE SECOND STRAIGHT
DAY WITH UNITED AIRLINES AND
MASTERCARD WARNING INVESTORS
EARNINGSLET FAKE A HIT.
>> I THINK IT WILL BE UNDER
CONTROL.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
AND HIS AIDES STRUCK A DIFFERENT
TONE.
>> STOW FAR AS CONTAINMENT IS
CONCERNED, WE HAVE TIGHTLY
CONTAINED THIS.
>> Reporter.
>> Reporter: BUT REPUBLICANS
AND DEMOCRATS ON CAPITOL HILL
WHO GOT AN EMERGENCY BRIEFING ON
THE VIRUS REMEMBER NOT BUYING
THAT CLAIM.
>> BOTTOM LINE IS IT SEEMS TO BE
GETTING WORSE, NOT BETTER.
>> Reporter: THEIR ANGER
FOCUSED ON THE LACK OF MEDICAL
SUPPLIES.
>> MY BUDGET SUPPORTS--
>> YOU'RE THE SECRETARY OF
HOMELAND SECURITY.
>> YES, SIR.
>> AND YOU CAN'T TELL ME IF WE
HAVE ENOUGH RESPIRATORS.
>> Reporter: HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY ALEX AZAR
SAID THE AGENCY ONLY STOCKPILED
30 MILLION FACE MASKS.
DESPITE SAYING AMERICANS DON'T
NEED THEM RIGHT NOW, THE COST OF
FACE MASKS HAS RISEN
DRAMATICALLY, AND THE LARGEST
U.S. MANUFACTURER SAID IT'S
FIELDING 100 CALLS A DAY.
KRIS VAN CLEAVE, CBS NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: THIS IS MARK
PHILLIPS IN ITALY, WHERE THE
POLICE CORDON SET UP TO TRY IT
CONTAIN THE VIRUS IN THE NORTH
OF THE COUNTRY IS APPARENTLY
LEAKING.
THE OF CORONAVIRUS CASE SUPS 50%
IN A DAY TO WELL OVER 300.
AT LEAST 11 PEOPLE HAVE NOW
DIED.
THE BULK OF THE VIRUS CASES IN
ITALY HAVE BEEN FROM WITHIN THIS
CORDONED OFF AREA, BUT THERE
HAVE BEEN A FEW CASES REPORTED
NOW ELSEWHERE IN THE EXPRIRK
THAT'S A WORRY.
POLICE ROADBLOCKS CAN STOP
PEOPLE, BUT CAN THEY STOP A
VIRUS?
NEW CASES HAVE NOW SPREAD FROM
THE NORTH ACROSS THE WHOLE
COUNTRY, AND TWO OTHER
COUNTRIES, AUSTRIA, CROATIA,
SWITZERLAND, FRANCE, AND SPAIN.
ANOTHER UNRELATED CLUSTER HAS
EMERGED IN IRAN, WHERE AN
UNWELL-LOOKING DEPUTY HEALTH
MINISTER, IRAJ HARIRCHI, WHO HAD
DOWNPLAYED THE OUTBREAK OF THE
DISEASE THERE, HAS NOW ADMITTED
HE'S GOT IT.
THE 11 PEOPLE WHO HAVE DIED SO
FAR HERE HAVE BEEN THE
VULNERABLE-- THE ELDERLY WHO
CAUGHT THE VIRUS WHEN THEY WERE
ALREADY WEAKENED BY ANOTHER
ILLNESS.
AND, NORAH, RIGHT NOW, FLOWER
MORE THAN 30 PEOPLE WITH THE
VIRUS WHO ARE IN INTENSIVE CARE.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT, MARK,
THANK YOU.
TONIGHT, HARVEY WEINSTEIN IS
BEING HELD IN A PRISON WARD OF A
NEW YORK CITY HOSPITAL, ONE DAY
AFTER BEING CONVICTED ON CHARGES
THAT INCLUDE RAPE.
THE VERDICT IS BEING CHEERED BY
SOME OF WEINSTEIN'S ACCUSERS,
WHO APPLAUDS THE COURAGE OF THE
WOMEN WHO TESTIFIED AGAINST THE
MOVIE PRODUCER IN COURT.
AND TONIGHT, A JUROR IS SPEAK
OUT.
HERE'S JERICKA DUNCAN.
>> Reporter: HARVEY WEINSTEIN
REMAINS IN A NEW YORK CITY
HOSPITAL TONIGHT UNDER
OBSERVATION FOR HEART
PALPITATIONS AND HIGH BLOOD
PRESSURE.
HIS ATTORNEY, ARTHUR AIDALA:
>> OBVIOUSLY, FOR ANY HUMAN
BEING, YESTERDAY WAS A
TREMENDOUSLY JARRING AND
SHOCKING EVENT.
>> HARVEY, I MESSED WITH THE
WRONG WOMEN.
>> Reporter: BUT THERE WAS NO
SYMPATHY FOR WEINSTEIN ON THE
STEPS OF THE LOS ANGELES COUNTY
COURTHOUSE.
THIS GROUP, CALLING THEMSELVES
"SILENCE BREAKERS" IS COMPRISED
OF THE NEARLY 100 WOMEN WHO
ACCUSED THE 67-YEAR-OLDS OF
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.
TODAY, THEY SAF SAVORED THE VER.
>> EVEN A MAN AS POWERFUL AND
FAMOUS AS WEINSTEIN WILL BE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE.
>> Reporter: MI MIRIAM HALEY'S
TESTIMONY HELPED CONVICT
WEINSTEIN.
>> I FELT JUST VERY GRATEFUL
THAT THEY-- THAT I'D BEEN HEARD
AND BELIEVED.
>> Reporter: A MEMBER OF THAT
JURY, WHO ASKED NOT TO BE
IDENTIFIED, SPOKE OUT TODAY.
>> Reporter: DESCRIBE THE
MOMENT WHERE YOU ALL REACH AID
DECISION.
>> I FELT LIKE MY HEART WAS
LITERALLY GOING TO POP OUT OF MY
CHEST.
BUT IT WAS JUST, LIKE, THIS IS
IT.
LIKE, THIS IS THE MOMENT.
>> Reporter: AND THAT MOMENT
HAS BEEN DESCRIBED BY MANY AT
THE BEGINNING OF A NEW ERA OF
JUSTICE FOR SEXUAL ABUSE CASES.
AS FOR HARVEY WEINSTEIN, ONCE
HE'S RELEASED FROM THIS
HOSPITAL, HE'LL BE SENT STRAIGHT
TO PRISON, AND THEN HE'S
EXPECTED TO FACE A TRIAL ON
SEXUAL ABUSE CASE, SEXUAL
ASSAULT, RATHER, IN LOS ANGELES.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT.
A NEW ERA, INDEED, JERICKA.
THANK YOU.
TONIGHT, NEWLY RELEASED VIDEO IS
RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT POLICE
CONDUCT IN SCHOOLS.
THIS ALL STARTED WITH A
SIX-YEAR-OLD GIRL ACTING OUT IN
CLASS, AND IT ENDED WITH HER
RESTRAINED WITH ZIP TIES AND
BEING PUT IN THE BACK OF A
POLICE CRUISER.
MANUEL BOJORQUEZ ON WHAT THE
VIDEO REVEALS.
( CRYING ).
>> NO.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO HURT.
>> Reporter: BODY CAM VIDEO
CAPTURED THE MOMENT AN OFFICER
RESTRAINED SIX-YEAR-OLD KAIA
ROLLE WITH ZIP TIES BEFORE
PLACE, HER IN A POLICE CRUISER.
SHE WAS ACCUSED OF KICKING AND
PUNCHING STAFF MEMBERS, THOUGH
SOME SEEMED PUZZLED BY THE
ARREST.
THE OFFICER ACKNOWLEDGES SHE'S
THE YOUNGEST PERSON HE'S PLACED
IN CUSTODY.
THAT OFFICER, DENNIS TURNER, WAS
TIRED DAYS LATER.
KAIA'S CASE, AND THAT OF A
SIX-YEAR-OLD STUDENT WITH
SPECIAL NEEDS TAKEN INTO CUSTODY
IN JACKSONVILLE EARLIER THIS
MONTH, HAVE RAISED RED FLAGS FOR
CHILD ADVOCATES.
>> POLICE PRESENCE DOES NOT MAKE
A SCHOOL FEEL SAFE.
WHAT MAKES A SCHOOL FEEL SAFE
AND SUPPORTIVE IS ACTUAL
SUPPORTS AND SERVICES FOR
STUDENTS AND THEIR FAMILIES.
( CRYING )
>> Reporter: MANUEL BOJORQUEZ,
CBS NEWS, MIAMI.
>> O'Donnell: TONIGHT, CBS
NEWS HAS LEARNED THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
DISAPPEARANCE OF TWO CHILDREN
FROM IDAHO NOW COVERS AT LEAST
FIVE STATES, INCLUDING A TWO
MILLION-ACRE NATIONAL PARK.
THEIR MOTHER IS UNDER ARREST IN
HAWAII, AND JONATHAN VIGLIOTTI
IS THERE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, AS LORI
VALLOW SITS IN A KAUAI JAIL, NEW
DETAILS ON THE LAST DAYS HER TWO
CHILDREN WERE SEEN ALIVE.
COURT DOCUMENTS REVEAL
17-YEAR-OLDS TYLEE WENT ON A
FAMILY TRIP TO YELLOWSTONE
SEPTEMBER 8.
SHE'S NOT BEEN SEEN SINCE.
POLICE OBTAINED A PHOTO OF TYLEE
INSIDE THE PARK.
SOURCES CLAIM INVESTIGATORS PLAN
TO SEVERAL YELLOWSTONE FOR CLUES
ONCE THE SNOW BELTS INSPECT AND
DOORBELL VIDEO CAPTURES THE LAST
KNOWN IMAGE OF SEVEN-YEAR-OLDS
J.J., PLAYING OUTSIDE A
NEIGHBOR'S HOME IN IDAHO.
HE HASN'T BEEN SEEN SINCE
SEPTEMBER 23.
TWO MONTHS LATER, J.J.'S
GRANDPARENTS IN LOUISIANA ASKED
FOR A WELFARE CHECK.
INVESTIGATORS SAY LORI VALLOW
ALSO SPUN A WEB OF LIES ABOUT
THE CHILDREN.
SHE TOLD POLICE J.J. WAS WITH A
FRIEND IN ARIZONA.
THAT WOMAN LATER TOLD POLICE
VALLOW AND HER NEW HUSBAND, CHAD
DAYBELL, ASKED HER TO LIE.
LORI CLAIMS TYLEE WAS AWAY AT
COLLEGE.
SHE NEVER ENROLLED.
LORI TOLD DAYBELL'S PARENTS SHE
WAS AN EMPTY NESTER.
THE TWO FLEW TO HAWAII DECEMBER
1 ALONE.
>> THE IMPLICATION OF A PARENT
WHO FLIES TO HAWAII AND WON'T
RETURN TO A COURT ORDER IS THAT
SOMETHING VERY UNTOWARD HAS
HAPPENED TO THESE CHILDREN.
>> Reporter: AND POLICE HAVE
SEARCHED THE COUPLE'S CONDO AND
CAR AND SAY THERE ARE NO SIGNS
THE TWO MISSING CHILDREN WERE
HERE IN HAWAII.
VALLOW IS FIGHTING HER
EXTRADITION.
THERE'S A COURT HEARING TOMORROW
TO TRY TO REDUCE HER $5 MILLION
BAIL.
NORAH.
>> O'Donnell: ALL RIGHT,
JONATHAN, THANK YOU.
THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE NEWS
AHEAD RIGHT HERE ON TONIGHT'S
"CBS EVENING NEWS."
MILLIONS ARE IN THE PATH OF
DANGEROUS WEATHER TONIGHT.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE AND WHEN
IT'S EXPECTED TO HIT.
THE PLOT TWIST AT DISNEY.
ITS LONGTIME C.E.O. JUST STEPPED
DOWN.
LATER, THE COFFEE SHOP THAT LETS
CUSTOMERS SEE WHAT'S POSSIBLE IN
THE FACES OF ITS STAFF.
my caree.
my cause,...
my choir.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes...
into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO
is for adults
who are starting HIV-1 treatment
and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines
dolutegravir or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2...
medicines in...
1 pill to help you reach
and then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines...
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day,...
with food...
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if
you're allergic to any of its...
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become
harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening...
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO...
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,...
liver problems,
and liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash
and other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,...
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,...
including hepatitis B or C.
One of the ingredients in DOVATO
may harm your...
unborn baby.
Your doctor may prescribe
a different medicine...
than DOVATO. Your doctor should
do a pregnancy test...
before starting...
DOVATO. Use effective
birth control...
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache, diarrhea, nausea,
trouble sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am...
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment with DOVATO
is right for you.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment with DOVATO
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
♪♪
If you have moderate
to severe psoriasis,
little things can
become your big moment.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not a cream.
It's a pill that treats
plaque psoriasis differently.
With Otezla, 75% clearer
skin is achievable.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated...
...with an increased
risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have
a history of depression...
...or suicidal thoughts or
if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory
tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines,
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Otezla.
Show more of you.
>> O'Donnell: TONIGHT, THERE
ARE WINTER STORM ALERTS IN AT
LEAST 15 STATES FROM THE ROCKY
MOUNTAINS TO MAINE.
PARTS OF KANSAS GOT MORE THAN A
FOOT OF SNOW TODAY.
THERE WERE NUMEROUS ACCIDENTS,
INCLUDING A DEADLY PILEUP ON
INTERSTATE 70.
THE STORM IS PUSHING EAST AND
COULD MAKE TRAVEL DANGEROUS
IT'S THE END OF AN ERA AT DISNEY
TODAY.
BOB IGER RESIGNED AS C.E.O.
EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY.
IGER HAD RUN DISNEY FOR 15
YEARS.
HE'LL STAY ON AS EXECUTIVE
CHAIRMAN THROUGH NEXT YEAR.
THE UNIVERSITY OF OREGON'S
SABRINA IONESCU CAPTIVATED THE
SPORTS WORLD.
SHE BECAMELET FIRST COLLEGE
PLAYER, WOMAN OR MAN, TO RACK UP
2,000 POINTS, 1,000 REBOUNDS,
AND 1,000 ASSISTS IN A CAREER.
IT CAME JUST HOURS AFTER SHE
DELIVERED AN EMOTIONAL TRIBUTE
TO KOBE AND GIGI BRYANT IN
LOS ANGELES.
UP NEXT, WE DISCOVERED SOMETHING
SPECIAL WHILE HERE IN
CHARLESTON: THE COFFEE SHOP WITH
A STAFF THAT KNOWS ALL ABOUT
OVERCOMING OBSTACLES.
I knew about the tremors.
But when I started
seeing things,
I didn't know
what was happening...
so I kept it in.
He started believing things
that weren't true.
I knew something was wrong...
but I didn't say a word.
During the course
of their disease
around 50% of people
with Parkinson's
may experience hallucinations
or delusions.
But now, doctors are prescribing
NUPLAZID.
The only FDA
approved medicine...
proven to significantly reduce
hallucinations and delusions
related to Parkinson's.
Don't take NUPLAZID if you
are allergic to its ingredients.
NUPLAZID can increase the risk
of death
in elderly people
with dementia-related psychosis
and is not for treating symptoms
unrelated to
Parkinson's disease.
NUPLAZID can cause changes
in heart rhythm
and should not be taken
if you have certain
abnormal heart rhythms
or take other drugs
that are known to cause changes
in heart rhythm.
Tell your doctor
about any changes
in medicines you're taking.
The most common side effects are
swelling of the arms and legs
and confusion.
We spoke up and it made
all the difference.
Ask your Parkinson's specialist
about NUPLAZID.
(Mom)
Were you planning on mowing
the lawn today?
[Thunder]
Ask your Parkinson's specialist
(Son)
No.
(Burke)
Seen it. Covered it.
At Farmers Insurance,
we know a thing or two
because we've
seen a thing or two.
So call 1-800 Farmers to
get a quote.
♪ We are Farmers.
Bum-pa-dum, bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
When cravings come on strong,
be stronger...
With Nicorette
Coated Ice Mint.
Layered with flavor.
It's the first and only
coated nicotine lozenge.
For an amazing taste...
...that outlasts your craving.
Nicorette Ice Mint.
How do you get skin happy 24/7?
For an amazing taste...
...that outlasts your craving.
AVEENO®
with prebiotic oat.
It hydrates and softens skin.
So it looks like this.
and you feel like this.
AVEENO® Daily Moisturizer
Get Skin Healthy™
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
(VO)
Over 2,500 dogs compete,
but only one can be named
Westminster Best In Show
Champion.
Congratulations, Siba!
Thanks for choosing Purina Pro
Plan,
the #1 brand trusted by
champions.
So Bob, what do you take
for back pain?
Before I take anything,
I apply topical pain relievers
first.
Salonpas Lidocaine Patch blocks
pain receptors
for effective, non-addictive
relief.
Salonpas Lidocaine.
Patch, roll-on or cream.
Hisamitsu.
Do you have concerns about mild
memory loss related to aging?
Prevagen is the number one
pharmacist-recommended
memory support brand.
You can find it in the vitamin
aisle in stores everywhere.
Prevagen. Healthier brain.
Better life.
- Oh.
- What's going on?
- Oh, darn!
- Let me help.
Here we go.
Lift and push and push!
There... it's up there. Oh, boy.
Hey Joshie...
Wrinkles Send the Wrong Message.
Help prevent them before they
start with Downy WrinkleGuard.
Hey! Bud.
Hey, Pop Pop!
So you won't get caught with
wrinkles again.
[woman laughs]
The good news?
Our protection lasts all day.
The bad news?
Your patience might not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
>> O'Donnell: HERE IN
CHARLESTON, WE'VE BEEN GREETED
WITH A HUGE HELPING OF SOUTHERN
HOSPITALITY, ESPECIALLY AT A
COFFEE SHOP WHERE YOU'LL FIND A
LOT OF SWEETNESS, AND NOT JUST
ON THE MENU.
IT SMELLS LIKE COTTON CANDY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> O'Donnell: AT BITTY AND
BEAU'S COFFEE SHOP, COTTON CANDY
FRAPPES ARE THE HOUSE SPECIALTY.
IS THIS A POPULAR DRINK?
>> YEAH, VERY POPULAR.
>> O'Donnell: BUT THEY'RE NOT
THE ONLY THING THAT MAKES THIS
PLACE TRULY SPECIAL.
>> VERY GOOD, RIGHT?
>> O'Donnell: WOW.
IT'S THE PEOPLE WHO WORK HERE.
>> IS THAT IT TODAY?
>> Reporter: LIKE TRISTA
KUTCHER.
AS YOU CAN SEE I'M NOT QUALIFIED
TO WORK IN A COFFEE SHOP.
I NEED MORE TRAINING.
>> IT TAKES MORE PRACTICE.
>> O'Donnell: AMY WRITING IS
THE OWNER.
>> AS THE PARENT OF A CHILD WITH
SPECIAL NEEDS YOU START TO THINK
ABOUT THEIR FUTURE AND ONE OF
THE OBSTACLES PEOPLE WITH
DISABILITIES FACE IS FINDING
MEANINGFUL EMPLOYMENT.
AND THE COFFEE SHOP WAS BORNE
OUT OF THAT NEED.
>> Reporter: TWO OF AMY'S
CHILDREN HAVE DOWN SYNDROME,
BITTY AND BEAU.
>> FOR A LONG TIME, PEOPLE WITH
DISABILITIES HAVE HAD
OPPORTUNITIES TO WORK BUT
THEY'VE BEEN IN THE BACK.
THEIR FACES HAVEN'T BEEN SEEN,
SO AT BITTY AND BEAU'S COFFEE,
THE FIRST FACE YOU SEE WHEN YOU
WALK IN IS SOMEONE LIKE SAM.
>> O'Donnell: SO, SAM, WHAT'S
IT LIKE WORKING HERE AT BITTY
AND BEAU'S?
>> I'M HERE TO DO SOME WORK.
AND I'M NOT HEIR TO MESS AROUND.
I LOVE DANCE PARTIES, BUT I'M--
I'M HERE TO GET THE JOB DONE.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> O'Donnell: SOMETIMES DANCE
PARTIES ARE PART OF THE JOB,
ESPECIALLY SINCE SAM HAZELTINE
WAS RECENTLY PROMOTED.
EVERYBODY THAT WALKS THROUGH THE
DORS HERE LEAVES WITH NEW
PERSPECTIVE, KNOWS THAT THESE
INDIVIDUALS, THEIR LIVES HAVE
VALUE, AND THEY DESERVE TO BE
ACCEPTED AND INCLUDED.
>> ME, TRISTA, WE'RE NOT BROKEN.
WE'RE NOT BROKEN.
>> O'Donnell: THERE ARE NOW
FIVE    B BITTY AND BEAU'S COFFE
SHOPS.
>> WE REALLY FEEL LIKE THIS IS A
PLACE OF HOPE AND WE'RE JUST
GETTING STARTED.
>> O'Donnell: THAT'S THEIR
HASHTAG, NOT BROKEN.
AND NOW I HAVE SOME FRIENDS FOR
LIFE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
We are the Thrivers.
Women with metastatic
breast cancer
Standing in the struggle.
Hustling through the hurt.
Asking for science not sorrys.
Our time
for more time —
has come.
Living longer is possible
and proven in women taking
KISQALI plus fulvestrant
or a nonsteroidal aromatase
inhibitor.
KISQALI is the only treatment
in its class
with proven overall survival
results in 2 clinical trials.
Helping women live longer with
HR+, HER2-
metastatic breast cancer.
KISQALI was also significantly
more effective
at delaying disease
progression
versus a nonsteroidal
aromatase inhibitor
or fulvestrant alone.
KISQALI can cause lung problems
or an abnormal heartbeat,
which can lead to death.
It can cause serious liver
problems
and low white blood
cell counts
that may result in severe
infections.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have new or worsening
symptoms,
including breathing problems,
cough, chest pain,
a change in your heartbeat,
dizziness...
yellowing of the skin or eyes,
dark urine, tiredness,
loss of appetite,
abdomen pain, bleeding,
bruising, fever, chills, or
other symptoms of an infection,
are or plan to become
pregnant, or breastfeeding.
Avoid grapefruit during
treatment.
KISQALI is not approved for
use with tamoxifen.
It's our time.
To continue to shine
Because we are the Thrivers.
Ask your doctor about KISQALI,
the only treatment
in its class
proven to help women live
longer in 2 clinical trials.
Wow!
That's Ensure Max Protein,
with high protein
and 1 gram sugar.
It's a sit-up, Banana!
Bend at the waist!
I'm tryin'!
Keep it up. You'll get there.
Whoa-hoa-hoa!
30 grams of protein,
and one gram of sugar.
ENSURE Max Protein.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
and one gram of sugar.
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
>> O'Donnell: THE HALL IS
FILLING UP FOR THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE BEGINNING AT
8:00 EASTERN TIME RIGHT HERE ON
CBS.
GAYLE KING AND I WILL MODERATE
WITH MAJOR GARRETT, MARGARET
BRENNAN AND BILL WHITAKER
JOINING US.
UNTIL THEN, THAT'S TONIGHT'S
"CBS EVENING NEWS."
I'M NORAH O'DONNELL IN
CHARLESTON, SOUTH CAROLINA.
WE'LL SEE YO
McKissack and McKissack
is the nation's oldest
black-owned design
and construction firm.
Before Mike, we were desperate.
There were not a lot
of opportunities for
black-owned businesses
to compete.
Mike saw that and he leveled
the playing field for
black-owned businesses.
Over the years, we have
heard a lot of talk.
But Mike came in, and he
actually did something about it.
And that's how Mike will get
it done as president.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
I'm Amy Klobuchar and I approve
this message.
We live in a country of shared
dreams.
That no matter where you come
from.
No matter the color of your
skin.
No matter who you love.
That you can make it in the
United States of America.
So I stand before you today
as the grandaughter of an iron
ore miner.
As the daughter of a teacher and
a newspaperman.
As the first woman elected to
the U.S. Senate from the state
of Minnesota.
And a candidate for president of
the United States.