[happy sounds]
Girl: Because Isaac's got
special needs,
Daddy's always
sleeping downstairs.
- There, there.
Nick: We're here
to create a brighter future.
Girl: My mum's always
stuck in the house,
makin' my mum more tired.
- It literally just feels like
the walls are just
closing in on me.
Nick: To build a better home
for a little boy
who desperately needs our help.
Woman: All the hopes and dreams
that you have for your children,
all those things have been
taken away from him.
Nick: To help this family,
everyone is taking it
to the limit.
At some stage, we've got to go,
"That's enough."
Woman: I'm here for a reason,
to make it all look wonderful
and for it to work, surely.
- We're doing it
for a reason here.
Nick: And this one might just
get the better of us.
- This is the most difficult
job that I've done yet.
- It's a lot bigger
than what we was hopin'.
- Can't wait to see it all
presented back to the family.
- Wow.
- I like it.
- You've made this
a home again.
- We have nine days
to complete the build,
all the usual suspects
are here,
and Julia Kendell
is our designer this week,
but where are we going to find
an army up a cul de sac
in a village in Derbyshire?
[whistle]
- This is DIY SOS,
the Big Build!
[cheering]
[playing "Lights,"
by Ellie Goulding].
♪♪
Glasgow in Derbyshire
is home to the Smith family,
and their official
spokesperson Connie,
age seven and a half.
- In my family, I have my dad,
who's a bit grumpy,
[laughing]
Mom, she's very silly,
my little sister, Violet,
is very noisy.
- Ah?
Connie: And my little brother,
Isaac, he's very giggly.
Nick: Mum Rachel,
and Dad Andy, met in 2004,
when Rachel got a job where Andy
works as a civil engineer.
And it wasn't long
before romance blossomed.
- I ended up having
to actually ask you out,
because I would still--
I'd still be waiting there.
- I thought you'd say no.
[laughing]
Nick: Despite the stand-off,
they married in 2006,
and in the following year,
Rachel gave birth to Connie.
Rachel: We were so excited,
weren't we,
to be having our first child,
and just absolutely loved it.
It was just
in that little bubble, really,
weren't we, I suppose?
Nick: Yes, life was good.
The family moved
to a bigger house,
and were overjoyed
when they discovered
they were expecting
their second baby,
this time a little boy.
- For me, I wasn't bothered
either way, you know,
and again cliché, I know,
but I thought as long as
baby's healthy,
I'm-- I'm not
really bothered.
Nick: Rachel had no reason
to believe otherwise.
But 48 hours
before the due date,
she woke in agonizing pain
and was rushed into hospital.
Rachel: Then we went from like,
one midwife in the room
to there being like,
ten people in the room,
and we just realized
something's drastically wrong.
Nick: The pain
was Rachel's placenta
detaching from her uterus.
She had hemorrhaged
seven pints of blood,
leaving both her
and baby's life in danger.
Andy: I asked them
was it life-threatening,
and they said--
then she nodded,
and I said-- she then said
you was within five minutes
of walking out of here
on your own.
Nick: Thankfully,
Rachel pulled through,
but Isaac had been without
oxygen for around 20 minutes,
causing extensive
brain damage.
- I remember the doctors
coming 'round and thinkin',
"Where's my baby?"
Nick: Isaac was taken
into neonatal care,
where he stayed
for four weeks.
Andy: I saw a little boy
that I want to protect.
I was-- fast forwarding
and I was thinkin' about
what I used to do with my dad
when I was growin' up.
Having a little lad you can
play about with
and do everything
that I did as a boy.
- You just feel that someone's
ripped your heart out
of your chest
and just stamped on it
closely followed by just--
just a sadness
that just engulfs you.
And then you're feeling guilty
for feeling sad
because you should
just be feeling grateful
that you've got him.
- Stretch right.
Good boy.
Nick: Isaac has the most severe
form of cerebral palsy,
with little to no movement.
He can't feed or communicate
in any way.
He has a life-limiting
condition,
and has been left
almost totally blind.
- I just want him
to be my little boy.
I want it to be able to be--
son and dad.
Good boy, good boy.
Hey, you're smilin'.
Nick: Andy and Rachel
are fighting to give Isaac
the best possible life.
- Yay!
Well done me!
[laughing]
Rachel: He can show pleasure,
which is lovely,
because at one point
we were told
that we might not even
see a smile.
[laughing]
Nick: The family are doing
their best to manage,
but every aspect of life at home
is becoming tougher
to accommodate Isaac's needs.
It's physically getting harder
day to day.
He's gonna get bigger
and bigger, and I'll be scared
tryin' to get him
up and down the stairs.
Bathin's become an issue
for the same reasons.
Tryin' to get outside in the
garden's a task in itself,
we've got a big step
at the back door,
none of it's level.
The front room's become
not just Isaac's bedroom,
but his playroom,
where he has his physio.
Nick: And because of Isaac's
need for round-the-clock care,
it's also Dad Andy's bedroom.
Connie: Mommy and Daddy
sleep apart
because one of them
has to sleep with Isaac
because, um, sometimes
he cries in the night.
Nick: Rachel has become
Isaac's carer in the daytime,
juggling physio,
hospital visits,
and his everyday care,
whilst looking after
the rest of the family
in a really cramped house.
Connie: My mum and dad
help Isaac a lot.
He has to have loads
of equipment.
Rachel: Everythin's
on top of us.
It creates a lot of pressure
after school,
because Isaac
needs to go to bed,
and so the kitchen's essentially
just become the one--
we tend to just live,
do everythin', really,
in the kitchen--
- Yeah, yeah, we do.
Rachel: It really does
feel like all the walls
are just closin' in.
[baby sounds]
Connie: My mum's just always
stuck in the house.
I think the house
is makin' my mum more tired
because it's so small.
Nick: Not surprisingly,
the whole family
are at breaking point,
and that's why we're here.
All right, so what do you need
us to do to the house?
- It's about givin' Isaac his
sp-- his own space and dignity,
and for the house to function
for a family of five.
Rachel: Just bein' able to do
just something normal,
like watch a bit of telly
at weekends and just--
and a bit of a place to go to
to relax, really,
'cause obviously Isaac's bedroom
is our living room.
Nick: The house is fighting
against you, basically.
Rachel: Yeah.
Nick: If we can get this
turned around
to the house that you actually
need for the family,
a big change in lifestyle?
Rachel: It would take
a massive pressure off,
especially me, day-to-day.
Nick: Okay.
There's a lot to do,
so we are going to have
to destroy your family home
in order to give you
the home that you want, I think.
Ready?
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Plus, she looks like she wants
to tell a story or something.
You chatted all the way
through that, didn't you?
You are possibly the chattiest--
[baby sounds]
I can't get a word in edgewise,
and that doesn't
happen very often.
[laughing]
Despite the brave faces,
things need to change.
Luckily, this lot thinks so too.
Good morning, everybody.
Everyone: Good morning.
Nick: There you go,
see they're--
they're all very friendly.
We need to get you going,
because we need
to let these guys at the house
and don't come back
over the next three days,
because it will be really,
really upsetting.
[laughing]
He's giggling!
So, it's ta-ra to the Smiths
and hello to this lot
of Prince Charmings.
Yeah.
- Okay lads, you take the back
there and get in there.
- Go and have yourself
a look at it,
we'll come out
and join you in a minute.
Nick: And they're
straight in there,
and that's no bad thing,
because completing the job
in nine days is never easy.
In fact, it's ludicrous.
It's busy, look.
[chuckling]
This is the only way
we stand a chance
of getting it done.
Hit it hard and tear it out.
"Rip it up and start again."
No, we won't play that song,
it's too old.
But as well as destroying,
these guys
have to build, quickly.
A whole timber frame extension
by the end of the day.
What saith you, Mr. Perryman?
Ah yeah, easy.
Maybe. By lunchtime.
[laughing]
- Them pills are workin'.
- He's great, isn't he?
He's Mr. Enthusiasm.
There are another 80
enthusiastic people here today,
following the meticulous plan
laid out by our designer
du jour.
["Sexyback"
by Justin Timberlake]
Meet Big Dave.
Just fooling with you.
It's of course
the lovely Julia Kendell.
Although, I'm not sure
about the pick axe.
Slightly terrifying, innit?
These houses
are actually lovely.
I mean, beautifully built
miner's cottages.
- They are beautiful.
- And we're gonna
mess them up.
[laughing]
- Well, we're completely ripping
the guts out of this place.
- Yeah.
- The reason being
we have got to create
for the whole family
a wonderful, big space
that's easy for Rachel
to be able to navigate
with a wheelchair, and--
and just somewhere
that's got a fantastic sense
of vibrancy and positivity
about it again.
Nick: Scrubs up well
for a builder, doesn't she?
Julia's design has us removing
most of the walls downstairs
to create that sense
of space and flow,
starting with the old
living room,
which we'll turn into a new
bedroom and wet room for Isaac.
The old galley kitchen is going,
in its place,
a spacious
kitchen-cum-dining area,
and at the back of the house,
we're constructing
a timber frame extension
on existing foundations
to create a comfortable lounge.
Right, let's pop upstairs.
Here, we're widening the old
claustrophobic hallway,
remodeling the family bathroom
and bedrooms,
and we'll be installing
a monitoring system
for Rachel and Andy
so that sleeping downstairs
on a mattress
will be a thing of the past.
Julia: I mean, they're
a great team together,
but, you know,
they need to be a couple
together again now.
Nick: Yeah.
- Um, so I think in--
in doing what we're doing,
we're going to create a home
that really does allow her
to breathe again, I think.
Chris: Come on, boys.
Nick: To achieve this,
Chris is sending a crew
of 30 to destroy the upstairs
and 50 downstairs to remove
all the internal walls.
We're literally tearing it apart
quicker than we
can get rid of it.
And Truck-it-in Skips.
Now tell me this bloke doesn't
look like John Prescott.
- How you doing, mate?
Nice to see ya.
- Yeah.
- You're here to save the day.
Nick: But the workload's
not worrying him or her,
because we're working
with skilled people
that know exactly
what they're doing.
And Billy.
Billy: What I'm doing
is I'm getting rid
of all the old cables.
Unfortunately, they've run
some new ones in
and I got rid of them
as well, but.
Nick: Pilchard.
Unbelievably, the timber frame
extension is almost up,
making the floor space
downstairs bigger by a third.
Why is there
a double truss here
and why are these little
extensions in here?
- Oh, we just had some extra
stuff that we had to use up.
[laughing]
Nick: At the back, we're
stripping the old garden,
which is massive,
a colossal 29 metres by 10.
Luckily, that's
Julian's territory.
Wait, look, look,
look through there.
Look, look who's got his feet
under the table
with the neighbor?
A cup of coffee.
Mark: Oh my goodness.
- Choccie biscuit,
conversation in the sun.
Which is no bad thing,
because access is an issue,
so the lovely neighbors
have allowed us
to destroy their fencing.
That's nice, innit?
Julian: The neighbors
the house up on the corner--
- Yeah.
- That was the
knocker-upper's house.
He says he has a big stick
with like a knocker on the end,
and he walks up the street,
bangs everybody's doors,
up, back down,
get everybody out of bed.
- But what happens
if you're already up?
The missus wouldn't be
too happy, would she?
Nick: Do you want to finish
this section off for us now
so we can move on
to something else?
- We should go over to Jules
and see how he's doing
in the garden.
- I'm not in the garden,
I'm here.
- We won't go over to see Jules.
[laughing]
Nick: Imagine, you have him
for one hour this week,
we've had him for 16 years.
- Oh, done that.
Nick: Out back,
the activity has picked up,
and what we need
is a creative plan
for this colossal space.
Luckily, Julia
has come up with one.
The design marries
both the family
and Isaac's need
for sensory stimulation.
We'll be sourcing around
100 railway sleepers,
which will frame an artificial
grass descent,
with sweet-smelling borders
and rustling plants.
At the bottom,
a much-needed therapy hut
with hydro pool
so Isaac can stretch
and work his muscles every day.
It's impressive, but,
to be honest, very ambitious.
- It's gonna be so stunning
if we ever get it done.
So there is heck
of a lot to do.
Nick: That's an
understatement.
- C'mon, lads, let's have it.
Nick: Right, we'll start
with the ten tonne of concrete
required for the hydro pool
room foundations.
- Going on there, going on.
Nick: Therapy is vital
to Isaac's health and happiness,
but he currently only has access
to it twice a week
at his specialist school,
and you're about to see
just how much it means to him.
Rachel: We still don't know
a lot ourselves
about what the future's
gonna hold, you know,
in terms of what
his development's going to be.
- He's giggling a lot, isn't he?
[giggling]
Rachel: He has
a vision impairment,
we don't know to what extent
the images are sort of comin'
into his brain if he likes--
strugglin' to be processed
because of his brain damage,
basically.
Therapist: You see a lot, that
one, well done, Isaac.
Rachel: Any therapy we do with
him helps with his condition.
Therapist: A lot of red lights.
That's very good.
He catches where they are.
Isaac is absolutely a dream.
He's a very happy young boy,
very sociable.
He needs the environments
to be right for him
so that he can develop
all his senses.
He needs stimulation.
I mean, Isaac absolutely
loves swimmin' as well,
so somethin' to do to give him
an opportunity with water
would be lovely.
Oh, good, lovely.
Rachel: I try to take things
one day at a time,
I try and not think
too far ahead.
We just want to try and help him
be the best
that he can be, really.
[giggling]
Nick: And that's
what we want to do for him
in his own home.
Unfortunately, the house
is currently being held up
like a melon on cocktail sticks,
so it's time to get
some strength back in
with steel joists.
And what we need is someone
intelligent to explain
what's happening here.
What's going on
at the moment?
Somebody needs to explain
what's going on.
Julian: They're lifting it up.
Nick: I can see
they're lifting it up.
Don't patronize me.
- They're doing it the, um,
Egyptian style.
- Murdering each other.
What have the Egyptians done?
- When you're setting
a massive piece of stone
you place it on ice,
so you can get the straps out
and the ice melts
and it slowly
goes down into place.
- How do they make ice
in Egypt?
- Well, that's what I was
going to say.
I didn't know whether it was
the Egyptians,
but it was somebody done it.
- It's like talking to a walking
encyclopedia, really, innit.
An encyclopedia
that's lost the index.
This is steel number two
of five to go in,
all donated to the build
by our lovely trades.
You got a three or four-hour
turnaround for us there
on the steels,
thank you very much.
- Yeah, that's no worries, mate.
- Well, and it's a lot
of money's worth too,
so why have you decided
to join and help out?
- Um, my sister's got a daughter
who basically got
cerebral palsy,
um, they give her
a week to live.
Um, she's still here now
and she's fightin',
and she's what 28
the other week, so,
that's going week to week,
so--
- Wow.
- she's doing really well.
The lads have all
contributed their time, so.
For a good cause.
- Brilliant.
Well, look, we really appreciate
you joining as well.
Thank you.
Julian: See you again
in the morning.
Nick: All right, see you
tomorrow morning.
Thank you very much.
Out the back,
the guys are now tamping
the concrete foundations,
which should set in time
for a big push
in the garden tomorrow.
What a day, what a day,
and all the house is now
held up on acrow props,
because we've taken walls out
and put new steels in there,
new steels in here,
a new window there,
in fact, new windows
all around the house
apart from two windows.
A chimney breast
taken out there,
through the acrow props again,
grooves in the floor
for drainage,
through more acrow props which
hold up the back of the house,
because it isn't there anymore,
because this
is the new extension
with a new roof on already,
look at the size of it.
It's just fantastic.
Back through the acrow props
to a doorway that wasn't here
this morning.
Oh, and we've made a good start
on the electrics
and the plumbing.
Not bad, eh?
Tomorrow, we'll get busy.
Good morning.
A little bit too close?
All right.
Yesterday was
a magnificent day.
I feel today is gonna be
equally magnificent,
although we are facing a bit
of an issue with access
and egress to the garden.
We'll work it out though.
Yesterday we cleared out
the old backyard,
or bomb site,
as we like to call it,
so today, it's on
to the hard graft
constructing our
ambitious new garden.
Man: Well, all this area here
is going to be artificial grass.
- Yeah.
- So all this grass
has got to come off,
the top has got to come off.
Nick: Landscaping
almost 300 square metres
is frankly a big ask from Julia,
but I have to say it's not
worrying Farmer Giles.
Sorry. Farmer Jules.
Julian:
♪ Dig-dig-ig-dig-diggy! ♪
♪ Dig a little trench with me! ♪
[honking]
Nick: Or Mark.
But it is affecting Billy.
He's none too happy, as I've
dabbled with his wiring.
Billy: They filled it in
with the concrete,
and they forgot
to put the pipe--
Nick: Well, I asked them not to.
- But you shouldn't.
- It's got a feed box
on the outside,
it goes up on the outside
of the building.
Billy: The parties that are
involved must be informed,
not someone come along
and say, "We--"
Don't, Mark.
We don't need people
coming along and saying,
"Well, we ain't gonna
put it in there."
Don't belittle us!
You're belittling!
- Who's belittling?
- You are!
- I'm not!
We don't want cuddles.
We just want
to get it sorted.
Nick: You might
want a cuddle?
- He doesn't,
I don't need a cuddle.
No, I'm upset because
no one involved us.
We do it for a reason, this,
not to be underminded.
And that's what we've
been done, underminded.
- Underminded?
[laughing]
I think for the next few hours,
Billy is best left alone,
or avoided-ed.
In the house upstairs,
the wall stud himself,
Mr. Frediani,
along with some new buddies
are busy changing
the room configuration
so they feel more spacious.
Man: I just wanna
pick these bricks up.
- Yeah.
- They're floating
in no man's land.
Nick: Nothing is being
left to chance.
Now, since Isaac's birth,
Dad Andy hasn't slept
in the bedroom upstairs,
but on a mattress
in the living room,
so he can keep an eye
on his son,
and that has
to have taken its toll.
You're one
of the world's worriers.
- I am a world's worrier.
I don't know
if I'm the worst,
but I'm certainly not the best.
[laughing]
I worry about things that--
that I can't
have an influence over,
but that being said,
it doesn't stop me worrying.
The big thing is Isaac
and the kids, Connie and Violet.
How they deal
with the family life that's--
that they've been brought into.
Connie, with her,
she's dealing with adapting to
Isaac, 'cause she's--
her brother,
with the needs he's got.
Isaac, for the first six months
of his life, is in pain,
abdominal spasms
and muscle spasms.
And the impact was huge.
When he was still in hospital,
she drew a picture and stuck it
on his bedroom wall, and that--
that upset me, because
she drew him with a big smile,
saying he's cute.
Within two weeks
of him being home,
she drew another picture,
and it had a big sad face,
because he's always crying,
I don't want him here.
And that's really tough, too.
I do worry about
how tough, mentally,
she has to be at her age.
- Do you worry
about the future,
or try not to think about it?
- It does scare me.
There is a life expectancy
for all of us.
Isaac's has been compromised,
but we don't know
by how much.
And once that's been said
to you, how do you deal with it?
- This kind of thing
will put a massive pressure
on your relationships,
and it has to have done,
the stress, the strain,
the worry,
the sleep deprivation.
- I've seen Rachel when she's--
that strength isn't there.
And I guess that's one
of the worries that--
that might become the norm.
I do think a lot
of Rachel at home,
and wanting to be there
to help her out
with pressures
of dealing with Isaac.
We have drawn
on a strong relationship.
And I think the value--
the value of that to me
has made me worry a bit more,
'cause I don't want to lose it.
You know, I've worried
that the stress is gonna be--
reach breaking point.
To have Rachel
in an environment
that is a stress-free,
that's one less stress
that's on Rachel's shoulders.
That will hopefully have a--
a release of the pressure
all 'round,
from the relationship
point of view on the family.
- And you're still obviously
very much in love with her?
- Oh yeah.
'Cause she is just a--
she's amazing.
Nick: It's clear to me
that the work we're doing
on the house
won't just help ease
the situation with Isaac,
but relieve the pressure
for Andy and Rachel, too.
There is, however,
a slight problem.
We're getting
numerous deliveries,
but none of them are carrying
the key ingredient
required for Julia's
epic garden design.
- Okay, not to worry.
Yeah, no, I understand.
Okay.
Nick: She wants 100
straight railway sleepers
to cut into circular paths.
- I'm so keen to keep
the shape that we've got,
because I think it's gonna work
so beautifully,
so I'm gonna have to amend
the design a little bit.
- Eighty-two treated joists.
- Treated joists,
about 40 metres off,
rather than sleepers.
- If we can get 50,
then it allows us
a little bit of leeway.
- I shall see what I can do.
Nick: Hm.
An eight-inch-by-two
rectangular wooden block
doesn't sound very circular.
Eight-by-two joists
will not give you a curve.
Julia: Well, according to my,
uh, my garden specialists,
who happen to be experts--
- But you just said
they're going to try
and get eight-by-two joists.
Man: But she liked
the feature of the timber
sticking out the back.
- Oh, goodness.
But she's designing--
at some stage,
we've got to go,
"That's enough."
- We've changed.
- We listen to the designer--
- As opposed to listening
to the TV presenter?
You know, come on,
I am here for a reason,
to make it all look wonderful
and for it to work, surely.
- You know,
there comes a point
where you've got to say,
well, we're not
gonna achieve that, are we?
Julia: Yeah, but we're not quite
at that point yet, though.
- It's achievable.
- Thank you.
Before I had a conversation
with Nick,
I was quite happy, actually,
just so long as it ended up
working the way that I wanted,
but now that we've had
that conversation,
I'm absolutely determined that
it's gonna be finished, frankly.
Nick: Fighting talk
from Kendell there,
who used to be a boxer
when she was a man.
There's one bit of the garden
design I am happy with.
When it's up,
the therapy hut will house
a hydro pool and hoist,
which means more electrics.
- We've wired upstairs,
sparks to the bathroom.
Nick: Billy and his team
are installing
over 1,000 metres of electrical
cable in this build,
which is a big responsibility.
- We just found two cables.
We're just wondering
where they go.
[laughing]
Nick: Well, you can't
win them all, Bill.
Something won't switch on.
We're winning
in the old living room, however,
as the timber frame for Isaac's
wet room has emerged.
And the boys on the roof
have been very busy.
What do you make
of this site, then?
'Cause it's kind of weird
and different and...
- Yeah, it's busy.
I've never seen so many
blokes on site.
It's nice, we've got so many
people all of the time
who want to do-- you know.
- Sometimes you give money
to charities,
you don't know where it goes,
this you can actually see,
physically,
what a difference you're
making for somebody's life.
Nick: This big fella', is he one
of your lot?
- That's John.
- I'm granddad.
Man: That's granddad.
Nick: Is that right?
Man: My father-in-law.
Man: He's the godfather
of faces.
Nick: Godfather of faces.
- Yeah, yeah.
[laughing]
Nick: And Chris's team
should feel very proud
of their performances
in the bedroom.
Chris: Well, basically,
we've had to join this in,
we've replaced
all the rotten walls,
ready for a big my day tomorrow.
The plasterers will be here,
and we can start putting this
little baby back together again.
Nick: Now that's an offer
we can't refuse.
[playing The Godfather Waltz,
from Il Padrino]
He really is the godfather.
It's our third day on site,
and it's centerstage for
Mr. Frediani's favourite trade,
a veritable spread
of plasterers.
- My boys!
Look at 'em, that.
They're like ants all over it.
So, a couple rolls of scrim
up on these.
Nick: Big hands, mind you.
Rachel felt the walls
were closing in on her,
so Chris and the boys
have been working on
getting the upstairs area
feeling and looking
more spacious.
[drilling]
Man: Beautiful.
- We've just pushed these walls
out to give more access up here,
so they're gonna re-board
and then re-skim the upstairs,
giving the sparkies
and the plumber
time downstairs
to finish the kitchen area,
but I'm very excited
'cause there's about
16 plasterers on board,
and I've only got
the upstairs to do,
so they'll eat this.
- Nice.
Nick: Christopher
is a happy work bunny,
but after Cablegate,
I'm approaching Billy
with extreme caution.
Am I allowed
to hug you today?
- Hey! Of course you are!
That's all forgotten, that's all
forgotten, sausage.
Nick: I have to say,
I'm sorry that
I underminded you.
- Oh, uh, it's a long,
it's um...
What am I going to say now?
[laughing]
Nick: Aw, he's all totes emosh.
Outside, they're bricking it,
and in the garden,
someone's digging it,
having a lovely time,
courtesy of
a three-tonne machine.
- Could I get a bit more
over here?
- Yeah, please.
Nick: But despite
my reasonably
and politely
explained objections,
Julia is refusing to scale back
on the garden design,
which is putting these guys
under pressure.
Man: We're-- we're, uh,
we're on top of it, we're uh...
Like I say, we're getting there.
Nick: All right,
enjoy the rest of the day,
and I'll try to keep
the designer away from you.
[laughing]
At the bottom
of the controversial slope,
the therapy hut is up,
and I have to say,
is looking fantastic.
It's being clad
in natural cedar,
which is hard-wearing and,
by the way, smells fantastic.
I wish you could have
a scratch-and-sniff telly
so you could smell this cedar.
It's really beautiful,
very lovely.
It's pretty, innit?
- Yeah.
Nick: Feel free to dance
to the music, by the way.
[upbeat music]
On the inside,
we're waiting for the plasterers
to do their thing.
Look at them go.
Magnificent, it's flying up.
- It's manic in here,
absolutely manic in here.
It's good luck, though.
Man 2: What? It's mad.
Man 1: He's mad.
Nick: Nevertheless,
Chris is plowing on
with making the floors
wheelchair friendly.
- Well, you've got the walls,
and a slight discrepancy,
so we need to self-level it
tonight, get everyone out,
so tomorrow we can carry on
with the plaster-boarding
and the skimming.
That's all planned.
Nick: And the reason
everyone's working so hard,
well, it's the family.
This house hasn't fitted
their needs for some time,
and that's especially hard
for Mum Rachel,
who feels trapped
in her own home.
What would people
not understand
about what you do
on a day-to-day basis?
How do you-- How do you cope?
- The answer is I don't know.
Every day with a child
with special needs is just hard,
even just gettin' him dressed,
gettin' him in and out
of his pram, puttin' him to bed,
he's on pain relief
all the time
because he has
a lot of muscle spasms
as part of his cerebral palsy.
He's got sleep disorder,
so we have broken sleep
most nights,
and that makes it
difficult to function.
I always think if you get
in sleep,
you can pretty much cope
with anythin',
that's become like,
the norm, really,
broken sleep every night.
- Well, that's
an internationally banned
form of torture.
- Yeah.
It's a-- I can see why.
- How do you think Andy
copes with it?
- I always worry more about Andy
than what I do about me.
It's just put a massive strain
on our relationship together.
I always used to feel that
nothing could sort of touch us,
but as times sort of gone on,
it's just hard sometimes.
I think Andy's struggled
a lot more than me,
to be honest.
I know he feels
a lot of guilt.
His life hasn't really
sort of changed,
he still goes out to work
every day
whereas I'm at home-- the need--
He worries
about me a lot.
- Would it be fair to say
it's been wearing you out?
- I feel--
I feel pretty wrung out, to be
honest, just lately.
I do have my days
when I could just sit and cry.
It could just sort of
come over me all of a sudden.
If I was to actually
start cryin',
properly cryin',
I would be worried
that I wouldn't be able to stop.
- You could see every day
what Isaac gets from you,
what do you get from Isaac?
- Just the joy
from seeing him laugh,
the fact that he can show
pleasure for things and--
it's just-- it's just amazin'.
Every single day is like
the first time you've seen it.
[laughing]
But even if a doctor
categorically told me
he's never going to do this,
I think, as a parent,
you've still got
that fighting spirit,
that well, no, actually,
he might be able
to do something,
you never do know.
There's always got a bit
of a hope there,
and I suppose that's
what keeps us going, really.
[happy sounds]
[birds tweeting]
Nick: Well, we might be
2,500 man hours in,
but this place
is far from finished,
and Mark knows it.
[beeping]
Mark: Where do you
want to be today, then?
Man: The pub?
Mark: Really, where do you
want to be here?
- I want this circle feature in,
just to prove that it does work,
so when Nick comes back,
he can say sorry.
- Is that Nick,
the garden designer,
or Nick the electrician?
- Nick the oracle.
- Nick the oracle, right, okay.
- So we can say
we were right.
Nick: I'm not accustomed
to sticking my nose in,
but I will say getting 10 tonnes
of hard-core down
in four hours
is asking the impossible.
[whistling]
- That's it.
[continue whistling]
Nick: But there
is no escaping this job.
Mark: If that's
all done tonight,
I'm going to pull my pants down
and run down the garden
with my bare bum out.
Nick: Yeah, please don't.
You know who I blame?
Kendell, that's who.
- It's going to get done,
honestly.
Have faith.
The guys are already--
do you see how many
there are out there?
- Yes, and they're all
looking at each other going,
"Help!"
See?
Irrespective
of the garden issues,
we've got a schedule
to stick to,
so the kitchen's arrived
and joiners are joining things,
but the inside
isn't quite ready.
However, they are smiling.
- Are we all happy?
All: Yeah.
- And they're all happy,
Look, I didn't have to give them
any money.
Look at that, cup of tea,
on the go,
whilst travelling up.
See, he's happy!
Look!
Nick: Chris's boys have now
happily worked their way
over virtually every piece
of board in the place,
that's every wall
and ceiling.
Man: Another hour and a half.
Skimming this
and this 'round here,
and then we'll be done.
Nick: The old living room
is gone.
In its place
is a wheelchair-accessible
bedroom and wet room.
- It needs to come up.
Nick: Whilst we're
making it easier
to get into the house
with widened doorways
and a new flattened curb.
[drilling]
There are no
half measures here,
which means
a phenomenal amount of work,
so Billy is boosting morale.
- My granddaughter's
got a pet mouse, and it--
it died, I got the phone call,
it's died.
It was called Elvis.
It was caught in a trap.
It's a joke.
[laughing]
Nick: I think
I preferred him angry.
[laughing]
- That's the last
bit of plastering.
Have you enjoyed it?
- Yes, every bit.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'd be here for a
bloomin' six weeks,
doing this by meself, normally.
It's a good crack.
Throw the boys at it,
and they've got it done.
Nick: Okay, just four days
left in the build.
Normally at this stage,
we'd have broken
the back of the garden,
but this job looks
like it might break us.
The thing is,
we simply can't ask any more
of the people working on it.
- Very suddenly,
we've got to put a gentle rocket
up the posterior of the garden.
- Of the garden, right.
Nick: You can't ask any more!
- It's a very big job.
It's a lot bigger
than what we was hopin'.
Nick: Yes, and I said
the design wouldn't help.
We've been trying to cut circles
out of square timber
for the past five days,
and it's nowhere near
finished.
I warned you, I said.
Man: Needs round posting
all the way, innit, that.
Both sides.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that'll do it, won't it?
- It will be a lot easier,
wouldn't it?
Nick: Finally, a voice
of reason, thank you.
- That's more
like, [indistinct].
Nick: This is getting
ridiculous, we're--
we're not going
to finish this,
it doesn't matter
what the designers say.
There's come a point
where we've got to go,
that's it, that's enough.
Whatever we've got,
we just have to lawn
the rest of it and finish.
- Well, let's give it
until 3 o'clock this afternoon,
'cause we've got a lot
of extra people turning up,
and if they turn up,
we'll get a good push on,
and then we'll call it at 3.
Is that all right?
- Fair enough.
So, the garden
is in the balance,
but at least the house
is looking less wrecked,
which means the decorators
get to splash on some color.
- Ooh!
Nick: Just realized
she's on telly.
Woman: Well, it's gonna be
to the wire, I suppose,
uh, everybody knows
what they're doing, don't they?
We're used to a bit of pressure.
Nick: The decorators aren't
the only team under pressure.
The joiners have a lot
on their plate.
Julia's design has
space-saving cupboards
and a fabulous new kitchen area.
- Looking good, innit?
Nick: Yes, it is.
- Can't wait to see it
all finished
and everyone's
out of the way
and when it gets presented
back to the family.
Nick: Yeah, that's something
we're all looking forward to.
Every single member
of this family
has been affected
by Isaac's condition.
When Isaac was born,
Connie was only four,
and his illness
had a big impact on her.
Connie loves to draw pictures
of the whole family,
so Julia has asked her
to create something
just for the house.
- I found these really lovely,
and little pennants,
and I thought what we could do
is paint one
for everybody in the family.
Shall I do one for your dad,
maybe?
- Mm...
you'll have to put
quite a lot of football on it.
- Football on it, will I?
- Forest and football.
- Right, okay, so off you go,
then, sweetie.
- I'm doing
a bit of a dinosaur,
'cause Isaac likes creatures.
- Yeah?
That's lovely.
So what's it been like
up until now,
until we got ahold
of the house?
- Uh, it's been--
it's been a bit tricky
for everyone,
especially my mum.
And my sister's a monkey,
so it's even harder.
- [laughing] She's a monkey,
she-- aw.
- And I'm going to put
some smiley faces,
'cause Isaac's
always giggling.
- He is always giggling,
isn't he?
I've noticed that.
He seems very, very happy.
It wasn't like that
in the beginning, was it,
when he was born?
- Much better now,
but he still cries a bit.
- So, do you think that when
Isaac's got his own bedroom,
that is going
to make him happier?
Yeah?
That's lovely.
You can have a nice,
big smiley face.
Yay.
That's fabulous.
I think he's gonna love that.
Nick: I think so too.
Back at the house,
and the garden isn't where it
needs to be at this late stage.
But we have got extra people,
and they brought gifts.
Uh, can I guess from the van
that you've got a hot tub
for us?
- Yes.
- Is it big?
- Yeah. Massive.
Nick: Look at the
ridiculous--
that's not going
to go in the shed.
- Oh, yes, it will.
It's all been designed
for the size of the hot tub.
It is-- I don't know
what they were expecting.
You know, it is a hot tub,
it's not a bath.
And frankly, you know,
of course all of the family
are going to want to use it.
You're not going
to expect the other children
to stand by and watch, are they?
I mean, how ridiculous.
Nick: Release the tub.
- See, I told you it would fit.
- Yeah, no, it does fit,
it does fit.
Mark: Up! And...
Man: How's that?
- Nice.
Nice, ah...
Nick: More realistic.
Okay, I'll give her that,
she can get a tub in a shed.
But this design
is becoming my nemesis.
It's crazy.
We're on version three
of the circles,
and all the posts
need individually cutting
and placing.
- [playing a fanfare
on a pretend bugle]
The last post.
[laughing] The last post!
Nick: That's very good,
actually.
With only two days left,
it's now decision time.
We said that at 3 o'clock
we would take a view
of where we are
with this garden.
Are we now at a position
where we can say
that we can stick
with this design,
or do we have
to cut holes in it?
- Stick with it.
- You reckon we've got it
back under control today?
- Yeah, just.
Just-- really, really happening.
- Well done you,
'cause this has been your--
Can I interrupt your brownie
just for a second, 'cause--
- It's not a brownie.
It's actually tiffin,
and it's really, really nice.
- I don't care
how nice it is,
I'm trying to interview you
for the program,
and you're sat there chewing
away like a milching cow.
- It's almost finished now.
- Well, the gard--
are we still talking
about the garden, or the tiffin?
- Tiffin.
- Unbelievable.
In the house,
the guys are busy
installing equipment
that should make life
much easier.
A new top-of-the-range hoist
will mean Isaac
can move comfortably
from his bedroom
through to his wet room.
- A bit of grouting
going on in here,
it's very lovely,
add a nice finish on the tiles.
The boys, uh,
fixing one of these all-singing,
all-dancing toilets.
Fantastic.
With so many trades,
all in at the same time,
things can go wrong.
- Yeah, not good.
- What's happened here?
Oh, that's not good.
- Uh, plaster's
comin' off the wall.
That's bad.
That's unusual, in fact.
In the rush
to get things done,
we've ripped some wallpaper
and tried to replace it
with a new bit.
But the plaster
has come away with it.
Sixteen years,
first time I've ever seen
a plastering disaster.
- It's not a disaster.
- Well it's--
it's come off the wall,
Chris, right,
I'd say that was a disaster.
- What was the disaster was
the chipping of the wallpaper.
If they hadn't have pulled
the wallpaper off,
it would have dried, been all
put back in, yeah, yeah,
it would have been all right.
- So that's his fault,
you see that right here.
- It's the joiner's fault.
Chris: Oh, that!
[indistinct]
- I don't believe that.
I don't believe it.
- Are you all right
to do that, lads?
Strip it back to that corner?
Man: Yeah.
- And then, uh, and then
just wallpaper straight--
Have we got enough wallpaper
to carry out?
- Yeah.
Nick: Brilliant.
Excellent.
Crisis and blame averted.
Everyone is busting a gut
to push this over the line.
I'm still not convinced,
however, about the design.
- What's gone wrong here?
- What do you mean,
what's gone wrong?
It's beautiful.
We've got a fabulous
wallpaper over here,
we're just introducing some
texture and color.
Wait, it will be lovely.
- Do you-- uh, mm.
But it's gonna take a bit more
than just trust
to get the outside done
on the last day.
Well, at least it's not raining.
Weather has actually
been very good to us
whilst we're here.
I'm not convinced, though,
what I'm being told,
which is that
this space out here
is going to be
a beautiful environment
in which the family
can enjoy themselves
as from tomorrow night.
I think there's at least
still two days' work here,
which is a bit of a worry,
because we have
to finish tomorrow night.
We've only got one day left.
But then, what do I know?
We'll find out whether I'm right
or they're right tomorrow.
See you then.
[piano music]
Overnight, we've received
some bad news.
Isaac has been
rushed into hospital
with seizures
and breathing difficulties.
He is now stable,
but will stay in with Dad Andy
while Mum Rachel
looks after the other kids.
It's times like this
I'm reminded of the worries
this family must face every day.
Rachel: Since Isaac's
diagnosis,
it's tested my strength
and my family's strength
beyond anything we ever thought
we'd ever have to go through.
Worryin' about how long
we may or may not have with him.
You don't think that--
I mean, that your children
are gonna go before you.
I worry about Isaac, because
he's just so vulnerable,
because he can't tell anybody
what he wants.
I try to-- I try to stay
positive a lot of the time,
and just try to hope
that he will be able
to do some things.
It's scary to think
that he might--
he might never know who I am.
It scares me that--
well, that not only will he not
know who I am, but he'll never--
he'll never be able--
he'll never be able
to run to me, give me a cuddle,
to say, "Mummy."
Nick: Isaac has had
to fight for life from day one,
but his strength continues
to surprise both medics
and those who love him most.
Rachel: Things we take
for granted,
he struggles with
every second.
So, if he can keep going
with that fight every day,
then that-- that gives me
the strength to keep going.
♪♪
Nick: We are on our last day,
and with news that Isaac
is doing better,
we are now more determined
than ever
to give this family
a home to come back to.
And at last, the garden
has turned a corner.
Or, if you like, a swirl.
You've got a big day,
haven't you?
- Very big, very big.
Is there like a resin you use
to bond it all together?
-Yeah, there's a glue
that we--
- How long does it take
to go off?
- Normally 24 hours.
- We haven't got 24 hours,
really.
- We'll need to keep off
the joints.
[laughing]
Nick: And not all of us
are feeling the stress.
♪ Don't you wish your
girlfriend was hot like me? ♪
girlfriend was free like me? ♪
Nick: Arrr, proper handsome,
he is.
The inside is looking
a little underdone,
but I can't fault
their enthusiasm.
You've enjoyed yourself,
haven't you?
Good.
Having a good time?
- Absolutely.
Nick: Who are you talking to,
then?
- It's a little bit
of a squeeze.
- We had six in there
yesterday.
[laughing]
- You've got 20 tonnes
of topsoil turning up.
How you's feeling?
- Yeah!
Nick: Well, there's just
three hours
to get the job done,
and we're still bringing
huge amounts of materials
into the garden.
However, the plants
have arrived.
Sensory-wise, this is great,
'cause when the wind gets in it,
you get the noise
of it rustling,
and that garden
that was a dead space
is really going to come to life,
isn't it?
Julia's design aims to ease
the family's situation,
but right now, it's put in
the thumb screws on this lot.
- I've been laying
this artificial grass
for the past six years.
This is the most difficult,
intricate job
that I've done yet.
Nick: Yeah, sorry about that.
Julia!
Finding it stressful, are we?
- We've got to be out of here
in about ten minutes, I think.
We're under a bit of pressure,
to be honest.
- If you don't need to be
in the house,
don't go into the house.
- Good job.
- The green grass is not
going to your house.
[laughing]
Nick: But as we rush
to the finish line,
I can't wait to hand it back.
[clinking]
Eight hours ago,
I said this garden
wouldn't be finished.
And I was wrong, it is.
But we can't show it to you
at this point,
we're not allowed to.
Go on, just a quick
sneaky peek, then.
That's enough!
It's good, innit?
Just nine days ago,
we arrived to find
a family in despair,
struggling day to day
with everything
from sleep deprivation
to leaving the house.
- It literally just feels
like the walls are just
closin' in on me.
Nick: With a severely
disabled son
needing special care
around the clock,
their home was claustrophobic
and working against them.
Andy: I've worried
that the stress
is going to reach
breaking point.
Nick: At a time when they needed
to be strong and come together,
the house was forcing
everybody apart.
Connie: 'Cause Isaac's
got special needs,
Daddy's always
sleeping downstairs.
Nick: Something
had to be done.
Look, it's busy, look.
[chuckling]
We sent out an S.O.S.,
and Derbyshire responded.
Heroes, every single
one of them.
Just take a look,
what they've built.
At the front
there is a new drive
and wheelchair-friendly ramp
and widened doorways
so Rachel and Andy
no longer have to struggle
to get in and out
of their own home.
Inside, the old cramped kitchen
is gone,
and I have to say Julia's design
is magnificent,
with a new kitchen
and a fantastic dining area.
And, at the back of the house,
we've extended out to make
a comfortable family lounge,
something they
were desperate for.
The old living room,
which doubled
as Dad's bedroom, is no more.
In its place, we've built
a brand-new stylish bedroom
and wet room for Isaac,
all-easy access
with the equipment he needs,
without ever
looking clinical.
Upstairs, we've widened
the hallway,
making the whole area
feel less cramped,
and redesigned
the family bathroom.
Violet's room and Connie's
room have been transformed.
Now they are spaces
to be proud of,
bright and girly
and worthy of sleepovers.
And finally, Mum and Dad's room.
A fully integrated
monitoring system
connects with Isaac's bedroom,
meaning that Rachel and Andy
can finally get some rest
in comfort.
And that's not all.
The garden, once inaccessible
to a little boy
reliant on his senses,
is now breathtaking.
Julia's circular paths
are bordered with plants
that will appeal to Isaac's
hearing and sense of smell,
leading to the therapy hut,
where he can have regular
hydro therapy sessions
to help with his development.
85 construction workers a day
have been working
to try and give you
the house you need.
So, open your eyes.
[gasps]
- Oh my.
Rachel: It's just amazin'.
- Oh. This is incredible.
Absolutely incredible.
Rachel: I love it.
Absolutely love it.
Andy: Can we get to live here?
Oh.
Nick: I want to draw your
attention to the middle one,
the face that's Connie's
painted for Isaac.
- Oh, he's smilin'.
- His smile.
- She always draws him--
she always draws him smiling
when he was first born,
didn't she?
Andy: Oh, that's amazin'.
Nick: Have a look.
Rachel: I love all the colors.
She couldn't have got the colors
any better, could she?
I just love it,
I just love it all.
It's so-- it's just--
- How lucky are we.
- It's just amazin'.
Andy: It's incredible.
It's so overwhelmin'.
- Look at our pictures.
It's just beyond the wildest
dreams, to be honest.
Nick: Well, we've only
just started.
There's a lot more
to show you.
- Okay.
- Ready to come have a look?
- I think so.
- I think so, yeah.
- Come on.
- Oh.
- Oh wow.
Andy: He's got a room!
- Look at his-- it's amazin'.
Look at his bed,
it doesn't look
like a hospital bed.
It just-- it just looks
like a little boy's bed.
- I was wantin' too,
his own space
and a little bit of a choice
and some dignity and his--
- It just doesn't--
- You can't have given it--
even at him.
This is phenomenal.
Nick: The monitoring system
will link to a tablet,
which we have for you
as well, so that basically,
you two will be able to be
upstairs in your bedroom,
will be able to see him all
the time you want to see him,
you'll be able to hear him all
on the tablet.
Rachel: That will just make
such a difference, won't it?
Oh.
Andy: We've got space.
Rachel: It's amazin',
to be able to just move him
from here just to over there,
not havin' to lift him
up and down the stairs.
I feel that wears on.
I can't believe what my eyes
are seein', to be honest.
Andy: They've nailed it,
haven't they?
Rachel: Completely.
Nick: This isn't a house
just for Isaac, obviously.
It's got to be a house
for you guys as well.
Family space downstairs,
we've got to get
other rooms upstairs.
Ready to see some more?
- I think so.
[gasps]
Nick: Step in, step in.
Come in and have a look.
Rachel: I love it.
I love it all.
Andy: Is that a big enough
mirror for you?
[laughing]
- Yeah, don't think
you're getting a look-in.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's stunnin'.
- Amazin'.
- It's stunnin', innit?
Wow.
It just feels like
everything's changed.
Well, I think--
I think something
had to change,
'cause we'd pretty much
hit rock bottom, to be honest.
Andy: It just
means the world.
To take the pressure off
Rachel on a day-to-day basis
was always
a big worry of mine,
and so much of our worries
have just dissipated
with what we've seen today.
- Can you see the future
being better now?
- Yeah, I can see it--
just feel it already.
I can visualize what it's
gonna be like now,
just movin' around
in the house
and just doing
day-to-day things.
Andy: It can give us time
to be-- to be a couple again.
I think the light at the end
of the tunnel is just--
brighter, definitely.
[gasping]
Andy: What do you think,
Connie?
- I like it.
[laughing]
It's beautiful.
One day, can Amelie come
and sleep here?
- Of course she can, darling,
yeah.
- Violet, your room.
What do you think
of your room?
Oh, what is it?
[laughing]
Do you like it?
Andy: Wow.
[baby sounds]
- What do you think?
Hey, mister.
Andy: Hey, champ,
look at your new room.
Rachel: It's your new bedroom.
It's your new bedroom.
What do you think
of your new bed?
- He's got his fox mate.
Yeah, good lookin'.
- Yeah, do you like it?
- He's going to like
the light too, over there.
Rachel: The lights?
♪♪
[laughing in disbelief]
Rachel: Oh wow.
- I'm just speechless.
Nick: What do you think,
Connie?
- I love it.
Rachel: It's wonderful.
Nick: Kind of cute, innit?
Rachel: I just never dreamed
of it being this fantastic.
Nick: Well, let's go
for a little walk,
'cause these are designed
for you to be able
to take the children
up and down,
and the whole point
of the garden
is a sensory garden.
Rachel: Oh.
Andy: Wow.
- It's kinda cool, innit?
- It's-- it is absolutely
brilliant.
Rachel: You've-- you've just
thought of everythin'.
There's just nothing that
you've not thought about,
is there?
Andy: It's out of this world.
Nick: And then of course
there's this whole issue
of the room at the bottom here.
We've got a little surprise.
[laughing]
And let's have a look inside,
shall we?
Come on in here.
[gasping]
Come on in.
Rachel: Wow.
[release of breath]
Nick: Obviously,
hydrotherapy pool.
Why do a hydrotherapy pool
for one,
when you can all jump in
with him?
It's kinda cool.
Let me show you, look.
- Oh my.
Nick: Look at the jets.
shall we just press a button
and see what happens?
Oh-ho-ho!
There's a light show as well.
Rachel: Connie,
what do you think
we might be doin'
this weekend?
Nick: It's pretty cool, huh.
- Can I get in it after school?
[laughing]
Rachel: Sure you can, Connie.
Nick: And, at the end
of a stressful day,
not only is it good for Isaac,
it's good for you.
You can come down
and de-stress down here.
- It's just-- I'm just
completely blown away by it.
Nick: Imagine all those jets
and the way it will work
his muscles and everything.
Rachel: It's just gonna get
so much benefit.
Andy: Way beyond anything
that you could even imagine,
dream of, wish for,
it feels like I'm back
in a family house.
And that we can all enjoy it.
How can you not enjoy this?
How can you not?
♪♪
Connie: I think that
it's gonna help us a lot,
because Daddy doesn't
have to worry about Mummy,
Mummy doesn't
have to struggle,
and it'll just make Isaac
really happy.
[clapping]
- Everythin' that all you guys--
every--
every one of you's done for us
is just-- it's just massive.
I just feel different already,
I just feel like a big weight's
been lifted.
I've been livin' in that house
for so long now,
feelin' like the walls
are just closin' in on me.
I just feel like we've all
been given a new start.
We've just taken you all
into our hearts,
and we'll just-- we'll never
forget what you've done.
It'll just change
all of our lives.
- We've got everything we need
to fulfil Isaac's potential now,
thanks to you guys.
You've made this
our home again.
The fact that people
are just selflessly--
put theirselves through all that
for my family-- just--
There will never be enough
thank yous.
Will there?
- No.
[clapping]
- It makes a difference to you.
[talking indistinctly]
- They say helping someone
doesn't change the world,
but it makes a world
of difference to that person.
And these trades and supplies
have absolutely proved that.
Rachel said that she was come
to the end of her tether,
and, despite her best efforts,
the walls were closing in
on her.
And Andy was worried for the
future unity of the family.
But that's what this lot
have done,
they've brought the family
back together,
as husband and wife,
as father and daughters,
brothers and sisters,
and who knows what Isaac
can now achieve?
You know,
you can't help everybody,
but everybody
can help someone.
♪♪