DRIVER NARROWLY ESCAPES AFTER
A TREE COMES CRASHING DOWN ON
HIGHWAY.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE CLOSE CALL.
"FOX5" AMORNING AT 7 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>>  GOOD MORNING THANKS FOR
WAKE UP WITH US THIS MORNING
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>>  I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR.
>>.
>>  AND MICHAEL THOMAS IS WITH
US AND ERIN COMO QUICK LOOK AT
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC LET'S
START WITH YOU.
>>  GOURJS SURPRISE GOING ON
OUTSIDE RIGHTS NOW.
TAKE A LOOK AT.
IT THAT'S LIVE FROM TOWER CAM
BEHIND THAT GRAPHIC.
THERE 33 DEGREES OUTSIDE THIS
MORNING.
IT'S COLD.
SKIES ARE CLEAR THROW.
EXPECT SUN THIS AFTERNOON AND
KEEP THE JACKET HANDY.
HIGH TEMPERATURES UPPER 30s
LOWER 40s THIS AFTERNOON.
>>  STRAIGHT UP BIG PROBLEMS
INSIDE THE BELTWAY.
66 EASTBOUND WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD A SHOULDER SQUAIZING
BY CRASH DELAYS BACK TO BELT
WAY.
BACK TO YOU.
>> NEW DETAILS AFTER A
4-YEAR-OLD.
>>  HOUSE DEMOCRATS BEGIN ITCH
PEOPLING PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES IN A COUPLE
HOURS.
>>.
>>  AND PRESIDENT CAME OUT
SWING AGO HEAD OF TODAY'S
EXPECTED VOTE.
NAP THAN WITH A SIX PAGE
LET'SER.
MEANWHILE THE TWO TOP SENATORS
ARE FIGHTING OVER THE UPCOMING
SENATE TRIAL AND WHETHER THERE
WILL BE A WITNESS.
>> I THINK WHILE GET ALMOST
ENTIRELY PARTISAN IMPEACHMENT.
I WOULD AND ALMOST ENTIRELY
PART SAN OUTCOME AS WELL.
>> WHAT IS LEADER Mc CONNELL
AFRAID OF AND PRESIDENT TRUMP
APP FRAYED OF.
THE TRUTH.
THE FACTS?
>> THE DEBATE SUPPOSED TO
START AT 9 AND VOTE LIKELY
COMING IN EARLY EVENING.
AND THEY DEBATE FOR SIX HOURS.
>> AND I WILL LEGAL SETTLEMENT
AFTER A DEBATELY GAS EXPLOSION
IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY MARYLAND.
>> SEVERAL PEOPLE DIED AND
DOZENS INJURED AT THE PLOW TER
BRANCH IN SILVER SPRING BACK
IN 2016.
MELANIE ALNWICK IS LIVE IN SUL
VER SPRING THIS MORNING WITH
THE LATEST.
ANOTHER CHAPTER IN THIS
ONGOING STORY, MEL, GOOD
MORNING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, STEVE,
ALLISON NOW WE CAN CLOSE THE
CHAPTER ON TWO LAWSUITS FILED
SHORT ILY AFTER THE EXPLOSION
AT THE FLOWER BRANCH
APARTMENTS.
BOTH NOW COVERED IN GLOBAL
SETMENT COVERING BOTH LAWSUITS
AND HUNDRED OF PEOPLE HERE.
>>  AT THE SAME TIME
WASHINGTON GAS FACING POSSIBLE
FINES.
IT WAS AUGUST 10, 2016 WHEN A
GAS EXPLOSION TORE APART THE
BUILDING AT FLOWER BRANCH
APARTMENTS AND RESIDENTS M
MRUNPIED INTO DARKNESS, FIRE
AND CHOKING SMOKE.
MANY GATHERED FOR A HEARING AT
THE PUBLIC SERVICE COMMISSION
TO TELL REGULATORS WHAT THEY
WENT THROUGH.
FIVE ADULTS WITH TWO CHILDREN
KILLED MATH MANY NOR INJURED
AND DISPLACED AND REPORT BY
NATIONAL TRANSPORTATION
SAFEITY BOARD BLAMED FAILED
MERCURY REGULATOR THAT WAS NOT
KEPINGTED TO VENT LINE.
THAT BAD PART ALLOWED GAS TO
BUILD UP TO DANGEROUS.
AND STATE SAYS REGULATORS SAID
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN REPLACED
AND WASHINGTON GAS DIZ AGREES
WITH NTSB.
THE.HEAR
>>  THERE'S STILL NOT THAT
NEEDS TO BE DONE TO ENSURE
THERE'S IS ACCOUNTABILITY AND
THAT WE PROTECT OUR TENANTS.
>>  WE AS A COMPANY ARE VERY
SADDENED BY WHAT HAPPENED AND
COMMITTED TO ENSURING SAFE AND
RELIABLE NATURAL GAS SERVICE
THROUGHOUT COMMUNITY.  COULD
FACE SUBSTANTIAL FINES AND
WE'LL HEAR WHAT THE RESULTS
ARE SOMETIME AFTER JANUARY 31
12K34R-7 04 PLAN ACCUSES IN
DEADLY STABBING FROM POP EYE'S
RESTAURANT IN COURT TODAY.
AND RICOH McCLAIN ON COMPANIES
CHARGES AND INVESTIGATORS
BELIEVED DAVIS CUT IN LINE AND
CONFRONTED BY McCLAIN.
>>  OPPOSING ARGUMENTS
EXPECTED TODAY IN A MURDER
CASE THAT STUPID TWO LOCAL
COLLEGE CAMPUSES AAND
PROSECUTORS SAY SHAWN URBAN
SAY SKILLED BUOY STATE RICHARD
KOL IPZ THE THIRD ON
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND CAMPUS
IN 2017.
BECAUSE OF HIS RACE.
BECAUSE HE WAS
AFRICAN-AMERICAN.
A JUDGE DROPPED HATE CRIME
CHARLES AGAINST URBAN SKI
YESTERDAY.
>>  AND WARM TODAY.
>>  THAT'S A START.
>>  WE NEED IT.
>>  MONDAY AND TUESDAY HERE
LET'S BE HONEST.
NOT GREAT.
>> I HATE TO BE LIKE DREARY
DAY OUT THERE BECAUSE YOU KNOW
WHO AM I TO TELL WHAT YOU KIND
OF DAY YOU WILL HAVE IT WAS
PRETTY FUNKY.
>>  IT WAS FUNKY I LIKE THAT.
>>  FUNKY.
>>  WHAT IS THAT SONG.
>>  TIME TO GET 23U6R7BGY
SDMRU DON'T KNOW THAT OKAY I
THINK WE GOT THAT.
>>  LET'S ME GO TO MY SOUND
CLOUD.
>>  HIGH DULLES YOU'RE 30 THIS
MORNING, MANNASAS IN 20s.
AS IS FREDERICKSBURG.
AND 55 AAT THIS HOUR.
LEONARDTOWN WAKING TO FREEZING
MARK AT 3 WITH 2 IT SOUTHERN
MARYLAND.
NOT MUCH GOING ON ON SATELLITE
AND RADAR UNLESS YOU GETS TO
GREAT LAKES.
YOU ENCOUNTER SNOW SHOWERS AND
SNOW FLURRY OR TWO AND SOME
NORTHWESTERN ZONES I DON'T
EXPECTS TOO MANY TO MAKE IT TO
D.C..
MOST OF THE DAY IS SUN FILLED
WITH PASSING CLOUDS HERE AND
THERE AND YOU'LL NOTICE MORE
THROUGHOUT THE DAY IS THAT
WIND ILL BE ON THE RISE INTO
THE EVENING HOURS TONIGHT AND
WE COULD HAVE GUSTS OVER 30.
THAT MAKES WIDESPREAD
TEMPERATURE IN THE 30s FEEL
LIKE 20s THIS EVENING AND BY
TOMORROW MORNING LIKELY
FEELING LIKE WIDESPREAD TEENS
AAND MAYBE -- WE HAVE TO
PREPARE FOR COLD HERE.
GOOD NURKSZ NO SNOW ON THE 7
DAY.
IN FACT A WARM-UP TOWARDS
CHRISTMAS.
>>  OKAY.
>> HOW ABOUT WE PREVIEW THAT
COMING UP.
>>  COMING UP.
>> SEE YOU 7:15.
>>  I LIKE YOUR STYLE MICHAEL
THOMAS, 7:07.
66 OF EASTBOUND SKY FOX
PROBLEM INSIDE BELTWAY RIGHT
NOW.
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS CRASH MOVED
OVER TO THE RIGHT SHOULDER,
RIGHT LANES JUST EXCUSE ME
LEFT SHOULDER LEFT LANES JUST
RIGHT SHOULDER EXERCISING PI
THE CRASH.
TRAFFIC GETTING BY IN THE WORK
ZONE INSIDE THEBILITY WAY
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD AND
MASSIVE DRIZ BACK TO BELTWAY
KAWINGZ OVERFLOW AND BAILOUT
TRAFFIC AS WELL AS 29.
THOSE ADD IRTIONAL SECONDARIES
SEEING HEAVY SLOW DOWNS.
ROUTE IS JEFFERSON DAVIS
HIGHWAY IN WOODBRIDGE.
DOWN POLE BLOCKED.
LEFT LANE GETS BY.
PALS CREEK DRIVE.
SOUTHBOUND SIDE HEAVY AS WELL
PAST SCENE.
5 BETTER BET.
COMING UP FROM 23 WITH 4.
270 NORTHBOUND CRASH BLOCKING
MULTIPLE LANES INVOLVING
SEVERAL VEHICLES.
TWO RIGHT LANES BLOCKED AFTER
370 SOUTHBOUND SIDE.
HEAVY AS WELL.
METRO SOUTHBOUND SIDE.
BACK TO YOU.
>>  POLICE IN NEW YORK CITY
INVESTIGATING WHAT APPEARS TO
BE A SKAIJED KIDNAPPING.
>>  16-YEAR-OLD GIRL AT CENTER
OF INVESTIGATION ALLEGEDLY
ADMITTED TO AUTHORITIES THE
WHOLE THINGS WAS A HOAX.
MADE UP.
HOLLY JOINS US LIVER IN THE
NEWSROOM WITH THOSE NEW
DETAILS.
HOLLY ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT IS
THAT MOTHER YOU KNOW PAIN OF
THINKING HER DAUGHTER WAS
GOING AN STRUGGLES OF
EMOTIONS.
>>  COMBINATION OF HAPPY, SAD,
FEAR, ALL OF THAT INFORMED
INTO ONE.
LATE MONDAY NIGHT CAROL
SANCHEZ WAS WALKING WITH HER
MOM IN BRONX WHEN A FOUR DOOR
BATHE SEDAN PULLED UP THIS WAS
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
TWO MEN GRAB SANCHEZ RIGHT
THERE AND PUSH HER MOM.
SUSPECT DRAINGTD THE TEEN TO
CAR AND SPED OFF.
VIOLENT KIDNAPPING PROMPTED
AAMBER ALERT AAND WIDESPREAD
FEAR.
WELL THEN THE NEXT DAY SHE WAS
FOUND UNARMED.
YOU CAN SEE HER HERE WITH NEW
YORK CITY POLICE OFFICERS IN
THIS EXCLUSIVE FOX NEWS VIDEO
AALONG WITH A TEARFULL REUNION
BETWEEN THE TEENAGER AND HER
FAMILY.
BUT THE INVESTIGATION TOOK A
MAJOR TURN.
SEVERAL SOURCES SAY THE TEEN
KNEW AT LEAST ONE OF THE
PEOPLE INVOLVED AND TEEN
ALLEGEDLY ADMITTED SHE FAKED
THE WHOLE THING WITH HELP OF
HER BOYFRIEND.
INCIDENT MAY HAVE STARTED AS A
FAMILY DISPUTE.
THERE ARE REPORTS THAT THE
FAMILY WANTED TO SEND SANCHEZ
BACK TO HER NATIVE COMMUNITY
HEN DOORS.
>>  SHE CAME TO THE COP CARS
AND SHE WAS TREMBLING AND IT
LOOKED LIKE HER WITH HER
PICTURES AAND STUFF.
SO WE KNEW IT WAS HER AND WE
WERE BOTH IN IT SHOCK BUT
HAPPY SHE'S HOME.
>>  SO NOW AS YOU CAN IMAGINE
MORE QUESTIONS THAN ANSWERS AS
AUTHORITIES TRY TO CONNECT ALL
THE DOTS.
POLICE ARE STILL LOOKING FOR
THE MEN CAPTURED ON VIDEO IN
THE INCIDENT.
SO CLEARLY MORE TO THIS STORY.
>> GOOD NEWS SHE'S SAFE.
>>  SHE'S SAFE AND HOME.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> NEW THIS MORNING FRI
FRIGHTENING ROBBERY AT ATM
CAUGHT ON CAMERA THIS HAPPENED
EARLIER THIS MONTH IN THE 1900
BLOCK OF 1 IS 4th STREET.
POLICE SAY THE THREE SUSPECT
ACONSULT SALTED VICTIM TOOK
HIS PROPERTY BEFORE TAKING
OFF.
POLICE ARE ASKING FOR THE
PUBLIC HELP IN IDENTIFYING THE
THREE SEEN ON SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO.
IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING YOU'RE
ASKED TO CALL D.C. POLICE.
>> TODAY AIRPORT AUTHORITY
WILL VOTE ON POLICY TO RAISE
HOURLY CHARGES IF IMPROVED IT
WILL INCREASE HOURLY PAY 12.7
A5 TO $15, 2023.
D.C. MAYOR BOWSER AND GROUP OF
VIRGINIA DELEGATES SEPTEMBER A
LET TO AIRPORT AUTHORITY UMING
BOARD MEMBERS TO MAKE SURE
WORKERS REACH THAT PARK MARK.
>>  TODAY CATHOLIC CHARITIES
OF ARCHDIOCESES OF WASHINGTON
HELP TO FEED PEOPLE IN NEED
THIS WILLING A DINNER ON G
STREET NORTH WEST CHARITIES,
D.C. EMPLOY AND AND VOLUNTEERS
WILL HOST MORE THAN 300 PEOPLE
FOR THE DAY MEAL THERE WILL
ALSO BE SEVERAL ACTIVITY THAT
STARTS AT 5 P.M. AT THE HICKEY
CENTER.
>>  TALK ABOUT A CHRISTMAS
CRIME A MAN TRIED TO DISGUISE
DRUGS BY WRAPPING THEM AS
GIFTS.
>>  OKAY.  COMING UP WE'LL
TELL XWHAW TIPPED
INVESTIGATORS OFF AS HE WAS
TRAVELING THROUGH THE AIRPORT.
>>  AND PLANNING TO TRAVEL
YOURSELF THIS HOLIDAY SEASON?
IF SO.  PREPARE YOURSELF NOT
JUST FOR THE OTHER TRAVELERS
BUT MAYBE SOME FAMILY DRAWM A
WE'LL TELL WHAT YOU ARE YOU
MOST LIKELY TO DISAAGREE B
COMING UP NEXT AT 7:00.
SKL.
SKL
J RILTION BACK WITH YOU AT
7:12 A SHORT BREAK FOUR.
>> THERE'S NO PLACE LIKE HOME
FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
>>  AND FEW FOR A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
PARKING APRIL FOLKS SPOT HERO.
>>  FORGETTING I.D., LOSING
SOMETHING, THAT'S ALWAYS A
PROBLEM IF YOU HEAD TO THE
AIRPORT.
NOW IT'S A PARKING APP.
IT ONLY MAKES SENSE PEOPLE
ARGUE ABOUT NOT BEING ABLE TO
FIND A PARKING SPOT AND THEN
OF COURSE PACKING FOR THE
JOURNEY.
>> THIS IS PROBABLY BETWEEN
SPOUSES OR WHOEVER IS --
GIRLFRIEND, BOYFRIEND, WHOEVER
IS SITTING UP IN FRONT ORCHIDS
IN THE BACK.
>> ANY TIME YOU SIT -- LOOK I
SIT IN TRAFFIC ON A RANDOM
WEDNESDAY AND GETTING A VAITED
EVEN IF I'M ONLY ONE IN THE
CAR I MIGHT ARGUE WITH MYSELF.
>> REALLY TELL US MORE ABOUT
THAT.
>>> YOU GET CONVICTED
SOMETIMES AND QUESTION THINGS
AS IN WHY AIM ON THE ROAD NOW.
>> THOSE ARE TYPICAL.
>>  WHY WOULD I POSSIBLY BE ON
6 OF 6 AT 5:30 IN THE
AAFTERNOON.
>>  NOW YOU'RE OVER SHARING.
>>  WELL.
>>  THAT'S --.
FEELING THAT VOIDS THAT YOU
ASKED FOR.
>>.
>>  LET'S MOVE ON 7:113.
>> THIS VOTE CAME AFTER A
HEARING WHERE HUNDREDS OF
PEOPLE SHOWED UP TO VOICE
THEIR OPINION IN THIS MORNING
BOB BARNARD IS FOLLOWING UP HE
HAS THE LATEST ON WHAT CAME
FROM ALL THAT SHARING OF
OPINION AND THE MOVE BY THE
COUNTRY BOARD OF SUPERVISORS,
GOOD MORNING, BOB.
>>  HEY, ALLISON, STEVE, GOOD
MORNING TO YOU.
DOZENS OF PEOPLE WERE SIGNED
UP AND SPOKE BEFORE THE SEVEN
P.M. MEMBER STAFFORD COUNTY
BOARD OF SUPERVISORS AND THERE
WERE MAYBE 100 OR SO PEOPLE
INSIDE.
LET'S SHOW WHAT YOU IT LOOKED
LIKE OUTSIDE.
THERE WERE HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
OUTSIDE MEETING LAST NIGHT.
IS THERE TO SUPPORT THE
COUNTRY AND SECOND AMENDMENT
SANCTUARY AHEAD OF THE GENERAL
ASSEMBLY BEING CONTROLLED BY
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTIES
STARTING NEXT YEAR.
AND THEIR PUSH TO ENACT TO
TOUGHER GUN LAWS.
THERE'S PROPOSALS TO BAN
ASSAULT STYLE WEAPONS.
HIGH CAPACITY MAGAZINES AND
BUMP STOCKS AND SILENCERS AND
DEMAND A BACKGROUND CHECK ON
ALL GUN SALES.
SO, THEREFORE, A NUMBER OF
COUNTIES ACROSS THE
COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA HAVE
BEEN DOING THIS AMONG THE
PEOPLE OUTSIDE LAST NIGHT THE
OVER WOMENING MAJORITY
SUPPORTED WHAT THE BARRED OF
SUPERVISORS DID.
THERE WAS ONE PERSON THAT
YOU'LL HEAR FROM HERE WHO DID
NOT.
HERE'S SOME OF THE REACTION
OUTSIDE OF THAT MEETING LAST
NIGHT.
>>  WE'VE HAD TWO ATTEMPTED
BREAKS INS.
IF THEY TAKE MY GUN AS WAY
I'VE GOT NO WAY TO PROTECT MY
FAMILY, MY HOME, NOTHING.
>>  WE HAVE A CONSTITUTIONAL
RIGHT TO PROTECT OUR PROPERTY
AND LIVES AND THEY'RE
INFRIVRPINGING UPON THAT RI
RIGHT.
>> SOME PEOPLE GO I SHOOT GUNS
IT'S NO REASON FOR ME TO
BECOME A FELON JUST FOR OWNING
A FIREARM.
>> WHY DO WE NEED BUMP STOCKS
AND WHY DO WE NEED MASS
AMOUNTS OF AMMUNITION.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THESE
PEOPLE WANT THAT.
WHY DOES STAFFORD COUNTRY WANT
TO BE A SAFE HAVEN FOR THOSE
PEOPLE.
>> THE BOARD OF SURPRISE
VISORS OTED UNANIMOUSLY 7-0
LATE LAST NIGHT IN FAVOR OF
DECLARING STAFFORD COUNTY A
SECOND AMENDMENT SANK TU
AAIRY.
JOINING OTHERS IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA PRINCE WILLIAM,
CULPEPER, SPOTSYLVANIA COUNTY
WHICH AGAIN HAVE DONE THIS AS
WELL, GUYS.
IT'S MORE SYMBOLIC THING BUT
OBVIOUSLY TOUCHING AA LOT OF
PASSIONS HERE IN STAFFORD
COUNTY, GUYS.
>> A LOT OF COUNTIES BEING
PROACTIVE TAKING THAT STEXT OF
COURSE WON'T KNOW WHAT THE
LEGISLATURE DOES UNTIL
JANUARY.
>>  THANKS, BOB.
>>  7:16 NOW.
>>  LET'S GET TO WEATHER.
TAKE A LOOK OUTSIDE OCEAN CITY
WE LIKE TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON
AT THE BEACH EVERY NOW AND
THEN.
>>  GOOD MORNING SURPRISE
OCEAN CITY.
WARM TEMPERATURES IN
SUMMERTIME.
COULDN'T BE MORE THE OPPOSITE
HERE IN D.C..
ANOTHER LIVE LOOK SUN COMING
UP OVER OXON HILL THIS MORNING
AND RIGHTS NOW OUTSIDE HERE
D.C. 33 DEGREES.
WINDS BLOWING JUST A TOUCH.
MAKING THEM FEEL LIKE 28.
IN RESPONSIBLE SOTS NORTH AND
WEST AND BLOWING AGO LITTLE
MORE.
GAMERS BURGES FEELING LIKE 17,
FEELS LIKE 2 IT 4 DULLES AND
MARTINSBURG 18 AND LEONARDTOWN
27 FOR YOU AND FREDERICKSBURG
28 AS YOU START THE DAY.
WATCH THESE REAL FEEL
TEMPERATURES INTO EVENING
HOURS TONIGHT DROPPING AS WIND
INCREASE AND GUSTS UP TO OVER
30 MILES AN HOUR LATER.  LOOK
AT SINGLE DINGIT WIND CHILLS
DROPPING INTO HOUN TAPS OFF
NORM AND WEST INTO THE LATE
EVENING SHOWERS TONIGHT AND
TOMORROW MORNING WEIGHING UP
GETTING WORK, GETTING KID OFF
TO SCHOOL IT MIGHT FELT LIKE
JUST DEGREES IN GAITHERSBURG
AND MAR TIR CONTINUESBURG AAND
1 QUANITCO.
GOOD NEWS SATELLITE AND RADAR
QUIET HERE.
BOTH TODAY AND TOMORROW SHOULD
BE SUNNY, BRIGHT, BEAUTIFUL
LOOKING AAND COULD BE BETTER
FEELING AS TEMPERATURES WILL
BE COLD.
4 IT DUNKIN' DONUTS, 35
TOMORROW WE KEEP IT DRY
THROUGH THE WEEKEND.
WEEKEND TRAVELERS JUST TO LET
YOU KNOW WE'RE FINE HERE IF
YOU TRAVEL AAROUND THE DMV.
IF YOU MAKE YOUR WAY TO
CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY CHRISTMAS
EVE RIGHT NOW LOOKS PHONE
TASTIC.
SUNSHINE, 55.
SHOULD BE A GOOD HOLIDAYWEEK
HERE IN D.C..
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
AIRPORT AIRPORT IS WATCHING
ROADWAYS THIS MORNING HOW DOES
IT LOOK, ERIN.
>>  SKY FOX OVER 66 INSIDE THE
BELTWAY OUT BY WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD.
YOU CAN SEE THEY'RE DIVERTING
TRAFFIC ACTUALLY IT'S NOT
GETTING THROUGH AT ALL THROUGH
THE WORK ZONE AND BACK TO 66.
SDMR TRAFFIC BACK TO 66
SQUEEZING BY OWNER.
IT'S A HOT MESS OUT.
THERE WE ALSO HAVE AS I
MENTIONED BAILOUT TRAFFIC.
ROUTE 1 JEFFERSON DAVIS
HIGHWAY NORTHBOUND SIDE WITH
DOWNED POLE.
RIGHT LANES BLOCKED POWELL'S
CREEK.
KEEP IT TO 9 THE 5.
THAT'S IN WOODBRIDGE BACK TO
YOU.
>>  AMAZON IS CRACKING DOWN ON
ITS DELIVERY DRIVERS DURING
THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
THEY'RE USING TECHNOLOGY TO
HELP.
>> WE'LL EXPLAIN THE NEW APP
THAT IS TACKLING BAD HABITS.
RIGHT AFTER THE BREAK.
7:18.
>> 7:21.
AMAZON TACKLING BAD HABITS OF
DELIVERY DRIVERS USE SMART
PHONE APP.
NOW IT TRACKS DRIVERS AND
RATES DRIVING HABITS.
>>  BUSINESS INSIDER REPORTS
APP RATES BEHAVIORS SCORE OF 0
TO 850 SCORING ROAD PROBLEMS
SPEEDING, RAPID AACCELERATION,
HARD BRAKING USING HOPE TO
WHILE DRIVING AND WEARING
SEATBELTS.
IN THE SURE IF IT COULD
ACTUALLY TERMINATE A DRIVER
FROM BAD PERFORMANCE BUT
THEY'RE DOING IT AND TRACKING
THEM AND LET'S SEE IF IT
TRANSFORMED TO WHAT WE WANT
PACKAGES DELIVERED ON TIME.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
coe
mpetition
and we broke through.
You've tried retinol,
but you have never tried one
like this.
Olay's Retinol24 complex
hydrates
better than the #1 retinol.
Visibly smoother brighter skin
in just 24 hours.
A skin upgrade?
Crushed it.
New Olay Retinol24.
Face Anything.
Olay.
Now available with retinol serum
and retinol eye cream.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS LOOK AT
CLOSE CALL FOR NOTE VISIT IN
MASSACHUSETTS A TREE FALLING
ACROSS THE EYE HIGH.
RIGHT AFTER THAT NOTE VISIT
WENT UNDERNEATH.
POLICE RELEASED SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO OF THE TREE JUST
NARROWLY MISSING THAT PASSING
CAR.
>>  THAT VIDEO SHOWING HOW THE
DRIVER AGAIN JUST BARELY
AVOIDS.
IT POLICE SAY THE DRIVER JUST
KEPT GOING AND MIGHT NOT HAVE
NOTICED THAT TREE COMING DOWN.
THAT TREE FELL DOWN BECAUSE OF
STRONG WINDS.
IT JUST WAS NOT HIS DAY TO BE
HIT BY THAT TREE.
>>  NO BUT THE POLICE OFFICER
WAS RIGHTS THERE AS IF THEY
WERE WAITING FOR IT TO FALL
RIGHT.
>>  THAT RESPONSE THYME VROOM
ON THE SCENE.
>>  INCREDIBLE.
SUNNY DAY.
ONE OF THE THINGS YOU WOULD
NOT EXPECT.
TREES MOVING A LITTLE BIT.HE
SCARY THING.
THERE ALL RIGHT.
REAGAN NAG AA NATIONAL 33.
DULLES 30, BWI 33.
GOOD MORNING SUBURBS ALL
WAKING UP TO TEMPERATURES IN
THE 20s.
IT'S COLD OUT.
THERE SATELLITE AND RADAR
SHOWS CLEAR SKIES.
THAT'S A GOOD THINGS.
FEW SNOW SHOWERS OFF TO THE
FAR,  FAR, FAR, NORTHWEST ONE
OR TWO MAY SNEAK INTO THE
MOUNTAINS.
HERE IN D.C. I SUSPECT WE'LL
KEEP IT DRY FOR THE DAY.
HERE'S YOUR DAY AHEAD PLANNER
THIS WEDNESDAY BEFORE
CHRISTMAS, 34 BY 9:00 AND
WE'LL RISE TO LOW 40s BY
LUNCHTIME HOURS AND FALL BACK
QUICK AND FALL BACK PRETTY
HARD LATER TONIGHT IT WILL BE
A COLD ONE IN D.C..
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST, ERIN
COMO HAS YOUR TRAFFIC JAM.
>>  SANTA AND  ELVES I HOPE
THEY STAY WARM WHEN THEY LOAD
THE SLEIGH I THINK THEY GET
READY A WEEK OUT.
>>  SPECULATING.
>>  66 EASTBOUND SIDE.
WE HAVE BIG DELAYS LOOK AT
THAT PARKING LOT INSIDE THE
BELTWAY IN FALSE CHURCH.
WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH IS
SERIOUS CRASH BLOCKING ALL
LANES.
THEY'RE DIVERTING TRAFFIC OFF
THE CONSTRUCTION ZONE
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD AND THEN
PEOPLE EEMING KER EXIT THERE
OR HOOK BACK ON TO 66 ON THE
SHOULDER.
THIS IS CAUSING A HUGE MESS.
YOU'RE PARKED BACK TO 7P,
LEESBURG PIKE.
DELAYS EXTEND PAST THE BEL
BELTWAY.
BAILOUT TRAFFIC ON 2 IT IT IT
9 AS WELL AS DULLES TOLL ROAD
AND PEOPLE BAILING OUT DULLES
TOLL ROAD TRYING TO GET TO
BELTWAY.
IT'S A MESS.
I WOULD AVOID 66 OF INSIDE THE
BELTWAY IF POSSIBLE BACK TO
YOU.
>>  FACEBOOK TAKING STEPS TO
SPEED UP THE PLATFORM FACT
CHECK PROCESS.
>>  AND WE'LL EXPLAIN HOW THE
SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANY IS
PLANNING TO DO THIS.
7:27, WE'RE BACK AFTER THIS
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
♪
>>> VERY PRETTY, RIGHT?
>> CHRISTMAS EXACTLY ONE WEEK
FROM TODAY.
HANUKKAH BEGINS ON SUNDAY.
KWANZAA BEGINS NEXT THURSDAY.
SO WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON ALL
THESE HOLIDAY TRADITIONS.
>> NO MATTER YOUR OPINION.
WE CERTAINLY HOPE YOU HAVEN'T
FALLEN VICTIM TO AN UNFORTUNATE
HOLIDAY TRADITION THAT THE PORCH
PIRATES.
>> JOINING THE DISCUSSION THIS
MORNING THE HOST OF MORNINGS ON
THE MALL MARYANN.
YOU CAN LISTEN TO THEM ON
105.9WMAL.
GOOD MORNING.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
>> HEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> I EVEN HATE THIS LITTLE NAME
PORCH PIRATES FOR ME IT'S TOO
WHIMSICAL.
THESE ARE THIEVES THAT COME AND
TAKE YOUR PROPERTY.
>> YES.
>> ON YOUR PROPERTY.
IT REALLY MAKES ME SO ANGRY
ACTUALLY.
>> IT'S INFURIATING THESE ARE
LOW LIVES.
AT LEAST IF WE WERE GOING TO
CALL THEM PORCH PIRATES THEY
SHOULD DRESS UP ASPIRE RATS TO
SETTLE EFFECT THEY DON'T EVEN DO
THAT.
THEY JUST COME TO YOUR PORCH.
THEY STEAL YOUR PACKAGES AND
THEN THEY LEAVE.
IN FACT IN ALEXANDRIA WE SAW A
REPORT EARLIER THIS WEEK THAT
THE PORCH PIRATES ARE LITERALLYY
>> MY GOSH.
>> AND GOING AND STEALING THESE
PACKAGES.
>> HOW HOW BRAZEN THEY AE.
IT'S CRAZY.
SUCH A VIOLATING FEELING TO HAVE
SOMETHING STOLEN FROM YOU LIKE
THAT.
IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
LIKE THEY DIDN'T EVEN TRY.
>> YEAH.
>> AT LEAST PICK A LOCK.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THEY DID NOTHING
TO GET THAT PACKAGE.
IT'S SO INFURIATING AND THEY
KNOW THAT THE COMPANIES ARE JUST
GOING TO REPLACE IT.
YOU JUST CALL AND SAY IT WAS
STOLEN OR I DIDN'T GET THE
PACKAGE AND THEY KNOW IT'S GOING
TO BE REPLACE THED SO NO HARM NO
FALL IT DOESN'T GET RID OF THAT
FEELING OF BEING VIOLATED.
IT'S AWFUL.
>> I HATE IT.
>> DID YOU EXPERIENCE THIS FIRST
HAND IN FULL DISCLOSURE HAVE I
NOT BUT YOU HAVE.
>> YES.
NO, I HAVE.
IT IS AS OUTRAGEOUS AS YOU FEEL
SEEING IT HAPPEN TO SOMEBODY
ELSE.
IT IS LIKE YOU GO TO THAT
PERFORM AND YOU EXPECT A
DELIVERY.
OFF DELIVERY NOTIFICATION FROM
WHATEVER SERVICE YOU USED.
IT'S THERE.
IT'S AT YOUR HOUSE.
OH, NO, IT'S NOT.
SOMEONE CAME AND STOLE IT AND SO
IN MY COMMUNITY WHAT WE'VE DONE
IS WE'VE -- WE ACTUALLY SHARE
VIDEOS BECAUSE SOME PEOPLE HAVE
VIDEOS SURVEILLANCE SYSTEM ON
THEIR DOOR BELLS WHERE THEY CAN
SEE WHO'S BEEN IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
WHAT CAR HAS BEEN DRIVING AR
AROUND.
WHAT PERSON WAS GOING UP TO
PEOPLE'S DOORS AND TRYING TO
CHECK ON THESE TYPES OF THINGS.
WE TRY AND COBBLE TOGETHER SOME
SEMBLANCE OF IDENTITY WHO IT IS
AND HAND IT OFF OH TO OUR LOCAL
POLICE DEPARTMENT IN THE HOPES
THEY CAN CATCH THESE PEOPLE F
THEY STEAL SOMETHING VALUABLE
ENOUGH THAT GETS INTO THE
ELEMENT OF GRAND LARCENY YOU
COULD ACTUALLY FACE 20 YEARS IN
JAIL IF YOU STEAL EXPENSIVE FROM
SOMEONE'S FRONT PORCH.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF ANYBODY EVER
HAS.
HAS ANYBODY SPENT 20 YEARS IN
PRISON FOR STEALING A PACKAGE.
>> THEY SHOULD.
>> PROBABLE NOT BUT THEY SHOULD.
>> GOOD FOR YOU GUYS PULLING
TOGETHER WITH ALL THAT VIDEO.
THE LATEST TREND THEY'RE ROBBING
THE DELIVERY DRIVER BEFORE THEY
EVEN GET A CHANCE TO DROP OFF
THE PACKAGES.
A LOT OF PROBLEMS OUT THERE
WHICH IS VERY TROUBLING.
ALL RIGHT.
ON A LIGHTER NOTE, WHEN IT COMES
TO THE HOLIDAYS THEMSELVES, WE
HAVE SOME PEOPLE OUT THERE NOW
JUST LIKE, YOU KNOW, WHAT, THE
HECK WITH IT I'M NOT SETTING UP
A TREE BECAUSE IT'S TOO MUCH
TROUBLE.
HAVE WE LOST THIS HOLIDAY SPIRIT
IN ITS ENTIRETY NOW OR DO YOU
JUST KIND OF CAST THE PEOPLE
ASIDE THAT ARE LIKE, I DON'T
EVEN WANT TO PUT UP A TREE IT
TAKES UP SPACE AND TAKES UP A
GOOD HOUR OF MY LIFE AND JUST
LET THEM WOMAN LOW IN THEIR
UNSEASONAL MISERY?
>> YOU KNOW THEY SHOULD ALL BE
FORCED TO SIT DOWN AND WATCH
SCROOGE WITH THEIR EYES TAPED
OPEN AND HAVE TO WATCH IT OVER
AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
BA HAM BUG.
SOMETHING WRONG WITH PEOPLE WHO
JUST TRY TO GET RID OF TRADITION
MUCH THAT'S AN OLD TRADITION
MUCH THAT'S A HORRIBLE TRAD
TRADITION.
TRADITIONS ARE WHAT BRING PEOPLE
TOGETHER, BRING FAMILIES
TOGETHER.
IT'S WHAT BRINGS A COMMUNITY
TOGETHER, AND WHEN WE START TO
LOSE OUR TRADITIONS, I THINK
THAT'S A VERY VERY DANGEROUS
THING.
SO YOU CAN CHANGE IT.
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR OWN TRADITION
BUT YOU NEED TO HAVE TRADITIONS.
>> IF YOU WANT TO BE REMINDED OF
THE QUALITY OF SEASON OF
CHRISTMAS THERE'S NOTHING LIKE A
LITTLE KID GOING DURING THE
CHRISTMAS SEASON BLURRY EYED
SQUINTING AT THE TREE AND SEEING
ALL THOSE LITTLE LIGHTS TWINKLE
AS STARS.
SOMETHING ALMOST SPIRITUAL ABOUT
IT.
LET'S NOT GIVE UP ON TRADITIONS.
THEY'RE GOOD FOR US.
>> AGREED.
>> LET'S END WITH THE QUESTION
OF SHOULD YOU GO TO YOUR EX'S
HOLIDAY PARTY.
NOW, OKAY, MARY I KNOW YOU LOVE
WINDY AND WENDY WANTS JENNIFER
AND BRAD TO GET BACK TOGETHER
BECAUSE BRAD WENT TO JENNIFER'S,
YOU KNOW, CHRISTMAS PARTY AND
ALL OF THAT.
IS THIS GET COAT OR JUST TROUBLE
IN THE MAKING?
>> WELL, IT DEPENDS ON THE
RELATIONSHIP AND WHAT YOU WANT
TO GET OUT OF IT.
I THINK THAT THEY'RE EACH
OTHER'S LOBSTER.
HE'S HER LOBSTER AND SHE'S HIS
LOBSTER AND I BET THEY GET BACK
TOGETHER I'M SO GLAD YOU BROUGHT
THIS UP.
I'M SO EXCITE.
>> I DON'T KNOW EVEN KNOW WHAT
LOBSTERS ARE.
>> FROM FRIENDS, PHOEBE FROM
FRIENDS.
FROM FRIENDS WITH PHOEBE SHE'S
HIS LOBSTER.
>> YES.
>> ROSS AND RACHEL THEY WERE
EACH OTHER'S LOBSTERS.
>> LITTLE DEEP FOR THAT ANALOGY.
>> LOBSTERS MATE FOR LIFE
ACCORDING TO PHOEBE.
>> I'LL USE THAT AT HOLIDAY
PARTIES I GO TO.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS BOTH OF YOU.
>> FEEL FREE.
HAVE A GREAT SHOW.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> THANKS.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
7:35.
LET'S GET OVER TO MIKE THOMAS
AND GET A CHECK OF THE FORECAST.
>> GOOD MORNING STEVE AND
ALLISON.
WAKING UP TO COLD TEMPERATURES
OUTSIDE IN D.C.
WAKING UP TO SUNSHINE AS WELL
SOMETHING WE HAVEN'T SEEN IN A
COUPLE OF DAYS IT'S WELCOMED
BACK HERE FOR SURE.
WHAT'S NOT SO WELCOMED SOME OF
THESE NUMBERS.
25 DEGREES GAITHERSBURG THIS
MORNING.
26 MANASSAS GOOD MORNING
LEONARDTOWN SITTING AT 32.
D.C. ONE OF THE FEW SPOTS
ACTUALLY ABOVE ONLY SPOT ON THIS
MAP WEST OF THE BAY THAT IS
WAKING UP ABOVE FREEZING AT
33 DEGREES.
TAKE A LOOK AT SATELLITE/RADAR.
HONESTLY NOT TOO MUCH TO TALK
ABOUT HERE IN THE IMMEDIATE D.C.
AREA.
A COUPLE OF PASSING CLOUDS FROM
TIME TO TIME.
OVER THE MOUNTAINS THERE COULD
BE A SNOW SHOWER OR SNOW FLURRY
LATER ON THIS AFTERNOON AS A
REINFORCING SHOT OF COLD AIR
COMES OUR WAY THAT WILL MAKE
YOUR THURSDAY EVEN COLDER THAN
TODAY AND IN FACT YOUR NUMBERS
RIGHT NOW COULD BE YOUR HIGH
TEMPERATURES TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
SO GET READY FOR A COLD ONE.
42 TODAY.
COLDER BUT MORE SUNSHINE
TOMORROW AT 35 DEGREES.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
ERIN, HOW DO ROADS UKEE.
>> THEY'RE JUST NASTY THIS WEEK.
WEDNESDAY MORNING 66 EASTBOUND
AT WASHINGTON BOULEVARD THEY'RE
DETOURING TRAFFIC ON TO THE EXIT
RAMP TO WASHINGTON BOULEVARD.
IT'S A WORK ZONE AND PEOPLE ARE
HOOKING BACK ON TO 66 EASTBOUND
ON THE RIGHT SHOULDER.
THIS IS CAUSING A LOT OF BAILOUT
TRAFFIC.
YOU ARE PARKED BACK TO SEVEN
DELAYS EXTENDING BACK ACTUALLY
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY NOW INTO
FAIRFAX.
WE ALSO HAVE BAIL OUT TRAFFIC ON
BELTWAY AND 29 BIG PROBLEMS IN
FALLS CHURCH THIS MORNING.
SEEING RUBBERNECK DELAY ON THE
WESTBOUND SIDE HEADING AWAY FROM
THE KEY BRIDGE TOWARD THAT
LOCATION.
95 NORTHBOUND A CRASH BY 123 AND
ONE LANE GETS BY 270 NORTHBOUND
PASSED 370.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> A DRUG RESISTANT INFECTION
FOUND IN HUMANS IS BEING LINKED
TO PUPPIES.
SEVERAL STATES ARE REPORTING
CASES INCLUDING MARYLAND.
WE'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT THIS
NEXT.
>> ALSO, IF YOU WERE HOPING TO
STRIKE IT RICH LAST NIGHT IN THE
MEGA MILLIONS JACKPOT YOU BOUGHT
YOUR TICKET NEAR D.C., YOU'RE
OUT OF LUCK.
THAT TICKET WAS SOLD ABOUT
400 MILES AWAY.
>> LIVE LOOK -- HOW ABOUT THIS,
THOUGH?  A CONSOLATION PRIZE.
BEAUTIFUL SUNRISE IN THE DMV.
IT IS 7:37.
WE'RE BACK AFTER THIS.
♪
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
♪
>>> BACK NOW AT 7:40 ON A
WEDNESDAY.
HEADS UP IF YOU HAVE A PUPPY.
THE CENTERS STORE DISEASE
CONTROL WARNING OF A DRUG
RESISTANT INFECTION LINKED TO
PUPPIES FROM PET STORES.
30 CASES IN 13 STATES HAVE BEEN
REPORT THE INCLUDING ONE IN
MARYLAND.
THE CDC SAYS MANY OF THOSE
AFFECTED -- INFECTED HAD CONTACT
WITH A PUPPY FROM A PET STORE OR
WORKED AT A PET STORE.
>> WELL IF YOU WANTED TO STRIKE
IT RICH LAST NIGHT'S MEGA
MILLIONS HOPEFULLY YOU WERE
TRAVELING TO OHIO THAT'S WHERE
THE WINNING TICKET WAS SOLD.
$372 MILLION WORTH.
THE CASH VALUE 251 MILLION.
THERE WAS A $1 MILLION TICKET
SOLD IN WEST VIRGINIA HOWEVER SO
A LITTLE BIT CLOSER TO HERE IN
D.C.
>> AWESOME.
WHO SNEEZING AT A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> NOBODY.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> HOW FACEBOOK IS STEPPING UP
ITS FIGHT AGAINST WEEDING OUT
FAKE NEWS.
>> PLUS AN UPDATE ON A MORTGAGE
EXAM WE TOLD YOU ABOUT YESTERDAY
AS YET ANOTHER VICTIM COMES
FORWARD TO FOX5.
THE ACTION THAT SHE SAYS SHE
TOOK MONTHS AGO THAT WENT
ANSWERED.
♪
I'm LáDeia, and there's
more to me than HIV.
There's my career...
my cause...
and creating my dream home.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO is for
adults who are starting
HIV-1 treatment and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines dolutegravir
or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2 medicines
in 1 pill
to help you reach and
then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day
with food
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if you're
allergic to any of its
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,
liver problems, and
liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash and
other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,
including hepatitis B or C.
Don't use DOVATO if you plan
to become pregnant
or during the first 12
weeks of pregnancy
since one of its ingredients may
harm your unborn baby.
Your doctor should do a
pregnancy test
before starting DOVATO.
Use effective birth control
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache,
diarrhea, nausea, trouble
sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment
with DOVATO is right
for you.
Step right up!
Try the all new Tyson
Air Fried Chicken.
With 75% less fat.
It's all pleasure and no guilt.
Plus we air fry it
before you buy it.
It's the best thing to happen
to fried chicken since...
fried chicken.
♪♪
I've slain your dreaded dragon.
For saving the kingdom
what doth thou desire?
My Lord?
Hey Good Knight.
Where are you going?
♪♪
♪ Climbing up on Solsbury Hill ♪
♪ grab your things, ♪
Salutations.
Coffee that is a cup above
is always worth the quest.
Nespresso.
Tis all I desire.
Did thou bring enough
for the whole kingdom?
George: Nespresso, what else?
♪
>>> 7:43.
IN TODAY'S BUSINESS BEAT GOOGLE
PUTTING THE HEAT ON APPLE WITH
ITS NEW TEXTING SERVICE.
JOINING US NOW FROM THE FOX
BUSINESS NETWORK STUDIO TRACEE
CARRASCO.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> LET'S START WITH FACEBOOK
ADDING WHEN I READ THIS I HAD TO
DO IT TWICE LIKE REAL PEOPLE TO
HELP WITH FACT CHECKING.
>> YUP.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY THAT CONCEPT
BLEW MY MIND.
>> WELL, THIS NEW PILOT PROGRAM
THAT FACEBOOK IS TRYING OUT IN
THE U.S.
THEY'RE GOING TO USE PART-TIME
CONTRACTED COMMUNITY REVIEWERS
TO HELP SPEED UP THE FACT CH
CHECKING PROCESS.
SO WHAT THESE COMMUNITY
REVIEWERS WILL DO, THEY WILL
EITHER CORROBORATE OR DEBUNK
STORIES THAT FACEBOOK'S MACHINE
LEARNING TOOLS HAVE FLAGGED AS
POTENTIALLY MISINFORMATION.
FACEBOOK HAS BEEN CRITICIZED
THEY'VE COME UNDER FIRE FOR NOT
REMOVING MISINFORMATION FROM THE
PLATFORM FAST ENOUGH SO THEY'RE
HOPING THAT THIS WILL BE THE
ANSWER TO THAT PROBLEM.
OF COURSE THIS COMES AHEAD OF
THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
WHEN A LOT OF THESE SOCIAL MEDIA
PLATFORMS WILL BE UNDER SCRUTINY
FOR HOW THEY HANDLE INFORMATION
THAT IS INCORRECT ON THE
PLATFORM.
SO WE WILL SEE IF THIS WORKS.
AS WE SAID, IT IS A TEST PRO
PROGRAM.
THEY MIGHT TWEAK IT.
THEY MIGHT EXPAND IT.
WE'RE NOT SURE BUT HOPEFULLY
THIS IS SOMETHING MOVING IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION TO STOPPING THE
SPREAD OF FALSE INFORMATION.
>> OKAY.
WE'RE FINGERS CROSSED THAT THAT
WORKS.
MEANTIME, GOOGLE HAS FINALLY
COME UP WITH AN ANSWER TO THAT I
MESSAGE FROM APPLE.
>> YES.
THEY'VE ROLLED OUT THEIR OWN
MESSAGING PROGRAM THAT LOOKS
JUST LIKE APPLE'S I MESSAGE.
IT IS CALLED CHAT ANDROID DE
DEVICES IN THE U.S. WILL BE ABLE
TO USE THIS STARTING VERY SOON.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT WAS
ROLLED OUT IN THE UK IN FRANCE
AND MEXICO EARLIER THIS YEAR.
SO SOME OF THE FEATURES YOU WILL
BE ABLE TO SEND TEXT MESSAGES
WITH UP TO 8,000 CHARACTERS.
SEND HIGH RESOLUTION PICTURES
AND VIDEOS.
YOU'LL ALSO BE ABLE TO ACTIVATE
THOSE RED RECEIPTS WHICH YOU
HAVE WITH THE APPLE I MESSAGE
AND THOSE, N LITTLE THOUGHT
BUBBLE THAT YOU SEE WHEN SOMEONE
IS TEXTING.
THEY'RE TYPING.
YOU WILL HAVE THAT AVAILABLE IN
CHAT AS WELL.
SO NOW BOTH PLATFORMS WILL HAVE
VERY SIMILAR MESSAGING SYSTEMS.
I DO BELIEVE THAT WITH GOOGLE
CHAT IT'S STILL GOING TO BE A
GREEN MESSAGE IT'S NOT GOING TO
BE BLUE LIKE APPLE'SISM MESSAGE.
>> RIGHT.
OKAY.
AT LEAST THEY'VE COME UP WITH
SOMETHING.
OKAY.
TRACEE LET'S LEAVE IT THERE.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> THANKS, BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
>>> 7:46.
HI, MIKE.
>> GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING.
>> HOW WE DOING OUT THERE.
>> WE'RE DOING ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE JUST COLD HONESTLY THAT'S
WHAT WE'LL BE FOR THE NECK
SEVERAL DAYS.
GOOD NEWS ON THE SEVEN DAY IF
YOU CAN BELIEVE THIS WE DON'T
HAVE ANY RAIN.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY SNOW.
>> OKAY.
>> RIGHT ON THROUGH THE
CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY.
>> HALLELUJAH.
>> LET'S GET WHERE WE NEED TO
BE.
LET'S HAVE A HAPPY HOLIDAY.
>> CHRISTMAS MIRACLE, MIKE.
>> IT IS.
>> YEAH.
LIVE LOOK AT YOUR WEATHER
>> IT IS.
HEADLINES OUT THERE FOR YOUR
LIVE LOOK AT YOUR WEATHER
WEDNESDAY MORNING HERE.
HEADLINES OUT THERE FOR YOUR
SUNSHINE IS BACK.
WEDNESDAY MORNING HERE.
LAST WEDNESDAY OF FALL BY THE
SUNSHINE IS BACK.
WAY IF YOU CAN BELIEVE IT.
LAST WEDNESDAY OF FALL BY THE
WINTER STARTS ON SATURDAY.
WAY IF YOU CAN BELIEVE IT.
SUNSHINE COMING BACK TODAY.
WINTER STARTS ON SATURDAY.
LITTLE BIT OF, YOU KNOW, FALSE
SUNSHINE COMING BACK TODAY.
HOPE WITH THE SUNSHINE BECAUSE
LITTLE BIT OF, YOU KNOW, FALSE
YOU'D THINK MAYBE A NICE WARM
HOPE WITH THE SUNSHINE BECAUSE
AFTERNOON.
YOU'D THINK MAYBE A NICE WARM
NOT NECESSARILY.
AFTERNOON.
WINDS GOING TO BLOW LATER ON
NOT NECESSARILY.
TODAY UPPER 30S, LOWER 40S FOR
WINDS GOING TO BLOW LATER ON
DAYTIME HIGHS EVEN COLDER AS WE
TODAY UPPER 30S, LOWER 40S FOR
WORK OUR WAY THREW YOUR DAY ON
DAYTIME HIGHS EVEN COLDER AS WE
THURSDAY.
WORK OUR WAY THREW YOUR DAY ON
REALLY GOING TO BE A WINTER
THURSDAY.
CHILL KIND OF FEEL AROUND HERE
REALLY GOING TO BE A WINTER
OVER THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
CHILL KIND OF FEEL AROUND HERE
GOOD NEWS AS MENTIONED JUST A
OVER THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
MOMENT AGO WEEKEND LOOKS DRY FOR
GOOD NEWS AS MENTIONED JUST A
THOSE OF YOU GETTING OUT OF TOWN
MOMENT AGO WEEKEND LOOKS DRY FOR
FOR CHRISTMAS DESTINATIONS.
THOSE OF YOU GETTING OUT OF TOWN
THINK YOU'LL BE OKAY.
FOR CHRISTMAS DESTINATIONS.
VAST MAJORITY OF THE COUNTRY
THINK YOU'LL BE OKAY.
PUTTING STUFF TOGETHER FOR OUR
VAST MAJORITY OF THE COUNTRY
TRAVEL FORECAST VAST MAJORITY OF
PUTTING STUFF TOGETHER FOR OUR
THE COUNTRY LOOKS LIKE THEY'LL
TRAVEL FORECAST VAST MAJORITY OF
BE DRY HEADING INTO THE WEEKEND.
THE COUNTRY LOOKS LIKE THEY'LL
33 FOR WASHINGTON.
BE DRY HEADING INTO THE WEEKEND.
25 GAITHERSBURG.
33 FOR WASHINGTON.
WEST MINSTER 28.
25 GAITHERSBURG.
32 FOR MEN LEONARDTOWN.
WEST MINSTER 28.
FLED BURG YOU'RE AT 28 DEGREES.
32 FOR MEN LEONARDTOWN.
THE WIND IS BLOWING HERE AND
FLED BURG YOU'RE AT 28 DEGREES.
THERE AND THIS IS GOING TO KIND
THE WIND IS BLOWING HERE AND
OF INCREASE THROUGHOUT THE
THERE AND THIS IS GOING TO KIND
DAYTIME HOURS TODAY.
OF INCREASE THROUGHOUT THE
MAKING IT FEEL LIKE 17
DAYTIME HOURS TODAY.
GAITHERSBURG THERE.
MAKING IT FEEL LIKE 17
MARTINSBURG FEELS LIKE 18.
GAITHERSBURG THERE.
19 FOR CUMBERLAND.
MARTINSBURG FEELS LIKE 18.
22 WEST MINSTER OVER TO THE
19 FOR CUMBERLAND.
BALTIMORE METRO AREA FEELS LIKE
22 WEST MINSTER OVER TO THE
22 DEGREES AS THEY START THEIR
BALTIMORE METRO AREA FEELS LIKE
DAY.
22 DEGREES AS THEY START THEIR
THIS IS FUTURE CAST WIND CHILLS
DAY.
WHAT THE AIR TEMPERATURE WILL
THIS IS FUTURE CAST WIND CHILLS
FEEL LIKE WATCH IT INTO THE
WHAT THE AIR TEMPERATURE WILL
EVENING HOURS TONIGHT AS THINGS
FEEL LIKE WATCH IT INTO THE
REALLY START TO FALL BACK.
EVENING HOURS TONIGHT AS THINGS
MAYBE SINGLE DIGIT WIND CHILLS
REALLY START TO FALL BACK.
MUCH THIS IS MIDNIGHT, OF
MAYBE SINGLE DIGIT WIND CHILLS
COURSE, NOT TOO MANY FOLKS OUT
MUCH THIS IS MIDNIGHT, OF
AND ABOUT AT THAT TIME MAYBE YOU
COURSE, NOT TOO MANY FOLKS OUT
ARE I DON'T JUDGE.
AND ABOUT AT THAT TIME MAYBE YOU
13 DEGREES COULD BE THE REAL
ARE I DON'T JUDGE.
FEEL BY MIDNIGHT TONIGHT HERE IN
13 DEGREES COULD BE THE REAL
WASHINGTON BUT IT'S AS WE GET UP
FEEL BY MIDNIGHT TONIGHT HERE IN
AND GO TO WORK AND GO TO SCHOOL
WASHINGTON BUT IT'S AS WE GET UP
TOMORROW MORNING THAT THOSE REAL
AND GO TO WORK AND GO TO SCHOOL
FEEL TEMPERATURES WILL REALLY
TOMORROW MORNING THAT THOSE REAL
KIND OF BE HITTING YOU PRETTY
FEEL TEMPERATURES WILL REALLY
HARD.
KIND OF BE HITTING YOU PRETTY
10 DEGREES MAYBE AS KIDS GET OFF
HARD.
TO SCHOOL EARLY TOMORROW MORNING
10 DEGREES MAYBE AS KIDS GET OFF
HERE IN GAITHERSBURG.
TO SCHOOL EARLY TOMORROW MORNING
14 HERE IN WASHINGTON.
HERE IN GAITHERSBURG.
15 DULLES.
14 HERE IN WASHINGTON.
SEVEN MAYBE FOR HAGERSTOWN.
15 DULLES.
SOME OF THE COLDEST AIR WE'VE
SEVEN MAYBE FOR HAGERSTOWN.
EXPERIENCED SO FAR THIS FALL
SOME OF THE COLDEST AIR WE'VE
COMING YOUR WAY LATER ON
EXPERIENCED SO FAR THIS FALL
TONIGHT.
COMING YOUR WAY LATER ON
GOOD NEWS, SATELLITE/RADAR NICE
TONIGHT.
AND QUIET.
GOOD NEWS, SATELLITE/RADAR NICE
WE'LL KEEP IT THAT WAY THROUGH
AND QUIET.
MOST OF THE AFTERNOON.
WE'LL KEEP IT THAT WAY THROUGH
MAYBE ISOLATED SNOW FLURRY FARYR
MOST OF THE AFTERNOON.
42 TODAY.
MAYBE ISOLATED SNOW FLURRY FARYR
COLD 35 TOMORROW.
42 TODAY.
THEN WE DO START LITTLE BIT OF A
COLD 35 TOMORROW.
WARMUP AS WE WORK OUR WAY
THEN WE DO START LITTLE BIT OF A
THROUGH THE WEEKEND WHICH IS DRY
WARMUP AS WE WORK OUR WAY
AS WE BRING IN THE NEW SEASON.
THROUGH THE WEEKEND WHICH IS DRY
WINTER BEGINS JUST PAST
AS WE BRING IN THE NEW SEASON.
11:00 O'CLOCK IN THE EVENING ON
WINTER BEGINS JUST PAST
SATURDAY.
11:00 O'CLOCK IN THE EVENING ON
HEADING THROUGH YOUR FIRST FULL
SATURDAY.
WEEK OF WINTER STARTING RUN UP
HEADING THROUGH YOUR FIRST FULL
TO THE CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY, MAYBE
WEEK OF WINTER STARTING RUN UP
FEELS MORE LIKE LATE FALL AS WE
TO THE CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY, MAYBE
GET 50'S BACK ALL THE WAY
FEELS MORE LIKE LATE FALL AS WE
THROUGH CHRISTMAS EVE AND WHY
GET 50'S BACK ALL THE WAY
NOT QUICK LOOK EARLY OUTLOOK FOR
THROUGH CHRISTMAS EVE AND WHY
CHRISTMAS DAY DOESN'T LOOK SO
NOT QUICK LOOK EARLY OUTLOOK FOR
BAD HERE IN D.C.
CHRISTMAS DAY DOESN'T LOOK SO
HOW ABOUT PARTIAL SUNSHINE,
BAD HERE IN D.C.
53 DEGREES.
HOW ABOUT PARTIAL SUNSHINE,
MERRY ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
53 DEGREES.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
MERRY ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
ERIN COMO HAS GOT YOUR TRAFFIC.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
>> I LOVE THAT SEASONAL JOY.
ERIN COMO HAS GOT YOUR TRAFFIC.
7:49.
>> I LOVE THAT SEASONAL JOY.
ON THE FREEWAY THERE'S A CRASH
7:49.
RIGHT LANE BLOCKED BEFORE THE
ON THE FREEWAY THERE'S A CRASH
THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
RIGHT LANE BLOCKED BEFORE THE
THAT IS CAUSING AN OVERFLOW OF
THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
TRAFFIC.
THAT IS CAUSING AN OVERFLOW OF
BACK ON TO THE 14th STREET
TRAFFIC.
BRIDGE.
BACK ON TO THE 14th STREET
IN FACT 10 MILES AN HOUR AVERAGE
BRIDGE.
COMING UP FROM THE PENTAGON OVER
IN FACT 10 MILES AN HOUR AVERAGE
AN HOUR DELAY EDSALL ROAD TO THE
COMING UP FROM THE PENTAGON OVER
14th STREET BRIDGE BECAUSE OF
AN HOUR DELAY EDSALL ROAD TO THE
THAT.
14th STREET BRIDGE BECAUSE OF
YOU'RE STACKED ON THE INBOUND
THAT.
SIDE OF THE 11th STREET BRIDGE
YOU'RE STACKED ON THE INBOUND
AS WELL.
SIDE OF THE 11th STREET BRIDGE
MOVING IT OVER TO 66, THIS HAS
AS WELL.
BEEN A NASTY COMMUTE THIS
MOVING IT OVER TO 66, THIS HAS
MORNING.
BEEN A NASTY COMMUTE THIS
THERE'S A CRASH EASTBOUND INSIDE
MORNING.
THE BELTWAY AT WASHINGTON
THERE'S A CRASH EASTBOUND INSIDE
BOULEVARD.
THE BELTWAY AT WASHINGTON
DETOURING TRAFFIC ON TO THE RAMP
BOULEVARD.
TO WASHINGTON BOULEVARD THROUGH
DETOURING TRAFFIC ON TO THE RAMP
THE CONSTRUCTION ZONE.
TO WASHINGTON BOULEVARD THROUGH
AND THEN YOU CAN SEE THOSE CARS
THE CONSTRUCTION ZONE.
COMING BACK THROUGH THAT EXIT
AND THEN YOU CAN SEE THOSE CARS
THERE GETTING THROUGH ON THE
COMING BACK THROUGH THAT EXIT
SHOULDER VERY VERY SLOW-MOVING
THERE GETTING THROUGH ON THE
TRAFFIC BECAUSE IT'S A LITTLE
SHOULDER VERY VERY SLOW-MOVING
TRICKY THERE.
TRAFFIC BECAUSE IT'S A LITTLE
USE CAUTION.
TRICKY THERE.
WE'RE PARKED ALL THE WAY BACK TO
USE CAUTION.
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY INTO FAIRFAX
WE'RE PARKED ALL THE WAY BACK TO
RIGHT NOW.
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY INTO FAIRFAX
THERE'S ALSO A LOT OF BACKED UP
RIGHT NOW.
TRAFFIC ON THE DULLES TOLL RO
THERE'S ALSO A LOT OF BACKED UP
ROADS.
TRAFFIC ON THE DULLES TOLL RO
WATCH FOR THAT.
ROADS.
29 BACKS UP, ALSO.
WATCH FOR THAT.
BACK TO YOU.
29 BACKS UP, ALSO.
>> ERIN, THANKS VERY.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> SO YESTERDAY ABOUT THIS
>> ERIN, THANKS VERY.
TIME, WE TOLD YOU ABOUT A WOMAN
>>> SO YESTERDAY ABOUT THIS
IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY WHO
TIME, WE TOLD YOU ABOUT A WOMAN
LOST HER HOME AFTER FALLING
IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY WHO
VICTIM TO A MORTGAGE SCHEME.
LOST HER HOME AFTER FALLING
WELL, NOW ANOTHER WOMAN IS
VICTIM TO A MORTGAGE SCHEME.
COMING FORWARD SAYING SHE ALSO
WELL, NOW ANOTHER WOMAN IS
WENT INTO FORECLOSURE AFTER SHE
COMING FORWARD SAYING SHE ALSO
TRUSTED THE SAME MAN BEHIND THAT
WENT INTO FORECLOSURE AFTER SHE
SCHEME.
TRUSTED THE SAME MAN BEHIND THAT
WHAT'S MORE SHE FILED A
SCHEME.
COMPLAINT WITH THE STATE MONTHS
WHAT'S MORE SHE FILED A
AGO BUT IT WENT NOWHERE.
COMPLAINT WITH THE STATE MONTHS
FOX5'S LINDSAY WATTS HAS THE
AGO BUT IT WENT NOWHERE.
FOLLOW YUP.
FOX5'S LINDSAY WATTS HAS THE
>> WHEN I PULLED THE ARTICLE AND
FOLLOW YUP.
I SAW IT WAS WILLIAM WHELAN, I
>> WHEN I PULLED THE ARTICLE AND
ALMOST LOST MY MIND.
I SAW IT WAS WILLIAM WHELAN, I
>> Reporter: AFTER LESEAN
ALMOST LOST MY MIND.
DUNCAN POWELL SAW OUR STORY.
>> Reporter: AFTER LESEAN
>> THIS IS THE SAME GUY THAT WE
DUNCAN POWELL SAW OUR STORY.
WERE WORKING WITH TO GET THE
>> THIS IS THE SAME GUY THAT WE
LONE MODIFICATION.
WERE WORKING WITH TO GET THE
>> Reporter: SHE REALIZED HOW
LONE MODIFICATION.
CLOSELY IT MATCHED HER OWN
>> Reporter: SHE REALIZED HOW
STORY.
CLOSELY IT MATCHED HER OWN
SHE SAYS WILLIAM WHELAN PROMISED
STORY.
TO GET THE MORTGAGE PAYMENT DOWN
SHE SAYS WILLIAM WHELAN PROMISED
ON HER HOME IN UPPER MARLBORO.
TO GET THE MORTGAGE PAYMENT DOWN
>> IT SOUNDED AWESOME.
ON HER HOME IN UPPER MARLBORO.
>> Reporter: SHE PAID WHELAN
>> IT SOUNDED AWESOME.
OVER TWO GRAND AND HE TOLD HER
>> Reporter: SHE PAID WHELAN
STOP PAYING THE MORTGAGE.
OVER TWO GRAND AND HE TOLD HER
JUST LIKE HE TOLD PATRICIA DUCT.
STOP PAYING THE MORTGAGE.
>> HE TOLD ME HE NEVER LOST A
JUST LIKE HE TOLD PATRICIA DUCT.
CASE.
>> HE TOLD ME HE NEVER LOST A
>> Reporter: DUCT ENDED UP
CASE.
LOSING HER DISTRICT HEIGHTS HOME
>> Reporter: DUCT ENDED UP
WHERE SHE WILL LIVED FOR ALMOST
LOSING HER DISTRICT HEIGHTS HOME
20 YEARS.
WHERE SHE WILL LIVED FOR ALMOST
>> MY HEART BREAKS FOR HER.
20 YEARS.
>> DUNCAN POWELL'S HOUSE ALSO
>> MY HEART BREAKS FOR HER.
WENT INTO FORECLOSURE.
>> DUNCAN POWELL'S HOUSE ALSO
BUT SHE WAS SAVED FROM THE SAME
WENT INTO FORECLOSURE.
FATE AFTER WORKING WITH HER
BUT SHE WAS SAVED FROM THE SAME
BANK.
FATE AFTER WORKING WITH HER
>> THEY TOLD ME IT'S ILLEGAL FOR
BANK.
SOMEONE -- FOR TO YOU PAY
>> THEY TOLD ME IT'S ILLEGAL FOR
SOMEONE UP FRONT FOR MORTGAGE
SOMEONE -- FOR TO YOU PAY
SERVICES.
SOMEONE UP FRONT FOR MORTGAGE
HE SAID -- SHE SAID BASICALLY
SERVICES.
YOU GOT HOSED YOU GOT TAKEN.
HE SAID -- SHE SAID BASICALLY
>> Reporter: SHE REALIZED
YOU GOT HOSED YOU GOT TAKEN.
WHELAN HAD A TRACK RECORD THAT
>> Reporter: SHE REALIZED
THE MARYLAND DEPARTMENT OF LABOR
WHELAN HAD A TRACK RECORD THAT
HAD BANNED HIM FROM WORKING IN
THE MARYLAND DEPARTMENT OF LABOR
MORTGAGE SERVICES AND HE WAS
HAD BANNED HIM FROM WORKING IN
CONVICTED IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
MORTGAGE SERVICES AND HE WAS
IT PROMPTED HER TO FILE THIS
CONVICTED IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
COMPLAINT AGAINST WILL LAND WITH
IT PROMPTED HER TO FILE THIS
THE DEPARTMENT OF LABOR.
COMPLAINT AGAINST WILL LAND WITH
THAT WAS MORE THAN SIX MONTHS
THE DEPARTMENT OF LABOR.
AGO.
THAT WAS MORE THAN SIX MONTHS
BUT IT DIDN'T GO ANYWHERE.
AGO.
A LABOR DEPARTMENT SPOKESWOMAN
BUT IT DIDN'T GO ANYWHERE.
TELLS FOX5 THE AGENCY GOT THE
A LABOR DEPARTMENT SPOKESWOMAN
COMPLAINT BUT NEEDED MORE
TELLS FOX5 THE AGENCY GOT THE
INFORMATION.
COMPLAINT BUT NEEDED MORE
THEY SENT DUNCAN POWELL A
INFORMATION.
FOLLOW-UP LETTER IN THE MAIL.
THEY SENT DUNCAN POWELL A
>> I DIDN'T RECEIVE THAT LETTER.
FOLLOW-UP LETTER IN THE MAIL.
>> Reporter: AGENCY CONFIRMS
>> I DIDN'T RECEIVE THAT LETTER.
THAT WAS THE ONLY ATTEMPT TO
>> Reporter: AGENCY CONFIRMS
FOLLOW YUP ON THE COMPLAINT.
THAT WAS THE ONLY ATTEMPT TO
THEN THE CASE WAS CLOSED.
FOLLOW YUP ON THE COMPLAINT.
>> I FELT LIKE MAYBE IF THEY
THEN THE CASE WAS CLOSED.
WOULD HAVE TOOK MY CASE MORE
>> I FELT LIKE MAYBE IF THEY
SERIOUSLY MISS DUCT WON PROBABLY
WOULD HAVE TOOK MY CASE MORE
HAVE LOST HER HOME.
SERIOUSLY MISS DUCT WON PROBABLY
I FEEL LIKE THEY DIDN'T DO
HAVE LOST HER HOME.
ANYTHING AND HE CONTINUED TO
I FEEL LIKE THEY DIDN'T DO
PREY ON VICTIMS.
ANYTHING AND HE CONTINUED TO
>> Reporter: AFTER WE REACHED
PREY ON VICTIMS.
OUT, THE LABOR DEPARTMENT
>> Reporter: AFTER WE REACHED
CONTACTED DUNCAN POWELL ALMOST
OUT, THE LABOR DEPARTMENT
IMMEDIATELY.
CONTACTED DUNCAN POWELL ALMOST
SPOKESPERSON SAYS THE CASE WILL
IMMEDIATELY.
BE REOPENED.
SPOKESPERSON SAYS THE CASE WILL
>> LINDSAY WATTS REPORTING.
BE REOPENED.
WILLIAM WHELAN WAS IN INDICTED
>> LINDSAY WATTS REPORTING.
IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
WILLIAM WHELAN WAS IN INDICTED
EARLIER THIS MONTH AFTER
IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
PATRICIA DUCT WENT TO POLICE.
EARLIER THIS MONTH AFTER
THE WOMAN THAT LINDSAY JUST
PATRICIA DUCT WENT TO POLICE.
SPOKE TO LAST NIGHT PLANS TO GO
THE WOMAN THAT LINDSAY JUST
TO POLICE AS WELL AND WE'LL HAVE
SPOKE TO LAST NIGHT PLANS TO GO
MORE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE
TO POLICE AS WELL AND WE'LL HAVE
WHAT TO DO IF YOU THINK YOU'RE A
MORE INFORMATION ON OUR WEBSITE
VICTIM AND HOW TO AVOID MORTGAGE
WHAT TO DO IF YOU THINK YOU'RE A
FRAUD.
VICTIM AND HOW TO AVOID MORTGAGE
>>> UPS DRIVER ROBBED AT GUN
FRAUD.
POINT YESTERDAY IN SOUTHEAST
>>> UPS DRIVER ROBBED AT GUN
WASHINGTON.
POINT YESTERDAY IN SOUTHEAST
THIS HAPPENED IN THE PARKING LOT
WASHINGTON.
OF A SAFE WAY AT ALABAMA AVENUE
THIS HAPPENED IN THE PARKING LOT
AND NAYLOR ROAD THE SAFEWAY
OF A SAFE WAY AT ALABAMA AVENUE
THERE.
AND NAYLOR ROAD THE SAFEWAY
AUTHORITIES SAY THE UPS DRIVER
THERE.
WS SORTING BOXES IN THE TRUCK
AUTHORITIES SAY THE UPS DRIVER
WHEN A GROUP WALKED UM.
WS SORTING BOXES IN THE TRUCK
UPS DRIVER SAID THEY FLASHED A
WHEN A GROUP WALKED UM.
GUN, TOLD HIM TO GET ON THE
UPS DRIVER SAID THEY FLASHED A
GROUND.
GUN, TOLD HIM TO GET ON THE
THEY STOLE A NUMBER OF PACKAGES
GROUND.
AND THE DRIVER'S BOOK BAG HIS
THEY STOLE A NUMBER OF PACKAGES
SATCHEL AS WELL.
AND THE DRIVER'S BOOK BAG HIS
SILVER LINING HERE, THE DRIVER
SATCHEL AS WELL.
WASN'T HURT.
SILVER LINING HERE, THE DRIVER
>>> BURGLARS TARGETED AT LEAST
WASN'T HURT.
TWO HOMES IN POTOMAC, MARYLAND.
>>> BURGLARS TARGETED AT LEAST
THIS IS DOORBELL VIDEO FROM ONE
TWO HOMES IN POTOMAC, MARYLAND.
OF THE HOMES ON IRON GATE ROAD.
THIS IS DOORBELL VIDEO FROM ONE
NOW, THIS VIDEO SHOWS SEVERAL
OF THE HOMES ON IRON GATE ROAD.
SUSPECTS TRYING TO BREAK IN TO A
NOW, THIS VIDEO SHOWS SEVERAL
HOME ON MONDAY.
SUSPECTS TRYING TO BREAK IN TO A
THE HOMEOWNER TELLS FOX5 THE
HOME ON MONDAY.
SUSPECT GOT SPOOKED WHEN THEY
THE HOMEOWNER TELLS FOX5 THE
HEARD, WHEN THEY HIT THE PANIC
SUSPECT GOT SPOOKED WHEN THEY
BUTTON THE MEN TRIED KICKING IN
HEARD, WHEN THEY HIT THE PANIC
ONE OF THE DOORS BUT THEY DID
BUTTON THE MEN TRIED KICKING IN
NOT GET IN THAT WAY.
ONE OF THE DOORS BUT THEY DID
POLICE ARE LOOKING INTO WHETHER
NOT GET IN THAT WAY.
THESE ARE THE SAME SUSPECTS THAT
POLICE ARE LOOKING INTO WHETHER
BROKE INTO A HOME IN THE NEARBY
THESE ARE THE SAME SUSPECTS THAT
CLAGGAT FARM NEIGHBORHOOD.
BROKE INTO A HOME IN THE NEARBY
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP GAVE FEDERAL
CLAGGAT FARM NEIGHBORHOOD.
WORKERS AN EARLY CHRISTMAS
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP GAVE FEDERAL
SIGNING AN EXECUTIVE ORDER
WORKERS AN EARLY CHRISTMAS
GIVING WORKERS CHRISTMAS EVE OFF
SIGNING AN EXECUTIVE ORDER
WITH BABY.
GIVING WORKERS CHRISTMAS EVE OFF
>> OLYMPIC GOLD MEDALIST DOMINIC
WITH BABY.
OPENING A ACADEMY.
>> OLYMPIC GOLD MEDALIST DOMINIC
IT WILL OFFER CLASSES, HOST
OPENING A ACADEMY.
CAMPS AND DEVELOP A STUDENT
IT WILL OFFER CLASSES, HOST
TEAM.
CAMPS AND DEVELOP A STUDENT
SHE LIVES IN MARYLAND WAS PART
TEAM.
OF TEAM IN 1992, 1996 AND 2,000.
SHE LIVES IN MARYLAND WAS PART
THAT GYM IS SCHEDULED TO OPEN
OF TEAM IN 1992, 1996 AND 2,000.
NECK SPRING.
THAT GYM IS SCHEDULED TO OPEN
>> GIVING BACK A LITTLE BIT OF
NECK SPRING.
HOLLYWOOD COMING TO DUPONT
>> GIVING BACK A LITTLE BIT OF
CIRCLE THIS WEEK.
HOLLYWOOD COMING TO DUPONT
MOVIE STARRING MICHAEL B. JORDAN
CIRCLE THIS WEEK.
FILMING IN THAT AREA TOMORROW.
MOVIE STARRING MICHAEL B. JORDAN
THE MOVIE IS CALLED WITHOUT
FILMING IN THAT AREA TOMORROW.
REMORSE IT'S BASED ON OOH TOM
THE MOVIE IS CALLED WITHOUT
CLANCY NOVEL.
REMORSE IT'S BASED ON OOH TOM
DUE OUT NEXT SEPTEMBER SO IT'S
CLANCY NOVEL.
THE FIRST OF A SERIES.
DUE OUT NEXT SEPTEMBER SO IT'S
YOU CAN EXPECT CLOSURES ON THE
THE FIRST OF A SERIES.
SURROUNDING STREETS FROM 6:30
YOU CAN EXPECT CLOSURES ON THE
THURSDAY EVENING TO 6:00 A.M.
SURROUNDING STREETS FROM 6:30
FRIDAY BUT HERE'S THE HEADLINE.
THURSDAY EVENING TO 6:00 A.M.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN DUPONT CIRCLE.
FRIDAY BUT HERE'S THE HEADLINE.
SOME GREAT STAR GAZING.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN DUPONT CIRCLE.
HEY.
SOME GREAT STAR GAZING.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
>> ♪
THANK YOU.
>>> SUCH A CUTIE PIE.
>> ♪
IT IS 7:54 RIGHT NOW.
>>> SUCH A CUTIE PIE.
LET'S GIVE YOU A LOOK AT THE
IT IS 7:54 RIGHT NOW.
GOOD DAY GUEST LIST.
LET'S GIVE YOU A LOOK AT THE
STAR WARS WEEK ROLLS ON.
GOOD DAY GUEST LIST.
WHY DID I THINK THAT WAS TUCKER
STAR WARS WEEK ROLLS ON.
AT FIRST BUT THAT'S JJ ABRAMS.
WHY DID I THINK THAT WAS TUCKER
>> DEFINITELY NOT.
AT FIRST BUT THAT'S JJ ABRAMS.
>> AS THE REST OF THE WORLD
>> DEFINITELY NOT.
WAITS TO SEE THE RISE OF SKY
>> AS THE REST OF THE WORLD
WALKER KEVIN MCCARTHY HAS SEEN
WAITS TO SEE THE RISE OF SKY
THE MOVIE.
WALKER KEVIN MCCARTHY HAS SEEN
HE SAT DOWN WITH THIS MAN
THE MOVIE.
DIRECTOR JJ ABRAMS AND STAR
HE SAT DOWN WITH THIS MAN
ISAAC -- OSCAR ISAAC.
DIRECTOR JJ ABRAMS AND STAR
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS FROM
ISAAC -- OSCAR ISAAC.
HIS INTERVIEW.
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS FROM
>> TONIGHT THE SEASON FINALE OF
HIS INTERVIEW.
THE MASKED SINGER.
>> TONIGHT THE SEASON FINALE OF
ONLY THREE SINGERS REMAIN,
THE MASKED SINGER.
ROTWEILER, FLAMINGO AND THE FOX.
ONLY THREE SINGERS REMAIN,
WE'LL GIVE OUR FINAL GUESSES
ROTWEILER, FLAMINGO AND THE FOX.
WHO'S UNDER THOSE MASKS.
WE'LL GIVE OUR FINAL GUESSES
>> IT'S WEDNESDAY.
WHO'S UNDER THOSE MASKS.
SO THAT MEANS THE GOOD FOLKS
>> IT'S WEDNESDAY.
FROM TMZ WILL JOIN US LIFE
SO THAT MEANS THE GOOD FOLKS
BRINGING US ALL THE CELEBRITY
FROM TMZ WILL JOIN US LIFE
NEWS AND GOSSIP THAT YOU DIDN'T
BRINGING US ALL THE CELEBRITY
KNOW YOU NEEDED ABOUT YOUR
NEWS AND GOSSIP THAT YOU DIDN'T
FAVORITE TINSELTOW TINSELTOWN S.
KNOW YOU NEEDED ABOUT YOUR
>> GETS GET TO MIKE THOMAS.
FAVORITE TINSELTOW TINSELTOWN S.
>> I'M EXCITED WHEN THE MASK
>> GETS GET TO MIKE THOMAS.
SINGER ENDS.
>> I'M EXCITED WHEN THE MASK
I DEFINITELY KNOW WHO THE
SINGER ENDS.
ROTWEILER IS.
I DEFINITELY KNOW WHO THE
>> YOU THINK IT'S DAUTE.
ROTWEILER IS.
>> NOT TO BE.
>> YOU THINK IT'S DAUTE.
THE OTHER TWO I'M ON THE FENCE
>> NOT TO BE.
ABOUT.
THE OTHER TWO I'M ON THE FENCE
>> I THINK I KNOW THE OTHER TWO.
ABOUT.
>> YOU DO?
>> I THINK I KNOW THE OTHER TWO.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DO?
>> WAYNE BRADY.
>> YEAH.
>> UH-HUH.
>> WAYNE BRADY.
>> THE FOX AND ADRIEN BY LOAN
>> UH-HUH.
THE FLAMINGO.
>> THE FOX AND ADRIEN BY LOAN
>> NOW THOSE ARE --
THE FLAMINGO.
>> WE'LL SEE TONIGHT.
>> NOW THOSE ARE --
>> WE'LL FIND OUT TONIGHT FOR
>> WE'LL SEE TONIGHT.
SURE.
>> WE'LL FIND OUT TONIGHT FOR
WIND CHILL VALUES THIS IS WHAT
SURE.
WE'RE REALLY WATCHING WE'RE DRY
WIND CHILL VALUES THIS IS WHAT
TODAY AND TOMORROW.
WE'RE REALLY WATCHING WE'RE DRY
BUT THOSE TEMPERATURES WILL BE
TODAY AND TOMORROW.
PLUMMETING TO NIGHT LOOK AT
BUT THOSE TEMPERATURES WILL BE
THAT.
PLUMMETING TO NIGHT LOOK AT
WIND CHILL VALUES IF YOU'RE
THAT.
HEADING OUT LATER ON THIS
WIND CHILL VALUES IF YOU'RE
EVENING IN THE LOWER TEENS AND
HEADING OUT LATER ON THIS
SOME OF OUR NORTHWEST SUBURBS
EVENING IN THE LOWER TEENS AND
AND BY TOMORROW MORNING AS YOU
SOME OF OUR NORTHWEST SUBURBS
GET YOURSELF OFF TO WORK AND THE
AND BY TOMORROW MORNING AS YOU
KIDS OFF TO SCHOOL COULD BE
GET YOURSELF OFF TO WORK AND THE
SINGLE DIGIT WIND CHILLS OFF TO
KIDS OFF TO SCHOOL COULD BE
THE NORTH AND TO THE WEST.
SINGLE DIGIT WIND CHILLS OFF TO
EXPECT A COLD MORNING AS WE --
THE NORTH AND TO THE WEST.
COLD NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS HERE IN
EXPECT A COLD MORNING AS WE --
D.C. AS WE WRAP UP THIS FINAL
COLD NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS HERE IN
WEEK IN THE SEASON OF FALL.
D.C. AS WE WRAP UP THIS FINAL
42 TODAY.
WEEK IN THE SEASON OF FALL.
35 TOMORROW.
42 TODAY.
AND THEN HEADING INTO FRIDAY, 4.
35 TOMORROW.
GOOD NEWS FOR TRAVELERS THIS
AND THEN HEADING INTO FRIDAY, 4.
WEEKEND, NO CONCERNS AS WE START
GOOD NEWS FOR TRAVELERS THIS
THAT RUN UP TOWARDS CHRISTMAS
WEEKEND, NO CONCERNS AS WE START
AND THE CRAZINESS OF CHRISTMAS
THAT RUN UP TOWARDS CHRISTMAS
TRAVEL WEATHER WILL NOT BE A
AND THE CRAZINESS OF CHRISTMAS
HEADACHE FOR YOU AROUND THE D.C.
TRAVEL WEATHER WILL NOT BE A
AREA.
HEADACHE FOR YOU AROUND THE D.C.
ALL RIGHT.
AREA.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
ALL RIGHT.
OFF TO ERIN FOR TRAFFIC.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
>> 7:56 RIGHT NOW.
OFF TO ERIN FOR TRAFFIC.
TAKING A LOOK AT OUR ROADS AND
>> 7:56 RIGHT NOW.
OUR RAILS.
TAKING A LOOK AT OUR ROADS AND
METRO IS ON TIME BIG PROBLEMS ON
OUR RAILS.
THE FREEWAY.
METRO IS ON TIME BIG PROBLEMS ON
CRASH BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE
THE FREEWAY.
BEFORE THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
CRASH BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY EASTBOUND
BEFORE THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
DELAYS BACK PASTED PENTAGON
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY EASTBOUND
RIGHT NOW SEEING ABOUT AN HOUR
DELAYS BACK PASTED PENTAGON
DELAY EDSALL ROAD TO THE THIRD
RIGHT NOW SEEING ABOUT AN HOUR
STREET TUNNEL.
DELAY EDSALL ROAD TO THE THIRD
295 NORTHBOUND AND SOUTHBOUND
STREET TUNNEL.
JAMMING TOWARD THE 11th STREET
295 NORTHBOUND AND SOUTHBOUND
BRIDGE SUITLAND PARKWAY AND
JAMMING TOWARD THE 11th STREET
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE HEAVY.
BRIDGE SUITLAND PARKWAY AND
50 WESTBOUND THERE IS A CRASH
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE HEAVY.
BLOCKING TWO RIGHT LANES AT
50 WESTBOUND THERE IS A CRASH
GLEBE ROAD KEEP IN MIND 50 AS
BLOCKING TWO RIGHT LANES AT
WELL AS 29 DEALING WITH BAIL OUT
GLEBE ROAD KEEP IN MIND 50 AS
TRAFFIC BECAUSE OF THIS CRASH.
WELL AS 29 DEALING WITH BAIL OUT
66 EASTBOUND AT WASHINGTON
TRAFFIC BECAUSE OF THIS CRASH.
BOULEVARD WITH STILL JUST THAT
66 EASTBOUND AT WASHINGTON
SHOULDER SQUE SQUEEZING PASSED.
BOULEVARD WITH STILL JUST THAT
BACK TO YOU.
SHOULDER SQUE SQUEEZING PASSED.
>> KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
BACK TO YOU.
MORNING.
>> KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
SO MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR 8:00
MORNING.
A.M. HOUR.
SO MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR 8:00
INCLUDING THE LAST MINUTE
A.M. HOUR.
HOLIDAY SHIPPING DEADLINES THAT
INCLUDING THE LAST MINUTE
YOU NEED TO KNOW THIS WEEK.
HOLIDAY SHIPPING DEADLINES THAT
>> WEEK AWAY FROM CHRISTMAS.
YOU NEED TO KNOW THIS WEEK.
IS IT BETTER TO GIVE KIDS A
>> WEEK AWAY FROM CHRISTMAS.
VACATION OR TOYS THIS HOLIDAY
IS IT BETTER TO GIVE KIDS A
SEASON?  IT'S AN ARGUMENT
VACATION OR TOYS THIS HOLIDAY
SUPPORTING SOME R AND R
SEASON?  IT'S AN ARGUMENT
ACTUALLY.
SUPPORTING SOME R AND R
PERFECT GIFT.
ACTUALLY.
SEEMS LIKE THAT'S COMING FROM
PERFECT GIFT.
PARENTS, NOT THE KIDS.
SEEMS LIKE THAT'S COMING FROM
>> RIGHT.
PARENTS, NOT THE KIDS.
>> I WANT TO GO ON VACATION.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU WOULD PREFER THAT.
OULD P.
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
♪
>>> ISN'T THAT PRETTY?
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS TO YOU.
ONE WEEK AND CHRISTMAS MORNING.
CHRISTMAS ALL DAY ACTUALLY MUCH
IT IS 8AM ON THIS WEDNESDAY
MORNING.
NOT ONLY IS IT HUMP DAY IT'S
ALSO AGAIN JUST SEVEN SHORT DAYS
TO THE BIG HOLIDAY.
>> TODAY WILL FEEL A LOT MORE
LIKE CHRISTMAS OUTSIDE.
A LITTLE BIT COOLER FOR SURE.
WE'RE FINALLY SEEING SOME
SUNSHINE.
THE TEMPERATURES MUCH COLDER.
WIND CHILLS WILL MAKE IT FEEL
LIKE IT'S IN THE 20S.
>> THAT'S PRETTY CHILLY LET'S
GET TO MIKE AND ERIN FOR FIRST
CHECK OF WEATHER AND TRAFFIC.
>> MIKE, LET'S START WITH YOU.
>> STEVE, YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THE
20S THAT MAY FEEL WARM COMPARED
TO WHAT'S COMING THIS EVENING.
THE WINDS WILL MAKE IT FEEL LIKE
SINGLE DIGITS AND TEENS.
WE HAVE TO GET YOU READY FOR
THAT.
AS YOU MENTIONED SUNSHINE
FINALLY BACK AND WE'LL KEEP IT
ALL THE WAY THROUGH THE WEEKEND
PREVIEW THAT CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY
COMING UP IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
ERIN HAS PREVIEW OF YOUR ROADS
THIS MORNING.
>> FUR IF YOU'RE HEADING OUT
INSIDE THE BELTWAY LOOK AT THE
PARKING LOT.
66 EASTBOUND ALL LANES BLOCKED
TO WASHINGTON BOULEVARD.
TRAFFIC CONVERT TO GO THAT
CONSTRUCTION RAMP SECONDARIES
OVERFLOWING WITH VOLUME CLOSER
LOOK AT THAT AS WELL AS THE REST
OF YOUR RIDE AROUND THE DMV
NEXT.
♪
>>> HEADLINES ALL EYES ON
CAPITOL HILL TODAY AND THAT'S
WHERE THE HOUSE WILL LIKELY VOTE
TO IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP BY
THE END OF THE DAY TODAY.
BUT THE DEBATE STARTS JUST ONE
HOUR FROM NOW AT 9AM.
THE PRESIDENT CAME OUT SWINGING
AHEAD OF THE EXPECTED VOTE
THOUGH LIGHTING INTO HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI WITH A
SIX-PAGE LETTER.
THE VOTE LIKELY WILL COME IN THE
EARLY EVENING HOURS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WOULD BECOME THE THIRD
PRESIDENT EVER TO BE IMPEACHED.
♪
LET'S GET LOCAL NOW, AND TO THE
SECOND AMENDMENT SANCTUARY
MOVEMENT SWEEPING ACROSS
VIRGINIA.
THE STAFFORD COUNTY BOARD OF
SUPERVISORS VOTED LAST NIGHT IN
FAVOR OF BECOMING A SECOND
AMENDMENT SANCTUARY.
>> VOTE CAME AFTER A HEARING
WHERE HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE SHOWED
UP TO VOICE THEIR OPINION.
THIS MORNING BOB BARNARD
FOLLOWING UP HE HAS THE LATEST
FOR US FROM STAFFORD COUNTY.
BOB.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
STEVE AND ALLISON.
THE BOARD OF SUPERVISORS VOTE
WAS UNANIMOUS.
SEVEN TO NOTHING.
80 PEOPLE SIGNED UP TO SPEAK.
THERE WERE ROUGHLY 300 OR SO
OUTSIDE WE CAN SHOW YOU WHAT
THAT LOOKED LIKE HERE MOST OF
THEM THE OVERWHELMING MAJORITY
IN SUPPORT OF STAFFORD COUNTY
DECLARING ITSELF SECOND
AMENDMENT SANCTUARY.
THIS ALL OF COURSE IS AHEAD OF
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY HERE IN
VIRGINIA LAUNCHING ITS NEXT
SESSION IN JANUARY NEXT MONTH.
DEMOCRATS TAKING CONTROL OVER
BOTH HOUSES AND EXPECTED TO
ENACT BANDS ON ASSAULT STYLE
WEAPONS, HIGH CAPACITY
MAGAZINES, BUMP STOCKS AND
SILENCERS AND MANDATING
BACKGROUND CHECKS ON ALL GUN
SALES.
LAST NIGHT WE SPOKE TO SOME WHO
WERE HER LAST NIGHT ALMOST ALL
OF THEM IN SUPPORT OF STAFFORD
BECOMING A SECOND AMENDMENT
SANCTUARY.
>> WE'VE HAD TWO ATTEMPTED BREAK
INS.
IF THEY TAKE MY GUNS AWAY, I'VE
GOT NO WAY TO PROTECT MY FAMILY,
MY HOME, NOTHING.
>> OUR CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHT TO
PROTECT OUR PROMPT AND OUR
LIVES.
SO THEY'RE INN FRINGING UPON
THAT RIGHT.
>> SOME PEOPLE I SHOOT GUNS.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR ME TO
BECOME A FELON JUST FOR OWNING A
FIREARM.
>> WHY DO WE NEED BUM MANY
STOCKS?  WHY DO WE NEED, UM, YOU
KNOW, MASS AMOUNTS OF AMMU
AMMUNITION?  I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THESE PEOPLE WANT THAT.
WHY STAFFORD COUNTY WANT TO BE A
SAFE HAVEN FOR THOSE PEOPLE?
>> Reporter: YES, HERE WHO
OPPOSE THE DECLARATION AGAIN THE
VOTE BY THE STAFFORD COUNTY
BOARD OF SUPERVISORS WAS
UNANIMOUS.
SEVEN TO NOTHING.
JOINING CULPEPER, SPOTSYLVANIA
AND PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTIES
WHICH HAVE ALREADY DECLARED
THEMSELVES SECOND AMENDMENT
SANCTUARIES.
GUYS?
>> BOB, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> 8:04.
HAPPENING TODAY, THE MAN ACCUSED
OF IN THE DEADLY STABBING AT A
MARYLAND POPEYE'S RESTAURANT
WILL BE IN COURT.
GRAND JURY INDICTED RICOH
MCCLAIN YESTERDAY ON MURDER AND
WEAPONS CHARGE, HE'S ACCUSED OF
STABBING KEVIN DAVIS LAST MONTH
OUTSIDE OF POPEYE'S IN OXON H
HILL.
>>> ALSO TODAY, IN MARYLAND,
CLOSING ARGUMENTS EXPECTED IN
THE TRIAL OF SEAN URBANSKI
THAT'S THE MAN YOU SEE THERE
CHARGED WITH FIRST DEGREE MURDER
IN THE KILLING OF BUOY STATE
STUDENT LIEUTENANT RICHARD
COLLINS, II.
PROSECUTORS SAY URBANSKI KILLED
COLLINS ON THE CAMPUS OF
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND BECAUSE
OF HIS SKIN COLOR BECAUSE HE'S
AFRICAN-AMERICAN.
HOWEVER, A JUDGE DROPPED HATE
CRIME CHARGES AGAINST URBANSKI
YESTERDAY.
STEVE?
>> IN THE DISTRICT, A
FOUR-YEAR-OLD BOY FIGHTING FOR
HIS LIFE AFTER HE WAS HIT BY A
CAR LAST NIGHT IN SOUTHEAST D.C.
ABOUT 8:15 OUTSIDE OF ROCKET
SHIP LEGACY PREP WHERE THAT
YOUNG MAN IS A STUDENT.
HE WAS TAKEN BY HELICOPTER TO A
TRAUMA CENTER.
UNCLEAR IF THE DRIVER OF THE CAR
WHO STRUCK HIM STAYED ON THE
SCENE.
>>> ALSO, IN THE DISTRICT
FRIGHTENING ROBBERY AT TM CAUGHT
ON CAMERA.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS WAS EARLIER THIS MONTH IN
THE 1900 BLOCK OF 14th STREET.
POLICE ASKING FOR THE PUBLIC'S
HELP IDENTIFYING THOSE THREE
SUSPECTS SCENE ON THE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO WHO WERE
ROBBING THAT MAN INSIDE OF THE
A TM ENCLOSURE.
>> IT IS AT 05:00 RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GET TO WEATHER.
>> GOOD MORNING.
WE'RE STARTING THINGS OFF COLD
MUCH COLDER THAN THE PAST COUPLE
OF DAYS.
MOSTLY BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE THE
CLOUDS OUT THERE ACTUALLY.
SKIES HAVE CLEARED NICELY.
BAD NEWS, WINDS WILL KICK UP AND
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE THINGS FEEL
COLDER.
SUNSHINE IS BACK, THOUGH.
>> YAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I'M JUST JOKING.
GREAT.
>> THERE'S THE ENTHUSIASM I
LOVE.
GOOD MORNING.
32 DEGREES.
FINALLY HIT THE FREEZING MARK
HERE IN D.C. AS WELL AS
ANNAPOLIS AND LEN TOWN CHECKING
IN AT 32 THIS HOUR.
29 FOR QUANTICO.
24 MANASSAS.
28 FOR GAITHERSBURG.
THE WIND IS BLOWING PARTICULARLY
NORTH AND WEST IT FEELS LIKE 20
FOR GAITHERSBURG.
27 FOR -- I'M SORRY FOR
MARTINSBURG.
27 THERE FOR FREDERICK.
28 FOR DULLES.
27 FOR COMER LAND.
NOT BLOWING TOO BAD.
WINDS WILL INCREASE, THOUGH,
INTO THE LATE AFTERNOON AND
EARLY EVENING HOURS TONIGHT.
AND STICK WITH US THREW AT LEAST
TOMORROW MORNING.
SATELLITE/RADAR PRETTY QUITE
HERE ACROSS THE MID ATLANTIC
REGION FOR THOU NOW.
YOU SEE THAT STRETCH OF SNOW
SHOWERS TRYING TO COME OFF THE
GREAT LAKES AND MAKE ITS WAY IN
OUR DIRECTION DON'T EXPECT ANY
SNOWFLAKES HERE IN TOWN BUT SOME
OF OUR NORTHWEST ZONES COULD
MAYBE SNEAK IN A SNOW FLURRY OR
TWO.
NOTHING WOULD ACCUMULATE OR
CAUSE ANY PROBLEMS.
HAGERSTOWN JUST 29 DEGREES FOR
DAYTIME HIGH TODAY.
32 FOR FREDERICK.
HERE IN D.C. WE MAKE LOWER 40
FORCE A PERIOD OF TIME BUT THE
GENERAL THEME IS WE'RE KEEPING
IT COLD TODAY.
WE'RE EVEN COLDER TOMORROW AND
THIS IS THE LAST WEEK OF FALL.
WINTER HASN'T EVEN OFFICIALLY
GUN YET.
THAT COMES SATURDAY.
WE'LL HAVE THE FULL WEEKEND
FORECAST GET YOU TO YOUR TRAVEL
DESTINATIONS ALL RIGHT AND
PREVIEW CHRISTMAS AS WELCOMING
UP IN 10 MINUTES.
>> THANKS, MIKE.
APPRECIATE IT HERE'S ERIN WITH
THE COMMUTE.
>> BAD COMMUTE, TOO.
8:06 RIGHT NOW.
EASTBOUND 66 AT WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
STARTING TO FINALLY LET TRAFFIC
THROUGH IN ONE OF THE LANES OF
66.
PREVIOUSLY THEY'D BEEN DETOURING
TRAFFIC TO THE OFF-RAMP TO
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD THROUGH THE
CONSTRUCTION ZONE HOOKING BACK
ON TO 66 EASTBOUND.
UNFORTUNATELY 17 MILES AN HOUR
AVERAGE WE HAVE BAIL OUT TRAFFIC
ON 267 DULLES TOLL ROAD HEAVY
BACKUPS FROM THE BELTWAY TO 66
ON THE DULLES TOLL ROAD
SOUTHBOUND HEAVY DELAYS ON 66
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY AND BAIL OUT
TRAFFIC ALONG 29 AND 50 A LOT OF
HEAVY TRAFFIC IN ARLINGTON AND
WEST FALLS CHURCH THIS MORNING.
THERE'S ALSO A CRASH ON ONE OF
THOSE ALTERNATES 50 ON THE
WESTBOUND SIDE THOUGH HEADING
THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION TWO RIGHT
LANES BLOCKED AT GLEBE ROAD.
NOTICE HOW ALL OF THOSE
SECONDARIES JUST HAVE A TON OF
BACKED UP TRAFFIC IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS THIS MORNING.
ON THE FREEWAY THERE'S A CRASH
BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE BEFORE
THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
IT WILL TAKE YOU ALMOST AN HOUR
AND A HALF RIGHT NOW TO GET FROM
EDSALL ROAD TO THE THAT THIRD
STREET TUNNEL BIG PROBLEMS
THERE.
ANY QUESTIONS ERIN FOX5 D.C. ON
TWITTER.
I HATE SEEING DRIVE TIMES LIKE
THAT.
BACK TO YOU.
♪
>>> OH, MY GOD IT'S GOING UP.
THE BUILDING IS ON FIRE.
>> I WAS SLEEPING.
WHEN I WAKE UP THE WHOLE ROOM
WAS ON FIRE.
♪
>> HELP US!
>> ANYBODY INJURED?  ANYBODY
INJURED?
>> THERE WERE PEOPLE WHO WERE
DROPPING THEIR CHILDREN OUT OF
THE THIRD FLOOR WINDOWS.
>> IS THIS YOUR BOY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A TRAIL OF
PEOPLE TO BLAME FOR WHAT
HAPPENED I BELIEVE.
>> ♪
>> HARD TO WATCH BUT KNEW THIS
MORNING, LEGAL SETTLEMENT AFTER
A DEADLY GAS EXPLOSION IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
SEVEN PEOPLE DIED.
DOZENS WERE INJURED AT THE
FLOWER BRANCH APARTMENTS IN
SILVER SPRING BACK IN 2016.
FOX5'S MELANIE ALNWICK IS LIVE
IN SILVER SPRING NOW WITH THE
VERY LATEST.
MEL, WE JUST SHOWED THAT REALLY
TOUCHING PACKAGE TO REMIND
EVERYONE OF THE DEVASTATION AND
THE TRAGEDY THAT HAPPENED ON
THAT SUMMER DAY.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
I WAS HERE THAT VERY MORNING.
IT WAS THE STRANGEST SCENE AND
VERY ERIE.
I MEAN IN THIS TREE RIGHT HERE,
IT WAS FULL OF BELONGINGS.
PEOPLE'S BELONGINGS THAT WERE
BEEN BLASTED OUT OF THE
APARTMENT ACROSS THE PARKING LOT
ALL THE WAY UP ON THAT GRASSY
AREA THERE WERE DOORS AND WINDOW
FRAMES AND NOW THE BUILDING
ITSELF HAS BEEN COMPLETELY
REBUILT AS IF NOTHING EVER
HAPPENED HERE.
WELL WE FOUND OUT YESTERDAY TWO
LAWSUITS FILED BY PEOPLE WHO
EITHER DIED OR SUFFERED DAMAGES
IN THIS THERE WAS A SETTLEMENT.
IT WAS MADE ON FRIDAY BUT THE
TERMS ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
SO WASHINGTON GAS AND THE
RESIDENTS THEY CAN'T DISCUSS THE
DETAILS OF IT.
BUT BOTH OF THOSE LAWSUITS
SETTLED IN THE SAME BASICALLY IN
THE SAME AGREEMENT.
NOW, AT THE SAME TIME THOUGH
WASHINGTON GAS STILL FACING
POSSIBLE FINES FROM THE STATE OF
MARYLAND.
THAT GAS EXPLOSION TOUR APART
THE BUILDING AT THE FLOWER
BRANCH APARTMENTS.
RESIDENTS WERE PLUNGED INTO
DARKNESS, FIRE AND CHOKING
SMOKE.
NOW MANY OF THEM GATHERED
TUESDAY NIGHT BEFORE A HEARING
OF MARYLAND'S PUBLIC SERVICE
COMMISSION TO TELL REGULATOR
WHAT WENT THROUGH.
FIVE ADULTS AND TWO CHILDREN
WERE KILLED.
MORE INJURED AND DISPLACED.
NTSB BLAMED A FAILED PARK
MERCURY REGULATOR THAT WASN'T
CONNECTED TO A VENT LINE WHICH
ALLOWED GAS TO BUILD UP TO
DANGEROUS LEVELS.
THE STATE SAYS THE REGULATOR
SHOULD HAVE BEEN REPLACED.
WASHINGTON GAS STILL DISAGREES
WITH THE NTSB FINDINGS, AND THE
FLOWER BRANCH COMMUNITY IS
KEEPING THE HEAT ON WASHINGTON
GAS IN THESE PUBLIC SERVICE
COMMISSION HEARINGS.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THAT THE
COMMISSION MAKE SURE THAT
WASHINGTON GAS DO WHAT THEY
SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
>> YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE THIS
DOESN'T HAPPEN TO ANYONE ELSE?
>> YES.
NO ONE.
>> WE AS A COMPANY ARE VERY
SADDENED BY WHAT HAPPENED.
WE'RE COMMITTED TO ENSURING SAFE
AND RELIABLE NATURAL GAS SERVICE
THROUGHOUT THE COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: NOW WASHINGTON
GAS SAYS ALL THE GAS INTRA
STRUCTURE HERE AT THE FLOWER
BRANCH APARTMENTS HAS AND
UPDATED AND WORKING TO REPLACE
THE REST OF THE AGING MERCURY
REGULATORS IN THE NEXT 10 YEARS
THROUGHOUT ITS SERVICE AREA.
AS FAR AS THOSE FINES, PUBLIC
SERVICE COMMISSION AGAIN
CONTINUING ITS HEARINGS AND ITS
FACT FINDING TALKING TO PEOPLE
AND GETTING ANSWERS FROM
WASHINGTON GAS AND PUBLIC
SERVICE COMMISSION SHOULD HAVE
ITS DECISION AFTER JAN
JANUARY 31st.
>> MELANIE, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> 8:11.
STILL AHEAD THIS MORNING
TEENAGER WHO WAS AT THE CENTER
OF AN AMBER ALERT NOW ADMITS SHE
STAGED HER OWN KIDNAPPING.
WHY POLICE BELIEVE SHE MADE THE
WHOLE THING UP.
>> PLUS, WE WILL TALK ABOUT A
DOUBLE STANDARD HYPED THE WHEEL.
A POLICE OFFICER FOUND PASSED
OUT DRUNK IN HIS PATROL CAR BUT
HE HASN'T BEEN CHARGED.
THE KEY PIECE OF EVIDENCE THAT'S
MISSING IN THE CASE.
>> FIRST THOUGH IS IT BETTER TO
GIVE KIDS A VACATION OR TOYS
THIS HOLIDAY SEASON?  THE
ARGUMENT SUPPORTING A LITTLE R
AND R AS THE PEFECT GIFT FOR
YOUR KIDS.
>> LIVE LOOK AS WE TAKE YOU TO
THE BREAK.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC COMING UP
FOR YOU ON THE 5'S AT 8:15.
SIT TIGHT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
♪♪
I'm going to the ball.
Tonight is a magical night.
Anything is possible.
I love it.
HOLIDAY TRAVEL SEASON CAN
CERTAINLY BE TRESS FULL BUT
IMAGINE BEING ON A FLIGHT FOR
EIGHT HOURS ONLY TO LAND
85 MILES FROM WHERE YOU TOOK
OFF.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED TO
PASSENGERS ON BOARD A LOU FAN IS
A FLIGHT WHICH TOOK OFF FROM
FRANKFURT, GERMANY TO NEW YORK
CITY.
THERE WERE FIERCE THERE MIGHT
HAVE BEEN A FAULT IN THE PLANE
HAAS' HYDRAULIC SYSTEM THE PLANE
HAD TO DO A U-TURN.
FRANKFURT AIRPORT IS CLOSED AT
NIGHT.
THEY LANDED IN FRANCE AND GOT ON
A BUS AND WENT BACK TO GERMANY.
SPOKESPERSON SAID NO PROBLEMS
OCCURRED ON THE PLANE DESPITE
THE TECHNICAL CONCERNS.
SO ALL THAT TIME ON TRAVEL.
>> IT IS AN ADVENTURE DID YOU
GET WHERE YOU WANTED TO BE?
>> WELL, ARE YOU -- THIS IS AN
EXTENT SHALL QUESTION YOU DID
GET WHERE YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN.
NOT MAYBE WHERE YOU WANTED TO
BE.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS GOING TO WHERE
YOU SHOULD BE..
TO BE.
>> THERE ARE NO ACCIDENTS.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> I'M SURE THE BOSS WILL EXTEND
I WAS FEW EXTRA HOLIDAY DAYS.
>> SURE.
>> MAKE SURE YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
AMOUNT OF TIME WHERE YOU SHOULD
HAVE BEEN.
OR WANTED TO BE.
IT ALL WORKS OUT.
>> GLASS HALF FULL.
>> HI, MICHAEL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
COLD OUTSIDE HERE THIS MORNING.
NO ADVENTURES IN THE WEATHER
DEPARTMENT.
BUT LAY IF YOU'RE ON ADVENTURE
TIS WEEKND YOU'LL WANT TO KNOW
HOW THE WEATHER IS.
LET'S DO THAT.
HOW ABOUT YOUR TRAVEL FORECAST
FR THIS SATURDAY IF YOU'RE
HEADING OUT OF TOWN LOOK HOW
QUIET THE COUNTRY IS.
HONESTLY THE ONLY PLACES YOU
HAVE TO BE CONCERNED IF YOU'RE
HEADING DOWN TO THE SOUTH DUE TO
RAIN BUT NORTHEAST TRAVEL YOU'RE
FINE.
JUST SOME COLD TEMPERATURES
AROUND THE REGION IT'S DOWN TO
THE SOUTH HOUSTON, NEW ORLEANS,
TALLAHASSEE COULD SEE STEADY
RAIN THAT MAY CAUSE DELAYS DOWN
IF YOU'RE HEADING IN THAT
DIRECTION.
BUT UP THROUGH THE MIDWEST,
NORTHERN PLAINS, THEY'RE ALL
NICE AND DRY NO BIG SNOWSTORMS
TO WORRY ABOUT THIS WEEKEND.
SAME DEAL WITH THE INTERIOR
SOUTHWEST.
PHOENIX LOOKING NICE.
70 DEGREES FOR THEM.
ANOTHER TRAVEL ISSUE COULD BE
THE SEATTLE PORTLAND AREA WHERE
THEY EXPECT RAIN AND FOG ON
SATURDAY BUT LON NEST PHYSICAL
YOU'RE TRAVELING ANYWHERE IN THE
COUNTRY FOR THE MOST PART ON
SATURDAY YOU SHOULD BE PRETTY
GOOD TO GO.
AS IT'S A QUIET WEATHER PATTERN
SETTLING IN FOR THE WEEKEND.
32 OUTSIDE IN WASHINGTON.
31 FOR RICHMOND.
21 BECKLY WEST VIRGINIA LOOK AT
DETROIT AND CHICAGO 12 DEGREES
THIS HOUR.
SOME OF THAT COLD IS BREAKING
OFF AND HEADING IN OUR DIRECTION
AND BY TOMORROW MORNING, A
DECENT NUMBER OF US PARTICULARLY
NORTH AND WEST LIKELY TO WAKE UP
TO TEMPERATURES IN THE TEENS AND
LOW 20S.
SO DO GET READY FOR THAT
TOMORROW.
TODAY'S COLD.
TOMORROW IS COLDER.
SATELLITE AND RADAR A COUPLE OF
SNOW SHOWERS UP TOWARDS THE
GREAT LAKES.
ONE OR TWO COULD HIT THE
MOUNTAINS TO THE FAR WEST BUT
HERE IN D.C. WE EXPECT TO KEEP
IT DRY A COUPLE OF PASSING
CLOUDS FROM TIME TO TIME.
OTHER THAN THAT SUNSHINE IS BACK
IT WILL BE WELCOMED TEMPERATURES
BRIEFLY IN THE LOW 40S THIS
AFTERNOON.
BEFORE WE COOL THINGS DOWN
TONIGHT.
ONLY 35 TOMORROW AS JUST
MENTIONED WE'RE DRY HERE AS WE
BRING IN WINTER ON SATURDAY.
NO MAJOR WEEKEND ISSUES HERE.
AS WE START THE RUN UP TO
CHRISTMAS DAY.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
OFF TO ERIN FOR TRAFFIC.
>> 8:17 RIGHT NOW.
AND WE DO HAVE SOME BIG PROBLEMS
LINGERING AROUND THE DMV NEW
CRASH 270 NORTHBOUND RIGHT LANE
BLOCKED AFTER 85.
WE HAD EARLIER CRASH OUT BY 370
THAT WAS CLOSING ALL LANES
NORTHBOUND A TYPICAL DELAYS.
SOUTHBOUND SIDE AN HOUR SLOW
DOWN 70 TO THE BELTWAY.
GETTING REPORTS SOME OF THE BACK
ROADS AROUND THE DMV DEALING
WITH SLICK SPOTS.
MAKE SURE YOU TAKE IT SLOW USE
INDICATION OUT THERE.
66 EASTBOUND CONDITIONS
IMPROVING INSIDE THE BELTWAY IN
FALLS CHURCH.
PREVIOUSLY ALL LANES BLOCKED AND
TRAFFIC WAS BEING FORCED TO
DETOUR ON TO THE EXIT RAMP TO
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD THROUGH THE
CONSTRUCTION ZONE BACK ON TO 66.
NOW THAT BOTH LANES ARE OPEN,
I'M HOPING THESE MASSIVE DELAYS
BACK TO THE BELTWAY START TO
DISSIPATE.
DULLES TOLL ROAD FROM THE
BELTWAY JAMMED TO 66 AND ALL OF
OUR SECONDARIES 50, 29 ALL ARE
DEALING WITH A LOT OF TRAFFIC
INCLUDING A CRASH 50 WESTBOUND
TWO RIGHT LANES BLOCK AT GLEBE
ROAD.
HUGE DELAYS 395 NORTHBOUND
TOWARD THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL
AS WELL.
THAT'S WHAT WE GOT.
>> THANKS ERIN.
GIVING THE YOUNGSTERS SOME
QUALITY BONDING TIME INSTEAD OF
MATERIAL GIFTS HAILED AS A GOOD
THING FOR THEIR SOUL AND MIND.
THIS IS RESEARCH BOYETTE TISSUE
DOCTOR BUT THAT DOCTOR SAYS
VACATIONS ACTIVATE CERTAIN
SYSTEMS OF THE BRAIN AND CAN
MAKE THE KIDS SMARTER.
>> SO ACCORDING TO HER RESEARCH,
THE SEEKING SYSTEM IS ACTIVATED
WHEN YOUR CHILD EXPLORES A NEW
PLACE AND THEIR PLAY SYSTEM IS
USED WHENEVER THEY'RE HAVING
FUN.
THE MORE KIDS USE THESE SYSTEMS
THE MORE CLEVER AND INNOVATIVE
THEY CAN BECOME.
R ALSO SUGGESTS WHEN THEY GROW
UP THIS TRAN LATES INTO THE
ABILITY TO PLAY WITH IDEAS.
>> ALSO KEEP IN MIND THIS IS THE
EUROPEAN MODEL OF MANY, MANY
VACATIONS IN A YEAR THAT'S JUST
THE NORM.
>> RIGHT.
OVERSEAS.
>> LET'S BRING IN OUR FOX5
COLLEAGUES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK.
>> I THINK OBVIOUSLY EXPERIENCE
SHALL GIFTS ARE AMAZING AND TAKE
TIME AND EXPLORE WITH YOUR KIDS
SOMEWHERE ALLOWING THEM IS
WONDERFUL BUT I THINK IN THE
SEASON OF GIVING, UM, I THINK IT
IS FUN SOMETIMES TO GIVE THAT.
BUT ALSO ON CHRISTMAS MORNING,
IT'S JUST FUN TO ACTUALLY REALLY
OPEN A GIFT AND PLAY WITH A TOY.
JUST MY 2 CENTS.
>> LITTLE BIT OF BOTH HOLLY.
I AGREE WITH THAT AS A CHILD I
USED TO BEG TO GO TO DISNEYLAND
AND THEN YOU SEE THOSE GREAT
VIDEOS OF KIDS GETTING THEIR
RECORDED VIDEOS FINDING OUT
THEY'RE GOING TO DISNEYLAND TO
MEET MICKEY AND THEY SEEMED SO
EXCITED I THINK IT'S A BALANCE
OF TOYS AND VACATIONS.
MAYBE HEAD TO THE BEACH IN THE
SUMMER.
GET THEM THAT GREAT PRESENT TO
RIP OFF CHRISTMAS MORNING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK MIKE.
>> I'M A LITTLE BIASED THE WAY
MY FAMILY AND EVERYBODY HAS
ALWAYS DONE CHRISTMAS IS IT'S
NOT ABOUT WHERE YOU ARE IT'S
ABOUT WHO YOU'RE WITH.
IT'S ALWAYS ABOUT FAMILY AND
WE'VE ALWAYS JUST KIND OF KEPT
IT QUIET.
KEPT IT AT HOME AND DONE THE
FAMILY THING.
YES, WE DO THE GIFT EXCHANGES
AND THAT'S ALL BEEN GREAT, BUT
TO ME EVEN IF YOU'RE TRAVELING
AS LONG AS YOU'RE WITH FRIENDS
AND FAMILY, THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS REALLY
FOR THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
NOT THAT GIFTS ARE NECESSARY BUT
I DON'T THINK THAT CHRISTMAS AND
VACATIONS TO ME HAVE NEVER KIND
OF LINKED UP IN TERMS OF GETTING
AWAY FROM HOME.
>> FULL DISCLOSURE WE WOULD HAVE
GIFTS UNDER THE TREE MY MOM
WOULD WRAP EACH SOCK SEPARATELY
SO THOSE ARE THE KIND OF THINGS
YOU WOULD OPEN UNDER THE TREE.
IT WAS THE EXPERIENCES THAT
OBVIOUSLY WE TREASURED MORE
LOOKING BACK ON IT ESPECIALLY.
>> RIGHT.
OH YEAH.
I THINK THAT MIKE I'M GOING TO
AGREE WITH YOU JUST BEING
TOGETHER AND DOING THE WHOLE
CHRISTMAS SCENE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, LOOK, I ALSO
THINK THAT GOING PLACES IS FUN,
TOO.
I JUST FEEL LIKE FOR CHRISTMAS,
YOU KNOW --
>> KIND OF DISTRACTING, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
>> RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE SOMEONE YOU'RE NOT TO
BEING YOU'RE FOCUSED ON THAT
INSTEAD OF THE HOLIDAY.
>> HERE'S MY QUESTION.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU SHOULD
GO ON A VACATION INSTEAD OF GIVE
GIFTS FOR CHRISTMAS.
>> RIGHT.
>> OR GIVE A VACATION AS A GIFT?
>> NO, THEY'RE SAYING.
>> I BELIEVE THE RESEARCHERS SAY
LIKE WHAT'S MORE IMPACTFUL IS,
YOU KNOW, GOING ON AN EXPERIENCE
VERSUS A MATERIAL ITEM.
>> OH, I THINK SOMETIMES YOU CAN
DO A LITTLE BIT OF BOTH.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT HOLLY.
>> IN THE END IT DEPENDS WHO
YOU'RE WITH.
>> IF SOMEONE WAS TO GIVE ME A
CRUISE FOR CHRISTMAS I'M ALL FOR
IT.
>> THAT IS NICE.
>> GIFTING LIKE WHAT YOU SAID
ERIN A TRIP TO DISNEYLAND OR
WHATEVER THAT'S ALWAYS FUN.
YOU KNOW WHAT WHAT I REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT WHEN I HEARD THE
STUDY AND HOW IT SORT OF LIKE
OPENS AND AWAKEN THE DIFFER
NEURONS IS FOR ALL THE KIDS WHO
ARE -- DON'T EVER GET TO GO
ANYWHERE ON VACATION FUN OR A
LEARNING THING AND SORT OF STAY
ON THEIR BLOCK.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> OH YEAH.
>> IT SPEAKS TO THE OPPOSITE
BEING TRUE AS WELL.
>> IT ALSO SPEAKS TO MAYBE JUST
GETTING OUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO FAR.
>> NO.
>> TO EXPLORE.
I MEAN LOOK AT WHERE WE LIVE IN
D.C.
I MEAN YOU CAN EXPLORE MUSEUMS
FOR FREE.
>> OH YEAH.
>> TAKE IT ADVANTAGE OF WHERE
YOU ARE AND OPEN YOUR MIND.
>> RIGHT.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
I WASN'T ON AIRPLANE UNTIL I WAS
18 I DIDN'T GET TO TRAVEL AT ALL
AS A KID.
I CAN RELATE TO THAT.
>> THANKS, GUYS, FOR WEIGHING IN
AND HOWEVER YOU CELEBRATE, JUST
HOPEFULLY YOU GET SOMEBODY YOU
LOVE TO DO IT WITH.
WE'LL SEE YOU GUYS A LITTLE BIT
LATER.
>>> 8:22 RIGHT NOW.
STILL AHEAD THE LAST MINUTE
HOLIDAY SHIPPING DEADLINES YOU
NEED TO BE AWARE OF THIS WEEK AS
WE INCH EVER SO CLOSER TO
CHRISTMAS MORNING TO HANUKKAH,
TO KWANZA.
ALTHOUGH WITH KWANZAA YOU HAVE A
COUPLE OF DAYS.
I DIGRESS.
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
♪
>>> ALWAYS MY REQUEST FOR OUR
STELLAR AUDIO.
>> GET YOU GOING ON A WEDNESDAY.
>> YEAH.
I LOVE THAT.
>> GOT ME FEELING BRAND NEW.
GOOD MORNING.
>> LOVE THE SUNSHINE OVER THE
OWING.
BEAUTIFUL LOOK AT OCEAN CITY,
MARYLAND.
FISHING PIER THIS MORNING.
LOOKS GOOD.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HOW COLD THE
WATER IS, MIKE, BUT IT LOOKS
NICE OUT THERE.
>> IT LOOKS TROPICAL.
YEAH.
I MEAN CULL ON IT'S MAKING ME
THINK OF SUMMERTIME.
>> RIGHT.
>> ONLY SIX MONTHS AWAY.
>> IT WILL BE HERE BEFORE YOU
KNOW IT.
>> WE HAVEN'T OFFICIALLY HIT
WINTER YET.
>> DAY CLOSER THAN YESTERDAY.
>> THAT IS TRUE.
ONE DAY AT A TIME, STEVE.
LET'S GET TO YOU YOUR WEATHER
FORECAST OUT THERE THIS MORNING.
>> LOOK HOW GOOD WE LOOK WITH
THE FLOWERS IN THE BACKGROUND.
>> CHRISTMAS RED.
YES, IT'S GORGEOUS.
FEELS LIKE CHRISTMAS OUT.
TEMPERATURES COLD.
32 REAGAN.
DULLES 28.
31 FOR BWI.
GOOD NEWS, SATELLITE/RADAR NICE
AND QUIET.
IT'S GOING TO STAY THAT WAY
THROUGH MOST OF THE AFTERNOON.
CHECK OUT YOUR PLANNER.
SUNSHINE IS BACK, YES, COLD
TEMPERATURES WILL BE STICKING
AROUND.
GRAB THE JACKET IF YOU'RE
HEADING OUT AND ABOUT.
BUT AGAIN NO NEED FOR THE
UMBRELL TODAY.
ERIN?
>> ALL RIGHT.
8:26 RIGHT NOW.
270 NORTHBOUND RIGHT LANE
BLOCKED AT 85 WITH A CRASH.
66 EASTBOUND FALLS CHURCH BIG
DELAYS LINGERING AFTER EARLIER
CRASH BY WASHINGTON BOULEVARD
CLEARED.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD 8:30, WHY
PIZZA HUT IS ON DAMAGE CONTROL
OVER WHAT SOME WORKERS ALLEGEDLY
TOLD A GROUP OF SPECIAL NEEDS
STUDENTS.
>> ALSO THE TEENAGER WHO
APPEARED TO BE KIDNAPPED IN THIS
VIDEO NOW SAYS SHE MADE THE
WHOLE THING UP.
STAY WITH US.
MORE DETAILS COMING UP AT 8:30.
SEE YOU IN A MINUTE.
♪
I'm Jimmy Dean and thank you
very much for lettin'
us become just a little
part of your holiday.
And we sincerely hope
that Jimmy Dean sausage
might make your holiday just
a little bit brighter.
Happy Holiday to ya.
♪
>>> COMING UP ON 8:30.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
USE THE #GOODDAYDC.
WHERE ARE YOU?  HAVE YOU FINISH
YOUR HOLIDAY SHOPPING?  YOU
FEELING PANICKED.
ARE YOU CHILLED OUT FOR THIS
HOLIDAY.
TALK TO US USE THE GOOD DAY D.C.
HASH TAG.
WE'LL SHARE YOUR COMMENT ON THE
AIR.
>> LET'S GET TO NEWS UP IN NEW
YORK CITY.
POLICE INVESTIGATING WHAT
APPEARS TO BE A STAGED
KIDNAPPING AFTER A 16-YEAR-OLD
GIRL AT THE CENTER OF THE
INVESTIGATION HAS ALLEGEDLY
ADMITTED TO STAGING THE WHOLE
THING.
HOLLY JOINS US ONCE AGAIN.
HOLLY IS LIVE IN THE NEWSROOM
NOW WITH THOSE DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
THIS HAS BEEN EVER DEVELOPING
STORY FOR SURE.
LATE MONDAY NIGHT 16-YEAR-OLD
CAROL SANCHEZ WAS WALKING WITH
HER MOM IN THE BRONX WHEN A FOUR
DOOR BEIGE SEDAN PULLED UP THE
ENTIRE INCIDENT WAS CAPTURED ON
CAMERA.
YOU CAN SEE AT LEAST TWO MEN
GRAB SANCHEZ AND PUSH AWAY HER
MOM.
THE MEN THEN DRAGGED THE TEEN
INTO THE CAR AND SPED OFF.
THE ENCOUNTER PROMPTED AN AMBER
ALERT FOR SANCHEZ.
THEN YESTERDAY ANOTHER EMOTIONAL
MOMENT.
THIS IS AN EXCLUSIVE VIDEO BY
OUR SISTER STATION THERE IN NEW
YORK.
THE 16-YEAR-OLD IS SEEN WALKING
UP TO POLICE OFFICERS AND SHE
ASKS FOR HELP.
SHE APPROACHED THE OFFICERS IN
THE SAME AREA WHERE THE ALLEGED
KIDNAPPING OCCURRED.
SANCHEZ WAS EVENTUALLY REUNITED.
YOU CAN SEE THERE WITH HER
FAMILY.
BUT THEN THE INVESTIGATION TOOK
A MAJOR TURN.
SANCHEZ SINCE ADMITTED TO
STAGING THE ENTIRE INCIDENT.
SOURCES SAY THE TEEN NEW AT
LEAST ONE OF THE PEOPLE INVOLVED
AND THAT HER BOYFRIEND MAY HAVE
ALSO BEEN IN ON THE WHOLE THING.
AS FOR WHY, OFFICIALS SAY IT MAY
HAVE BEEN OVER HER MOTHER'S
DESIRE TO MOVE THE FAMILY TO
THEIR NATIVE HONDURAS.
SO IT IS UNCLEAR IF THE MEN THAT
WERE SEEN IN THE SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO WILL FACE ANY CHARGES, OF
COURSE, UPDATES WILL STILL COME.
ALLISON.
>> SURELY THEY WILL.
HOLLY, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> 8:31 RIGHT NOW.
>>> FBI AND TEXAS RANGERS HAVE
JOINED THE SEARCH FOR MISSING
MOTHER AND A THREE WEEK OLD
BABY.
IT'S BEEN NEARLY A WEEK SINCE
HEIDI BRUSARD AND HER BABY
MARGOT LAST SCENE LAST THURSDAY
MORNING THE 33-YEAR-OLD DROPPED
HER SON OFF AT SCHOOL AND
THOUGHT TO HAVE GONE HOME
AFTERWARDS BUT WHAT HAPPENED
NEXT IS STILL A MYSTERY.
FOUR HER FIANCE' GOT BACK FROM
HER WORK AND FOUND ALL HER
BELONGINGS STILL THERE INCLUDING
HER VEHICLE.
>> DISTURBING STORY OUT OF
CALIFORNIA AS WELL.
NOW A GROOM WHO WAS KILLED AT
HIS OWN WEDDING RECEPTION THIS
HAPPENED OVER THE WEEKEND THE LA
TIMES REPORTS THAT JUST HOURS
AFTER 30-YEAR-OLD JOE, TIED THE
KNOT TWO MEN CRASHED THE
RECEPTION AND ATTACKED HIM WITH
BASEBALL BATS.
POLICE SAY HE WAS BEATEN TO
DEATH FOLLOWING A FIGHT AT THE
HOME WHERE THE WEDDING RECEPTION
WAS TAKING PLACE.
THE TWO MEN WERE BOTH ARRESTED
THEY ARE BEING HELD WITHOUT
BAIL.
POLICE SAY HE WAS TRYING TO
PROTECT HIS GUESTS FROM THE
WEDDING CRASH SCHERS.
>> THERE'S A MAN INSIDE WHO'S
NOT RESPONSIVE, AND IT'S A
POLICE OFFICER.
>> IT'S A POLICE OFFICER?
>> 911 CALLERS MADE IT CLEAR ONE
POLICE OFFICER IN COLORADO WAS
NOT WAKING UP WHEN HE PARKED IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE STREET.
BODY CAM FOOTAGE SHOWS
FIREFIGHTERS HAD TO BREAK A CAR
WINDOW JUST TO GET TO HIM.
THE OFFICER NATHAN MEYER WAS
INTOXICATED.
REPORTEDLY SO INN TOCK INDICATED
HE HAD NO IDEA HIS FELLOW
OFFICERS HAD TO REMOVE HIS
JACKET AND HIS SERVICE WEAPON.
THE DEPUTY CHIEF LATER ADMITTED
SMELLING ALCOHOL ON MEYER BUT
NEVER HAD OFFICERS SEEK A SEARCH
WARRANT TO DO A BLOOD DRAW.
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY IS NOW
REVIEWING THE CASE.
SO FAR NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED.
>>> PIZZA HUT ON DAMAGE CONTROL
AFTER ONE OF ITS EMPLOYEES
ALLEGEDLY TOLD A GROUP OF
STUDENTS WITH SPECIAL NEEDS TO
HURRY UP TO MAKE WAY FOR QUOTE
REGULAR CUSTOMERS.
TEACHER WHO WAS WITH THAT GROUP
IN TENNESSEE SAID EMPLOYEES KEPT
RUSHING THEM BECAUSE OTHER
CUSTOMERSWERE COMING IN.
SEVERAL PARENTS AND COMMUNITY
MEMBERS HAVE SUBMITTED FORMAL
COMPLAINTS NOW TO PIZZA HUT.
COMPANY OFFICIALS SAY THEY DID
APOLOGIZE AND THEY'LL BE MEETING
WITH THE GROUP LATER THIS WEEK.
♪
>>> CHRISTMAS, HANUKKAH, KWANZAA
ALL JUST A FEW DAYS AWAY NOW.
IF YOU WANT YOUR HOLIDAY GIFTS
TO ARRIVE ON TIME, THE CLOCK
IT'S TICKING.
HERE'S WHAT UPS, POTTY AL
SERVICE, FED EX AND OTHER MAJOR
CARRIERS ALL HAVE STRICT CUT OFF
DAYS FOR DELIVERING PACKAGES
DURING THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
BUT HERE'S GOOD NEWS.
THERE IS STILL TIME TO MAIL
THOUGH THOSE LAST MINUTE
PACKAGES.
>> IF YOU HAVEN'T SHIPPED YOUR
HOLIDAY GIFTS YET, YOU MAY WANT
TO GET MOVING.
IN ORDER FOR YOUR CHRISTMAS
PRESENTS TO ARRIVE ON TIME,
THERE ARE A FEW DEADLINES YOU
HAVE TO PAY ATTENTION TO.
>> WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING FOR THE
PERFECT GIFT AND THEN YOU FIND
IT, BUT IT'S LAST MINUTE AND
THEN YOU HAVE TO PAY FOR THAT
EXTRA SHIPPING JUST TO GET IT
THERE IN TIME.
>> HERE'S SOME OF THE DATES YOU
NEED TO KNOW.
FOR UPS THURSDAY IS THE LAST DAY
FOR THREE DAY SELECT SHIPPING
WHILE FRIDAY IS THE CUT OFF FOR
TWO DAY SHIPPING.
FRIDAY IS ALSO THE DEADLINE FOR
FIRST CLASS MALE WITH U.S. PS
AND WITH FED EX YOU HAVE UNTIL
MONDAY TO CHOOSE THE OVERNIGHT
SHIPPING OPTION.
LOOKING TO SAVE MONEY THIS
SEASON?  SHOPPING EXPERTS
RECOMMEND HITTING THE MALL TO
AVOID EXTRA SHIPPING COSTS.
>> TRY TO GO IN STORE AND GET
THE REST OF YOUR SHOPPING DONE
THERE IF POSSIBLE.
>> AND IF YOU PLAN ON FLYING
WITH YOUR GIFTS MAKE SURE THEY
AREN'T COVERED IN WRAPPING
PAPER.
TSA AGENTS SAY THE BETTER THEY
CAN SEE YOUR ITEMS THE FASTER
YOU'LL GET THROUGH SECURITY
LINES.
>> IF WE ALREADY CAN SEE WHAT IT
IS, THAT WOULD MAKE IT JUST A
BREEZE FOR YOURSELF AND FOR US
HERE AT THE TSA SCREENING AREA.
>> POST OLD AVENUES ESTIMATES IT
WILL DELIVER AN AVERAGE OF
20.5 MILLION PACKAGES PER DAY
THROUGH THE REST OF THE YEAR.
>> YEAH.
>> HARD TO WRAP YOUR HEAD AROUND
NUMBERS LIKE THAT.
THE NUMBERS WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE
ON OUTSIDE INVOLVE THE
TEMPERATURE IT'S CHILLY, MIKE.
>> IT IS CHILLY.
LIVE LOOK IN GAITHERSBURG THAT
LOVE CHRISTMAS TREE OUTSIDE
FOLKS GETTING INTO THE CHRISTMAS
AND HOLIDAY SPEAR OR KWANZAA OR
HAHANUKKAH WHATEVER YOUR HOLIDAY
HAPPENS TO BE.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS FROM US HERE AT
FOX5.
THE NUMBERS THAT WE WILL SEE
STARTING TO PLUMMET ON US ARE
THESE ONES.
WIND CHILL OR REAL FEEL WHAT IT
ACTUALLY FEELS LIKE OUTSIDE.
STILL FEELING JUST FINE BECAUSE
WINDS AREN'T BLOWING THAT BAD IN
D.C. AT 32.
MARTINSBURG THOUGH FEELS LIKE 20
AS DOES CUMBERLAND, 22 FOR
WINCHESTER AND LATER ON THIS
EVENING, TEENS AND MAYBE EVEN BY
TOMORROW MORNING SOME SINGLE
DIGIT REAL FEEL NUMBERS COMING
YOUR WAY.
DO EXPECT A COLD NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS HERE IN THE D.C. REGION.
SNOW SHOWERS GOING ACROSS THE
GREAT LAKES.
ONE OR TWO OF THOSE MAY SNEAK
INTO OUR NORTHWEST SUBURBS.
COVERS AL SNOW FLURRY NOTHING
THAT WOULD CAUSE ANY PROBLEMS.
SORRY KIDS YOU'RE GOING TO
SCHOOL THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO SCHOOL NICE
AND COLD.
BECAUSE 42 WE MAY BRIEFLY TOUCH
THAT THIS AFTERNOON.
MOST OF THE DAYTIME HOURS TODAY
WILL BE SPENT IN THE 30S.
DO BUNDLE UP IF YOU'RE HEADING
OUT AND ABOUT FOR YOUR DAY ON
THURSDAY, LOTS OF SUNSHINE
DECEPTIVE SUNSHINE THOUGHPTIVE H
PEAK HERE IN TOWN IN THE LOWER
30S MANY WILL STAY BELOW
FREEZING ALL DAY LONG.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S YOUR FORECAST.
ERIN HOW DO THE ROADS LOOK THIS
MORNING.
>> 8:36 A ROUGH RIDE OUT THERE.
270 NORTHBOUND THE RIGHT LANE IS
STILL BLOCKED AFTER 85.
A TYPICAL NORTHBOUND SOUTHBOUND
TOWARDS 70.
AN HOUR DELAY TOWARD THE
BELTWAY.
EARLIER CRASH CLEARED AT
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD ON 66
EASTBOUND, INSIDE THE BELTWAY
HEAVY DELAYS.
THOSE DELAYS EXTEND FROM THE
BELWAY TOWARD THE KEY BRIDGE.
WE ALSO HAVE VERY HEAVY VOLUME
ON THE BELTWAY ON THAT INNER
LOOP SIDE OF THINGS TOWARD THE
LEGION BRIDGE.
AND THEN WE'RE ALSO SEEING
DELAYS ON 267 AND GW PARKWAY.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON YOUR COMMUTE
IN JUST A FEW.
BACK TO YOU STEVE AND ALLISON.
>> USE SOCIAL MEDIA A LOT DURING
THE HOLIDAYS?  IF YOU DO YOU'RE
NOT ALONE.
THOSE DETAILS COMING UP NEXT.
>> PLUS IS 2019 THE YEAR OF
SPAM?  NOT JUST OF JUNK MALE BUT
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THIS SPAM.
THE CANNED PROCESSED MEAT
CLASSIC.
REACTION FROM SOME OF OUR FOX5
COLLEAGUES TRYING IT FOR THE
VERY FIRST TIME.
♪
♪♪
>> AFTER 72 YEARS.
♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Tuition goes up each
year ♪
♪ 5% so I hear ♪
♪ I really can't do math ♪
♪ But that's a lot,
I fear ♪
♪ And room and board ♪
(laughs)
- [Narrator] Invest529
gift cards make great gifts.
Learn more at
Invest529.com
- Ooh! (blows air)
I love that song.
(laughs)
Mmm, it tastes blue!
>>> 8:40.
2019 COMES TO AN END SHOULD WE
DUB IT AS THE YEAR OF SPAM?
>> HERE'S WHY.
>> NOT THE MAIL.
>> TURNS OUT SPAM LIKE THE HAM
THE SALES OF SPAM SKY ROCKED
THIS YEAR.
SPAM HAD ITS FIFTH CONSECUTIVE
YEAR OF RECORD SALES.
THIS DESPITE THE FACT THAT THESE
DAYS CONSUMERS ARE BUYING LESS
PROCESSED FOOD.
IN SEPTEMBER, HORMEL WHO MAKES
SPAM LAUNCHED LIMITED EDITION OF
PUMPKIN SPICED SPAM.
IT WAS AVAILABLE ONLINE SOLD OUT
IN LESS THAN SEVEN HOURS I DID
SEE IT IN THE STORE.
WHY, BECAUSE MY CHILD LIKES
SPAM.
WEIRD.
BUT ANY WAY,.
>> NOT WEIRD.
>> LAST NIGHT'S LIKE IT OR NOT,
THE CREW HAD A SPAM TASTE TEST
WITH SOME TRYING IT FOR THE
FIRST TIME EVER.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> REALLY?
>> IT'S VERY GOOD.
>> TASTES LIKE TOENAILS.
>> TOENAILS?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT IS A LIE.
>> IT CERTAINLY DOESN'T.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WANT TO TRY IT.
>> IT CERTAINLY DOESN'T.
I'VE NEVER HAD IT.
>> I WANT TO TRY IT.
>> IT'S VERY SALTY BUT IT'S NOT
I'VE NEVER HAD IT.
BAD.
>> IT'S VERY SALTY BUT IT'S NOT
IT'S REALLY NOT BAD.
BAD.
>> WHY DO PEOPLE HATE ON IT.
IT'S REALLY NOT BAD.
>> IT'S ALSO GOOD.
>> WHY DO PEOPLE HATE ON IT.
YOU HAVE A SPAM SANDWICH.
>> IT'S ALSO GOOD.
>> IT TAKES LIKE TOENAILS BUT
YOU HAVE A SPAM SANDWICH.
IKE IS GOING IN FOR SECONDS.
>> IT TAKES LIKE TOENAILS BUT
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M PROUD OF
IKE IS GOING IN FOR SECONDS.
THIS OR NOT BUT I DID EAT A FAIR
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M PROUD OF
AMOUNT OF IT GROWING UP TO ME
THIS OR NOT BUT I DID EAT A FAIR
IT'S NOT LOST ON ME I FEEL LIKE
AMOUNT OF IT GROWING UP TO ME
IT'S TOFU IT TAKES ON WHATEVER
IT'S NOT LOST ON ME I FEEL LIKE
YOU COOK IT WITH.
IT'S TOFU IT TAKES ON WHATEVER
LIKE THOSE FLAVORS.
YOU COOK IT WITH.
SWEET AND SOUR, COOK IT UP IN
LIKE THOSE FLAVORS.
THAT YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
SWEET AND SOUR, COOK IT UP IN
>> I DO HATE THAT PEOPLE HATE ON
THAT YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
SPAM.
>> I DO HATE THAT PEOPLE HATE ON
>> YEAH.
SPAM.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> I DO ALSO -- YOU KNOW HOW
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THEY SAY THEY EAT IN IT HAWAII A
>> I DO ALSO -- YOU KNOW HOW
LOT.
THEY SAY THEY EAT IN IT HAWAII A
WHEN I WENT TO HAWAII THEY
LOT.
ACTUALLY HAD IT THERE.
WHEN I WENT TO HAWAII THEY
I CANNOT GET TUCKER TO TRY IT.
ACTUALLY HAD IT THERE.
>> FUN FACT MY BEST FRIEND WHO
I CANNOT GET TUCKER TO TRY IT.
NOW LIVES IN HAWAII BUT WE WERE
>> FUN FACT MY BEST FRIEND WHO
COLLEGE ROOMMATES ALL FOUR YEARS
NOW LIVES IN HAWAII BUT WE WERE
IT WAS A STAPLE IN OUR DORM R
COLLEGE ROOMMATES ALL FOUR YEARS
ROOM.
IT WAS A STAPLE IN OUR DORM R
SHE LOVED SOME SPAM.
ROOM.
>> SHE'S IN THE RIGHT PLACE
SHE LOVED SOME SPAM.
THEN.
>> SHE'S IN THE RIGHT PLACE
>> SHE'S IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
THEN.
>> IT COMES FULL CIRCLE.
>> SHE'S IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
>> STAR WARS WEEK CONTINUES.
>> IT COMES FULL CIRCLE.
KEV SITS DOWN WITH DIRECTOR JJ
>> STAR WARS WEEK CONTINUES.
ABRAMS AND STAR WARS STAR OSCAR
KEV SITS DOWN WITH DIRECTOR JJ
ISAAC.
ABRAMS AND STAR WARS STAR OSCAR
>> DID HE PLAY BABY YODA?  LIVE
ISAAC.
LOOK OUTSIDE AS HE TAKE YOU TO
>> DID HE PLAY BABY YODA?  LIVE
THE BREAK.
LOOK OUTSIDE AS HE TAKE YOU TO
A COLD WEDNESDAY AHEAD.
THE BREAK.
I KNOW HE DOESN'T PLAY BABY
A COLD WEDNESDAY AHEAD.
YODA.
I KNOW HE DOESN'T PLAY BABY
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC ON THE 5'S
YODA.
NEXT.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC ON THE 5'S
>> BABY YODA TAKING OVER THE
NEXT.
SERIES, THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> BABY YODA TAKING OVER THE
>> OKAY.
SERIES, THOUGH, RIGHT?
♪