COUNTY HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT.
CHARGING DOCUMENTS SHOWING HOW
THE SUSPECT AND VICTIM WERE
COMMUNICATING WITH EACH OTHER
ON A VERY POPULAR SOCIAL MEDIA
PLATFORM JUST MINUTES BEFORE
THAT SHOOTING.
>> IKE EJIOCHI IS LIVE IN
CHARLES COUNTY.
THE TWO WERE SNAPCHATTING EACH
OTHER.
SO WHAT DID POLICE SAY ABOUT
IT?
>> Reporter: YEAH, THAT'S
EXACTLY WHAT THOSE CHARGING
DOCUMENTS SAY.
THEY CLAIM THAT THE VICTIM
17-YEAR-OLD BRADLEY BROWN WAS
ACTUALLY SELLING AND
ADVERTISING THC VAPE PRODUCT
ON SNAPCHAT.
NOW THOSE DOCUMENTS GO ON TO
SAY THAT THE SUSPECT,
17-YEAR-OLD DARRYL FREEMAN WAS
TEXTING AND COMMUNICATING WITH
BROWN ALL THE WAY UP UNTIL THE
SHOOTING.
NOW THE POLICE GO ON TO SAY
THAT AFTER THE SHOOTING BROWN
NOT ONLY TRIED TO BLOCK -- I'M
SORRY, FREEMAN NOT ONLY TRIED
TO BLOCK BROWN ON NAP CHAT BUT
HE WENT ON AND EVEN CHANGED
HIS USER NAME IN AN ATTEMPT TO
TRY TO EVADE POLICE
PRESUMABLY.
>> IKE EJIOCHI LIVE FOR US.
THTHANK YOU, IKE.
>> ♪
>> Reporter: I APOLOGIZE.
>> WELL, WE WANT TO CHECK IN
WITH CAITLIN ROTH NOW AND GET
A LOOK AT OUR WEATHER.
I KNOW WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
IT EARLIER, IT WAS QUITE THE
GEAR SHIFT WHEN WE TALK ABOUT
THE TEMPERATURES.
>> IT WAS A DROP BUT IT WASN'T
AS COLD AS I WAS EXPECTING.
THIS IS THE COLDEST DAY WE'VE
HAD IN AWHILE.
>> AND CLOUD COVER.
>> KEEP ON GOING.
>> YOU BRACED US FOR THE WORST
'CAUSE YOU SAID IT WILL BE THE
COLDEST MORNING YOU FELT IN A
LONG TIME AND IT JUST DIDN'T
FEEL THAT COLD.
>> I THINK TOMORROW MORNING
WILL FEEL A LITTLE BIT COLDER
AND YOU'RE RIGHT THE CLOUD
COVER --
>> LOOK.
LOOK AT THE NUMBERS BEHIND
YOU.
THAT'S COLD TO ME.
IT'S CHILLY.
>> IT DEFINITELY IS.
TOMORROW WILL FEEL A LITTLE
BIT COLDER BUT YEAH IT'S GOING
TO BE COLD BUT IT WON'T LAST
LONG.
INTO THE WEEKEND MUCH BETTER.
TEMPERATURES IN THE 30'S TO
AROUND 40 DEGREES, 40 IN D.C.
RIGHT NOW, 38 MANASSAS, 36
WINCHESTER AND 38 IN
CUMBERLAND A BIT OF A
DIFFERENCE COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY.
24 HOUR TEMPERATURE CHANGE ON
THE ORDER OF 10 TO 15 DEGREES
COLDER.
13 DEGREES COLDER THAN WHERE
WE WERE AT THIS TIME YESTERDAY
IN D.C. SO BACK TO NORMAL OR
ACTUALLY BELOW NORMAL FOR THIS
TIME OF YEAR, WHICH IS
SOMETHING WE HAVEN'T DONE MUCH
HERE IN FEBRUARY.
STORM TRACKER RADAR ALL QUIET
AROUND THE METRO BUT NOTICE
SOME SNOW SHOWERS WELL TO OUR
SOUTH MAINLY FROM THE RICHMOND
AREA THROUGH EXTREME SOUTHERN
MARYLAND TO THE LOWER EASTERN
SHORE.
THEY'RE GETTING FLURRIES AND
SNOW SHOWERS DOWN INTO NORTH
CAROLINA.
IN LEONARDTOWN YOU'RE SEEING
SOME OF THESE MIXED SPRINKLES
AND FLURRIES, THAT'S PROBABLY
IT.
SAINT MARY'S COUNTY THE
SOUTHERN PART AT LEAST ON
RADAR SHOWING UP WITH SOME
SHOWERS AND THEN FURTHER SOUTH
INTO THE NORTHERN NECK MAYBE A
FEW FLURRIES TOO.
THAT'S THE BEST CHANCE OF
WHERE WE'LL SEE SPRINKLES AND
FLURRIES THROUGH THE EVENING
HOURS.
WATCH FUTURECAST.
HAS A GOOD HANDLE ON MOST OF
THE ACTIVITY SUPPRESSED TO OUR
SOUTH AND THAT'S WHERE IT'S
GOING TO STAY THROUGH THE
EVENING HOURS.
SEE, I PAUSE AT 9 O'CLOCK,
SOME FLURRIES OUT HERE BY 81.
THERE'S ACTUALLY A TINY PIECE
OF ENERGY UP INTO
PENNSYLVANIA.
THAT WILL DROP FROM NORTH TO
SOUTH IT'S INDEPENDENT OF THIS
AND THAT COULD BRING FLURRIES
TO OUR AREA ESPECIALLY WESTERN
SUBURBS.
BY TEAM MORNING IT'S BRIGHT
SUNSHINE.
HERE'S YOUR FORECAST FOR YOUR
FRIDAY.
MADE IT TO THE END OF THE WEEK
AND IT'S GOING TO BE A CHILLY
ONE.
A BRIGHT AND SUNNY ONE,
THOUGH, DEFINITELY COLDER
TOMORROW MORNING STARTING OUT
IN THE 20'S.
WIND CHILLS WILL BE IN THE
TEENS SO TOMORROW WILL REALLY
BE THE CRUX OF THE COLD AIR
AND THAT'S WHEN IT'S GOING TO
FEEL THE MOST DRAMATICALLY
CHILLY.
WE'LL SLOWLY WARM INTO THE
30'S BY NOON, 38 FOR THAT HIGH
TEMPERATURE TO ROUND OUT YOUR
FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
THERE IS GOING TO BE A BIT OF
A WARMUP OVER THE WEEKEND.
I'LL SHOW YOU THAT FULL
WEEKEND FORECAST COMING UP
STILL AHEAD.
ANGIE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH CAITLIN.
>>> DAMASCUS HIGH SCHOOL HIRED
A FEW FOOTBALL COACH.
COACH JOSH CLOTS.
COACH CLOTS SPENT EIGHT YEARS
AS RICHARD MONTGOMERY'S HEAD
COACH.
>> SALISBURY UNIVERSITY IN
MARYLAND WAS CLOSED TODAY
AFTER TWO RACIST RANTS WERE
DISCOVERED ON CAMPUS.
ONE WAS WRITTEN IN A STAIRWELL
OF THE SCIENCE BUILDING AND
CALLED FOR VIOLENCE TOWARDS
MINORITIES.
THE FBI IS NOW INVOLVED AND
THE UNIVERSITY IS GETTING
SUPPORT FROM THE MAYOR OF
SALISBURY WHO HAD THESE WORDS
FOR WHOEVER IS RESPONSIBLE.
>> RACISTS, YOU HAVE NO HOME
HERE IN OUR COMMUNITY.
GET OUT.
HATE, YOU HAVE NO HOME HERE.
MISOGYNY, BIGOTRY, GET OUT.
GET OUT.
WHEN YOU'RE ON THE CORRECT
MISOGYNY, BIGOTRY, GET OUT.
SIDE OF HUMANITY YOU DON'T
WHEN YOU'RE ON THE CORRECT
NEED TO SHRINK AROUND IN
SIDE OF HUMANITY YOU DON'T
STAIRWELLS TOO AFRAID OF BEING
NEED TO SHRINK AROUND IN
ACCOUNTABLE FOR OPINIONS THAT
STAIRWELLS TOO AFRAID OF BEING
YOU CAN'T OWN PUBLICLY.
ACCOUNTABLE FOR OPINIONS THAT
>> STUDENTS REPORT THIS IS THE
YOU CAN'T OWN PUBLICLY.
THIRD TIME IN THE LAST SIX
>> STUDENTS REPORT THIS IS THE
MONTHS RACIST GRAFFITI HAS
THIRD TIME IN THE LAST SIX
BEEN FOUND ON CAMPUS.
MONTHS RACIST GRAFFITI HAS
>> IT IS DAY THREE OF
BEEN FOUND ON CAMPUS.
DELIBERATIONS FOR JURORS IN
>> IT IS DAY THREE OF
THE HARVEY WEINSTEIN RAPE
DELIBERATIONS FOR JURORS IN
CASE.
THE HARVEY WEINSTEIN RAPE
SO FAR THEY'VE ASKED THE COURT
CASE.
FOR LEGAL CLARIFICATIONS TON AND
SO FAR THEY'VE ASKED THE COURT
TO REPEAT TESTIMONY FROM KEY
FOR LEGAL CLARIFICATIONS TON AND
WITNESSES.
TO REPEAT TESTIMONY FROM KEY
WEINSTEIN IS CHARGED WITH FIVE
WITNESSES.
COUNTS STEMMING FROM
WEINSTEIN IS CHARGED WITH FIVE
ALLEGATIONS F.
COUNTS STEMMING FROM
>> SOME ENCOURAGING NEWS.
ALLEGATIONS F.
THE NUMBERS ARE STILL
>> SOME ENCOURAGING NEWS.
INTIMIDATING WITH MORE THAN
THE NUMBERS ARE STILL
2100 DEATHS, 75,000 CASES
INTIMIDATING WITH MORE THAN
REPORTED WORLDWIDE.
2100 DEATHS, 75,000 CASES
THE SILVER LINING IS THE
REPORTED WORLDWIDE.
NUMBER OF NEW CASES IN CHINA
THE SILVER LINING IS THE
IS DECLINING.
NUMBER OF NEW CASES IN CHINA
ONE TROUBLING DEVELOPMENT TWO
IS DECLINING.
PEOPLE ABOARD THAT CRUISE SHIP
ONE TROUBLING DEVELOPMENT TWO
IN JAPAN HAVE DIED AFTER
PEOPLE ABOARD THAT CRUISE SHIP
LEAVING THE QUARANTINE.
IN JAPAN HAVE DIED AFTER
AUTHORITIES SAY THOSE VICTIMS
LEAVING THE QUARANTINE.
WERE ALREADY BATTLING SERIOUS
AUTHORITIES SAY THOSE VICTIMS
HEALTH ISSUES.
WERE ALREADY BATTLING SERIOUS
THERE ARE MORE THAN 600 CASES
HEALTH ISSUES.
LINKED TO THAT CRUISE SHIP.
THERE ARE MORE THAN 600 CASES
D.C. CHEF JOSÉ ANDRES IS
LINKED TO THAT CRUISE SHIP.
SERVING MEALS FOR SHIP
D.C. CHEF JOSÉ ANDRES IS
PASSENGERS.
SERVING MEALS FOR SHIP
HE SAYS MANY PEOPLE ARE NOW
PASSENGERS.
OFF THE SHIP AND THERE ARE
HE SAYS MANY PEOPLE ARE NOW
MUCH MORE STILL IN NEED OF
OFF THE SHIP AND THERE ARE
HELP INCLUDING THE CREW.
MUCH MORE STILL IN NEED OF
>> TOP CAUGHT ON CAMERA
HELP INCLUDING THE CREW.
MOMENTS.
>> TOP CAUGHT ON CAMERA
A PARAGLIDER GOT TIED UP AFTER
MOMENTS.
FLYING INTO POWER LINES.
A PARAGLIDER GOT TIED UP AFTER
CREWS IN CALIFORNIA RESCUED A
FLYING INTO POWER LINES.
MAN AFTER HE WAS STUCK THERE
CREWS IN CALIFORNIA RESCUED A
FOR HOURS.
MAN AFTER HE WAS STUCK THERE
THEY CUT THE POWER TO ENSURE
FOR HOURS.
EVERYONE'S SAFETY WHICH LEFT
THEY CUT THE POWER TO ENSURE
46,000 PEOPLE IN THE DARK
EVERYONE'S SAFETY WHICH LEFT
UNTIL THAT GLIDER WAS SAFELY
46,000 PEOPLE IN THE DARK
REMOVED.
UNTIL THAT GLIDER WAS SAFELY
THE PARAGLIDER GAVE EVERYONE A
REMOVED.
THUMBS UP AS HE WAS TAKEN TO
THE PARAGLIDER GAVE EVERYONE A
THE HOSPITAL TO BE EVALUATED
THUMBS UP AS HE WAS TAKEN TO
BUT TALK ABOUT A CLOSE CALL.
THE HOSPITAL TO BE EVALUATED
>> LOOK AT THIS.
BUT TALK ABOUT A CLOSE CALL.
TAKING KAYAKING TO NEW HEI
>> LOOK AT THIS.
HEIGHTS.
TAKING KAYAKING TO NEW HEI
WHOA.
HEIGHTS.
THAT'S A PROFESSIONAL KAYAKER,
WHOA.
NOT AN AMATEUR.
THAT'S A PROFESSIONAL KAYAKER,
PADDLING RIGHT OVER A
NOT AN AMATEUR.
WATERFALL IN CHILE.
PADDLING RIGHT OVER A
THE WATERFALL IS MORE THAN 130 .
WATERFALL IN CHILE.
THIS IS THE SECOND HIGHEST
THE WATERFALL IS MORE THAN 130 .
KAYAK JUMP REPORTED ON RECORD.
THIS IS THE SECOND HIGHEST
WHEW.
KAYAK JUMP REPORTED ON RECORD.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
WHEW.
>> I'M SURE THERE'S SOME SKILL
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
TO IT THAT YOU HAVE TO LIKE
>> I'M SURE THERE'S SOME SKILL
LEAN BACK.
TO IT THAT YOU HAVE TO LIKE
>> BLOWS MY MIND.
LEAN BACK.
CHECK THIS OUT OKAY.
>> BLOWS MY MIND.
A WILD ENCOUNTER CAUGHT ON
CHECK THIS OUT OKAY.
CAMERA.
A WILD ENCOUNTER CAUGHT ON
THIS OUT IN CALIFORNIA.
CAMERA.
LOOK AT THEM SIZING EACH OTHER
THIS OUT IN CALIFORNIA.
UP.
LOOK AT THEM SIZING EACH OTHER
TWO RATTLESNAKES ENTANGLED IN
UP.
A FIGHT FOR THE RIGHT TO MATE
TWO RATTLESNAKES ENTANGLED IN
WITH A LADY WITH A FEMALE
A FIGHT FOR THE RIGHT TO MATE
RATTLESNAKE.
WITH A LADY WITH A FEMALE
ACCORDING TO NATIONAL
RATTLESNAKE.
GEOGRAPHIC THIS IS A RITUAL
ACCORDING TO NATIONAL
ALL MALE RATTLE SNAKES HAVE TO
GEOGRAPHIC THIS IS A RITUAL
GO THROUGH TO PROVE TO THE
ALL MALE RATTLE SNAKES HAVE TO
FEMALE WHO IS THE BIGGEST AND
GO THROUGH TO PROVE TO THE
STRONGEST.
FEMALE WHO IS THE BIGGEST AND
DESPITE ALL OF THE VENOM THESE
STRONGEST.
MALES ACTUALLY NEVER USUALLY
DESPITE ALL OF THE VENOM THESE
BITE EACH OTHER.
MALES ACTUALLY NEVER USUALLY
>> HM.
BITE EACH OTHER.
I DON'T KNOW THAT A
>> HM.
RATTLESNAKE'S VENOM COULD HURT
I DON'T KNOW THAT A
ANOTHER RATTLESNAKE.
RATTLESNAKE'S VENOM COULD HURT
MAYBE IT COULD.
ANOTHER RATTLESNAKE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT COULD.
>> WE'LL FIND AN EXPERT ON
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT.
>> WE'LL FIND AN EXPERT ON
>> GOOD QUESTION.
THAT.
>> BREAKING NEWS, FOX5 FIRST
>> GOOD QUESTION.
ON THE SCENE OF WHAT APPEARS
>> BREAKING NEWS, FOX5 FIRST
TO BE A CRASH AND SHOOTING IN
ON THE SCENE OF WHAT APPEARS
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
TO BE A CRASH AND SHOOTING IN
THIS IS ALL UNFOLDING ON
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
FAIRVIEW AVENUE IN TAKOMA
THIS IS ALL UNFOLDING ON
PARK.
FAIRVIEW AVENUE IN TAKOMA
>> THAT'S WHERE WE FIND
PARK.
FOX5's PAUL WAGNER, HE'S
>> THAT'S WHERE WE FIND
THERE RIGHT NOW.
FOX5's PAUL WAGNER, HE'S
PAUL AT THIS POINT WHAT DO YOU
THERE RIGHT NOW.
KNOW?
PAUL AT THIS POINT WHAT DO YOU
>> Reporter: HI, THERE,
KNOW?
GUYS.
>> Reporter: HI, THERE,
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO PIECE
GUYS.
THIS TOGETHER.
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO PIECE
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THAT ONE
THIS TOGETHER.
PERSON HAS BEEN CRITICALLY
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THAT ONE
INJURED IN A SHOOTING
PERSON HAS BEEN CRITICALLY
ACCORDING TO PRINCE GEORGE'S
INJURED IN A SHOOTING
COUNTY POLICE.
ACCORDING TO PRINCE GEORGE'S
THAT PERSON WAS TRANSPORTED
COUNTY POLICE.
FROM THE SCENE AND AS SOON AS
THAT PERSON WAS TRANSPORTED
WE ARRIVED ON THE SCENE, WE
FROM THE SCENE AND AS SOON AS
DID SEE A WOMAN IN HANDCUFFS,
WE ARRIVED ON THE SCENE, WE
SHE WAS PUT INTO A CRUISER AND
DID SEE A WOMAN IN HANDCUFFS,
TAKEN AWAY.
SHE WAS PUT INTO A CRUISER AND
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT IS GOING
TAKEN AWAY.
ON HERE RIGHT NOW.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT IS GOING
WE'RE GOING TO ZOOM IN UP THE
ON HERE RIGHT NOW.
STREET.
WE'RE GOING TO ZOOM IN UP THE
YOU'LL SEE TWO CARS CRASHED UP
STREET.
THERE.
YOU'LL SEE TWO CARS CRASHED UP
LOOKS LIKE TWO SEDANS.
THERE.
THERE'S AN OLDER MODEL BMW AND
LOOKS LIKE TWO SEDANS.
ANOTHER VEHICLE AND THAT'S
THERE'S AN OLDER MODEL BMW AND
WHAT THE POLICE ARE
ANOTHER VEHICLE AND THAT'S
CONCENTRATING ON HERE BUT IN
WHAT THE POLICE ARE
ADDITION TO THAT THEY CLOSED
CONCENTRATING ON HERE BUT IN
THE STREET UP OFF EVEN FURTHER
ADDITION TO THAT THEY CLOSED
ABOUT ANOTHER BLOCK UP THAT
THE STREET UP OFF EVEN FURTHER
HILLSIDE AND WE DID SEE SOME
ABOUT ANOTHER BLOCK UP THAT
TACTICAL OFFICERS WALKING UP
HILLSIDE AND WE DID SEE SOME
THERE A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
TACTICAL OFFICERS WALKING UP
IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT THEY MAY BE
THERE A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
LOOKING FOR.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT THEY MAY BE
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO PIECE
LOOKING FOR.
THIS TOGETHER.
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO PIECE
ALL WE KNOW IS THAT THERE WAS
THIS TOGETHER.
A SHOOTING AT AROUND 3:15 THIS
ALL WE KNOW IS THAT THERE WAS
AFTERNOON HERE ON THIS BLOCK.
A SHOOTING AT AROUND 3:15 THIS
WHAT'S UNUSUAL IS THAT THE
AFTERNOON HERE ON THIS BLOCK.
POLICE CHIEF'S CHIEF OF STAFF
WHAT'S UNUSUAL IS THAT THE
IS HERE ON THE SCENE WHICH
POLICE CHIEF'S CHIEF OF STAFF
WOULD INDICATE THAT THIS MAY
IS HERE ON THE SCENE WHICH
BE A LITTLE BIT MORE SERIOUS
WOULD INDICATE THAT THIS MAY
THAN WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT.
BE A LITTLE BIT MORE SERIOUS
IT'S UNUSUAL TO SEE THE POLICE
THAN WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT.
CHIEF'S CHIEF OF STAFF COMING
IT'S UNUSUAL TO SEE THE POLICE
OUT HERE TO THE SCENE.
CHIEF'S CHIEF OF STAFF COMING
SO WE'RE STILL TRYING TO
OUT HERE TO THE SCENE.
GATHER DETAILS.
SO WE'RE STILL TRYING TO
AGAIN, ONE PERSON SHOT AND
GATHER DETAILS.
WOUNDED TAKEN AWAY BY
AGAIN, ONE PERSON SHOT AND
AMBULANCE IN CRITICAL
WOUNDED TAKEN AWAY BY
CONDITION.
AMBULANCE IN CRITICAL
WE DID WITNESS ONE WOMAN IN
CONDITION.
HANDCUFFS BEING TAKEN AWAY.
WE DID WITNESS ONE WOMAN IN
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP WORKING
HANDCUFFS BEING TAKEN AWAY.
THIS AND AS SOON AS WE GET
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP WORKING
SOME MORE INFORMATION WE'LL
THIS AND AS SOON AS WE GET
BRING IT BACK TO YOU GUYS.
SOME MORE INFORMATION WE'LL
>> I KNOW YOU JUST GOT THERE.
BRING IT BACK TO YOU GUYS.
SO, GO AHEAD AND TALK TO
>> I KNOW YOU JUST GOT THERE.
PEOPLE AND BRING BACK SOME
SO, GO AHEAD AND TALK TO
MORE REPORTING FOR 5 O'CLOCK.
PEOPLE AND BRING BACK SOME
PAUL WE APPRECIATE IT.
MORE REPORTING FOR 5 O'CLOCK.
>> THANKS.
PAUL WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> STILL TO COME, DISTURBING
>> THANKS.
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST A NORTHERN
>> STILL TO COME, DISTURBING
VIRGINIA MAN, POLICE SAY HE
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST A NORTHERN
ATTEMPTED TO PREY ON MINORS
VIRGINIA MAN, POLICE SAY HE
FOR SEX AND HE USED SOME
ATTEMPTED TO PREY ON MINORS
SOCIAL MEDIA SITES TO DO IT.
FOR SEX AND HE USED SOME
>> ALSO, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SOCIAL MEDIA SITES TO DO IT.
RIGHT PLACE AT THE RIGHT TIME.
>> ALSO, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
EIGHT MONTHS LATER, A LOCAL
RIGHT PLACE AT THE RIGHT TIME.
MAN IS REUNITED WITH A WOMAN
EIGHT MONTHS LATER, A LOCAL
WHO SAVED HIS LIFE AND OUR
MAN IS REUNITED WITH A WOMAN
CAMERAS WERE THERE.
WHO SAVED HIS LIFE AND OUR
>> AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
CAMERAS WERE THERE.
AT TRAFFIC AROUND THE  DMV.
>> AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
OUR CAMERAS ARE THERE TOO.
AT TRAFFIC AROUND THE  DMV.
YOU CAN SEE RUSH HOUR RAMPING
OUR CAMERAS ARE THERE TOO.
UP.
YOU CAN SEE RUSH HOUR RAMPING
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
UP.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Can my side be firm?
And my side super soft?
Yes! With the Sleep Number 360
smart bed, on sale now,
you can both adjust your comfort
with your sleep number setting.
But can it help
keep me asleep?
Absolutely, it intelligently
senses your movements and
automatically adjusts to
keep you both comfortable.
And snoring?
No problem. ...and done.
So, you can really
promise better sleep?
Not promise... Prove.
Don't miss the final days of the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event.
Save 50% on the Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus 0% interest for 24 months
on all smart beds. Ends Sunday.
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
>> ♪
>> ADVICE FOR LOCAL PARENTS
RIGHT NOW.
ASK YOUR KIDS WHO THEY'RE
TALKING WITH ONLINE.
LOOK AT ALL OF THEIR APPS.
YOU CAN MESSAGE IN A LOT OF
APPS YOU COULDN'T EXPECT.
>>> A 21-YEAR-OLD MAN IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA FACING
CHARGES AFTER HE TRIED TO
SOLICIT SEX ONLINE.
>> POLICE SAY HE WAS USING
FAKE SOCIAL MEDIA NAMES AND
LYING ABOUT HIS AGE.
FOX5's AYESHA KAHN IS LIVE
IN FAIRFAX WITH MORE ON THIS
INVESTIGATION.
HI, AYESHA.
HEY, ANGIE.
THIS HAS BEEN A MONTH LONG
INVESTIGATION AND POLICE SAY
SO FAR ONLY ONE JUVENILE
VICTIM HAS BEEN ABLE TO COME
FORWARD AND THIS IS AFTER THEY
TOLD THEIR PARENTS BUT NOW
POLICE BELIEVE THAT THERE
MIGHT BE MORE VICTIMS OUT
THERE BECAUSE OF THIS MAN.
NOW, THAT'S WHY FAIRFAX COUNTY
POLICE SHARED WITH US THE FAKE
NAMES THAT THE 21-YEAR-OLD
JAMES GREGORY OF FALLS CHURCH
IS ACCUSED OF USING ONLINE.
NOW, POLICE DIDN'T TELL US
WHICH SOCIAL MEDIA SITES
GREGORY WAS USING THE FALSE
NAMES ON BUT THE THREE HANDLES
HE WENT BY ARE JIMMY ORGANIST,
JOHN MAIN 2345 AND SUSIE
WEBER.
POLICE WANT YOU TO TAKE NOTE
OF THESE HANDLES AND SEE IF
ANY OF THEM SOUND FAMILIAR TO
YOU ESPECIALLY IF YOU ARE THE
PARENT OF A MINOR AND YOUR
CHILD HAPPENS TO USE DIFFERENT
ELECTRONIC DEVICES OR SOCIAL
MEDIA SITES.
IN THE MEANTIME POLICE ALSO
TELL US THAT GREGORY HAD BEEN
MISREPRESENTING HIS AGE TO TRY
TO SOLICIT MINORS FOR SEX
ONLINE.
HE IS CURRENTLY OUT ON BOND.
BACK TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU, AYESHA.
>> A LIVE LOOK HERE AT THE
NATIONAL HARBOR NOW.
MAYBE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I KNOW.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> JUST A PREGNANT PAUSE.
>> WE DIDN'T KNOW WHETHER IT
WAS GOING.
WAIT AND SEE.
>> BACK TO YOU.
[LAUGHTER]
>> BUT IT IS GOOD TO SEE YOU
OUT THERE AND THE SKYLINE
LOOKING VERY CALM, VERY
PRETTY.
>> YEAH, AND HAVE YOU GUYS
NOTICED SUN NOT SETTING NOW
UNTIL JUST BEFORE 6 O'CLOCK.
>> WOW.
>> SO, WE'RE GETTING THAT
DAYLIGHT BACK.
MARCH IS LESS THAN TWO WEEKS
AWAY SO EVEN THOUGH WE HAVEN'T
DONE A LOT OF WINTER THIS
WINTER, IT'S QUICKLY COMING TO
A CLOSE BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
MARCH 1ST BEGINNING OF
METEOROLOGICAL SPRING.
FIRST OF SPRING MARCH 19TH.
TOMORROW WILL NOT BE WARM.
WE'LL GET YOUR SUNSHINE BACK
FOR FRIDAY BUT IT WILL BE COLD
WE'LL HAVE WIND ESPECIALLY IN
THE MORNING.
FUTURE WIND CHILLS SHOW WE'LL
START YOUR FRIDAY ONLY FEELING
LIKE IT'S IN THE TEENS.
40 DEGREES AT REAGAN NATIONAL,
MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES.
38 AT DULLES, FEW PEEKS OF
SUNSHINE AND 39 AT BWI.
WE'VE HAD CLOUD COVER ALL DAY
THANKS TO THIS STORM SYSTEM TO
OUR SOUTH THAT'S TRACKING
ACROSS THE CAROLINAS AND IT IS
BRINGING SNOW SHOWERS TO
PLACES LIKE ROANOKE VIRGINIA,
VIRGINIA BEACH NORFOLK AND
BACK TOWARDS RALEIGH AND
THEY'RE EXPECTED IN THAT AREA
TO GET A COUPLE INCHES OF
SNOW.
NOTICE THE SNOW FLURRIES BY
STATE COLLEGE.
THAT'S A TINY PIECE OF ENERGY
SWINGING THROUGH WITH THE COLD
AIR AND THAT IF IT HOLDS
TOGETHER COULD BRING FLURRIES
TO OUR AREA THIS EVENING.
BUT WE ARE NORTH OF THE JET
STREAM NOW.
IT'S TAKING A DIP RIDING ALONG
THAT SYSTEM ACROSS THE
CAROLINAS AND VIRGINIA SO THE
COLD AIR IS IN PLACE AND IT
WILL BE THROUGH TOMORROW.
WITH THE SUNSHINE BACK IT WILL
LOOK NICE BUT BITTER STARTING
OFF THE DAY IN THE 20'S WIND
CHILLS IN THE TEENS.
WE SHOULDN'T EVEN HIT
40 DEGREES LATER ON IN THE DAY
SO BUNDLE UP WEATHER AT THE
BUS STOP.
THESE ARE YOUR FUTURE WIND
CHILLS.
AT 10 O'CLOCK TONIGHT IT FEELS
LIKE IT'S IN THE 20'S BUT BY
THE TIME YOU FIRST STEP OUT AT
7:00 A.M. TOMORROW WIDESPREAD
FEELS IN THE TEENS AND THAT'S
AREA WIDE.
IT INCLUDES D.C. SOUTHERN
MARYLAND EASTERN SHORE.
THOSE NORTHWEST WINDS COULD BE
GUSTING OVER 20 MILES AN HOUR
WE'LL SEE THE WINDS DIE DOWN.
CHILLS IN THE TEENS BY NOON,
BACK UP CLOSE TO THE AIR
TEMPERATURE BY 4 O'CLOCK.
AHEAD TO THE WEEKEND THOUGH A
NICE WARMUP.
NOW, YOUR HIGH TEMPERATURES
ARE BACK INTO THE 50'S.
IT DOESN'T TELL THE WHOLE
STORY.
EACH MORNING WILL BE COLD,
SATURDAY IN THE 20'S, SUNDAY
IN THE 30'S SO IT WILL TAKE A
BIT TO WARM UP BUT THAT
SUNSHINE WILL HELP AND IF
YOU'RE OUT MAYBE GOING FOR A
WALK DOING SOME THINGS AROUND
TOWN IN THE AFTERNOON HOURS,
IT WILL FEEL PLEASANT
TEMPERATURES IN THE 50'S.
SO THE TREND IS TO HEAD UPWARD
AFTER TOMORROW, 52 SATURDAY,
55 SUNDAY AND EVEN BY NEXT
MONDAY, BACK TO FEELING LIKE
SPRING, 58 DEGREES.
THAT'S A LOOK AT THE NEXT FEW
DAYS.
I'LL HAVE YOUR SEVEN-DAY STILL
AHEAD.
ANGIE.
>> CAITLIN THANK.
WE WANT TO BRING YOU A STORY
ABOUT BEING IN THE RIGHT PLACE
AT THE RIGHT TIME.
A MAN NAMED BOB WAS GIVING A
EULOGY IN A FAIRFAX COUNTY
HOME PACKED WITH 50 PEOPLE AND
THAT'S WHEN HE COLLAPSED.
A WOMAN NAMED VIRGINIA
PERFORMED CPR ON BOB FOR SIX
MINUTES UNTIL MEDICS ARRIVED
AND NOW EIGHT MONTHS LATER THE
MAN IS REUNITING WITH THE
WOMAN WHO HELPED SAVE HIS
LIFE.
>> IF I HAD DIED, THE OBITUARY
WOULD HAVE SAID, OH, HERE'S
ROBERT FENTON, YOU KNOW, 78
YEARS OLD DIED.
YEARS OLD DIED. OU KNOW, THEY SS
OLD.
BUT 39 YEARS OLD WITH TWO
YOUNG KIDS THAT'S A LOT
DIFFERENT.
AND SO -- SO IT'S SO IMPORTANT
FOR EVERYBODY TO LEARN SOME OF
THE BASICS BECAUSE TIME IS
TIME IS TIME.
>> THAT IS TRUE.
WELL, FAIRFAX COUNTY FIRE AND
RESCUE IS HOSTING A FREE OPEN
HOUSE HANDS ONLY CPR EVENT
SATURDAY.
NOW IT'S GOING ON FROM 1:00
UNTIL 4:00 IN THE BINGO HALL
AT FIRE STATION 14.
THATS IN BURKE, VIRGINIA.
THE GOAL IS TO SHOW NEIGHBORS
JUST HOW EASY IT IS WHEN IT
COMES TO SAVING A LIFE.
>>> WELL, PET LOVERS, YOU KNOW
THIS DAY IS FOR YOU.
IT IS OFFICIALLY NATIONAL LOVE
YOUR PET DAY.
>> LOOK WHO THAT IS.
>> IT IS.
>> DOLLY REBECCA.
>> YES, AND WREN MY LITTLE
PETS.
MY LITTLE GIRLS HERE.
WE WANT TO SEE YOUR PICTURES
SO RIGHT THERE YOU SEE THE
HASHTAG, FOX5 PETS.
YOU CAN TWEET THEM TO US SEND
THEM TO US.
THIS IS ROMAN'S LITTLE ONE.
>> TRY TO INCLUDE THE NAMES,
ROMAN.
GIVE HER A SHOUT-OUT.
>> THIS IS LITTLE STINKER BELL
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> THIS IS WHY WE NEED THE
NAMES.
>> AND THAT IS REALLY CLEVER.
I LIKE THAT.
I WONDER IF THEY ARE A BIG
DISNEY FAN.
AND SASSY.
>> THE CAT'S NAME SASSY.
>> IT SAYS SPOILED CAT SASSY.
>> YOU HAVE PROBABLY SEEN THEM
ALL OVER SOCIAL MEDIA THE
CHALLENGE TRENDS.
TIDE POD WAS A BIG ONE.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT TWO OF THE
BIGGEST ONES ON TIK-TOK THERE
ARE POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS.
>> ♪
We made USAA insurance for
members like Kate.
A former Army medic, made of the
flexibility to handle
whatever Monday has in store and
tackle four things at once.
So when her car got hit, she
didn't worry.
She simply filed a claim on her
USAA app and said...
I got this.
USAA insurance is made the way
Kate needs it - easy.
She can even pick her payment
plan
so it's easy on her budget
and her life.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
VO: A great president
and an effective mayor.
Leadership that makes a
difference.
OBAMA: He's been a leader
throughout the country
for the past twelve years,
Mr. Michael Bloomberg is here.
VO: Together they worked
to combat gun violence,
and again to improve
education for every child.
OBAMA: I want to thank
the mayor of this great city,
Mayor Bloomberg, for his
extraordinary leadership.
I share your determination
to bring this country together
to finally make progress
for the American people.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
>> ♪
>> A LOOK NOW AT WHAT'S
TRENDING WITH MARINA MARRACO.
>> WE'RE STARTING THIS ONE
STORY.
A STARTLING ADMISSION FROM A
BOXER NAMED TYSON FURY GETTING
READY FOR A BIG FIGHT AND HIS
PREP WORK INCLUDES GIVING UP
SOMETHING THAT HE LOVES DEARLY
DIET COKE.
THE BOXER TELLING ESPN HE
USUALLY DRINKS 20 TO 30 DIET
COKES EACH DAY.
THAT'S CAN.
>> IS THAT HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
>> THAT'S 3 GALLONS A DAY OF
DIET COKE.
>> AND HOW MUCH SUGAR IS THAT.
>> WELL, IT DOESN'T, IT HAS --
>> SODIUM, ISN'T THE SODIUM
HIGH.
>> IT'S GOT SWEETENER ALONG
THE LINES OF SPLENDA.
>> GALLONS OF ANYTHING
PROBABLY ISN'T GOOD.
YOU CAN OVERDRINK WATER.
>> IT'S 3 GALLONS OF PURE
CHEMICALS.
>> MAYBE THAT'S THE KEY TO
WINNING.
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL FIND OUT.
APPARENTLY HE'S GIVING THAT
UP.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
TIK-TOK AND SOCIAL MEDIA
CHALLENGE THAT HAS A LOT OF
PEOPLE TALKING AND FOR GOOD
REASON.
IT'S CAUSING MAJOR CONCERNS
FOR PARENTS AFTER THIS
CHALLENGE CAME OUT.
IT'S CALLED THE SKULL BREAKER
CHALLENE.
TWO PEOPLE KICK A THIRD PERSON
TO JUMP KICK THEIR FEET OUT
CAUSING THEM TO FALL.
WHEN THEY FALL THIS IS ANOTHER
ONE, THIS IS WHEN THEY SWERVE
CARS TO THE BEAT OF THE MUSIC
AND OF COURSE AT ANY POINT IN
TIME THEY CAN JUST WRECK RIGHT
INTO IT.
IT'S CALLED A CHA-CHA DRIVE
CHALLENGE.
DRIVERS SWERVING INTO OTHER
DRIVERS TO THE BEAT OF THE
CAR.
TIK-TOK PUTTING OUT A WARNING.
THEY'VE NOT TAKEN THE VIDEOS
DOWN.
YOU CAN IMAGINE PEOPLE ARE
CONCERNED ARE WE GIVING A
PLATFORM TO EXHIBIT THIS TYPE
OF BEHAVIOR AND AT WHAT COST.
ARE WE GOING TO HAVE TEENS
BREAKING THEIR SKULLS CRASHING
INTO CARS.
YES, THAT IS THE BIG QUESTION.
DOES TIK-TOK NEED TO STEP IN
AND TAKE T THOSE VIDEO DOWNS.
>> SHOULD APPS DO MORE TO
POLICE POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS
SOCIAL MEDIA CHALLENGES.
VOTE NOW ON FOX5DC.COM OR THE
FOX5 D.C. APP.
WE'RE OVERWHELMINGLY YES ON
THIS.
THE THING I HAVE TO SAY THOUGH
IT'S VERY EASY TO POLICE
RACIST LANGUAGE OR THREATENING
LANGUAGE.
YOU CAN POLICE THAT.
IT'S HARD TO POLICE STUPID.
IF PEOPLE ARE DOING STUPID
THERE'S A BIG RANGE OF THAT
AND IT'S OBJECTIVE.
>> YOU WOULD HAVE TO TAKE THE
ENTIRE PLATFORM DOWN AT THIS
POINT BECAUSE THAT IS WHAT
TIK-TOK IS BECOMING.
IT'S A LOT OF DANCING.
IT'S GEARED TOWARDS TEENS AND
I THINK THIS IS WHERE THEY
FIND THE CLICKS.
>> IF YOU CAN PULL OVER FOR
USING MY CELL -- TO THEY CAN
PINPOINT WHO THESE KIDS ARE
THEY SHOULD BE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE.
>> AT WHAT POINT DID THE DOES
THE BUCK STOP.
>> HOW ABOUT THE PARENTS?  WHY
DOESN'T IT STOP THERE.
>> MONITOR YOUR KIDS' SOCIAL
MEDIA.
>> THAT'S WHY MY KIDS ARE
NEVER DRIVING AND NEVER HAVING
FUN.
>> NO BATTLE ANY FAMILY WANTS
TO FACE.
HOW A LOCAL FOUNDATION IS
HELPING TO FUND THE FIGHT
AGAINST PEDIATRIC CANCER AND
GIVING FAMILIES HOPE.
>> ♪
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>> WELCOME BACK.
WE NOW HAVE A CHECK ON SOME OF
OUR TOP STORIES.
FIRST, BREAKING NEWS FROM
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
A CAR CRASH AN SHOOTING IN
TAKOMA PARK.
THIS HAPPENED ON FAIRVIEW
AVENUE JUST AFTER 3:00 THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE KNOW THAT A MAN WHO WAS
SHOT IS IN CRITICAL CONDITION
RIGHT NOW.
NO WORD ON WHAT LED UP TO THAT
SHOOTING.
OUR CREWS ARE ON THE SCENE ARE
WE'RE GOING TO SHARE ANY NEW
INFORMATION AS SOON AS IT
COMES IN.
>> EARLY SIGNS THAT AN ATTACK
IN GERMANY YESTERDAY WAS
RACIALLY MOTIVATED.
AT LEAST NINE PEOPLE WERE
KILLED IN ATTACKS AT TWO
HOOKAH BARS.
POLICE SAY THE SUSPECTED --
THE SUSPECTS TARGETED TURKISH
CITIZENS IN AN ACTS OF RIGHT
WING EXTREMISM.
IT'S BELIEVED HE KILLED
HIMSELF AT HOME ALONG WITH HIS
MOTHER.
>> A JUDGE SENTENCED ROGER
STONE TO MORE THAN THREE YEARS
IN PRISON.
THE 67-YEAR-OLD WAS CONVICTED
FOR OBSTRUCTION WITNESS
TAMPERING AND LYING TO
CONGRESS.
TODAY'S SENTENCING MARKS AN
EXTRAORDINARY MOVE BY ATTORNEY
GENERAL WILLIAM BARR TO BACK
AWAY FROM HIS JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT'S ORIGINAL
SENTENCING RECOMMENDATION.
NEW TRIAL.FILED A MOTION FOR A-
>> SPARKS FLYING IN LAS VEGAS
LAST NIGHT AS MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG APPEARED IN HIS VERY
FIRST PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE.
ALL THOSE CANDIDATES HAVE DONE
FIVE OR SIX DEBATES NOW.
BLOOMBERG WALKED IN A LITTLE
UNPREPARED MANY FELT.
THE CANDIDATES EXCHANGED
SEVERAL BLOWS WITH THE
BILLIONAIRE ATTACKING HIM FOR
HIS WEALTH AND SOME OF THE
CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS HE'S
MADE.
AT TIMES HE SEEMED RATTLED BUT
HE ALSO DID FIGHT BACK.
>> I'D LIKE TO TALK ABOUT WHO
WE'RE RUNNING AGAINST, A
BILLIONAIRE WHO CALLS WOMEN
FAT BROADS AND HORSE FACED
LESBIANS.
AND NO, I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
DONALD TRUMP.
I'M TALKING ABOUT MAYOR
BLOOMBERG.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO THROW
OUT CAPITALISM.
WE TRIED THAT.
OTHER COUNTRIES TRIED THAT.
IT WAS CALLED COMMUNISM AND IT
JUST DIDN'T WORK.
>> WASHINGTON DEMOCRATS KEEP
ON --
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SLAMMED
BLOOMBERG'S PERFORMANCE ON
TWITTER.
HE'S HOLDING AN EVENT IN THIS
AFTERNOON AND ANOTHER RALLY
THERE TOMORROW NIGHT AHEAD OF
THE SATURDAY CAUCUSES IN
NEVADA.
>> CHILDHOOD CANCER IS THE
NUMBER ONE DISEASE KILLER OF
CHILDREN IN THE U.S.
FUNDING NEW RESEARCH IS A
CRITICAL NUDE BUT A LOCAL
FOUNDATION IS NOW GIVING HOPE
TO FAMILIES DESPERATE FOR
ANSWERS.
>> TELL DADDY YOU LOST.
>> I LOST A TOOTH.
>> HE WAS JUST SIX BUT LUKE
ENGLER WAS FULL OF WORDS TO
LIVE BY.
>> HOW AWESOME WAS THAT?
>> REALLY AWESOME.
>> MOMMY.
DON'T BE SAD.
SAD IS BORING.
OKAY, BUD, LIKE YOU JUST -- HE
CAME UP WITH WAYS THAT
ADDRESSED THE WORLD THAT A HE
WAS TRYING TO UNDERSTAND AND
FIGURE OUT.
>> ♪
>> A WORLD THAT CHANGED
FOREVER IN THE FALL OF 2017
WHEN A WO WOBBLY FEELING TURNED
INTO A CHIP TO ER AND TO
CHILDREN'S NATIONAL HOSPITAL.
>> WE'RE IN A ROOM WHERE A
COUPLE DOCTORS WALK IN THE
DOOR WHO NOW I FRIENDS THAT WE
KNOW AND A LADY WITH A TISSUE
BOX.
AND I'M LIKE OH, NO, THIS IS
NOT GOING TO BE GOOD.
>> RICH AND HIS WIFE NANCY
FOUND OUT THEIR SON HAD DI PG
AN INCREDIBLY FORM OF BRAIN
CANCER WITH AN AVERAGE
SURVIVAL RATE OF NINE MONTHS.
>> YOU'RE THROWN INTO THIS
WALL LIKE WHAT HAS JUST
HAPPENED AND YOU START TO
RESEARCH AND YOU START TO FIND
MORE INFORMATION OUT.
I FIND OUT THAT NEIL
ARMSTRONG'S DAUGHTER HAD DIPG
IN THE 1960'S AND WHAT THEY
HAD FOR HER RADIATION AND
STEROIDS IS WHAT THEY HAVE FOR
MY SON SOME ALMOST 60 YEARS
LATER.
THAT'S GOT CHANGE.
>> ♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY ♪
>> LUKE'S LITTLE BODY TOOK ON
TWO ROUNDS OF CHEMO A CLINICAL
TRIAL BUT IT WASN'T ENOUGH.
IN NOVEMBER OF 201814 MONTHS
AFTER HIS BATTLE BEGAN LUKE
PASSED AWAY IN THE ARMS OF HIS
FATHER.
>> I DESCRIBED HIM AS A SUPER
NOVA.
I SAID LIKE A SUPER NOVA IT'S
INTENSE AND BRILLIANT BUT IT
CAN'T LAST FOREVER BUT IT'S
AFTER EFFECTS ARE FELT FOR A
LONG TIME.
AND WE STILL FEEL CONSTANTLY.
>> I BELIEVE WHAT WE'RE DOING
IS CREATING HOPE WHERE USUALLY
THERE ISN'T ANY.
>> BRAD SAYS IT'S STORIES LIKE
LUKE'S THAT INSPIRES CHANCE
FOR LIFE A NONPROFIT
FOUNDATION HE FOUNDED WITH HIS
WIFE CALLIE 15 YEARS AGO WHEN
THEIR GODDAUGHTER WAS
DIAGNOSED WITH AN AGGRESSIVE
SPINAL CORD TUMOR.
>> WHEN I HEARD THE SCARY
STATISTICS THAT EVERY TWO
MINUTES A CHILD IS DIAGNOSED
WITH CANCER I KNEW THAT WE HAD
TO HELP.
>> THE CHANCE FOR LIFE EVENT
HAS DONATED MORE THAN
$6 MILLION TO PEDIATRIC CANCER
RESEARCH.
>> THIS IS A WAY I BELIEVE
FOLKS CAN GIVE BACK.
>> WHILE RAISING THE CURTAIN
ON A SERIOUS GAP WHEN IT COMES
TO CURING CANCER IN CHILDREN.
>> FOR CHILDREN IN PARTICULAR
T-WE GET LESS THAN A NICKEL
OUT OF EVERY DOLLAR OF THE
TOTAL POT OF FEDERAL FUNDING.
>> DR. WONG SAYS CHANCE FOR
LIFE IS CHANGING THAT DYNAMIC.
>> IT'S A TREATMENT THAT USES
YOUR OWN IMMUNE SYSTEM TO
ATTACK THE CANCER CELLS.
WE HAVE ACTUALLY GOTTEN
INQUIRIES AND PATIENTS FROM
ACROSS THE WORLD.
>> LIFE SAVING WORK GIVING
FAMILIES HOPE.
>> HE LOVED LEGOS.
I'VE GOT A ROTATION OF LEGOS
THAT I HAVE WITH ME THROUGHOUT
THE DAY.
>> EVEN WHEN THEY KNOW THERE'S
NOTHING THAT CAN BRING THEIR
CHILD BACK.
>> DIDN'T NECESSARILY ASK FOR
THE VISION WE WERE GIVEN OR
MAYBE THRUST UPON US BUT WE'RE
NOT GOING TO WASTE IT EITHER.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE HOPE, YOU
DON'T HAVE THAT CHANCE FOR
LIFE THEN WHY ARE YOU EVEN
HERE?
>> ♪
>> I KNOW YOU'RE EMCEEING
THEIR BIG EVENT THIS COMING
WEEKEND.
>> YES, THAT'S COMING UP ON
SATURDAY OVER AT THE MGM AND
LUKE'S FATHER RICH AND HIS
WIFE WILL BE THERE AGAIN.
LUKE ACTUALLY SPOKE AT THAT
EVENT COUPLE YEARS AGO AND THE
FAMILY SAYS THAT THEY -- AFTER
HE PASSED, THEY DONATED HIS
TUMOR FOR RESEARCH AND WE KNOW
THAT RIGHT NOW AT CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL HERE IN D.C. 16
FAMILIES AT CHILDREN'S,
THEY'RE UNDERGOING THOSE
CLINICAL TRIALS THAT ARE
FUNDED BY CHANCE FOR LIFE,
THIS ORGANIZATION ALONE.
>> WE KNOW THAT THIS
SATURDAY'S EVENT WILL DO SOME
GOOD.
>> IT HAS BEEN NEARLY 20 YEARS
SINCE THE D.C. SNIPER ATTACKS
TERRORIZED THE WASHINGTON
REGION.
NOW THE CASE IS THE SUBJECT OF
A NEW TRUE CRIME PODCAST AND
THE SHOW'S AWARD WINNING HOST
STOPPED BY FOR TO TELL US
ABOUT IT.
>> VERY COOL.
HERE'S A LIVE LOOK ALONG THE
WOODROW WILSON BRIDGE WHERE
TRAFFIC IS MOVING ALONG
ACTUALLY PRETTY GOOD FOR THIS
HOUR, RIGHT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ♪
LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ♪♪
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
>> THERE IS A RUTHLESS PERSON
ON THE LOOSE.
>> WHAT UNNERVES THIS
COMMUNITY THE MOST IS THE
RANDOMNESS OF THE MURDERS.
>> ORDINARY PEOPLE DOING
ORDINARY THINGS.
>> THEY KILLED THE FIVE PEOPLE
IN ONE DAY AND THEN WENT ON
THE RAMPAGE FOR THE NEXT
MONTH.
>> WOW.
IT IS A TRUE CRIMES STORY THAT
MANY IN OUR AREA WILL NEVER
FORGET.
THE D.C. SNIPER ATTACKS.
NOW THAT CASE IS THE TOPIC OF
A NEW PODCAST CALLED MONSTER
D.C. SNIPER.
IT DIVES INTO THE MONTH LONG
SHOOTING SPREE THAT KILLED 10
PEOPLE ACROSS D.C. MARYLAND
AND VIRGINIA AND ONE OF THE
SUSPECTS LEE BOYD MALVO WHO
WAS 17 AT THE TIME OF THE
SHOOTING IS STILL FIGHTING HIS
LIFE SENTENCE.
EARLIER THIS MORNING EMMY
WINNING INVESTIGATIVE REPORTER
TONY HARRIS WAS HERE TO
DISCUSS THE PODCAST.
>> WHAT I LOVE ABOUT GETTING
AN OPPORTUNITY TO WORK ON THIS
PIECE IS THAT WE TAKE ABOUT AS
DEEP A DIVE AS YOU CAN TAKE
INTO THIS CASE.
TO YOUR POINT THERE ARE A LOT
OF PEOPLE WHO THINK THEY KNOW
THE STORY BUT THEY KNOW IT
KIND OF ON A SURFACE LEVEL AND
IT'S BEEN 18 YEARS AND IT'S
NOT JUST A SITUATION WHERE WE
WANTED TO FIND SOME
SENSATIONAL STORY TO TELL, WE
FOUND A CURRENT DAY PEG AND
THAT'S THE FACT THAT LEE BOYD
MALVO WHO COMMITTED THESE
CRIMES WHEN HE WAS A MINOR, 17
YEARS OLD AND PEOPLE FORGET
THAT.
>> RIGHT.
HE IS HAVING HIS APPEAL LOOKED
AT BY THE SUPREME COURT.
>> EXACTLY, RIGHT.
>> ARGUMENTS HAVE BEEN HEARD.
WE'RE EXPECTING SOME KIND OF A
DECISION AS TO WHETHER OR NOT
HE SHOULD BE RESENTENCED
BECAUSE THE CRITICAL QUESTION
THAT WE'RE LOOKING AT AND
ASKING IN THIS PODCAST, AND I
LOVE SOME OF THE FEEDBACK THATOT
WE'RE ASKING THEM TO REALLY
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS ISSUE OF
HOW WE PUNISH MINORS WHO
COMMIT HEINOUS CRIMES.
>> EPISODE NINE OF THE PODCAST
COMES OUT TODAY.
YOU CAN LISTEN AND SUBSCRIBE
ON THE I HEART RADIO APP OR
WHEREVER PODCASTS ARE
AVAILABLE.
YOU KNOW THIS PODCAST IS OUT
WHAT'S SO INTERESTING ABOUT
THESE IS AT THE TIME WE'RE
ONLY GETTING THE INFORMTION
THAT POLICE ARE RELEASING,
RIGHT, OR THAT WE'RE GETTING
FROM INTERVIEWS BUT THERE'S SO
MUCH MORE THAT THEY KNOW THAT
THEY'RE HOLDING ONTO BECAUSE
THEY HAVE TO SAVE IT FOR THE
CASE AND IT'S RELEASED ONCE
THE CASE IS DONE BUT IT NEVER
GETS THE SAME ATTENTION.
>> BECAUSE IT'S NOT IN THE
DAILY CYCLE.
IT'S RIVETING TO GO BACK AND
HEAR ALL THE DIFFERENT DETAILS
AND LIKE YOU SAID WE THINK WE
KNOW THE STORY BUT WE DON'T.
SO, IT'S WORTH A LISTEN.
>>> WELL, TODAY FEDERAL
OFFICIALS THEY'RE WEIGHING
WHETHER TO REMOVE MORE
ARTIFACTS FROM THE SUNKEN
TITANIC.
A HEARING IS UNDER WAY THIS
AFTERNOON HAPPENING IN
NORFOLK, VIRGINIA, THE COMPANY
THAT HAS EXCLUSIVE RIGHTS TO
THAT SHIP NOW WANTS TO
RETRIEVE THE RADIO THAT WAS
USED TO CALL FOR HELP AFTER
THAT SHIP HIT THAT ICEBERG.
GETTING THE RADIO WOULD
REQUIRE RMS TITANIC
INCORPORATED TO REMOVE A PART
OF THE TITANIC'S DECK HOUSE
WHICH IN TURN WOULD REQUIRE
THE COURT AS APPROVAL.
>> I'M AMAZED THERE'S ANYTHING
STILL LEFT TO EXCAVATE EXCEPT
THE HULL OF THE SHIP.
>> THEY MUST HAVE EVIDENCE OR
THEY KNOW THAT THE RADIO IS
THERE.
>> COMING UP A SUBWAY STAR IS
BORN.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE MOMENT A
COMMUTER SHOPPED THE INTERNET
DURING A GAME OF FINISH THE
LYRIC.
>> SPOILER ALERT.
THE ELEPHANT GOT SENT PACKING
ITS TRUNK.
WE'RE GOING TO REVEAL WHO WAS
BEHIND THE MASK.
>> NOT A PROFESSIONAL SINGER.
>> NO?
>> NOPE, NOPE, NO.
>> MAYBE AN ATHLETE.
>> STAY TUNED.
I KNOW, IT'S A BIG ELEPHANT.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU ANGIE.
>>> WE ARE TRACKING SOME
FALLING TEMPERATURES FOR
TONIGHT.
WIND CHILLS IN THE TEENS WHEN
YOU STEP OUT TOMORROW MORNING
BUT THE WEEKEND SHAPING UP TO
BE REALLY NICE.
YOUR FULL SEVEN-DAY FORECAST
COMING UP WHEN FOX5 AT 4:00
RETURNS.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
We made USAA insurance for
members like Kate.
A former Army medic, made of the
flexibility to handle
whatever Monday has in store and
tackle four things at once.
So when her car got hit, she
didn't worry.
She simply filed a claim on her
USAA app and said...
I got this.
USAA insurance is made the way
Kate needs it - easy.
She can even pick her payment
plan
so it's easy on her budget
and her life.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
Uh oh!
What?
I think I forgot
to lock my Buick.
Got it.
I bet you lunch
you can't make it in there.
I'm thinkin' sushi.
Alexa, ask Buick
to start my SUV.
You can do that?
Yeah, with a Buick.
What?
At the heart of every
Buick SUV...is you.
Find out why Buick
is number one
in dealer sales
and service satisfaction.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick SUV models
plus current eligible
GM owners
get 7-50 purchase
allowance.
>> ♪
>> THERE'S CHANGE COMING TO A
POPULAR TOURIST SPOT IN
VIRGINIA SPECIFICALLY IF
YOU'RE LOOKING TO PICK UP A
LITTLE MEMENTO TO REMEMBER
YOUR TRIP.
>> SARAHSIMMONS HAS MORE ON
WHAT ELSE THEY'RE WORKING ON
FOR NEXT HOUR.
WHAT'S UP SARAH.
>> HELLO GUYS.
ALL NEW AT 5:00 WHY THE MOUNT
VERNON ESTATE IS PULLING A
POPULAR SOUVENIR FROM ITS GIFT
SHOP.
>>> AND FOX5 IS GETTING
ANSWERS TONIGHT AFTER SEVERAL
VIEWERS REACHED OUT TO US
FRUSTRATED OVER A YEARS LONG
DELAY IN GETTING A SIDEWALK IN
THEIR BUSY D.C. NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> PLUS, WE HAVE BASEBALL
BACKLASH.
A NEW FORM OF PUNISHMENT FOR
THE HOUSTON ASTROS IN THE WAKE
OF THAT CHEATING SCANDAL AND
IT HAS TO DO WITH LITTLE
LEAGUE TEAMS.
ALL NEXT AT 5:00.
>> TRICKLING DOWN.
>> JENNIFER LAWRENCE IS
TEAMING UP WITH FILMMAKER ADAM
McKAY FOR THE NETFLIX COMEDY
DON'T LOOK UP.
McKAY HAS ALSO WROTE THE
MOVIES VICE AND THE BIG SHORT.
J LAW WILL PLAY AN ASTRONOMER
WHO GOES ON A TOUR WITH HER
PARTNER WARNING PEOPLE ABOUT
THE AN ASTEROID.
PRODUCTION WILL START IN APRIL
AND IT WILL STREAM LATER THIS
YEAR.
>> I WAS WONDERING WHERE SHE'S
BEEN.
>> SHE'LL BE ON NETFLIX.
>> A WOMAN IN ENGLAND IS GOING
VIRAL AFTER SHE WAS STOPPED IN
A SUBWAY STATION BY A BRITISH
COMEDIAN FOR HIS FINISH THE
LYRICS STUNT.
>> FINISH THE LYRICS.
>> ♪ TELL ME SOMETHING, ARE
YOU HAPPY IN THIS MODERN
WORLD.
>> ♪ OR DO YOU NEED MORE.
>> WOW.
>> KEEP GOING.
WOULD YOUR, YOU'RE REALLY
GOOD.
KEEP GOING.
>> ♪
>> WOW.
>> WHOA.
I WAS NOT -- I WAS HAVING LIKE
A SUSAN BLOOM MUSIC.
>> I WAS READY FOR HER TO TAKE
OFF THE MASK AND IT IS LADY
GAGA.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SO FUNNY.
I KNOW.
BUT WE WOULD NEED THE VOICE
CHANGE.
THAT'S CHARLOTTE ARBURY.
REMEMBER HER NAME.
SHE'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE
SUPER MEGA FAMOUS NOW.
SHE NAILS THE REST OF BRADLEY
COOPER AND GAGA'S SHALLOW FROM
A STAR IS BORN.
TURNS OUT SHE'S ACTUALLY A
WEDDING SINGER.
WHAT ARE THE CHANCES OF
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I MEAN -- WOW, A STAR IS BORN
IN THE SUBWAY.
>> BUT SHE'S A COMEDIAN.&
SHE HAS TALENT LIKE THAT.
HER COMEDY MUST BE AMAZING IF
SINGING IS A SIDE JOB.
>>> THEY TOOK THE STAGE ON
MASKED SINGER THE BANANA KITTY
FROG FACT COMPANY AND MOUSE
BUT WE GOT TO SEE ANOTHER
CELEBRITY UNMASKED.
>> ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> TONY HAWK.
ICONIC AND LEGENDARY SKATE
BORDER.
>> YOU MAY NOT KNOW THE FACE
BUT YOU KNOW THE NAME, TONY
HAWK ONE OF THE GREATEST SKATE
BORDERS OF ALL TIME HE
PERFORMED FRIDAY I'M IN LOVE
BY THE CURE BUT IT WASN'T
ENOUGH TO HELP KEEP HIM IN THE
COMPETITION.
HE JOKED HE WAS GLAD HE WAS
LEAVING EARLY BECAUSE HE ONLY
HAD ONE SONG LEFT IN HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT FOR THESE
NONSINGERS THOUGH TO LAST
LONGER THAN CHAKA KHAN, LIL'
WAYNE IT'S GOT TO FEEL LIKE AN
ACCOMPLISHMENT.
>> I MEAN THAT'S WHAT MAKES
"THE MASKED SINGER" SO GREAT.
WHAT UNIVERSE ARE WE LIVING IN
WHEN TONY HAWK IS BEATING OUT
LIL' WAYNE AND CHAKA KHAN,
CHAKA KHAN.
>> VERY COOL.
>> CHAKA KHAN.
>> ♪
>> A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE ON THIS THURSDAY.
>> YEAH, IT'S THURSDAY, WE'RE
ONE DAY CLOSER TO FRIDAY.
>> THAT'S SOMETHING TO CHEER
ABOUT.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE COLD
TOMORROW BUT THE WEEKEND
WARMING UP IN THE AFTERNOON SO
THAT'S NICE ON THIS THURSDAY
OR FRIDAY EVE.
WEEKEND CLOSING IN ON IT SO
THAT ALWAYS FEELS NICE.
IT WILL FEEL A LITTLE COLD
WHEN YOU STEP OUTSIDE TOMORROW
MORNING.
WIND CHILLS FALLING INTO THE
TEENS OVERNIGHT.
IT WILL FEEL LIKE IT'S ONLY
15, 16, SOMETHING LIKE THAT
DEGREES 7:00 A.M. TOMORROW
MORNING.
WE'LL HAVE SUNSHINE THROUGHOUT
THE DAY TOMORROW.
THOSE WIND CHILLS WILL GET A
LITTLE BETTER BUT IT REMAINS
VERY COLD FRIDAY, SLOW WARMUP
AS WE WERE HEAD INTO THE
WEEKEND.
MORNINGS WILL BE CHILLY BUT
AFTERNOONS SHOW A BIT OF A
REBOUND.
HIGH TEMPERATURES TODAY A RARE
BELOW NORMAL AFTERNOON WITH
OUR HIGH TEMPERATURES, 42 AT
REAGAN, 38 AT DULLES, 40 AT
BWI.
AVERAGE HIGH 48.
AND TEMPERATURES OUTSIDE RIGHT
NOW MOSTLY IN THE 30'S IT'S
BEEN COLD IT'S BEEN CLOUDY BUT
GENERALLY HAVEN'T SEEN ANY
SNOW EXCEPT FOR EXTREME
SOUTHERN MARYLAND AND MAYBE
CENTRAL VIRGINIA BUT NOT
REALLY IN OUR AREA.
37 ANNAPOLIS, 39 IN BALTIMORE,
37 IN GAITHERSBURG, 38 DULLES
AND 36 IN WINCHESTER.
GOING TO BE A CHILLY NIGHT IF
YOU'RE STEPPING OUTDOORS.
TEMPERATURE CHANGE PRETTY
DRAMATIC COMPARED TO YESTERDAY
ON THE ORDER OF 10 TO
15 DEGREES.
SO, OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW, STORM
SYSTEM TO OUR SOUTH.
WE KNEW IT WOULD STAY TO OUR
SOUTH.
IT'S BRINGING SNOW SHOWERS
ACROSS THE VIRGINIA AND NORTH
CAROLINA BORDER MAKING IT
ABOUT AS FAR NORTH AS THE
LOWER EASTERN SHORE AND SAINT
MARY'S COUNTY SO IF YOU'RE
THERE AND YOU'RE SEEING A FEW
SNOW FLURRIES THAT'S WHY,
MAYBE EVEN SOME RAIN SPRINKLED
IN.
ANOTHER PIECE OF ENERGY NEAR
STATE COLLEGE BROKEN LINE OF
SNOW FLURRIES IF THEY HOLD
TOGETHER MOST LIKELY NORTHERN
MARYLAND OR NORTHERN VIRGINIA
GOING TO SEE FLURRIES TONIGHT.
HERE'S LOCAL RADAR.
SOUTHERN SAINT MARY'S COUNTY
DOWN TO THE NORTH NECK OVER TO
RICHMOND LIGHT RAIN SPRINKLES
AND FLURRIES.
GENERALLY NOT GOING TO SEE
ANYTHING STICK BUT THAT'S ALL
THAT WE HAVE, LEXINGTON PARK
MAYBE SEEING A COUPLE
FLURRIES.
NOT GOING TO GET ANY FARTHER
NORTH THAN THAT A.
WINTER STORM WATCHES AND
WARNINGS OUT FOR THAT AREA
INCLUDING NORFOLK AND VLADIMIR A
BEACH.
TEMPERATURES WILL BE FALLING
THROUGH THE 30'S THIS EVENING.
37 BY 7:00 P.M.
CLOUDY SKIES THROUGH 9 P.M. 35
BY 11 O'CLOCK.
WE SHOULD BE FALLING INTO THE
MID-20'S OVERNIGHT.
AFTER MIDNIGHT IS WHEN MORE OF
THAT COLD AIR REALLY POURS IN.
25 TO START THE DAY TOMORROW.
REMEMBER WIND CHILLS WILL BE
IN THE TEENS EARLY.
IN THE AFTERNOON WE SHOULDN'T
EVEN HIT 40 DEGREES.
WE'LL STAY IN THE 30'S.
ANOTHER BELOW NORMAL
AFTERNOON.
FOR THE WEEKEND, HIGH PRESSURE
RETREATING A BIT TO THE SOUTH.
IT WILL REMAIN DRY SUNNY AND
REALLY NICE.
BUT IN THE AFTERNOONS WE'LL
GET A GOOD BOOST.
IT WILL START OUT COLD
TEMPERATURES IN THE 20'S
SATURDAY MORNING, 30'S SUNDAY
MORNING.
LIKE I SAID WE SHOULD RISE
INTO THE 50'S BOTH DAYS.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO HEAD
OUTSIDE, AFTERNOON HOURS LOOK
PRETTY GOOD.
WE'LL CALL FOR 52 THERE ON
SATURDAY.
56 ON SUNDAY WITH JUST A FEW
MORE CLOUDS.
REALLY NOT A BAD WEEKEND FOR
OUR LAST ONE HERE IN FEBRUARY.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN-DAY.
NEXT WEEK SHOWERS RETURN TO
THE FORECAST MONDAY NIGHT INTO
THE FIRST HALF OF TUESDAY AND
THEN AGAIN THROUGHOUT THE DAY
ON WEDNESDAY, NOTICE TEMPS IN
THE 50'S ALL THREE DAYS SO WE
ARE JUST TALKING ABOUT RAIN
SHOWERS AT THE MOMENT.
LOOKS A BIT CHILLIER THERE ON
THE BACKSIDE FOR YOUR
THURSDAY.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN-DAY.
ANGIE, BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH CAITLIN.
>>> WELL, NOW A LOOK AT
FOX5's "LIKE IT OR NOT."
HERE'S THE QUESTION.
ARE PICKLES A VEGETABLE?  MOM
CLAIMS THAT SHE WAS LUNCH
SHAMED FOR GIVING HER SON A
PICKLE AS HIS DAILY VEGGIE
REQUIREMENT.
THE MINNESOTA MOM SAYS HER
FOUR-YEAR-OLD SON'S SCHOOL
SENT HER THIS NOTE SAYING THAT
VEGGIES PICKLES DON'T COUNT
FOR VEGGIES UNDER TOPIC NUMBER
THREE RIGHT THERE AND THE
U.S.D.A. GUIDELINES SAYS EACH
CHILD'S LUNCH MUST INCLUDE TWO
VEGGIES OR A VEGGIE AND A
FRUIT.
LAST NIGHT WE TALKED ABOUT
THIS.
>> WHAT IS THIS?  WHO ARE
THESE PEOPLE?  THEY'RE LOOKING
AT WHAT THE KID IS EATING AND
MAKING SURE THEY HAVE THE
APPROPRIATE FDA U.S.D.A.
APPROVED VARIETY.
>> HERE'S THE BILL.
>> SHE'S BEEN WAITING ON THAT.
BEEN PRACTICING ALL NIGHT.
>> SEEMS LIKE WE'RE REALLY IN
A PICKLE BUT COME ON, GUYS.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A TEACHER IS
BEING A REAL GHERKIN.
I'M RELISHING THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SAY SOME OF THESE JOKES.
>> IT IS A FRUIT BECAUSE IT
HAS SEEDS IN IT.
THAT'S A BIOLOGICAL THING BUT
I THINK IN MY MIND IT'S
CONSIDERED A VEGETABLE.
>> YEAH, BUT IT REALLY IS ITS
A FRUIT THAT'S A "VEGETABLE"
IT'S FRUIT BECAUSE IT HAS
SEEDS IN IT BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST LIKE PICKLE JOKES.
THAT'S WHAT I GOT OUT OF THAT
SEGMENT.
>> YOU MET YOUR MATCH
APPARENTLY WITH JIM LOKAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> HOPEFULLY NO MORE BAD
JOKES.
>> THE SWEET MOMENT WHEN A
YOUNG BOY HUGGED A PIZZA
DELIVERY MAN.
IT WAS CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
VO: A great president
and an effective mayor.
Leadership that makes a
difference.
OBAMA: He's been a leader
throughout the country
for the past twelve years,
Mr. Michael Bloomberg is here.
VO: Together they worked
to combat gun violence,
and again to improve
education for every child.
OBAMA: I want to thank
the mayor of this great city,
Mayor Bloomberg, for his
extraordinary leadership.
I share your determination
to bring this country together
to finally make progress
for the American people.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
>> ♪
>> PET LOVERS THIS DAY IS FOR
YOU.
IT'S OFFICIALLY NATIONAL LOVE
YOUR PET DAY AND WE WANT YOU
TO SEND US YOUR PICTURES USING
#FOX5 PETS.
LOOKS LIKE LITTLE ALEXANDER
THERE ENJOYING A NICE LITTLE
SNOOZE.
THERE'S A FAMILIAR FACE.
AND THIS IS NESHA THANK YOU
MRS. FRAZIER FOR SENDING THAT.
IT'S HER GRAND DOG ACTUALLY.
WHO IS THIS?  WHO IS THIS
HUMAN.
>> I DIDN'T THINK JIM HAD A
DOG HERE.
>> THIS MY ANGIE'S.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE -- DOES HE
HAVE HIS OWN TWITTER HANDLE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> KEEP THEM COMING.
>> OKAY.
SO, YEAH, KEEP THEM COMING.
FOX5 PETS IS THE HASHTAG TO
USE.
WE LOVE TO SEE THEM AND WE
LOVE TO SHARE THEM.
>> ♪
>> HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>> BBYE-BYE.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> ENJOY YOUR PIZZA.
>> YOU THINK HE LIKES PIZZA.
THAT'S TWO-YEAR-OLD COHEN
RUNNING OUTSIDE TO MAKE SURE
HE GIVES A HUG TO THE DELIVERY
DRIVER AFTER THE VIDEO WAS
WIDELY SHARED THE DRIVER
MESSAGED COHEN'S MOM TO LET
HER KNOW HE HAD RECENTLY LOST
HIS DAUGHTER.
>> WE WANT TO SHOW YOU THIS
PET POOCH.
THIS IS IN TORONTO.
AND HE'S PUTTING OTHER DOGS TO
SHAME AFTER A VIDEO OF HIM
PLAYING CONNECT FOUR SURFACED.
HIS OWNER ADMITS HE'S NOT GOOD
AT THE STRATEGIC PART OF THE
GAME.
PERCY DOES HAVE HIS OWN
INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT.
HE HAS OVER 1500 FOLLOWERS
ALREADY.
SO, I'M TELLING YOU THE GAMING
INDUSTRY IS HUGE.
YOU KNOW?  SO, GOOD LUCK TO
HIM.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
EVERYBODY FOR JOINING US AT
4:00.
>> YOUR NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
MARYLAND.
FOX5 FIRST ON THE SCENE OF A
CRASH AND SHOOTING IN TAKOMA
PARK.
WE'RE THERE LIVE.
>>> PLUS, A DRUG DEAL GONE
WRONG.
THAT'S WHAT INVESTIGATORS
THINK LED TO THE DEADLY
SHOOTING OF A MARYLAND POLICE
OFFICER'S SON.
THE NEW INFORMATION WE'RE
LEARNING TODAY.
>>> AND AN APP POPULAR WITH
TEENS IS GIVING MORE POWER TO
PARENTS BUT IS THAT SOCIAL
MEDIA DOING ENOUGH TO CRACK
DOWN ON VIRAL VIDEO CHALLENGES
THAT COULD BE DOWN RIGHT
DANGEROUS?  YOUR NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>> ♪
>> AND WE START WITH BREAKING
NEWS OFF THE TOP AT 5:00 OUT
OF PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
>> FOX5 FIRST ON THE SCENE OF
A CRASH AN SHOOTING ALL
UNFOLDING JUST OVER AN HOUR
AGO O