>> RIGHT NOW AT 7, CHRISTMAS
FORECAST STARTING WITH CHILLY
TEMPERATURES.
IS A WARM-UP ON THE WAY.
TUCKER BARNES HAS THE DETAILS
IN MINUTES.
SITTING AROUND THE FIREPLACE.
>> READY FOR THE KIDS TO OPEN
PRESENTS.
>>  WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR WHAT
DO YOU HAVE FOR CHRISTMAS FROM
SANTA KIDS.
>> STILL TOO EARLY.
>>  I CAN TILL YOU DIDN'T GET
MUCH.
>>  YOU ON THE OTHER HAND.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
>>  DID HE CONSIDER HIMSELF
SINGLE.
>> I SAW SANTA LAST NIGHT.
>> WHAT'S ONE THIS UNWRAPPED
THINGS ON YOUR DESK.
>> IT'S CHILLY START TO DAY.
TEMPERATURES THERE BELOW
FREEZING.
>> AUGUST TAKING THE DOG FOR A
WALK.
DETAILS IN THE FORECAST FOR
TODAY AND NEXT COUPLE DAYS
COMING UP.
>>  WHEN I CAME IN TODAY THERE
WERE LITERALLY TWO CARS ON THE
ROAD AND THEY HAD TWO FINE
OFFICERS IN THEM.
NOBODY WAS ON THE ROAD EXCEPT
FOR POLICE NO. TRAFFIC TODAY.
>>  I SAW SAFETY VEHICLES AND
RIDE SHARE VEHICLES.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
>> PRETTY MUCH IT.
>> EVERYBODY IS EP JOYING
CHRISTMAS MORNING.
>> YOU MAY NOTICE UNUSUALLY
HIGHWAY SIGNS.
>> GOOD MORNING.
BOTH MARYLAND DEPARTMENT OF
TRANSPORTATION AND VIRGINIA
DEPARTMENT OF TRANSPORTATION
HAVE PUT UP SIGNS ON
INTERSTATES AS YOU TRAVEL TO
GO SEE LOVED ONES FOR
CHRISTMAS THAT SANTA IS
WATCHING IF ARE YOU SPEEDING
AS WE TAKE A LIVE LOOK ON
ROADS RIGHT NOW ON 495.
AND WE NOTICE THAT RIGHT NOW
TRAFFIC IS PRETTY CLEAR.
YOU KNOW PEOPLE ARE JUST
DRIVING ALONG ON THE ROADS
THIS MORNING.
UP FORTUNATELY THOUGH SADLY
THIS MORNING SOMEONE DIED
OVERNIGHT KEEP ILL WORTH NEAR
CALVERT:00 THIS MORNING AND
IT'S NOW CLOSED.
WHILE WE DON'T KNOW WHAT CAUSE
THE THAT CRASH TO HAPPEN.
DURING THE HOLIDAY SEASON
THEY'RE SPELLING OUT A M
MESSIOUS FERPING ANOTHER SIGN
WAS SEEN VIRGINIA TO MARYLAND
THAT SAYS DRIVING SAFELY IS MY
FAVORITE.
WE'RE ACTUALLY PASSING RIGHT
UNDER THAT SIGN AT THIS MOMENT
AS WE SPEAK.
WE ALSO LOOKED AT SOME MEMBERS
FROM THE NATIONAL HIGHWAY
ADMINISTRATION DURING
CHRISTMAS AND NEW YEAR DAY
HOLIDAY PERIODS IN 2018 ALONE
THERE WERE MORE DRUNK DRIVING
RELATED FATALITIES THAN DOING
ANYWHERE AND IN MARYLAND LAST
YEAR BETWEEN MASS EAVE AND NEW
YEAR'S DAVE MARYLAND STATE
POLICE MADE 11 IS IS 71 DUI
ARRESTS AND 6 DRUG RELATED
ARRESTS.
TROOPERS ALSO ISSUED MORE THAN
5800 CITATIONS AND RESPONDED
MORE THAN 105 0 0 FOR.
STATE TROOPERS WILL BE OUT IN
FULL FORCE KEEPING AN EYE ON
ANY SPEEDERS.
WATCH FOR SIGNS, BACK TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
D.C. POLICE LOOKING FOR A
GUNMAN WHO SHOT THREE PEOPLE
IN SOUTH EAST YESTERDAY.
THE VICTIM SANE TONIGHT
HOSPITAL.
GOOD NEWS THEY'RE EXPECTED TO
YOU'RE VIV UP POLICE HAVE A
DESCRIPTION OF SHOOTER AND CAR
SHE WAS DRIVING THE MAP WAS
WEARING GRAY AND BLOOD HOOT
THE SWEATSHIRT AND DROVE AWAY
IN A NISSAN ROGUE ROGUE.
>>  THIS IS IS VIDEO OF HELP
WAITING FOREVER DELIVERY
DRIVER TO RETURN TO HIS
VEHICLE ON 63 STREET NORT
NORTHEAST.
WHEN HE GOT BACK THEY HURT THE
DRIVER AND STOLE FROM THE
DRIVER AND THEN THEY JUST TOOK
THE ENTIRE TRUCK FULL THE
PACKAGES.
IF YOU RECOGNIZE THE SPUS
INSPECTS IN THIS VIDEO CALL
POLICE.
YOU COULD ERP A WE EP THE
APPLIANCE WAS LEFT RUNNING
WHEN THEY LEFT YESTERDAY
MORNING.
THE FIRE GAMINGED TWO UNITS
AND NAIR FIGHTERS PUT OUT THE
FLAMES QUICKLY THE RED CROSS
IS EPING FAMILIES.
>>  LET'S KLT EP MOVR NIGHT
LOWs 0s AND 30s.
IF YOU WANT TO GO FOR A
CHRISTMAS JOG BEFORE THE BIG
MEAL YOU CAN DO IT.
>>.
>> KURN NUMBERS 3 REAGAN
NATIONAL.
3 WITH, DULLES BACK TO 2 IT 3.
THERE'S SPOTS IN LOW 20s.
26 THIS MORNING IN BALTIMORE.
BWI MARSHALL.
ALL RIGHT JUST A FEW CLOUDS TO
START THE DAY.
MOST OF THE DAY WILL BE PARTLY
TO MOSTLY SUNNY.
AND IT WILL BE A QUIET
AFTERNOON FOR US.
DAYTIME HIGHS UPPER 40s TO
PERHAPS 50 THERE WASHINGTON.
BUT, AS FAR AS ANY STORMYNESS
OR ANYTHING TO BE CONCERNED
ABOUT NOT THIS AFTERNOON AS
WE'LL BE QUIET.
HITTING ROADWAYS WEATHER
SHOULD TOTALLY COOPERATE.
MOST OF THE COUNTRY HERE WILL
TAKE A LOOK AT TRAVEL
CONDITIONS.
MOST EVER THE COUNTRY IS
FAIRLY QUIET FOR TRAVELING
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
HERE'S CHRISTMAS FORECAST.
50 DEGREES.
JUST A FEW CLOUDS OUT.
THERE AND A PLEASANT BUT COOL
AFTERNOON.
KHULLY AGAIN TONIGHT AND WE'LL
LOOK AT THE WEEKEND FORECAST
AS WELL IN A MINUTE.
>>  SINCERE THANK YOU.
>>  MY PLEASURE.
>>  LET'S GET BACK TO NEWS N
NOW.
PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY BE AWAY
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE FOR THE
HOLIDAY THAT DOESN'T STOP NRIM
NANCY PELOSI IMPEACH.
PROCESS SGLE ERIN COMO JOINS
US LIVER IN THE NEWSROOM WITH
DETAILS NOW SDMRAERN ALLISON,
STEVE, ERP HE ATTEMPTED
SERVICE IN HE WEST PALM BEACH
BUT HAD WORDS BEFORE THAT.
>> SHE HATES THE REPUBLICAN
PAERPT PARTY AND ALL THE
PEOPLE THAT VOTE FORD ME AND
REPUBLICAN PARTY.  HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY BELL'S JURY
STALLING SENATE TRIAL HOLDING
ON TO PAST IMPEACHMENT
ARTICLES TO ALLOW REPUBLICANS
TO ALLOW WITNESSES TO TESTIFY.
>>  IT'S HARD TO MATH UP A
TRIAL NOT HAVING DOCUMENTS AND
WITNESSES.
IF IT DOESN'T HAVE DOCUMENTS
AND WITNESSES IT'S GOING TO
STEAM MOST OF THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE THAT IT IS A SHAM TR
TRIAL.
SMO TRIAL NOT TO GET AT FACT.
>>  DEMOCRATIC SENATOR CHRIS
MURPHY WEETED YESTERDAY
REPRESENTS SAID WE SHOULD
OBSERVE IMPEACHMENT RULES AND
OPEN WITHOUT AGREEMENT ON
WITNESSES AND WHEN THE DRIL
BEGINS THEY'LL TELL US HOW
DIFFERENT IT SEAN WE CAN'T
HAVE.
>>  THESE WERE BAD PEOPLE
THESE ARE EVIL PEOPLE.
>> HE REFUSED TO RULE OUT A
PARDON ON FOR ROGER STONE A
COURT CONVICTED HIM LAST MONTH
FOR OBSTRUCTING CONGREGATIONAL
INVESTIGATION AND LYING UNDER
OATH.
>>  HI NOT THOUGHT OF IT I
THINK IT'S VERY TOUGH WHAT
THEY DID TO ROGER STONE
COMPARED TO WHAT THEY DO TO
OTHER PEOPLE ON THEIR SIDE.
I THINK IT'S VERY TOUGH.
AND TOP JUDGE VERY MUCH
INVOLVED AND HOPEFULLY THEY DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
>>  THE REPORT CAN APPROVAL
FEDERAL WIRE TAPS IN SECRET
JUDICIAL PROGRESS EARLIER THIS
MONTH THE INSPECTOR GENERAL
CRITICIZED USE OF THE COURT TO
SECURE A WIRE ATTACH CARTER
PAGE.
FORMER TRAUMA M CAMPAIGN
OFFICIAL.
>>  THE PRESIDENT TOUTD
UPDATED TRADE AGREEMENT WITH
MEXICO AND CANADA AND PHASE
ONE OF LIMITED DEALING WITH
CHINA WHICH HE SAYS HE EXPECTS
TO SIGN SHORTLY.
BACK TO YOU.
>>  AIRPORT THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
IT'S 7:09 NOW.
POPE FRANCIS HOLDING CHRISTMAS
EVE MASS FROM ST. PERIOD OF
TIME'S BASS ILL KAXT DURINGLE
HOSPITALLY HE SAID GOD LOVES
EVERYONE EVEN THE WORSE AMONG
PEOPLE THIS IS 7th CHRISTMAS
EVE MASS FRANCIS CELEBRATED AS
APPROPRIATE.
TODAY HE'LL DELIVER
TRADITIONAL CHRISTMAS DAY
MESSAGE FROM THE BALL COPY AT
ST. PETERS.
>> DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENT DEP
SHALL CANDIDATE MICHAEL
BLOOMBURG CUST TIES WITH A
CONTRACTOR THAT USED PRISONERS
TO MAKE CALLS FOR CAMPAIGNS.
THE INTERCEPT REPORTED
BLOOMSBURG PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN CONTRACTED A NMING
NNL BASED CALL CENTER COMPANY
WHICH IN PART USED INMATES IN
OKLAHOMA TO MAKE THOSE PHONE
CALLS ON BEHALF OF BILLI
BILLIONAIRE'S PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN.
FORMER NEW YORK MAYOR SAID HE
WAS UNAWARE IT WAS HAPPENING
AND CAM PAIN WILL PROP ARELY
VET SUBCONTRACTORS MOVING
FORWARD.
>> IT'S UP CLEAR IF OR WHEN
THE INVESTIGATION INTO MSU
WILL RESUME.
>>  HERE'S A REMIND TO ALL OF
US TO HAVE WORKING CARBON
MONOXIDE DETECTORS.
NUMBER OF FAMILIES IN
NORTHWEST D.C. ARE SAYING
THANKS TO NEIGHBOR WHO
DISCOVERED DANGEROUS LEVELS
THIS THEIR HOMES.
THIS UP FOLDED GALTON STREET
YESTERDAY A 7P-YEAR-OLD BOY
HAD TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL AND
HE'S DOING OKAY.
1 SHE PEOPLE BETWEEN THREE
HOMES WERE EVACUATED AND
TREATED.
>>  IF THAT FAMILY HAD NOT
ABOUT ALERTED TO THE CO IN
THEIR HOME BY THE NEIGHBOR'S
CO DETECTOR THAT FAMILY MAY
HAVE NEVER WOKEN UP THAT
MORNING.
>>  TUNZ DETECTABLE GAS YOU
CANNOT SMELL IT YOU DON'T KNOW
IT'S THERE UNLESS YOU HAVE THE
DETESTTORS.
THE LEVELS OF CARBON MOX
MONOXIDE WAS DANGEROUSLY HIGH.
>>  THIS IS CAYDEN AND TONIGHT
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT THE
LITTLE THINGS THAT MAKE
CHRISTMAS EXTRA SPECIAL.
SOUNDS GOOD TO HE YOU.
>>  SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>>  THAT STORY COMING UP.
It's been reported that
there's a cyberattack
on business every 39 seconds.
Ouch.
I don't even want
to think about it.
Comcast Business has a solution.
We go beyond fast with a
cloud-based security system
that automatically updates,
so you always have
the latest protection.
Phishing. Malware.
Risky sites.
It can help block all of that.
It's one less thing
for us to worry about.
Cybersecurity and
new business packages
that give you faster speeds,
more solutions
and bigger savings.
Call 1-800-501-6000.
Is skincare from around the
world better than Olay?
To find out, Olay faced the
world.
We tested our vitamin B3 formula
and beat Japan's top
moisturizers.
And even the $400 French cream.
Olay Regenerist faced
131 premium products
from 12 countries, Over 10
years.
Olay's hydration was unbeaten
every time.
Olay. Face anything.
Want a light as air feel? Try
Olay Whips.
>> 7:1 IS 4 CHRISTMAS SURPRISE
U.S. TROOPS OVER STHAEZ
HOLIDAY SEASON THIS IS
OPERATION HOLIDAY EXPRESS
TRAVELING BY HELICOPTER ACROSS
PARTS OF SYRIA HANDED OUT
GIFTS TO MANY HARD WORKING MEN
IN UNIFORM STATIONED THERE FOR
THE HOLIDAYS AND GIFT GIVING
DONE TON ACCOMPANIMENT OF
FESTIVE TUNES PLAYED BY
MILITARY BAND ACCOMPANYING
OFFICIALS ON THE TRIP.
>>  THANKS TO EVERYBODY ON THE
HOLIDAY SEASON KEEPING US SAFE
AROUND THE WORLD.
>>  LET'S GET TO WEATHER NOW.
>>  BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT'S A CHRISTMAS MIRACLE.
>> TUCKER BARNES.
>>  I LOOKED STAYED UP LATE
NOW WAITING FOR SANTA DEN DID
NOT SEE THEM I THOUGHT I SAW
LIGHTS.
>>  WE HAVE TO GO TO SLEEP.
HE'S NOT GOING TO --
>>  COOKIES ARE GONE THIS
MORNING WHEN I GOT UP.
>>  SO STAND BY.
>>  WE'LL SAY SANTA BRINGS YOU
YOU KNOW I HAVE A GIFT BUT NOT
LIKE OLD DAYS.
>>  IT'S MORE SO FOR THE KIDS.
>>  ONE NEVER GETS TOO HOLD
FOR A GOOD SANTA VISIT.
>>  THAT'S TRUE.
>>  LOOKING AT LOTS OF 0s OUT
THERE EARLY.
FREEZING TEMPERATURES IN
MRAISZ LIKE WALDORF, 25.
BUOY 27, LA PLAYTA 25.
LEESBURG 28.
AGAIN EVERYBODY BELOW FREEZING
AND YOU SAW THE LIVE SHOT
THERE WE'LL BE LOOKING
BEAUTIFUL HERE IN THE NEXT
COUPLE HOURS WITH LOTS OF
SUNSHINE TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
KIND OF PARTLY TO MOSTLY SUNNY
AFTERNOON AND AGAIN PLEASANT
CONDITIONS EXPECTED ACROSS THE
AREA HIGHs UPPER 40s AND 50s.
4 THE HAGERSTOWN.
SATELLITE AND RADAR QUIET.
HIGH, THIN CLOUDINESS AND
SURPRISE EARLY THIS MORNING
AND ADDING COLOR TO THE
SUNRISE OUT THERE.
BUT, VERY QUIET.
BOSTON, NEW YORK, D.C. AT LAP
TA, CHICAGO, REALLY MOST OF
THE COUNTRY HERE IS VERY QU
QUIET.
THE EXCEPTION IS THE WEST
COAST WITH A FEW SHOWERS SEE
AT TOLL LOS ANGELES.
FEW SNOW SHOWERS IN THE
MOUNTAINS.
OTHERS WISE WEATHER SHOULD NOT
IMPEDE TRAVEL ACROSS MID
ATLANTIC OR MOST OF COMMUNITY.
50 TODAY, 53 TOMORROW WE'LL
WARM UP TO NEAR 60 SATURDAY
AND SHOWERS RETURN SURPRISED
AVERAGE INTO MONDAY IT WILL BE
WARM IT WILL BE WET GUYS NOT
EXPECTING ANY FRONDZ WEATHER
FOR THE NEXT YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
GOING CALL IT RIGHT NOW.
NO MORE PHONES ARE WEATHER FOR
20 19.
>>  THANK YOU SO MUCH TUCKER.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>>  LET'S GET TO DEVELOPING
STORY OUT OF FLORIDA.
NOW A GROUP OF PACKERS
THREATENING CITY OF
PENNSYLVANIA COAL A HACKERS
HAVE POYINGTED STOLEN DATA
ONLINE AND IS DEMANDING ONE
MILLION FROM CITY OF PENS
PENSACOLA.
INFORMATION OF 60,000 PEOPLE
MAY HAVE BEEN COME MACEED CITY
HAS TO PERHAPS TO PAY THE
HACKERS WHAT THEY'RE ASKING
FOR AND PENSACOLA DOES GOT
HAVE CYBER SECURITY INSURANCE.
>> THERE'S ADD NEWS TO REPORT
CHRISTMAS MORNING COLLEGE
REPORTER EDWARD ASHOFF DIED
CHRISTMAS EVE WHICH WAS MORE
TRAMINGTIC WAS HIS 34th BIRTH
DAY.
HE CONTRACTED PNEUMONIA AFTER
BEING A SIDELINE REPORTER LAST
MONTH.
HE LEAVES BEHIND HIS FIANCEE
HE PLANNED TO MARRY NEXT
SPRING.
HE WAS 3 WITH 4 YEARS OLD.
>>  GET THAT CHECKED OUT.
BAD NEWS FOR SURE.
THIS TIME YEAR THERE'S NO
SHORTAGE OF MAIL DELIVERED
RIGHT.
SOME LETTERS ARE MORE
IMPORTANT THAT OTHERS.
>> THIS WEEK ONE MOM REACHED
OUT TO "FOX5" SAYING HIS 9D
THE-YEAR-OLD SOP RAN NUN
EXPECTED TROUBLE TRYING TO GET
THAT WISH LIST TO SANTA.
JOSH ROSENTHAL TALKED ABOUT
HOW A SEEMINGLY SMALL GESTURE
ENDED UP SAVING CHRISTMAS.
>>  OKAY FROM CAYDEN TO SANTA.
>>  9-YEAR-OLD CAYDEN BRIAN
SAMUEL JUST WANTED TO GET HIS
WISH TLOYS SANTA.
>> AND 150 GIGABYTE APPLE
LAPTOP.
>>  THIS YEAR THERE WAS A
PROBLEM.
>>  I FELT LIKE BROKEN DOWN.
>> BROKEN DOWN BECAUSE
CHRISTMAS AFTER CHRISTMAS
CAYDEN AND MOM HAND DELIVERED
WISH LIST TO SAME MALL MAILBOX
FOR WHATEVER REASON THE
MAILBOX WAS GONE.
>>  IT WAS A BIG DEAL I'VE
BEEN TAKING HIM SINCE HE'S AN
INFANT.
WE SEE SANTA AT THE MALL AND
WALK OVER TWO DAYS BEFORE
CHRISTMAS AND MAIL HIS LIST.
>>  THEY WENT TO FIND DELIVERY
DRIVER WHO WOULD TATE LETTER
INSTEAD.
THE FIRST ONE THEY FOUND
REFUSED.
>>  WE'RE LIKE REALLY THIS IS
KID.
TO ME HE WAS GRINCH.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> MOTHER AND SON WENT HOME
AND AOKAYED EP WAS CRUSHED SO
THEY FWHUKD THEIR LOBBY TO
GIVE IT ONE LAST SHOT.
>>  AS WE WERE COMING UP
THROUGH THE DOOR AND TURNED
THE CORNER AND SAY USPS AND IT
WAS LIKE OH, MY GOSH.
>>  MAIL CARRIER THAT
TYPICALLY COMES EARLIER IN THE
DAY HAPPILY TOOK CADEN LETTER
SAVING THE 9-YEAR-OLD'S
CHRISTMAS.
>>  WHAT DID IT MAKE YOU FEEL
LIKE WHEN THE POSTAL WORKER
TOOK YOUR LETTER.
>>  I FELT HAPPY BECAUSE IF
THIS HAPPENED I WOULDN'T HAVE
ANY PRESENTS.
HOW ARE THEY -- HOW IS IT
HAPPENING HOW IS THIS POS
POSSIBLE.
AND WELL IT'S A CHRISTMAS
MIRACLE.
>>  A CHRISTMAS MIRACLE BOTH
HE AND HIS MOM WON'T SOON
FORGET.
>> I WANT TO HOLD ON TO THIS
MOMENT AND I'M PROUD THIS
MOMENT AND WE MADE IT WORK,
YES.
>>  SUPER CUTE.
CAY DEVELOPMENT N I LOVE THE
STORY AND HER MOM SAID SHE'S
PRETTY SURE THAT SANTA WILL
DELIVER ON THAT LIST.
>>  AWESOME.
>>  NOW THAT THEY GOT IT TO
HIM WHICH WAS THE CHALLENGE.
>>  SO CUTE.
>>  7:20 RIGHT NOW.
BEING HELPER OF SANTA ASKLAWZ
CAN BE A REAL MONEY MAKER
DURING THE HOLIDAYS.
SEASONAL RETAIL WORKERS MAKE
BETWEEN 10 AND 11 AN HOUR AND
BUT SANTA CLAUS HELPERS CAN
EARN BETWEEN 30 AND 7P 5 DLRZ.
THAT MEANS REAL LIFE SANTAS
MAKE UP TO 20,000 FOR ABOUT 40
DAYS WORK.
YOU CANNOT PUT PRICE TAG ON
JOY IN SURE CAN'T.
>>  3-YEAR-OLD FROM COLORADO
GOT A CHRISTMAS SURPRISE FROM
RECYCLED TRUCK DRIVER.
>>  WHAT?
>> NO.
IT'S RECYCLE RICK.
>>  THE BOY'S FAMILY SAID HE
BE FRIENDED THEIR NEIGHBOR'S
RECYCLE TRUCK DRIVER WHO THEY
CALL RECYCLE RICK.
RECYCLE RICK GAVE THAT BOY A
SPECIAL CHRISTMAS PRESENT A
REPLICA OF THE TRUCK HE
DRIVES.
THE BOY'S MOM SAYS HE HAS NOT
STOPPED PLAGUE WITH THE TOY
SINCE HE OPENED IT.
THEY RECORDED IT TO SHOW HIM
HOW EXCITE HEAD WAS.
>>  7P:21 A SPECIAL CHRISTMAS
EVE REUNION AFTER A PREMATURE
BABY WAS DELIVERED ON STREETS
OF DISTRICTS.
>>  WE'LL SHOW YOU REUNION
WITH FIRST RESPONDER SAVED
THAT LITTLE GIRL'S LIFE.
>> JUST UNBELIEVABLE STORY
COMING UP AT 7:2 IT 1.
PERFECT FOR CHRISTMAS.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
Nature's Bounty.
>> LITTLE GIRL IS CELEBRATING
HER FIRST CHRISTMAS AND IT'S
ALL THANKS TO D.C. FIRST
RESPONDERS.
THE BABY WAS NOT BREATHING
WHEN SHE WAS BORN PREMATURELY
IN MARCH.
HER MOTHER SIERRA DUCKET WENT
INTO LABOR MIDDLE OF MINNESOTA
AVENUE NORTHEAST D.C..
FORTUNATELY D.C. FIRE AND EMS
WERE NEARBY AND HELPED WITH
DELIVERY AND WERE ALL REUNITED
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>>  SHE WAS LIKE THE BABY IS
COMING.
I WAS LIKE OH, MY GOD.
AND WE LOOKED AND THE BABY WAS
RIGHT THERE IN THE SACK.
SO WE HURRIEDLY PUT HER IN
AMBULANCE AND KICKED IN.
WE JUST OPENED THE SACK UP AND
SHE CAME OUT AND WAS BARELY
BREATHING WE STARTED CPR
IMMEDIATELY AND WE RADIOED TO
GW HOSPITAL TO LET THEM KNOW
THEY WERE COMING IN DOING CPR
AND IT ALL WORKED OUT.
>>  SHE'S BEAUT SGLUL YES SHE
IS.
>>  BABY THE SWEETEST.
OH, MY GOODNESS FIRST RES
RESPONDER WENT ON TO SAY THIS
WAS HER FIRST TIME ADMI
ADMINISTERING CPR TO A PAINY
AND REASON A LITTLE PREMATURE
BABY YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW TINY
AND ANOTHER FIRST RESPONDER
SAID IT WAS ONLY HER SECOND
DAY ON THE JOB.
>>  LOOK AT HER NOW.
ADORABLE.
>> SO CUTE.
>>  AND THAT OUTFIT.
YES, PLEASE.
>>  ALL RIGHTY.
>> SO SWEET.
>>  GREAT STORE YES, I 7:25 A
CHECK ON CHRISTMAS FORECAST
OFF TO A GREAT START TO FAR.
>> IT'S A BEAUTIFUL SUNRISE AT
7:2 IT 4 CHRISTMAS MORNING
SURPRISE.
ISN'T THAT GORGEOUS GUYS.
GEORGOUS.
>> TEMPERATURES BELOW FREEZING
FOR EVERYBODY.
BUNDLE UP.
IT SHOULD BE A NICE AFTERNOON
FOR US AND DAYTIME HIGHS WILL
BE IN THE UPPER 40s TO ABOUT
50s.
WE'RE LOOKING AT VERY, VERY
COMFORTABLE AND BEAUTIFUL
AFTERNOON FOR CHRISTMAS 20 19.
>>  ALL RIGHT LET'S DO
TEMPERATURES.
THERE WE GO.
YEAH, ACTUAL SHOT THERE TEST
UP 32 TO START THE MORNING.
WINDS LIGHT, NORTH, NORTHEAST
AT 3 AND WE'RE NOT FEATURING
-- THIS IS KIND OF WHAT YOU
SEE IS WHAT YOU GET LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
WITH DAYTIME HIGHs IN UPPER
40s AND NICE, QUIET WEATHER.
JUST A FEW CLOUDS OUT THERE
EARLY MAKEING FOR NICE
SURPRISE.
MORE CLOUDS LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
PARTLY SUNNY.
OTHERWISE NICE QUIET AFTERNOON
AND TRAVELING REGIONALLY HERE.
BEACHES LOOK FANTASTIC.
ALWAYS BEAUTIFUL AT THE BEACH.
MOUN TAPS LOOK GREAT.
HITTING ROADWAYS AND WE'RENER
GOOD SHAPE.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO THE
AIRPORT AND DOING TRAVEL BY
AIR LATER TODAY MOST OF THE
COUNTRY IS VERY QUIET.
THERE'S A COUPLE LIGHT
FLURRIES NEAR HOME AHARKS
NEBRASKA, RAIN SHOWERS OUT AND
BIG CITIES IN THE WEST COAST.
THAT IS IT AS FAR AS ANY
TRAVEL IMPACTS WARM-WISE.
50 THIS AFTERNOON.
HERE'S THE 7 DAY.
WARMING UP INTO 50s.
THURSDAY AND DPRI.
SATURDAY MAYBE A RUN AT 60.
YOU CAN BELIEVE IT'S CHRISTMAS
TIME WITH THESE TEMPERATURES
AND RAIN SHOWERS ON SUPPOSED
AFTERNOON.
AND SURPRISED EVENING 60
DEGREES.
BUT, MOST OF THE NEXT COUPLE
DAYS LOOK GREAT.
OKAY.
STEVE OVER TO YOU.
>> THANKS, TUCK, THIS YEAR'S
WHITE HOUSE CHRISTMAS THEME IS
THE SPIT OF AMERICA AND IF YOU
LIKE THE CHRISTMAS ORNAMENTS
WITH HISTORY THE WHITE HOUSE
HISTORIC AL ASSOCIATION CAME
UP WITH ONE THIS YEAR THAT
COULD PUT YOU ON THE ROOFTOP.
"FOX5" TOM FITZGERALD EXP
EXPLAINS.
>>  MATT COSTELLO WITH THE
WHITE HOUSE HISTORICAL
ASSOCIATION HAPPY HOLIDAYS TO
YOU MATT AND WE'RE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT WHITE HOUSE
CHRISTMAS ORNAMENT FOR 20 19.
THIS YEAR YOU'RE RECOGNIZING
TWO THINGS.
MARINE ONE THE OFFICIAL
PRESIDENTIAL HELICOPTER AND
ONE FORMER PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES DWIGHT
EISENHOWER TELL US HOW YOU
SELECTED THIS.
>>  WE WENT WITH THE
HELICOPTER THIS YEAR BECAUSE
EISENHOWER WAS FIRST PRESIDENT
TO USE A HELICOPTER WHILE IN
OFFICE AND THIS DESIGN IS
ACTUALLY ACTUALLY MODELED OFF
TWO FLIGHT DETACHMENTS HE USED
ONE THROUGH UNITED STATES
MARINE CORPS AND ONE THROUGH
UNITED STATES ARMY.
>>  YOU HAVE MARKINGS ON THERE
THAT INDZ INDICATE THE
HELICOPTER THAT FLEW PRECEDENT
INZ HOUR AS OPPOSED TO OTHERS
FROM HISTORY.
>> WE PICKED TWO DESIGNS.
ONE SIDE FIVE STARS REPRESENT
RANKING AS GENERAL OF ARMY OF
UNITED STATES AND OTHER SIDE
PRESIDENTIAL SEAL.
>>  THESE HAVE BECOME OWE
HIGHLY COLLECTABLE AMONGST
PEOPLE THAT RAL UTHESE
ORNAMENTS.
MY MOTHER WAS ONE FOR YEARS.
WHY HAS THIS TAKEN ON A LIFE
OF ITS OWN TO GET THIS
CHRISTMAS ORNAMENT AND MAKE
SURE THIS IS HAS A PROMINENT
PLACE ON THEIR TREE.
>>  IT'S LIKE MANY COLLECT
TIBLS YOU START AND ONCE YOU
START YOU WANT TO GIFT MORE TO
FAMILY AND FRIENDS AND THEN
PRETTY SOON YOU'VE BEEN
COLLECTING THEM FOR YEARS AND
YOU HAVE ENOUGH TO FILL A
WHOLE TREE.
WE'VE HAD A NUMBER OF PEOPLE
CONTACT US AND TELL US ABOUT
HOW THEY'VE COLLECTED
ORNAMENTS FOR MANY YEARS AND
IN FACT JUST THE OTHER DAY WE
HAD SOMEBODY COME IN AND BUY A
COMPLETE SET.
>>  COMPLETE SET.
>>  AND THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON
SINCE 1981.
>>  YES.
>>  THAT'S A LOT OF CHRISTMAS
ORNAMENTS.
>>  YES, BUT YOU KNOW ANY TIME
WE SEE THAT IT RESONATE WITH
US.
THESE ORNAMENTS ARE NOT JUST
FOR CHRISTMAS THEY TELL
STORIES ABOUT PRESIDENTS AND
FIRST LADIES THAT LIVED THERE
AT ONE TIME.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HISTORICAL
ASSOCIATION TELLS THE STORY
NOT ONLY OF WHITE HOUSE BUT
UNITED STATES HISTORY
CONNECTSED WITH THIS BUILDING
AND THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
INHABIT TODAY THROUGH THE
DIFFERENT ADMINISTRATIONS.
HOW DO YOU CHOOSE THE SUBJECTS
FROM YEAR TO YEAR ABOUT WHAT
BECOMES THE ORNAMENT.
>>  SO WE MOVED SEQUENTIALLY
THROUGH THE PRESIDENTS.
THIS YEAR IT WAS EISENHOWER
NEXT YEAR JOHN F. KENNEDY.
THE ASSOCIATION PICKS THE
DESIGN THEY THINK BEST
REPRESENTS THE PRESIDENT'S
TIME IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
>>  HERE'S THE LITTLE KNOWN
FACT THAT YOU MIGHT NOT KNOW
HENCE THE LITTLE KNOWN FACT WE
ACTUALLY DEBUTED THAT ORNAMENT
WITH THE WHITE HOUSE
HISTORICAL ASSOCIATION MONTHS
AND MONTHS AND MONTHS AGO
BECAUSE THEY START WORKING ON
THESE A YEAR IN ADVANCE FOR
THE NEXT ONE.
YOU WOULDN'T THINK ABOUT THAT.
FIBLINGLY OUT FOR THE HOL
HOLIDAYS.
FULL DISCLOSURE I HAVE ONE ON
MY FREE RIGHT NOW I LOVE THE
WHITE HOUSE ORNAMENTS I
STARTED COLLECTING THEM THE
FIRST YEAR I TO D.C.
>> NICE LITTLE KEEPSAKE.
>>  BEAUTIFUL.
>> I'M ONE OF THOSE COLLECTS
TORE PEOPLE.
>>  WE ALL END UP BEING THOSE
PEOPLE.
>>  NOT THE WORST THING TO
COLLECT THOUGH RIGHT.
>>  U.S. OFFICIALS ON HIGH
ALERT THIS MORNING AFTER NORTH
KOREA SAID WE HAVE A CHRISTMAS
GIFT FOR YOU AND THAT IS NOT
SOMETHING YOU WANT TO SEE
UNDER THE TREE.
>>  PRESIDENT TRUMP IS SAYING
ABOUT THIS POTENTIAL THREAT
THAT STORY AFTER THE BREAK
♪
>>> 7:34.
WE ARE BACK WITH THE TOP STORIES
WE'RE FOLLOWING ON THIS
CHRISTMAS MORNING.
FIRST UP, BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
THE PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S START THERE WHERE POLICE
IN GREEN BELT ARE INVESTIGATING
UNFORTUNATELY A DEADLY CRASH ON
THIS CHRISTMAS MORNING.
POLICE SAY A DRIVER CRASHED INTO
A TREE ON KENILWORTH AVENUE NEAR
CALVERT ROAD AROUND 2:00 A.M.
THIS MORNING.
SOUTHBOUND KENILWORTH AVENUE IS
STILL CLOSED AS POLICE TRY TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT HAPPENED HERE TO
CAUSE THIS ACCIDENT.
STAY WITH FOX5 FOR UPDATES
THROUGHOUT THE MORNING.
>>> D.C. POLICE LOOKING FOR A
GUNMAN WHO SHOT THREE PEOPLE IN
SOUTHEAST YESTERDAY THOSE
VICTIMS TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL
BUT THEY ARE ALL EXPECTED TO
SURVIVE.
THIS HAPPENED YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON ON WHEELER ROAD.
NOW POLICE DO HAVE A DESCRIPTION
OF THE SHOOTER AND THE VEHICLE
HE WAS DRIVING.
THEY SAY THE MAN WAS WEARING A
GRAY AND BLACK HOODED SWEATSHIRT
AND DROVE AWAY IN A RED NISSAN
ROGUE WITH A SKI RACK ON TOP.
>>> TOWNHOUSE FIRE NEAR TYSONS
CORNER THAT KILLED A FAMILY'S
DOG IS BEING BLAMED ON A FAULTY
DISHWASHER.
THE APPLIANCE WAS LEFT RUNNING
WHEN THE FAMILY LEFT THEIR HOME
ON MEADOWS SPRINGS DRIVE
YESTERDAY MORNING.
THAT FIRE DAMAGED TWO UNITS BUT
FIREFIGHTERS PUT OUT THOSE
FLAMES PRETTY QUICKLY.
SADLY NOT QUICKLY ENOUGH FOR THE
DOG.
BUT THE RED CROSS IS HELPING
THOSE TWO FAMILIES OUT OF THEIR
HOMES THIS MORNING.
>>> 7:35.
LET'S GET BACK OVER TO
MR. BARNES.
THE TUCKER CLAUSE THE FORECAST
DELIVERING SOMETHING MAGICAL FOR
ALL OF US THIS HOLIDAY.
>> YES.
MY SANTA -- I WAS THINKING MORE
OF THE SUNRISE.
>> THAT'S PRETTY NICE, TOO.
>> I RECOGNIZE THAT SWEATER.
>> THAT, TOO.
COLLECTOR'S EDITION ALLISON.
>> UM-HMM.
>> BEAUTIFUL SUNRISE FOR YOUR
CHRISTMAS MORNING AND IT WILL BE
A, YOU KNOW WHAT VERY PLEASANT
AFTERNOON.
A FEW CLOUDS AROUND A LITTLE
COOL UPPER 40S BUT REALLY
COULDN'T ASK FOR NICER WEATHER
FOR OUR CHRISTMAS DAY.
32 DEGREES AT REAGAN NATIONAL
EARLY THIS MORNING MOST
EVERYBODY IN THE 20S.
SO DRESS ACCORDINGLY HERE IF
YOU'RE GOING OUT FOR QUICK WALK
BEFORE EVERYBODY GETS UP AND
OPENS PRESENTS.
33 IN NEW YORK CITY.
BOSTON 32 DEGREES.
SO AGAIN REGIONALLY WE'RE QUITE
COLD.
THERE'S THAT LIGHT HIGH THIN
CLOUD COVER TO START YOUR
MORNING.
GUESSING US A NICE SUNRISE.
THERE ARE VERY FEW WEATHER
FEATURES TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT
ACROSS THE MID ATLANTIC.
AND FOR US THAT MEANS ANOTHER
PLEASANT AFTERNOON A LITTLE ON
THE COOL SIDE UPPER 40S TO ABOUT
50 BUT TRAVELING VERY QUIET
WEATHER BOSTON, ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO FLORIDA.
FLORIDA IN MUCH BETTER SHAPE
AFTER COUPLE DAYS OF RAIN THEY
WARMED UP AND SUN BACK FOR BEACH
WEATHER.
CHICAGO LOOKS GOOD.
LITTLE RAIN OUT ALONG THE WEST
COAST LOOK AT THAT IN JUST A
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
HERE'S YOUR FORECAST FOR THIS
AFTERNOON.
50 DEGREES IF YOU'RE GOING OUT
TONIGHT TO DO A LITTLE CHRISTMAS
CAROLLING OR CELEBRATING WITH
FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
TEMPERATURES WILL BE IN THE 30S
LATER THIS EVENING, PARTLY
CLOUDY AND A LITTLE CHILLY OUT
THERE.
OKAY.
SEVEN DAY FORECAST COMING RIGHT
UP.
GUYS.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> 7:36 NOW.
IN THE MIDST OF THIS HOLIDAY
TRAVEL SEASON, NEW DOCUMENTS
PROVIDING MORE DETAILS ABOUT THE
SAFETY OF BOEING.
>> THE REPORT REVEALING
DANGEROUS REVELATIONS WE'LL
EXPLAIN THAT WHEN WE COME BACK.
IT IS NOW 7:37.
♪
♪♪
I'm Jimmy Dean
and ah mother nature sure
doesn't cut any corners
when she paints a
morning like that.
And we know there is no
shortcut to quality.
And that's why we
use nothing but
the very best sausage
that money can buy.
Paint yourself a
beautiful morning.
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
♪
>>> 7:39 ON THIS CHRISTMAS
MORNING.
IT'S THE HOLIDAYS YOU WANT TO BE
EXTRA GENEROUS THIS TIME OF YEAR
AND WITH CHRISTMAS AND HANUKKAH
THERE MIGHT BE MORE FOOD TO
ENJOY THAT YOU CAN PHYSICALLY
EAT.
PROBLEM IS A LOT OF PEOPLE WANT
TO SHARE IT WITH THEIR FOUR
LEGGED FRIENDS AND AS YOU CAN
SEE IT'S NOT ALWAYS THE BEST
IDEA.
AS MUCH AS WE HAVE GOOD
INTENTIONS.
>> THEY PUT ON THOSE PUPPY OR
KITTEN EYES WE CAN'T RESIST.
BUT NOW SOME PET ADVOCATES ARE
SHARING WHAT IS A CAUTIONARY
TALE ABOUT OVER INN JUUL OF
DILIGENCE FOR ALL OF US.
STEPHANIE RAMIREZ HAS MORE FROM
FALSE CHURCH.
>>> WE'RE AT THE LOT OF DOG AND
CAT RESCUE FOUNDATION IN FALLS
CHURCH, VIRGINIA WHERE
VOLUNTEERS TELL ME FEEDING TABLE
SCRAPS IN YOUR PETS THAT CAN
HELP LEAD TO ANIMAL OBESITY
INNOCENTS WHY THEY'RE ASKING
EVERYONE TO TAKE A GOOD LOOK AT
THE TWO PETS THEY'RE CARING FOR
NOW AND REMEMBER THEM AS YOU
SHARE YOUR HOLIDAY MEAL.
>> COME THIS WAY.
YOU'RE SO GOOD.
>> I JUST THOUGHT TO MYSELF
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF WORK CUT OUT
FOR US.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
NINE-YEAR-OLD OREO, A HOUND
SPANIEL MIX THAT'S SUPPOSED TO
WEIGH AROUND 40 POUNDS.
HE'S CLOSER TO DOUBLE THAT.
IF THIS CASE ISN'T SERIOUS
ENOUGH, VOLUNTEERS AT THE FALLS
CHURCH LOST DOG AND CAT RESCUE
DEALING WITH TWO MORBIDLY OBESE
ANIMALS THIS IS WILL FRED
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD MEDIUM HAIRED
CAT.
>> A LOT OF TIMES THIS SORT OF
OBESITY COMES FROM PLACE OF JUST
SORT OF MISPLACED LOVE, YOU
KNOW, WANTING TO -- CAT LIKES TO
EAT SO YOU KEEP GIVING MORE AND
MORE FOOD BECAUSE YOU KNOW THAT
THE CAT ENJOYS IT BUT AT SOME
POINT, UM, IT JUST BECOMES
DETRIMENTAL.
>> STAFF CARING FOR THESE TWO
ANIMALS ARE ASKING EVERYONE TO
THINK ABOUT THEM BEFORE YOU GIVE
YOUR PET TABLE SCRAPS AT YOUR
HOLIDAY DINNERS.
RESCUE VOLUNTEERS TELL US THEY
SEE AROUND 10 TO 12 OF THESE
CASES EACH YEAR, BUT HERE 11 AND
12 CAME IN JUST A FEW DAYS AGO.
IT'S NOT CLEAR HOW OREO AND WILL
FRED ENDED UP THIS WAY AND NOW
BEGINS THE DELICATE PROCESS OF
GETTING THEM TO SLIM DOWN.
>> WHILE YOU WANT AN OVERWEIGHT
CAT TO LOSE WEIGHT IT NEEDS TO
HAPPEN VERY VERY SLOW PACE.
>> IT'S TOUGH WHEN DOGS WEIGH
THIS MUCH BECAUSE IT PUTS AN
EXCESSIVE AMOUNT OF PRESSURE AND
STRESS ON THEIR JOINTS AND EVEN
ON THEIR PAWS.
SO FIND A DIFFERENT WAY I THINK
TO INTERACT WITH YOUR PET DURING
THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
SO EXTRA PLAY TIME, GET SOME
HOLIDAY THEMED TOYS.
>> I'M TOLD WILL FRED AND/OR YO
WERE LET GO AT A NORTHERN
VIRGINIA SHELTER.
I ASKED AROUND ABOUT CHARGES AND
WAS HARD TO CHARGE PET OWNERS IN
THESE SITUATIONS WHERE THEY GIVE
UP THE PET SO KIT GET THE CARE
THEY NEED.
NOW, AT THE SHELTER THE
SHELTER'S CONCERN IS GETTING
ANIMAL SAFETY INFORMATION OUT
THERE AND HELPING THESE TWO PETS
GET HEALTHIER SO THAT THEY CAN
BE ADOPTED.
IN FALLS CHURCH, STEPHANIE
RAMIREZ.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> AS TOUGH AS IT IS SOMETIMES
YOU JUST HAVE TO SAY NO.
>> OH, YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
>>> HOW IMPORTANT IS GOOD PROOF
READING?  YOU MIGHT WANT TO
ACCIDENT RESIDENTS OF MOBILE
COUNTY, ALABAMA.
>> WE'LL SHOW YOU THE BAD
SPELLING MISTAKE NOW ON DISPLAY
ON HUNDREDS OF TRASH BINS.
THAT'S COMING UP AFTER THE
BREAK.
♪
I'm LáDeia, and there's
more to me than HIV.
There's my career...
my cause...
and creating my dream home.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO is for
adults who are starting
HIV-1 treatment and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines dolutegravir
or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2 medicines
in 1 pill
to help you reach and
then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day
with food
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if you're
allergic to any of its
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,
liver problems, and
liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash and
other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,
including hepatitis B or C.
Don't use DOVATO if you plan
to become pregnant
or during the first 12
weeks of pregnancy
since one of its ingredients may
harm your unborn baby.
Your doctor should do a
pregnancy test
before starting DOVATO.
Use effective birth control
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache,
diarrhea, nausea, trouble
sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment
with DOVATO is right
for you.
SOME SPELLING MISTAKES ARE TOUGH
TO SEE BUT NOT THIS ONE.
MOBILE, ALABAMA IS VERY PROUD
APPARENTLY OF BEING A COUNTRY.
NOT A COUNTY.
10,000 TRASH BINS PRINTED WITH
MOBILE COUNTRY INSTEAD OF CO
COUNTY.
THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO SAY
OBVIOUSLY MOBILE COUNTY.
MISTAKE NOT THE FINE PRINT IT'S
IN THE LARGE LETTERS ON BOTH
SIDES OF THE BEG GRAY CANS.
CITY SAYS THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
REPLACE THE BINS EVEN WITH THE
SPELLING ERROR THAT WOULD BE TOO
EXPENSIVE SO CONGRATULATIONS.
CROSSROADS OF MOBILE COUNTRY.
>> I THINK IT WORKS.
IT'S WHEN WE SAY THIS IS SKINS
COUNTRY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN A LOT
WORSE.
>> PLAY IT THAT WAY.
>> MAYBE THEY DID IT ON PURPOSE,
STEVE.
>> MAYBE THEY DID.
>> YEAH.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS!
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> GOOD MORNING.
COLD START TO YOUR DAY.
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE 20S
LOOK AT ALL YOUR 20S EARLY THIS
MORNING.
DALE CITY 27.
FAIRFAX 27.
WALDORF BACK TO 25 THIS MORNING.
BOWIE 27.
32 HERE IN WASHINGTON.
THE WARM SPOT COLONIAL BEACH
GOOD MORNING, GUYS, FOR YOU
33 DEGREES.
LOOKING ALT REGIONAL
TEMPERATURES WANT TO THANK
EVERYBODY THAT WAS TWEETING ME
EARLIER THIS MORNING UP EARLY A
LOT OF PEOPLE GOING TO WORK.
HAGERSTOWN 29 DEGREES.
23 IN WINCHESTER.
COULDN'T BE A NICER START TO OUR
CHRISTMAS MORNING IN FACT WE'RE
FEATURING PARTLY TO MOSTLY SUNNY
CONDITIONS, AND A COOL
AFTERNOON.
BUT A COMFORTABLE AFTERNOON.
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING AT DAYTIME
HIGHS IN THE UPPER 40S TO ABOUT
50 LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
AND REGIONALLY HERE YOU CAN SEE
A -- THIS IS REALLY SUCH A NICE
QUIET FORECAST FOR OUR CHRISTMAS
DAY.
SO WE'RE LOOKING GREAT.
HITTING 95 COULDN'T ASK FOR
NICER CONDITIONS AS AGAIN WE
SHOULD PART TOLL MOSTLY SUNNY
AND QUITE AROUND HERE NOT ONLY
TODAY BUT THE NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS.
TRAVELING EASTERN HALF OF THE
COUNTRY NICE AND QUIET.
FLORIDA LOOKS GREAT.
BACK INTO BEACH WEATHER DOWN
THERE.
THE ONE I'LL CALL IT TROUBLE
SPOT I'M USING THAT LOOSELY
BECAUSE IT'S JUST RAIN SHOWER
ACTIVITY SEATTLE DOWN TOWARDS
LOS ANGELES GETTING SOME RAIN
SHOWERS.
UT-OH.
>> ARE YOU OKAY.
>> I'M GOING TO MAKE IT.
I'VE GOT THIS, ALLISON.
A FEW SNOW SHOWERS OUT TO THE
WEST.
FOR US, 50 THIS AFTERNOON.
BACK IN THE 50S THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY.
IT WILL BE CHILLY TONIGHT IF
YOU'RE GOING OUT AND THEN A NICE
WEEKEND TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
57 SATURDAY.
NEXT CHANCE FOR RAIN SUNDAY
AFTERNOON, GUYS.
SUNDAY AFTERNOON LINGERING INTO
MONDAY THAT WILL BE ALL RAIN.
NO MORE WINTER WEATHER 2019.
>> GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
♪
I HAVE A FEELING WE'LL MAKE IT
FOR UP WEATHER PEOPLE IN JANUARY
AND FEBRUARY.
FOR NOW WE'RE LOOKING GOOD.
7:47.
CONGRATULATIONS IN ORDER FOR
SIXTH GRADERS AT NAVY ELEMENTARY
IN FAIRFAX.
THE ROBOTICS TEAM WON THE STATE
COMPETITION.
THEY'RE GOING TO THE WORLD
COMPETITION NOW.
>> THEY SHOW OFF THEIR ROBOT IN
APRIL IN DETROIT.
PHOTOJOURNALIST NELSON JONES
CHECKED OUT THE TEAM'S WORK.
♪
>> THERE'S 555 TEAMS IN THE
REGIONALS.
OUT OF THOSE, 108 TEAMS MAKE IT
STATES AND OUT OF THOSE, THREE
MAKE IT TO WORLDS.
SO WE'RE ONE OF THE THREE.
>> YOU PUT THIS ATTACHMENT ON.
>> IT'S A MULTI CULL CULTURAL
TEAM.
>> ONE OF THE ROBOTS WE HAVE
IT'S CALLED CRANE.
IT'S BASICALLY WHEN YOU PUSH A
BLOCK AND LOWER THE BLOCK AND
STACK IT ON.
>> YES.
>> TODAY WE ARE SEWING THE SEEDS
FOR THEM ON HOW THEY CAN HELP
THE COMMUNITY WITH WHAT THEY
LEARN TOMORROW.
>> IT'S CALLED SAFETY FACTOR
WHICH IS HOW STABLE A BUILDING
CAN BE WHICH IS ANOTHER THING
WHICH YOU HAVE TO TEST IF YOU
HAVE AN EARTHQUAKE OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT IN YOUR AREA.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE VERY CAREFUL
WITH KNOCKING DOWN THE BEAMS
WITHOUT THE BUILDING FALLING.
YES!
>> KIND OF IT HAPPENS EVERY DAY.
TRAFFIC JAM WHERE YOU HAVE TO
LIFT UP A TRAFFIC JAM TO SOLVE
THE PROBLEM.
>> ONCE IT DETECTS THAT LINE
THAT'S UNDER 21 IT WILL START
FOLLOWING THE LINE.
>> WE STARTED LEARNING HOW TO
PROGRAM, HOW TO USE A COLOR
SENSOR AND BE ABLE TO USE THE
ROBOT TO PUSH BLOCKS IN OR LIFT
SOMETHING UP OR PUSH SOMETHING
OVER.
WE CAN HIT IT WITH OUR FLEXIBLE
HOSE THAT WE USE THAT WE ALWAYS
KEEP ON OUR ROBOT TO DO THAT
MISSION.
>> IT'S PRETTY FUN, BECAUSE
WE'RE A TEAM AND WE ALL KNOW
EACH OTHER SO IT'S REALLY GOOD
EXPERIENCE.
MANY.
>> IT'S SO MUCH FUN WITH THEM.
I'M REALLY PROUD.
>> GOT TO LOVE WHEN THE COACH IS
PROUD.
CONGRATULATIONS TO THEM.
>> WE'RE PROUD, TOO.
>> GOOD LUCK AT WO WORLDS.
>> THANK YOU NELSON.
NEW PHOTOJOURNALIST NELSON JO
JONES.
>> ACCORDING A HOUSE
INFRASTRUCTURE COMMITTEE IS
INVESTIGATING BOEING'S ON GOING
CRISIS.
SEATTLE TIMES REPORTS THE
DOCUMENTS INCLUDE COMMUNICATIONS
FROM A FORMER TEST PILOT WHO HAD
PREVIOUSLY REPORTED PROBLEMS
WITH THE PLANE'S FLIGHT CONTROL
SYSTEM.
THE SAME SYSTEM BLAMED FOR BOTH
OF THE DEADLY CRASHES INVOLVING
THOSE MAX JETS.
>>> FORMER AMAZON MANAGER
ACCUSING THE COMPANY OF
PRIORITIZING SPEEDY DELIVERIES
OVER SAFETY.
THE REPORT SAID AMAZON PASSED ON
IMPLEMENTING SAFETY TRAINING BUT
IGNORED COMPLAINTS THAT DRIVERS
WERE OVER WORKED.
RECENT DATA SHOWS DELIVERY
DRIVES WHO WORK FOR AMAZON
INVOLVED IN MORE THAN 60
ACCIDENTS RUTTING IN SERIOUS
INJURIES AND 13 DEATHS.
AMAZON DENIED THE ALLEGATIONS
SAYING "NOTHING IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN US THAN SAFETY".
>> LET'S GOAT A SWEET GIFT MASS
GIFT FOR WORLD WAR II VETERAN.
92-YEAR-OLD FLOYD SMITH LOST A
LARGE CHUNK OF HIS SAVINGS AFTER
LOANING $10,000 TO A MAN WHO HAD
DONE WINDOW WORK FOR HIM AT HIS
HOME.
SMITH CLAIMS THAT MAN MARK
GLIZER SAID HE WAS IN SERIOUS
FINANCIAL TROUBLE, BUT SMITH
NEVER RECEIVED ANY OF THE MONEY
BACK.
THE STORY GAINED STEAM ACROSS
CALIFORNIA AND BEYOND AND 374
PEOPLE DECIDED TO MAKE DONATIONS
TO HIM.
>> WE WANTED TO PRESENT THIS TO
YOU.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
WOW! HONEY, LOOK AT THIS.
$12,472 AND 60 CENTS.
LOOK AT THAT.
SO MANY GOOD PEOPLE IN THIS
WORLD.
I TELL YOU WHAT, GOD HAS HIS ARM
AROUND MY SHOULDERS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I LOVE THE
REACTION.
I LOVE THE GENEROSITY BUT IT
INFURIATES ME EVERY TIME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOU SEE SOMEBODY TAKING
ADVANTAGE ESPECIALLY OF OUR
OLDER POPULATION OUT THAT.
IT'S HAPPENED TO MY FAMILY.
I KNOW IT'S HAPPENED TO MANY
OTHER FAMILIES AND, YOU KNOW,
FOR ALL THE BAD PEOPLE OUT THERE
GET SOME CHRISTMAS SPIRIT,
PLEASE.
>>> THANK YOU TO THE GOOD
PEOPLE.
>> YES.
>> THEY'RE OUT THERE, TOO.
>> TIME NOW FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA
MCCARTHY.
BEFORE THE LATEST STAR WARS
INSTALLMENT WAS RECENTLY
RELEASED, FOX5'S KEVIN MCCARTHY,
I THINK YOU KNOW HIM GOT A SNEAK
PEEK AT THE MOVIE ALSO GOT A
CHANCE TO CATCH UP WITH THE
STARS AND THE CREATORS OF THE
MOVIE.
SO HERE'S SIT DOWN WITH ACTOR
JOHN BOYEGA.
>> I KNOW YOU'VE ALREADY TALKED
ABOUT THE SCRIPT STORIES A SILL
I DON'T KNOW TIMES.
IT'S AN AMAZING STORY BUT I DO
HAVE A GENUINE QUESTION ABOUT
IT.
>> WHEN I FIRST STARTED READING
ABOUT STAR WARS AND JJ I WAS
TOLD JJ WAS VERY SECURE ABOUT
THE SCRIPTS.
HONESTLY HE WOULDN'T LET PEOPLE
LEAVE WITH THEM.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DID IT GET TO YOUR HOUSE
LIKE WAS THAT -- ARE YOU ALLOWED
TO TAKE IT HOME.
>> THE PRACTICALITY OF HAVING TO
LEARN LINES FOR A MOVIE THAT'S
OVER TWO HOURS AND NOT BE BE
ABLE TO TAKE IT HOME WAS DUMB.
LUCAS REALIZED IT.
MAYBE THE ACTORS WOULD BE BETTER
ACTS IF THEY HAD A SCRIPT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT SEEMS REASONABLE.
>> SEEMS REASONABLE TO TAKE THE
SCRIPT HOME.
BUT I WAS MOVING.
I WAS MOVING.
>> RIGHT.
>> APARTMENTS AND WHILE LIKE G
GETTING TO THE LAST LEG OF
SHOOTING SO I WAS -- THERE WERE
ALL SORTS OF LAYERS AND DETAILS
TO THIS DAY THE MASSES DON'T
KNOW --
>> WHAT'S CRAZY I'M WONDER WERE
THEIR COPIES MADE?  HOW DO WE
EVEN -- IT'S A CRAZY STORY.
>> I THINK IF THERE WERE COPIES
MADE, WE WOULD HAVE FOUND OUT,
YEAH, WE WOULD HAVE FOUND OUT BY
NOW.
THEY MANAGED TO GET AT IT PRETTY
SOON, YOU KNOW, THANKFULLY IT
WAS LOST IN MORE SECURE
ENVIRONMENT A CLEANER CAME IN AT
THIS TIME.
NOW I'VE GOT EVERYONE SAYING,
YOU KNOW, WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE
YOUR FURNITURE AS WELL, MAN?
NOW I GOT TO EXPLAIN MY LEASE
DEAL TO YOU.
>> LET'S LOOK AT YOUR MORTGAGE.
CREDIT CARD STATEMENTS.
>> LOOK, THE SCRIPT IS BACK.
>> WHAT HAPPENED AFTER THAT ALL
WENT DOWN?  DID YOU GET LIKE
TALKED TO?  LIKE DID JJ -- I
MEAN WE'RE ADULTS BUT I MEAN
FEEL LIKE WHAT WAS THAT
CONVERSATION WITH JJ WHEN HE
FOUND OUT.
>> JJ WAS ACTUALLY COOL ABOUT
IT.
AS LONG AS WE GOT IT BACK,
THAT'S THE PRIORITY.
THEN WHAT HAPPENED?  WHEN THEY
FOUND OUT THEY WERE LIKE HMM,
ACTUALLY WHILE I WAS WORKING ON
STAR WARS, MY ACCOMMODATION, I
WAS MOVING FROM PLACE TO PLACE.
OF ONE KIND OF FIGURED THAT I
WAS LIKE, YOU KNOW, STRESSED OUT
WITH THE MOVE WHILE FILMING.
SO I FEEL LIKE THERE WAS A NICE
BIT OF EMPATHY.
I DIDN'T EVEN GET AN OFFICIAL
CALL.
>> JJ IS RIGHT DOWNSTAIRS.
>> NO, NOT? -- DON'T NEED TO BE
SCARED OF J.
YOU SAY JJ.
>> HE'S TOO NICE.
>> HOW DID FIN CHANGE YOU?  YOU
THINK ABOUT SOMEONE YOU PLAY FOR
THREE MASSIVE FILMS.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY ABOUT I
THINK I CHANGED FIN.
>> CAN YOU ELABORATE.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> THE CHARACTER CAN'T REALLY
CHANGE ME BECAUSE I I CREATE H
HIM.
I LITERALLY THINK HIM UP.
I FEEL LIKE WHATEVER CHANGES
HAPPEN WITH ME I ADD TO THE
CHARACTER, SO THE CHARACTER IS
MORE THE EXPRESSION AND GETS
MORE THE INFLUENCE THAN ME BEING
INFLUENCED BY THE CHARACTER.
>> WHAT'S AN ASPECT OF JOHN ON
SCREEN THAT I'D SEE?
>> I THINK AFTER WATCHING IT
YESTERDAY, HE'S MUCH MORE --
HE'S GROWN UP.
YEAH, SIGNED ON AT THE FILM AT,
WHAT, 23, AND NOW I'M 27 AND I'M
LIKE, THERE'S BEEN A TRANSITION
OF GROWTH.
JJ WAS SAYING IT, TOO.
WE WATCHED IT.
IN FORCE AWAKENS YOU WERE
BABIES.
I'M WATCHING YOU IN NINE WE SEE
HOW YOU HAVE GROWN AND THE
CONFIDENCE WE GET IN REAL LIVE
ACTUALLY INFLUENCES THE
CHARACTERS RATHER THAN THE
CHARACTERS INFLUENCING US.
>>> 7:55.
NO NEED FOR THE BIG LOUD WEATHER
NOISE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL DAY OUT THERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> GORGEOUS DAY.
>> TUCK IS IN A GREAT MOOD.
IT'S A HOLIDAY.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS!
>> GOT A LITTLE COFFEE COUGH.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M BETTER.
IN FACT I HAD COFFEE NOW.
I FEEL GREAT.
>> OKAY.
>> NEXT 15 MINUTES YOU'LL GET
THE BEST OF ME THEN I'LL FADE
FAST HERE FOR THE REST OF THE
MORNING.
>> THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
>> UPPER 20S AND LOW 30S OUT
THERE EARLY.
WE LOOK FANTASTIC FOR YOUR DAY
TODAY.
TRAVELING WE'RE NICE AND QUIET
THIS AFTERNOON.
IT WILL BE A COOL AFTERNOON BUT
A PLEASANT DAY AN DRY DAY FOR
US.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET ANY RAIN
TODAY.
DAYTIME HIGHS UPPER 40S MAYBE
WE'LL HIT 50 DEGREES HERE AT
REAGAN NATIONAL.
AGAIN NICE AFTERNOON FOR US.
I MENTIONED THE TRAVEL FORECAST
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
REALLY REALLY FINE CONDITIONS
FOR MUCH OF THE COUNTRY A COUPLE
SHOWERS ALONG THE WEST COAST.
HERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY FORECAST,
AND WE'RE KEEPING IT NICE AND
QUITE THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
THOSE OF US THAT ARE WORKING
CHRISTMAS DAY ARE LOOKING
FORWARD TO THE WEEKEND, AND
SATURDAY LOOKS GREAT.
57.
RAIN SHOWERS WILL RETURN ON
SUNDAY.
THAT'S OUR NEXT CHANCE FOR ANY
RAIN AROUND HERE SUNDAY INTO
MONDAY.
SO WE KEEP IT NICE AND QUITE THE
NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
IT WILL BE COOL THIS AFTERNOON
IF YOU'RE GOING OUT THIS EVENING
COLD AGAIN WITH OVERNIGHT LOWS
BACK NEAR FREEZING BY EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
GUYS THAT'S A WEATHER WRAP.
WE'LL SEE IN YOU A COUPLE OF
MINUTES.
BACK TO YOU.
>> TUCK, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
7:56.
AS WE GET CLOSER TO THE
8:00 O'CLOCK HOURS THE STARS
LINING FOR THE NBA MARQUIS
MATCHUPS HERE ON CHRISTMAS DAY.
LEBRON JAMES, ANTHONY DAVIS,
KAWHI LEONARD EXPECTED TO PLAY
TONIGHT.
>> JAMES AND DAVIS LEONARD SAT
OUT THE CLIPS LAST GAME.
CLIPPERS BEAT THE LAKERS ON
OPENING NIGHT WITHOUT GEORGE.
THAT COULD BE PRETTY GOOD
MATCHUP.
NBA IS CRACKING DOWN.
SUPER STARS YOU GOT TO PLAY IN
THE BIG GAMES.
TUCKER HAS A QUESTION, ALLISON.
PUT IT ON PAUSE.
YES, TALK.
>> WHO'S THE HOME TEAM IF IT'S
THE LAKERS VERSUS THE CLIPPERS.
>> THEY BOTH PLAY IN THE SAME
ARENA.
I WOULD HAVE TO CHECK THE
SCHEDULE TO SEE WHO THE HOME
TEAM IS.
>> IF YOU COULD GET THAT FOR ME
AFTERWARDS I'D APPRECIATE IT.
>> I'LL DO MY BEST.
>> SUPER PERSONALIZED NEWSCAST.
>> HE DOES NEED HELP FROM TIME
TO TIME.
>> HE DOES.
KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
MORNING.
>> MUCH MORE NEWS AND WEATHER
COMING UP 8:00 O'CLOCK.
WHICH IS IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
♪
>>> WELL, GOOD MORNING, MERRY
CHRISTMAS, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US ON THIS
WEDNESDAY MORNING, CHRISTMAS
MORNING.
8:00 O'CLOCK.
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>> I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR.
IT IS IN FACT WEDNESDAY,
DECEMBER 25th.
HERE'S-LOOK AT OXON HILL,
MARYLAND, WE WISH EVERYBODY
WATCHING AND UP AND ALL THAT
GOOD STUFF A VERY MERRY
CHRISTMAS TODAY.
LET'S GET A QUICK CHECK -- UT
UT-OH.
HE'S DONNING THE FEDORA.
>> LET'S GET A QUICK CHECK OF
YOUR FORECAST WITNESS ONE AND
ONLY TUCKER BARNES.
>> COLD TEMP TO START THE DAY.
YOU CAN SEE THAT LIVE SHOT.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL AND GET OUT AND
PLAY WITH YOUR CHRISTMAS
PRESENTS SHOULD BE A NICE DAY
FOR IT.
32 TO START YOUR MORNING AT
REAGAN NATIONAL.
LOTS OF 20S SO AGAIN LOTS OF
LEARS IF YOU'RE OUT EARLY.
I DON'T CALL IT MILD AFTERNOON
BUT COMFORTABLE AFTERNOON HIGHS
NEAR 50.
DETAILS ON TODAY'S FORECAST AND
WE'LL LOOK FORWARD FROM HERE IN
JUST A MOMENT, GUYS, BACK TO
YOU.
♪
>>> WE ARE FOLLOWING BREAKING
NEWS OVERNIGHT OUT OF PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY.
WHERE POLICE IN GREEN BELT OR
INVESTIGATE A DEADLY CRASH WHERE
A DRIVER CRASHED IN A TREE ON
KENILWORTH AVENUE NEAR CALVERT
ROAD.
JUST ABOUT SIX HOURS AGO ABOUT
2:00 O'CLOCK THIS MORNING.
POLICE ARE STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT EXACTLY WHAT HAP
HAPPENED.
>>> POLICE IN MARYLAND AND
VIRGINIA NOT THE ONLY ONES
WATCHING OUT FOR SPEEDERS AND
AGGRESSIVE DRIVERS SO IS SANTA
APPARENTLY.
>> FOX5'S AYESHA KAHN RIDING
AROUND ON THIS CHRISTMAS MORNING
WITH HOW PEOPLE BEHIND THE WHEEL
MAY NOTICE SOME UNUSUAL HIGHWAY
SIGNS BASICALLY A WARNING TO
DRIVERS TO AVOID GETTING ON THAT
NAUGHTY LIST.
AYESHA, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: YEAH, IT'S A
WARNING BUT IN A FRIENDLY WAY
JUST TO LET PEOPLE KNOW TO BE
CAUTIOUS AND BE CAREFUL WHILE
YOU'RE DRIVING ON THE ROADS.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S NOT AS BUSY ON
THE ROADS AS WE ARE TRAVELING ON
495 HEADING INTO VIRGINIA THIS
MORNING.
SO, YEAH, IT'S A BIT OF A SLOW
PACE.
BUT PEOPLE ARE TRACH OF TAKING
THEY ARE TIME.
I HAVEN'T NOTICED ANYTHING TOO
CRAZY ON THE ROADS, BUT, YOU
KNOW, WHILE THOSE SIGN THAT IS
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT ARE, YOU
KNOW, DEPICTING ALL THOSE
HIGHWAYS, THAT'S JUST A REMINDER
FOR PEOPLE TO, YES, LISTEN TO
BEING FRIENDLY BUT PLEASE BE
CAREFUL.
WE SAW ONE MUCH THOSE SIGNS NEAR
MILE MARKER 55 AT SEMINARY ROAD
IN VIRGINIA.
ONE OF THEM READING SANTA SEES
YOU WHEN YOU'RE SPEEDING.
YES, HE IS.
AND ANOTHER ONE WAS SEEN AS WE
WERE DRIVING BACK FROM VIRGINIA
INTO MARYLAND THAT ONE SAYS
DRIVING SAFELY IS MY FAVORITE.
WE ALSO LOOKED AT SOME NUMBERS
FROM THE NATIONAL HIGHWAY
ADMINISTRATION.
NOW DURING THE CHRISTMAS AND NEW
YEAR'S DAY HOLIDAY PERIODS IN
2018 ALONE, THERE WERE MORE
DRUNK DRIVING RELATED FATALITIES
THAN DURING ANY OTHER HOLIDAY
PERIOD THAT YEAR.
ALSO, LAST YEAR IN VIRGINIA MORE
THAN 7100 ALCOHOL RELATED
CRASHES THAT CLAIMED MORE THAN
270 LIVES AND INJURED MORE THAN
4400 MEN, WOMEN AND KIDS AND IN
MARYLAND SAME TIME LAST YEAR
MARYLAND STATE POLICE MADE 71DUI
ARRESTS.
36 DRUG RELATED ARRESTS.
TROOPERS ALSO ISSUED MORE THAN
5800 CITATIONS AND RESPONDED TO
MORE THAN 10,500 CALLS FOR
SERVICE.
COMING BACK OUT HERE LIFE AS
WE'RE CONTINUING TO TRAVEL ON
495 HEADING INTO HAVE A HAVE
KEEP IN MIND THAT STATE RAPPERS
BOTH IN VIRGINIA AND MARYLAND
ARE GOING TO BE OUT IN FULL
FORCE THEY'RE GOING TO BE
KEEPING AN EYE ON SPEEDERS AND
ANY AGGRESSIVE DRIVERS.
THEY ARE NOT PLAYING AROUND.
I DEFINITELY DID NOTICE A LOT OF
MORE LOCAL COPS ALSO DRIVING
AROUND SO YEAH THEY'RE OUT AND
THEY ARE LOOKING FOR YOU AND IF
IT'S NOT THEM, AS I SAID IT'S
GOING TO BE SANTA KEEPING AN EYE
ON ANYONE WHO IS BREAKING THE
LAW ON THE ROADS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> AYESHA, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BE SAFE OUT THERE.
IT IS 8:03 NOW.
D.C. POLICE LOOKING FOR A GUNMAN
WHO SHOT THREE PEOPLE IN
SOUTHWEST -- SOUTHEAST
WASHINGTON YESTERDAY.
THE VICTIMS TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
GOOD NEWS THEY ARE EXPECTED TO
BE OKAY.
THIS HAPPENED AROUND 1:00 P.M.
ON WHEELER ROAD.
POLICE DO HAVE A VAGUE
DESCRIPTION OF THE SHOOTER BUT
GOOD DESCRIPTION OF THE CAR HE
WAS DRIVING.
THEY SAY THE MAN WAS WEARING A
GRAY AND BLACK HOODED SWEATSHIRT
AND HE DROVE AWAY IN A RED
NISSAN ROGUE.
>> THE UPS STILL ON THE, THIEF
STILL ON THE LOOSE.
THEY STOLE A DELIVERY TRUCK
EARLIER THIS MONTH.
THIS IS VIDEO OF THE MEN WAITING
FOR THE DELIVERY DRIVER TO
RETURN TO HIS TRUCK ON 63rd
STREET NORTHEAST.
WHEN HE GOT BACK, THEY HURT THE
DRIVER, THEY STOLE FROM THE
DRIVE, THEN THEY STOLE THE TRUCK
THAT WAS FULL OF PACKAGES.
YOU RECOGNIZE THE SUSPECTS FROM
THIS VIDEO CALL POLICE.
THEY SAY THERE IS A REWARD
AVAILABLE.
>>> TOWNHOUSE FIRE NEAR TYSONS
CORNER KILLED A FAMILY'S DOG.
IT'S BEING BLAMED ON A FAULTY
DISHWASHER.
THE APPLIANCE LEFT RUNNING WHEN
THE FAMILY LEFT THEIR HOME THIS
WAS ON MEADOWS SPRINGS DRIVE
YESTERDAY MORNING.
THAT FIRE ENDED UP DAMAGING TWO
UNITS BUT FIREFIGHTERS WERE ABLE
TO PUT OUT THE FLAMES PRETTY
QUICKLY.
THE RED CROSS IS HELPING THOSE
TWO FAMILIES THAT WERE DISP
DISPLACED.
>>> HERE'S A REMINDER TO ALL OF
TO US HAVE WOR WORKING CAR CARBN
MONOXIDE DETECTORS SELF FAMILIES
IN NORTHWEST SAFE THANKS TO
NEIGHBOR WHO DISCOVERED
DANGEROUS LEVELS IN THEIR HOME.
THIS UNFOLDED YESTERDAY.
THE SEVEN-YEAR-OLD BOY WENT TO
THE HOSPITAL.
HE'S DOING OKAY, THOUGH, TODAY.
11 PEOPLE THOUGH BETWEEN THE
THREE HOMES WERE EVACUATED AND
TREATED.
FIREFIGHTERS SAY THE LEVEL OF
CARBON MONOXIDE WAS DANGEROUSLY
HIGH.
OLDER HOMES YOU CAN DETECT IT
UNLESS YOU HAVE THE ACTUAL
DEVICE.
SO FORTUNATELY OF THOSE THEE
HOMES, ONE OF THEM HIT.
>> RIGHT.
>> THEY WERE ABLE TO ALERT
EVERYBODY.
>>> BE CAREFUL.
>> I JUST HAD A THOUGHT.
WE MIGHT BE IN LIVING ROOMS
RIGHT NOW PEOPLE ARE OPENING
PRESENTS.
SO LET'S --
>> YOU THINK WE'RE ON IN THERE.
>> PICK THE BIG ONE UP.
>> S CHAT BIG ONE.
>> SHAKE IT UP.
>> THEN OPEN IT.
>> LISTEN FOR IT.
>> TAKE THE ONE IN THE BACK
CLOSER TO THE TRUNK OF THE TREE.
>> SOMETIMES SMALLER ONES ARE
GOOD.
>> SOME PEOPLE LIKE TO HIDE THE
GOOD STUFF IN THE BACK.
>> WHAT'S YOUR STRATEGY.
DO YOU GO FIRST AND FURIOUS OR
DO YOU WAIT?
>> NO.
PLEASE, MAYBE AT SOME POINT
TODAY IN THE NEXT THEE HOURS
THAT WE HAVE TOGETHER I'LL
EXPLAIN THE WHOLE FAMILY
TRADITION.
>> WHAT?
>> BUT, YES, IT WAS VERY SLOW
AND METHODICAL.
>> REALLY?
>> IT'S GOOD.
IN MY HOUSE, YOU DO ONE, F THERE
ARE FIVE PEOPLE SITTING.
>> EVERYBODY DOES ONE AT A TIME.
>> YOU DO NOT OPEN -- EVERYONE
GIVES THE ATTENTION TO THE ONE
PERSON.
>> WE DID THE SAME THING.
>> WE LIKE TO SPREAD IT OUT.
>> OUR FAMILIES ARE VERY SIM
SIMILAR.
>> MY STRATEGY WITH MY BROTHER
VERY QUICKLY I WOULD GET THERE
EARLY HIDE ONE, RIGHT, WE'D OPEN
THEM ALL I WOULD BE ALL WHOOP.
I HAD ONE MORE.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING YOU
WOULD DO.
>> IT IS A PAIN FOR MY FAMILY
BECAUSE WE EXCHANGE GIFTS UP
HERE AND I SAFE THOSE LAST FOR
WHEN EVERYBODY IS DONE, HERE'S
ONE FROM STEVE AND THEY'RE ALL
LIKE -- OKAY.
>> ABOUT YOUR GIFT, I HAVE TO
RUN ACROSS THE STREET.
I'M STILL WORKING ON IT.
>> DON'T SAFE THOSE GIFTS TO BE
THE MAIN A TRACTION THIS YEAR.
>> WHY?
>> THERE'S ALL SO GOOD.
>> MORE OF AN OPENING ACT.
>> LAST YEAR STEVE GOT ME A
WHOLE MR. ROGERS THEME.
>> STEVE IS GREAT GIFT GIVER.
>> YEAH.
>> BEAUTIFUL WEATHER, COLD
TEMPERATURES TO START YOUR DAY
IN THE 20S AND LOW 30S.
32 RIGHT NOW IN WASHINGTON BUT A
VERY QUIET AFTERNOON.
PARTLY TO MOSTLY SUNNY, AND DRY.
DAYTIME HIGHS UPPER 40S TO ABOUT
50.
SO YOU KNOW YOU GET NICE PULL
OVER YOU CAN WEAR IT LATER THIS
AFTERNOON ALTHOUGH YOU WANT THE
COAT THIS MORNING.
AND THERE'S YOUR OUTLOOK.
50 DEGREES AND SUN AND CLOUDS.
>> MORE SUN THAN CLOUDS BUT NICE
AFTERNOON.
SEVEN DAY COMING UP.
>> BEAUTIFUL GRAPHIC.
DID MIKE LEAVE THAT FOR YOU.
MIKE THOMAS.
>> I'VE BEEN WORKING HARD ON
THAT.
MIKE IS WITH HIS GRANDMA THIS
MORNING.
>> MIKE HAS THE BEST WRAPPINGS.
>> MAYBE DID HE HELP A LITTLE
BIT.
>> VERY NICE PRESENT FOR HIM TO
DO SO.
>> IT WAS.
>> THANKS, TUCK.
>> WEATHER TEAM FAMILY.
>>> ♪
>>> 8:07.
WELL IT'S BEEN SOME THREE MONTHS
SINCE THE LAST CONFIRMED
SIGHTING OF TWO IDAHO SIBLINGS
WAS REPORTED.
>> POLICE SAY THEY'RE NOT
GETTING MANY ANSWERS NOW FROM
THE PARENTS WHO ARE NOW A KEY
PART OF THE INVESTIGATION.
ERIN JOINS US NOW LIVE IN THE
NEWSROOM WITH THE LATEST.
WHAT'S HAPPENING, ERIN.
>> STEVE AND ALLISON MUCH OF THE
FOCUS IS ON THE MOTHER AS WELL
AS THE STEPFATHER.
POLICE SAY THEY'RE NOT
CONSIDERED SUSPECTS BUT THEY ARE
PERSONS OF INTEREST IN THIS
INVESTIGATION.
THIS JOSHUA JJ VAL LOW AND
TILELY RILEY.
AUTISTIC SEVEN-YEAR-OLD AND
SEVEN-YEAR-OLD SISTER ARE
MISSING FROM THEIR HOME.
POLICE SAY THEY MAY BE IN
SERIOUS DANGER.
LORI AND CHAD ARE NOT CONSIDERED
SUSPECTS BUT PERSONS OF INT
INTEREST.
THE TWO HAVE BEEN LESS THAN
COOPERATIVE REFUSING TO REVEAL
THE CHILDREN'S LOCATION.
THEY GAVE FALSE STATEMENTS ABOUT
THE KIDS WHEREABOUTS AND PACKED
UP AND LEFT.
>> THEY ABRUPTLY MOVED FROM
THEIR RESIDENCE HERE.
LIKE WE SAID WE'VE GOTTEN THE
RUN AROUND FROM THEM.
HEY, WE JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THOSE CHILDREN ARE OKAY.
>> ACCORDING TO RELATIVES
46-YEAR-OLD LORI CHANGED AFTER
SHE MET DAY BELL.
HE'S PART OF AN OFF SHOOT OF THE
LDS CHURCH THE GROUP KNOWN AS
PREP PERS SEW FOCUSED ON NEAR
DEATH EXPERIENCES AND PREPARING
FOR THE END OF DAYS.
INVESTIGATORS ARE ALSO
REVISITING THE DEATHS OF THEIR
FORMER SPOUSES.
LORI VAL LOWES HUSBAND WAS
FATALLY SHOT BY HER BROTHER
WHO'S ALSO NOW DECEASED.
CHAD DAY BELL'S WIFE DIED IN
OCTOBER ALLEGEDLY OF NATURAL
CAUSES A FEW WEEKS BEFORE HE
MARRIED LORI.
INITIALLY OFFICIALS THOUGHT SHE
DIED IN HER SLEEP AT AGE 49.
BUT NOW THEY'VE EXHUMED HER BODY
FOR AN AUTOPSY.
POLICE BELIEVE HER DEATH IS
RELATED TO THE KIDS
DISAPPEARANCE ALTHOUGH THEY HAVE
NOT SAID HOW.
RIGHT NOW POLICE SAY NEITHER VAL
LOW NOR DAYBELL ARE CONSIDERED
SUSPECTS IN THE DEATHS OF THEIR
FORMER SPOUSES BUT THEY'RE
TRYING TO LOCATE THE COUPLE AND
THEIR CHILDREN.
GUYS?
>> BIZARRE CASE.
ERIN, THANK YOU.
>>> OTHER NEWS NOW 8:09.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE KEEPING A
CLOSE EYE ON NORTH KOREA TODAY
BECAUSE KIM JONG UN THREATENS TO
DELIVER A CHRISTMAS PRESENT TO
THE US.
SOME SPECULATE KIM WILL TEST A
LONG RANGE MISSILE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THE US WILL
RESPOND IF KIM TAKES ANY
PROVOCATIVE ACTION.
BOTH COUNTRIES HAD BEEN
NEGOTIATING FOR NORTH KOREA TO
DENUCLEARIZE BUT WITH THE
PRESIDENCY UP FOR ELECTION NEXT
YEAR, THAT SEEMS TO BE OFF THE
TABLE FOR NOW.
>>> RUSSIAN PRESIDENT VLADIMIR
PUTIN SAYS HIS COUNTRY IS
LEADING THE WORLD IN A NEW CLASS
OF WEAPONS.
HE SAYS RUSSIA IS THE ONLY
COUNTRY RECEIPT NOW WITH S
SO-CALLED HYPER SONIC WEAPONS
THAT CAN REPORTEDLY TRAVEL UP TO
20 TIMES THE SPEED OF SOUND.
AND EFFECTIVELY MAKE CURRENT
DEFENSIVE MISSILE SHIELDS
OBSOLETE.
UNITED STATES HAS BEEN WORKING
ON HYPER SONIC WEAPONS MUCH ITS
OWN.
DEFENSE SECRETARY SAID EARLIER
IN AUGUST IT MIGHT BE A COUPLE
OF YEARS OFF, THOUGH.
>>> SEVERAL PEOPLE INJURED AFTER
A HELICOPTER MADE A ROUGH
EMERGENCY LANDING IN RUSSIA
OVERNIGHT.
OFFICIALS SAY THERE WERE 21
MEMBERS ON BOARD.
THE HELICOPTER REPORTEDLY GOT
CAUGHT IN A SNOWSTORM SOON.
AFTER TAKING OFF TOPPLED OVER
ONCE IT LANDED IT INJURED 15
PASSENGERS AND CREW.
THEIR CONDITIONS ARE UNKNOWN.
>>> A CHRISTMAS SURPRISE IN
BETTER NEWS TO OUR US TROOPS
OVERSEAS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
THIS IS OPERATION HOLIDAY
EXPRESS.
TRAVELING BY HELICOPTER ACROSS
PARTS OF SYRIA HANDING OUT GIFTS
TO THE MEN HARD-WORKING MEN AND
WOMEN IN UNIFORM.
STATIONED THERE FOR THE HOLIDAYS
AND THE GUEST GIVING WAS DONE TO
FESTIVE TUNES PLAYED BY THE
MILITARY BAND ACCOMPANYING
OFFICIALS ON THEIR SURPRISE T
TRIP.
>> AS AMERICANS CELEBRATE
CHRISTMAS MOST OFFICERS AND
BUSINESSES WILL BE CLOSED THAT
INCLUDES BANKS, SCHOOLS AND
FEDERAL OFFICES.
NATIONAL PARKS AND U.S.
FINANCIAL MARKS ALSO CLOSED
TODAY.
IF YOU NEED LAST MINUTE GIFTS OR
GROCERY ITEMS, YOU ARE NOT
COMPLETELY OUT OF LUCK BUT YOUR
OPTIONS ARE CERTAINLY LIMITED.
MANY MAJOR RETAILERS ARE CLOSED
INCLUDING WALMART, TARGET AND
BEST BUY, CVS WALGREENS AND
CONVENIENT STORE CHAINS WILL
HOWEVER BE OPEN.
I'M A MATH NERD, ALLISON.
20 TIMES THE SPEED OF SOUND FOR
THE RUSSIAN HYPER SONIC WEAPONS
ABOUT 15,000 MILES AN HOUR.
>> OKAY.
LOOK FORWARD TO A DAY IN THAT
SONG WHERE THERE ARE NO MORE
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> YEAH.
>> AMAZON RAISE TO BUILD A FAST
DELIVERY NETWORK BEING CALLED
OUT BY ONE OF THE COMPANY'S
FORMER MANAGERS.
>> WE'LL TELL YOU SOME OF THE
DANGEROUS FINDINGS OF A NEW
REPORT.
THAT'S NEXT.
8:12.
♪
♪♪
8:14.
IN BEING A SANTA CLAUS HELPER
CAN BE A MONEY MAKER DURING THE
HOLIDAYS A LOT OF FOLKS LIKE TO
HELP OUT SANTA OBVIOUSLY CAN'T
BE EVERYWHERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> SEASONAL RETAIL WORKERS FOR
THE MOST PART MAKE ABOUT 11
BUCKS AN HOUR.
A SANTA'S HELPER, THOUGH, CAN
EASILY MAKE BETWEEN 30 AND $75
AN HOUR.
THAT MEANS THAT THE REAL LIFE
SANTA HELPERS IF YOU WORK A LOT
OF HOURS IN A SHORT AMOUNT OF
TIME OVER THE HOLIDAY SEASON
COULD MAKE UP TO $20,000.
>> THESE GUYS PUT ON A GOOD
SHOW.
THEY REALLY DO.
THEY EARN EVERY PENNY IT.
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY IF YOU
GREW OUT A BEARD YOU MIGHT BE
ABLE TO PULL IT OFF.
WOULD YOU THINK ABOUT IT?
>> NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I WON.
>> NO.
I DON'T NEED THE MONEY.
I WON.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I DON'T NEED THE MONEY.
>> IT'S NOT WORTH IT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> NO.
>> IT'S NOT WORTH IT?
IT WOULD BE -- IT WOULD BE FUN
>> NO.
BUT I DON'T THINK I'D WANT TO DO
IT WOULD BE -- IT WOULD BE FUN
IT FOR 30 DAYS.
BUT I DON'T THINK I'D WANT TO DO
>> THERE IS THE REAL --
IT FOR 30 DAYS.
>> I THINK THAT MIGHT BE SANTA..
>> THERE IS THE REAL --
I THINK THAT'S SANTA GOT A
>> I THINK THAT MIGHT BE SANTA..
LITTLE MAKEOVER WORKED ON IT
I THINK THAT'S SANTA GOT A
EARLIER THIS YEAR.
LITTLE MAKEOVER WORKED ON IT
I DO TOO.
EARLIER THIS YEAR.
>> LITTLE TRIM BACK, HAD THE
I DO TOO.
ROSY CHEEKS.
>> LITTLE TRIM BACK, HAD THE
>> CHECKING ON HIS HELPERS.
ROSY CHEEKS.
>> DENYING THE FACT HE HAS TO DO
>> CHECKING ON HIS HELPERS.
THE WORK.
>> DENYING THE FACT HE HAS TO DO
I THINK THAT MIGHT ACTUALLY BE
THE WORK.
SANTA.
I THINK THAT MIGHT ACTUALLY BE
>> THE NERVOUS LAUGH.
SANTA.
>> MORE MONEY YOU WORK CHRISTMAS
>> THE NERVOUS LAUGH.
DAY AND CHRISTMAS DAY -- EVE AND
>> MORE MONEY YOU WORK CHRISTMAS
CHRISTMAS DAY.
DAY AND CHRISTMAS DAY -- EVE AND
>> TUCK THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN THE
CHRISTMAS DAY.
REAL DEAL.
>> TUCK THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN THE
>> HE LOOKED A LOT LIKE HIM.
REAL DEAL.
>> ROSY CHEEKS GAVE LIMB AWAY.
>> HE LOOKED A LOT LIKE HIM.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
>> ROSY CHEEKS GAVE LIMB AWAY.
>> ANY WAY.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
>> I NEED YOUR HELP WITH
>> ANY WAY.
SOMETHING, GUYS.
>> I NEED YOUR HELP WITH
>> WE'RE HERE TO SERVE.
SOMETHING, GUYS.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> WE'RE HERE TO SERVE.
IT APPEARS TO ME ON THIS SWEATER
>> OKAY, GOOD.
THEY IMPOSED SANTA'S FACE ON MY
IT APPEARS TO ME ON THIS SWEATER
BODY AND I WANT TO RECOUP
THEY IMPOSED SANTA'S FACE ON MY
ROYALTIES FOR THAT.
BODY AND I WANT TO RECOUP
>> YOU SHOULD GO FOR IT.
ROYALTIES FOR THAT.
>> HOW DO I GET THAT?
>> YOU SHOULD GO FOR IT.
>> I SHOULD GET SOMETHING 40,
>> HOW DO I GET THAT?
RIGHT.
>> I SHOULD GET SOMETHING 40,
>> YOU NEED TO CONTACT A LAWYER
RIGHT.
FIRST AND FOR MOST.
>> YOU NEED TO CONTACT A LAWYER
>> DON'T ENCOURAGE BECAUSE HE
FIRST AND FOR MOST.
WILL ACTUALLY DISROBE TO PROVE
>> DON'T ENCOURAGE BECAUSE HE
THAT IS HIS BODY.
WILL ACTUALLY DISROBE TO PROVE
>> I NEED TO CHECK THE BICEPS
THAT IS HIS BODY.
OUT.
>> I NEED TO CHECK THE BICEPS
>> HE'S TRYING TO GO WITH THIS.
OUT.
>> OH, HE WANTS AN INVITATION.
>> HE'S TRYING TO GO WITH THIS.
>> HOW ARE YOUR GLUTES LOOKING.
>> OH, HE WANTS AN INVITATION.
>> THERE YOU GO AND THERE IT IS.
>> HOW ARE YOUR GLUTES LOOKING.
>> I'LL SHOW YOU AFTER THE SHOW.
>> THERE YOU GO AND THERE IT IS.
>> THAT'S TOO MUCH.
>> I'LL SHOW YOU AFTER THE SHOW.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
>> THAT'S TOO MUCH.
>> I'M USED TO IT.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
>> I'M LOSING IT.
>> I'M USED TO IT.
32 IN WASHINGTON.
>> I'M LOSING IT.
UPPER 20S AND LOW 30S OUT THERE
32 IN WASHINGTON.
EARLY.
UPPER 20S AND LOW 30S OUT THERE
COLD ENOUGH THAT YOU'LL WANT THE
EARLY.
JACKET OR NICE SANTA SWEATER
COLD ENOUGH THAT YOU'LL WANT THE
WHEN YOU HEAD OUT THIS MORNING.
JACKET OR NICE SANTA SWEATER
WHAT ARE WE FEATURING TODAY?
WHEN YOU HEAD OUT THIS MORNING.
WE'RE FEATURING DAYTIME HIGHS IN
WHAT ARE WE FEATURING TODAY?
THE UPPER 40S TO ABOUT 50, AND
WE'RE FEATURING DAYTIME HIGHS IN
QUITE COMFORTABLE CONDITIONS
THE UPPER 40S TO ABOUT 50, AND
ACROSS THE REGION WE'LL SEE SOME
QUITE COMFORTABLE CONDITIONS
CLOUDS THIS AFTERNOON BUT NOT
ACROSS THE REGION WE'LL SEE SOME
EXPECTING ANY RAIN AND NO WINTER
CLOUDS THIS AFTERNOON BUT NOT
WEATHER ON THE HORIZON HERE.
EXPECTING ANY RAIN AND NO WINTER
NICE QUIET AFTERNOON FOR US.
WEATHER ON THE HORIZON HERE.
OFF TO NICE START BEAUTIFUL
NICE QUIET AFTERNOON FOR US.
SUNRISE OUT THERE EARLY.
OFF TO NICE START BEAUTIFUL
AND AGAIN JUST A FEW CLOUDS
SUNRISE OUT THERE EARLY.
EXPECTED THIS AFTERNOON AS WE'RE
AND AGAIN JUST A FEW CLOUDS
LOOKING AT HIGH PRESSURE
EXPECTED THIS AFTERNOON AS WE'RE
OVERHEAD AND THERE'S NOT A LOT
LOOKING AT HIGH PRESSURE
HAPPENING WEATHER WISE ACROSS
OVERHEAD AND THERE'S NOT A LOT
MOST OF THE UNITED STATES.
HAPPENING WEATHER WISE ACROSS
YOU GO TO THE GET UP TO ALASKA
MOST OF THE UNITED STATES.
TO FINAL THE REAL CRAZY WEATHER
YOU GO TO THE GET UP TO ALASKA
TEMPERATURES ARE GOING TO BE
TO FINAL THE REAL CRAZY WEATHER
RUNNING 30, 40 DEGREES BELOW
TEMPERATURES ARE GOING TO BE
NORMAL.
RUNNING 30, 40 DEGREES BELOW
SOME PARTS OF ALASKA OVER THE
NORMAL.
NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS MINUS 40S.
SOME PARTS OF ALASKA OVER THE
MINUS 50 POTENTIALLY.
NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS MINUS 40S.
THAT IS SOME COLD OFF TO THE
MINUS 50 POTENTIALLY.
NORTH AND WEST.
THAT IS SOME COLD OFF TO THE
NOT THAT BAD FOR US.
NORTH AND WEST.
AS WE'LL KEEP TEMPERATURES ABOVE
NOT THAT BAD FOR US.
NORMAL.
AS WE'LL KEEP TEMPERATURES ABOVE
50 THIS AFTERNOON AND THEN WE'LL
NORMAL.
HAVE A NICE STREAK GOING INTO
50 THIS AFTERNOON AND THEN WE'LL
THE END OF THE WEEK.
HAVE A NICE STREAK GOING INTO
INTO THE MID 50S ON FRIDAY, AND
THE END OF THE WEEK.
APPROACHING 60 DEGREES BY THE
INTO THE MID 50S ON FRIDAY, AND
WEEKEND.
APPROACHING 60 DEGREES BY THE
RAIN SHOWERS SUNDAY AFTERNOON
WEEKEND.
INTO MONDAY, GUYS.
RAIN SHOWERS SUNDAY AFTERNOON
ALLISON, BACK TO YOU.
INTO MONDAY, GUYS.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
ALLISON, BACK TO YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>>> A NORTHERN VIRGINIA PAINTER
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IS SHARING HER ART INSPIRING
>>> A NORTHERN VIRGINIA PAINTER
OTHERS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
IS SHARING HER ART INSPIRING
FOX5 PHOTOJOURNALIST STEVE
OTHERS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
WILLIAMS INTRODUCE US TO HER.
FOX5 PHOTOJOURNALIST STEVE
>> ♪
WILLIAMS INTRODUCE US TO HER.
>>> I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS
>> ♪
FOR LIKE 10 MONTHS.
>>> I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS
EVERYONE IN MY FAMILY KNOWS THE
FOR LIKE 10 MONTHS.
PICTURE THAT I'M TRYING TO PA
EVERYONE IN MY FAMILY KNOWS THE
PAINT.
PICTURE THAT I'M TRYING TO PA
I LIKE GETTING THESE BLOND OR
PAINT.
LIGHT STREAKS.
I LIKE GETTING THESE BLOND OR
IT'S ONE THAT I LOVE OF HER.
LIGHT STREAKS.
MY NAME IS PAGE CROUCH AND I'VE
IT'S ONE THAT I LOVE OF HER.
BEEN PAINTING FOR 14 YEARS.
MY NAME IS PAGE CROUCH AND I'VE
WHILE I GET MOST OF MY
BEEN PAINTING FOR 14 YEARS.
INSPIRATION FROM PHOTOS THAT I
WHILE I GET MOST OF MY
GET FROM FRIENDS OR RELATIVES,
INSPIRATION FROM PHOTOS THAT I
YOU KNOW, THE MORE YOU DO
GET FROM FRIENDS OR RELATIVES,
SOMETHING, THE BETTER YOU GET.
YOU KNOW, THE MORE YOU DO
THIS IS MY MOM WHEN SHE WAS IN
SOMETHING, THE BETTER YOU GET.
HER 20S.
THIS IS MY MOM WHEN SHE WAS IN
SHE'S 89 NOW.
HER 20S.
I'M GOING NEED SOME OF THE WHITE
SHE'S 89 NOW.
AND A LITTLE BLACK.
I'M GOING NEED SOME OF THE WHITE
POUR A LITTLE ON TOP.
AND A LITTLE BLACK.
MY BIGGEST CHALLENGE IS BLENDING
POUR A LITTLE ON TOP.
PAINT, UM, BEING ABLE TO
MY BIGGEST CHALLENGE IS BLENDING
DESCRIBE TO PEOPLE WHAT I NEED,
PAINT, UM, BEING ABLE TO
WHAT I WANT, HOW MUCH, WHEN I
DESCRIBE TO PEOPLE WHAT I NEED,
HAD MY ACCIDENT, EVERYTHING
WHAT I WANT, HOW MUCH, WHEN I
CHANGED.
HAD MY ACCIDENT, EVERYTHING
SINCE THEN, I HAVE BEEN TRYING
CHANGED.
TO FIND WAYS TO BE INDEPENDENT.
SINCE THEN, I HAVE BEEN TRYING
>> BRING IT OVER.
TO FIND WAYS TO BE INDEPENDENT.
I'LL GET UNDER.
>> BRING IT OVER.
>> WANTEED TO SOMETHING THAT
I'LL GET UNDER.
WOULD BE JUST ME INDEPENDENT,
>> WANTEED TO SOMETHING THAT
YOU KNOW.
WOULD BE JUST ME INDEPENDENT,
I HAD HEARD ABOUT DIFFERENT
YOU KNOW.
MOUTH ARTISTS AND I STARTED WITH
I HAD HEARD ABOUT DIFFERENT
THIS HAND SPLINT AND I PUT A
MOUTH ARTISTS AND I STARTED WITH
BRUSH IN IT AND I COULD DO
THIS HAND SPLINT AND I PUT A
STROKES AND IT LOOK ADD LITTLE
BRUSH IN IT AND I COULD DO
LIKE IMPRESSIONISM BUT IT WASN'T
STROKES AND IT LOOK ADD LITTLE
VERY GOOD.
LIKE IMPRESSIONISM BUT IT WASN'T
MY ASSISTANT PUT A BRUSH IN MY
VERY GOOD.
MOUTH AND IT WAS MORE PURPOSEFUL
MY ASSISTANT PUT A BRUSH IN MY
AND I STARTED DOING IT MORE AND
MOUTH AND IT WAS MORE PURPOSEFUL
MORE AND APPLIED TO THE MOUTH
AND I STARTED DOING IT MORE AND
AND FOOT PAINTING ARTIST, THEY
MORE AND APPLIED TO THE MOUTH
CEMENTED ME AS A STUDENT AND
AND FOOT PAINTING ARTIST, THEY
I'VE BEEN PAINTING WITH THEM FOR
CEMENTED ME AS A STUDENT AND
13 YEARS.
I'VE BEEN PAINTING WITH THEM FOR
WHAT I'VE GOT NOW IS WAY MORE
13 YEARS.
THAN WHAT GOT ME INTO IT.
WHAT I'VE GOT NOW IS WAY MORE
I ONLY DECIDED TO DO THE
THAN WHAT GOT ME INTO IT.
DEMONSTRATIONS WORKSHOPS LIKE
I ONLY DECIDED TO DO THE
MAYBE FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN
DEMONSTRATIONS WORKSHOPS LIKE
YEARS AFTER I STARTED PAINTING.
MAYBE FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN
BUT I WANTED TO GET OUT THERE
YEARS AFTER I STARTED PAINTING.
AND DO SOMETHING THAT WOULD
BUT I WANTED TO GET OUT THERE
INSPIRE ME AS WELL BUT HOPEFULLY
AND DO SOMETHING THAT WOULD
GIVE AND EXPIRATION TO PEOPLE.
INSPIRE ME AS WELL BUT HOPEFULLY
THEY SEE I'M PARALYZED FROM THE
GIVE AND EXPIRATION TO PEOPLE.
CHEST DOWN AND DOING IT AND I
THEY SEE I'M PARALYZED FROM THE
THINK -- I THINK IT INSPIRES AND
CHEST DOWN AND DOING IT AND I
GIVES PEOPLE HOPE.
THINK -- I THINK IT INSPIRES AND
>> GOOD FOR HER.
GIVES PEOPLE HOPE.
I MEAN CAN YOU IMAGINE.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> NO.
I MEAN CAN YOU IMAGINE.
>> BUT THE FACT THAT SHE'S BEEN
>> NO.
ABLE TO ADAPT HER TALENT NOW IN
>> BUT THE FACT THAT SHE'S BEEN
THE DIFFERENT WAYS AND SHE TRIED
ABLE TO ADAPT HER TALENT NOW IN
IT WITH HER HANDS, THAT DIDN'T
THE DIFFERENT WAYS AND SHE TRIED
WORK.
IT WITH HER HANDS, THAT DIDN'T
SHE WENT WITH THE MOUTH PEACE
WORK.
AND --
SHE WENT WITH THE MOUTH PEACE
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND --
>> CONTINUES TO WORK.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HONORING HER MOM AT THE SAME
>> CONTINUES TO WORK.
TIME.
HONORING HER MOM AT THE SAME
>> WHAT A LOVELY PICTURE.
TIME.
ALL RIGHTY.
>> WHAT A LOVELY PICTURE.
>> THANK YOU, STEVE.
ALL RIGHTY.
>> GOOD STORY, STEVE.
>> THANK YOU, STEVE.
>>> PRESIDENTIAL HOPEFUL MICHAEL
>> GOOD STORY, STEVE.
BLOOMBERG SAYS HIS CAMPAIGN USED
>>> PRESIDENTIAL HOPEFUL MICHAEL
INMATES TO HELP SWAY VOTER.
BLOOMBERG SAYS HIS CAMPAIGN USED
>> COMING UP WHAT THE FORMER NEW
INMATES TO HELP SWAY VOTER.
YORK MAYOR CESTUS TIPPED HIM OFF
>> COMING UP WHAT THE FORMER NEW
ABOUT THE PRISON LABOR MUCH IT'S
YORK MAYOR CESTUS TIPPED HIM OFF
8:21.
ABOUT THE PRISON LABOR MUCH IT'S
♪
8:21.
♪♪
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
Nature's Bounty.
Does scrubbing grease feel like
a workout?
Scrub less with Dawn Ultra.
It's superior grease-cleaning
formula gets to work faster.
Making easy work of tough
messes.
Dawn takes care of tough grease,
wherever it shows up.
Scrub Less, Save More...
with Dawn.
I'm Jimmy Dean and thank you
very much for lettin'
us become just a little
part of your holiday.
And we sincerely hope
that Jimmy Dean sausage
might make your holiday just
a little bit brighter.
Happy Holiday to ya.
8:24 RIGHT NOW.
ROUGH CONDITIONS EXPECTED IN
RETURN TO PARTS OF AUSTRALIAN
THIS WEEKEND THE DEALS WITH
DEADLY WILDFIRES.
OFFICIALS SAY MORE THAN
12 MILLION ACRES OF LAND BURNED
OVER THE PAST FEW MONTHS.
NINE PEOPLE HAVE BEEN KILLED.
HUNDREDS OF HOMES DESTROYED BY
THE FLAMES.
THE NEW SOUTH WALES -- IN NEW
SOUTH WALES THE COUNTRY'S MOST
POPULOUS STATE EXPERIENCED THE
MAJORITY OF THE DAMAGE SEEING A
LITTLE COOLER CONDITIONS ON
CHRISTMAS DAY.
BUT HIGH TEMPERATURES ARE SET TO
RETURN SOME PLACES WELL OVER 10.
♪
HOW DO YOU DO CHRIST MACE AT 10.
>> HAVE YOU EVER DONE CHRISTMAS
IN FLORIDA.
>> I HAVE.
>> IT TAKES A LITTLE GET USED
TO.
>> YOU SEE SANTA HATS THAT THE
BEACH A LOT OF WHITE LIGHTS ON
PALM TREES WHICH IS PRETTY BUT
SOMETHING DOESN'T QUITE FEEL THE
SAME.
>> I AGREE.
THOUGHTS, ALLISON.
>> NO.
>> I'M FILLING TIME RIGHT NOW.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> 32 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
WE'RE OFF TO BEAUTIFUL START.
ALTHOUGH A CHILLY START.
CERTAINLY NOT GOING TO BE 100
AROUND HERE LATER THIS AFTERNOON
WE'LL BE COMFORTABLE UPPER 40S
TO ABOUT 50 A LITTLE LATER TO
TODAY.
AND THAT'S AFTER A VERY CHILLY
OVERNIGHT.
MOST OF THE REGION HERE IN THE
MID 20S EARLY.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST A FEW CLOUDS TO START YOUR
DAY.
AND GUESS WHAT?  THE WEATHER
COULD NOT BE QUIETER.
I DON'T THINK THEY'LL BE ANY
COMPLAINING AS I KNOW A LOT OF
YOU ARE GOING TO BE OUT ON THE
ROADWAYS LATER DRIVING OFF TO
FRIENDS HOUSES OR GRANDMA'S
HOUSE FOR CHRISTMAS DINNER AND
IT LOOKS ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL.
AGAIN DAYTIME HIGHS UPPER 40S
MAYBE WE'LL HIT A 50-DEGREE
TEMPERATURE FOR PARTS OF THE
AREA LITTLE LATER TODAY WITH NO
RAIN EXPECTED NO STORMINESS
EXPECTED UNTIL PERHAPS THIS
WEEKEND I THINK SUNDAY AFTERNOON
AND MONDAY OUR NEXT CHANCE FOR A
LITTLE RAIN.
HERE'S BIGGER PICTURE GOING TO
THE AIRPORT DOING AIR TRAVEL
MOST OF THE COUNTRY FAIRLY
QUIET.
THE EXCEPTION IS THE BIG CITIES
ON THE WEST COAST GETTING SOME
RAIN SHOWERS.
SEATTLE DOWN TOWARDS SAN
FRANCISCO AND LOS ANGELES A FEW
RAIN SHOWERS.
EVEN THAT STORM IS NOT TERRIBLY
STRONG.
OKAY.
50 THIS AFTERNOON THEN GRADUALLY
WARMING IT UP INTO THE MID 50S
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY.
MAYBE UPPER 50S BY SATURDAY AND
COULD WE DO 60 DEGREES YES, WE
COULD SUNDAY WITH RAIN SHOWERS.
SO KEEPING IT VERY MILD TO END
2019 BUT BEAUTIFUL CHRISTMAS
AFTERNOON.
GET OUT AND ENJOY, GUYS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> FORMER AMAZON MANAGER
ACCUSING THE COMPANY OF
PRIORITIZING SPEEDY DELIVERIES
OVER SAFETY.
THE REPORT SAYS AMAZON DECLINED
TO IMPLEMENT SAFETY TRAINING AND
IGNORED COMPLAINTS THAT DRIVERS
WERE OVER WORKED.
RECENT DATA SHOWS DELIVERY
DRIVERS WHO WORK FOR AMAZON WERE
INVOLVED IN MORE THAN 60
ACCIDENTS RESULTING IN SERIOUS
INJURIES AND 13 DEATHS.
AMAZON DENIED THE ALLEGATIONS
SAYING QUOTE NOTHING IS MORE
IMPORTANT TO US THAN SAFETY.
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE MICHAEL BLOOMBERG
CUTTING TIES WITH THE CONTRACTOR
WHO USED PRISONERS TO HELP
WITNESS CAMPAIGN.
INTER SETTLEMENT REPORTED
BLOOMBERG'S CAMPAIGN CONTRACT
ADD NEW JERSEY BASED CALL CENTER
COMPANY.
NOW THAT COMPANY USED INMATES IN
OKLAHOMA TO MAKE CALLS ON BEHALF
OF THE BILLIONAIRE'S
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
FORMER NEW YORK MAYOR SAID HE
WAS UNAWARE IT WAS HAPPENING.
WHEN HE FOUND OUT, THEY SEVERED
THE TIES.
HIS CAMPAIGN WILL PROPERLY VET
SOME SUBCONTRACTORS MOVING
FORWARD.
>>> FORMER PRESIDENT BARACK
OBAMA HAS BEEN REPORTEDLY
PRIVATELY PRAISING PRESIDENTIAL
HOPEFUL SENATOR ELIZABETH WA
WARREN.
THE HILL REPORTS THAT PRESIDENT
OBAMA HAS BEEN TALKING UP WARREN
IN CONVERSATIONS WITH DONORS WHO
ARE HESITANT TO SUPPORT A
CANDIDATE RUNNING CAMPAIGN
CRITICAL OF WALL STREET AND
AMERICA'S BILLIONAIRE CLASS.
♪
>>> THAT DOES IT FOR US FOR
RIGHT NOW.
8:30.
BUT WE HAVE A LOT MORE NEWS AND
WEATHER COMING UP AT 9:00.
>> GOING TO TAKE A QUICK SHORT
BREAK FROM OUR COVERAGE RIGHT
NOW AND SHOW YOU SOME GREAT
STORIES.
I HOPE EVERYBODY IS HAVING A
MERRY CHRISTMAS AND WE WILL SEE
YOU RIGHT BACK HERE FOR GOOD DAY
D.C. AT THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT 9:00 O'CLOCK.
>> GET A CUP OF COFFEE, STEVE.