DEGREES, 39 IN WASHINGTON, 38 IN
MANASSAS, 37 AT DULLES, 36 IN
WINCHESTER AND 39 IN CULPEPER.
WINDS ARE STARTING TO DIMINISH A
BIT, WE HAD BITTER WIND CHILLS
EARLY THIS MORNING BUT RIGHT NOW
WIND SPEEDS ABOUT FIVE TO TEN
MILES AN HOUR THAT GIVES YOU A
WIND CHILL, FEELS LIKE 33 IN THE
DISTRICT, 32 IN BALTIMORE AND
FEELS LIKE 32 IN FREDERICK 30 IN
HAGERSTOWN BUT I THINK THE WIND
WILL BECOME LESS AND LESS OF AN
ISSUE AS WE GO THROUGH TONIGHT
IT'S JUST STRAIGHT UP COLD.
TOMORROW AFTERNOON IS WHEN YOU
START TO FEEL A BIT OF A
WARM-UP.
QUIET OUT THERE TODAY, SATELLITE
AND RADAR NOTHING TO SHOW AND
YOU PROBABLY MISSED IT
COMPLETELY.
SLEPT THROUGH IT.
BUT SNOW FLURRIES LAST NIGHT
SHORTLY AFTER MIDNIGHT
REGISTERED AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
SO WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?  WE HAVE
NOW OFFICIALLY HAD A TRACE OF
SNOW HERE IN DC IN FEBRUARY
PREVENTING YOU FROM HAVING A
COMPLETELY SNOWLESS FEBRUARY.
SO YES, THOSE FLURRIES TOWNSHIP
MIDNIGHT AND 1:00 A.M. LAST
NIGHT COUNTED ALTHOUGH IT DID
NOT FOR DULLES AND BWI.
THEY DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING, THAT
WAS THE LAST TIME WE SAW FLAKES
SINCE YELLOW AND BLUE 18TH.
I CANNOT PROMISE WE'LL SEA VERY
SEE ANYMORE THIS WINTER.
NOTHING IN THE FORECAST.
TONIGHT STRAIGHT COLD, 37 BY
NINE, 33.
FALL BELOW FREEZING QUICKLY.
IF YOU'RE UP EARLY AND THINGS
GOING ON WITH THE KIDS, BRIGHT
SUNSHINE BUT COLD, TEMPERATURES
IN THE 20S MAYBE EVEN TEENS
NORTH AND WEST.
THERE WILL BE A WARM-UP LATER ON
IN THE AFTERNOON, SAME THING FOR
SUNDAY.
WE HAVE A LOOK AT THAT FULL
WEEKEND FORECAST STILL AHEAD.
BLAKE?
>>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
WE NOW HAVE BREAKING NEWS FROM
NEW YORK CITY.
THE JURY DELIBERATING THE FATE
OF DISGRACED MOVIE MOGUL HARVEY
WEINSTEIN HAS NOW FINISHED ITS
WORK FOR DAY.
EARLIER THIS AFTERNOON THE PANEL
TOLD THE JUDGE IT HAS REACHED A
PARTIAL VERDICT.
THE JURY SAYS IT IS REACHED A
UNANIMOUS DECISION ON THREE OF
THE FIVE SEXUAL ASSAULT CHARGES
FACING WEINSTEIN.
THE JURY REMAINS DEADLOCKED
THOUGH ON THE TWO MORE SERIOUS
CHARGES OF PREDATORY SEXUAL
ASSAULT.
THE JUDGE INITIALLY TOLD THE
JURY TO KEEP WORKING BUT AFTER
HALF AN HOUR THE JUDGE DID
DISMISS THE JURY FOR THE DAY AND
WE ARE TOLD THEY WILL BE DONE
FOR THE WEEKEND AND WILL RESUME
ON MONDAY.
>> AND ALSO ANOTHER BREAKING
STORY WE'RE FOLLOWING CLOSELY,
THREE TEEN-AGERS ARE NOW IN
CUSTODY AND CHARGED WITH
MURDERING A 17 YEAR OLD IN
CHARLES COUNTY MARYLAND.
BRADLEY BROWN DIED OUTSIDE OF
HIS HOUSE ON BRYANS ROAD TUESDAY
NIGHT.
SHERIFF DEPUTIES ARRESTED ONE
TEEN ON WEDNESDAY BUT THE TWO
OTHER ARRESTS CAME WITHIN THE
PAST 24 HOURS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THAT BROWN'S
DEATH WAS A RESULT OF A ROBBERY
GONE BAD.
COURT DOCUMENTS SAYING THAT
BROWN WAS SELLING THC VAPING
CARTRIDGES, SHERIFFS DEPUTY
RECOVERED SOME STOLEN FERN
BROWN.
HE WAS THE SON OF A PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY HOMICIDE
DETECTIVE.
>>> WHAT STARTED OFF AS A FEW
JABS IN IOWA HAS TURNED INTO
FULL BLOWN PUNCHES IN NEVADA,
THE DEMOCRATS RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT ARE FIGHTING FOR VOTES
IN THE STATE ONE DAY AHEAD OF
THE ALL IMPORTANT CAUCUSES
THERE.
SOME ARE WARNING OF POTENTIAL
CHAOS IN THE NEVADA CAUCUSES
EVEN THOUGH THEY DECIDED TO
SCRAP THE FAULTY APP USED IN
IOWA.
STILL THE IOWA DEMOCRATIC PARTY
HAS TOLD CAUCUS WORKERS NOT TO
MAKE EARLY PLANS TOMORROW FOR,
THE NEVADA CAUCUS PARTY BECAUSE
THEY EXPECT THE RESULTS TO COME
OUT LATE.
>> WE KNOW PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
CAMPAIGNING OUT WEST TODAY, AND
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATE MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG APPARENTLY SEES THAT
AS A PRIME OPPORTUNITY TO TROLL
HIM.
TAKE A LOOK FOR YOURSELF.
BLOOMBERG'S CAMPAIGN HAD
BILLBOARDS PUT UP IN PHOENIX AND
LAS VEGAS IN HIGH VISIBILITY
AREAS SHOULD SOMEONE GLANCE OUT
OF THE WINDOW NEAR THE VEGAS
STRIP THEY MAY SEE A BILLBOARD
READING DONALD TRUMP CHEATS AT
GOLF OR DONALD TRUMP EATS BURNT
STEAK.
>> IN DC SOME ARE RAISING AN
EYEBROW TO WHAT'S GOING ON
NATIONALLY ON THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL.
THEY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH DC
MAYOR MURIEL BOWSER DEFENDING
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG ON STOP AND
FRISK.
FOX5 STEPHANIE RAMIREZ IS
OUTSIDE OF POLICE HEADQUARTERS
WHERE SOME SAY DC POLICE ARE
STILL CARRYING OUT THIS
CONTROVERSIAL PRACTICE.
STEPHANIE, AND MAYOR BOWSER HAS
TIED HERSELF VERY CLOSELY WITH
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG IN THIS
ELECTION.
>> REPORTER: YEAH, BLAKE.
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT IT.
STOP AND FRISK IS A PRACTICE
WHERE POLICE CAN STOP A PERSON
WHERE, IF THEY'RE SUSPECTED OF
COMMITTING A CRIME OR POSSIBLY
ABOUT TO DO SO POLICE CAN STOP
THEM AND FRISK THEM AS WELL
THAT'S WHY IT'S CALLED THAT.
COMMUNITY ACTIVIST SAY THIS IS A
PRACTICE THAT TARGETS AND
TERRORIZES COMMUNITIES OF COLOR.
HERE IN DC, THERE IS NO OFFICIAL
STOP AND FRISK PROGRAM, BUT THE
DCACLU SAYS THERE IS A SIMILAR
THING, THEY SAY DC POLICE DO
JUMP OUTS AND THIS IS A SIMILAR
PRACTICE.
AND, IN FACT, IT IS THE DC
ACLU'S EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR WHO IS
RAISING THAT EYEBROW AT DC'S
MAYOR MURIEL BOWSER.
THE EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR, SHE HAS
AN ISSUE WITH BOWSER DEFENDING
MAYOR BLOOMBERG ON CONTROVERSIAL
STOPS AND THIS HAS TO DO WITH
THAT HISTORY THIS DC.
THE DC ACLU HAD SUED THE BOWSER
ADMINISTRATION TRYING TO GET
POLICE TO RELEASE IMPORTANT DC
POLICE STOP INFORMATION THAT THE
DEPARTMENT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
COLLECTING UNDER THE NEAR ACT.
THIS WAS A LAW ENACTED IN 2016,
THAT WAS A LAW PASSED TO PROMOTE
PUBLIC SAFETY.
NOW, WE DID TALK WITH THE MAYOR
AND THE DC ACLU ON THIS TODAY.
I CAN TELL YOU, THOUGH, IN 2019,
POLICE DID RELEASE IMPORTANT
STOP DATA THAT LOOKED AT A
4-WEEK PERIOD.
SO THIS WAS A SNAP SHOT.
IN THAT SNAP SHOT THEY SHOWED
THE INFORMATION ON THE MORE THAN
11,SIX00 STOPS THAT WERE MADE
AND IN PART OF THAT INFORMATION
THEY ALSO SHOWED A LITTLE BIT OF
A DISPARITY HERE ACTUALLY,
SIGNIFICANT DISPARITY.
IT SAID THAT 70% OF THE PEOPLE
STOPPED DURING THAT TIME WERE
BLACK COMPARED TO AROUND 15% WHO
WERE WHITE.
AND THIS IS WHEN THE POPULATION
IN THE CITY IS AROUND 46% BLACK
AND AROUND 37% WHITE.
SO, YES, THE DISPARITY THERE.
BUT THEY AGAIN SAY THIS IS A
SNAP SHOT.
WE'RE TOLD MORE DATA IS GOING TO
BE RELEASED IN SIX MONTHS.
SO WE'RE SUPPOSED TO SEE THAT
NEW INFORMATION IN MARCH.
BLAKE?
>> ALL RIGHT, STEPHANIE RAMIREZ
LIVE FOR US.
THANK YOU, STEPHANIE.
>> AND SPEAKING OF THE ELECTION,
WHEN YOU'RE BROWSING YOUTUBE
COME NOVEMBER PREPARE TO SEE A
LOT OF ADS FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN HAS
REPORTEDLY PURCHASED THE HIGH
PROFILE ADVERTISING SPOT.
THE DEAL MEANS ADS FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL BE FEATURED
PROMINENTLY ON THE VIDEO SHARING
SIGHT'S HOME PAGE IN THE DAYS
LEADING UP TO ELECTION DAY.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE BROWSE
YOUTUBE EVERY DAY AND ACCORDING
TO PUGH RESEARCH CENTER ABOUT
THREE QUARTER OF US ADULTS SAY
THEY ACTUALLY USE THE SITE AND
PR ESTIMATES THE AD SPACE COSTS
ABOUT $1 MILLION A DAY.
>>> WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON THIS
JOHN HOPKINS MAP TRACKING THE
LATEST ON CORONAVIRUS CASES.
THERE ARE NOW MORE THAN 2200
DEATHS, YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE
DEATHS HERE, AND THE TOTAL
NUMBER OF CONFIRMED CASES IS NOW
NEARING 77,000.
YOU CAN SEE ALMOST ALL OF THEM
ARE STILL IN CHINA, BUT THERE IS
A BIG NEW DISCOVERY IN SOUTH
KOREA TODAY.
SEE THIS CIRCLE?  IT'S GETTING
BIGGER.
MORE THAN 200 CASES WERE
DISCOVERED THERE.
THAT'S ALMOST DOUBLE THE NUMBER
FROM YESTERDAY.
MEANTIME, THERE IS STILL A LOT
OF ATTENTION THAT CRUISE SHIP
DOCKED IN JAPAN.
TWO PEOPLE HAVE DIED, MORE THAN
600 CASES HAVE BEEN CONFIRMED
TERE.
11 OF THE 13 AMERICANS WHO WERE
EVACUATED FROM THE SHIP, THEY'RE
NOW UNDER QUARANTINE IN NEVADA
BUT 11 OUT OF 13 HAVE NOW TESTED
POSITIVE FOR THE VIRUS.
HEALTH LEADERS IN THE U.S. SAY
THE INFECTED ARE SHOWING MILD OR
NO SYMPTOMS.
THAT BRINGS THE TOTAL NUMBER OF
U.S. CASES NOW TO 26.
>>> PEOPLE UNTIL THE PHILIPPINES
ARE BEING EXTRA CAREFUL.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS WEDDING.
THEY'RE ALL WEARING FACE MASKS.
A WEDDING CEREMONY ON THURSDAY
HAD EVERYONE WEAR THEIR MASKS.
THE VIRUS HAS LED TO AT LEAST
ONE DEATH IN THE PHILIPPINES AND
INFECTED AT LEAST TWO OTHERS.
IN SOME COUNTRIES THOUGH LIKE
THIS, THEY'RE CONCERNED THAT THE
IMPACT, THE VIRUS OUTBREAK, MAY
BE MUCH BIGGER BECAUSE THE
OFFICIAL NUMBERS ARE ONLY WHAT'S
REPORTED BY THE HEALTH
DEPARTMENTS IN THESE INDIVIDUALS
COUNTRIES.
ANGIE?
>> THANK YOU, BLAKE.
>>> WELL, DEVELOPING IN VIRGINIA
RIGHT NOW LAWMAKERS WANT A STUDY
DONE TO SEE IF METRO'S BLUE LINE
CAN EXTEND THROUGH FAIRFAX INTO
PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY.
THIS IS A STUDY THAT'S GOING TO
COST ABOUT $2 MILLION.
IT'S CURRENTLY A DIRECTIVE IN
THE STATE'S PROPOSED BUDGET.
NOW, IF THE STUDY IS INCLUDED IN
THAT BUDGET, IT WOULD EXPLORE
THE COST OF EXTENDING THE LINE
SOME 15 MILES TO PORT BELL ROAR,
LORTON, POTOMAC MILLS AND MARINE
CORPS BASE QUANTICO.
>>> SOME TOP CAUGHT ON CAMERA
MOMENTS NOW, JAIL BREAK GONE
WRONG.
I'D SAY.
A WOMAN TRIED TO SNEAK OUT OF AN
OHIO JAIL BY CLIMBING INTO THE
CEILING OF A WAITING ROOM.
YOU DID SEE IT DIDN'T WORK.
THE CEILING GAVE WAY.
SHE CAME CRASHING DOWN INTO THE
ARMS OF GUARDS WHO WERE WAITING
FOR HER.
THE WOMAN WAS BEING HELD FOR
KIDNAPPING AND ASSAULTING AN
ELDERLY MAN.
>>> WELL, A BIG STORM HITTING
ENGLAND CAUSED BIG PROBLEMS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY INCLUDING
HERE IN HERE FORD WHERE
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS COULD ONLY
WATCH AS A DRIVER WENT RIGHT
INTO THE FLOOD WATERS.
IT HAPPENED LAST WEEK, BUT SOME
ROADS STILL REMAIN CLOSED
BECAUSE OF THE EXCESSIVE
RAINFALL OUT THAT WAY.
THE JOURNALIST WHO SHOT THIS
VIDEO POSTED A FOLLOW-UP
REPORTING THAT RESCUE CREWS WERE
ABLE TO GET EVERYBODY SAFELY OUT
OF THAT VEHICLE.
>> IF YOU HAPPENED TO WATCH THE
BASKETBALL GAME LAST NIGHT, THE
WARRIORS LOST TO THE ROCKETS BY
30 POINTS BUT IT WAS THIS MOMENT
THAT SOCIAL MEDIA JUST CAN'T GET
ENOUGH OF.
ONE OF THE WARRIOR'S TOWEL GUYS
FOUND HIMSELF IN A PRECARIOUS
POSITION WHEN A PLAYER GOT A
QUICK STEAL WHEN HE WAS WIPING
DOWN THE COURT.
LUCKILY DISASTER WAS AERT HAVED
AND HE GOT OFF THE COURT JUST IN
THE NICK OF TIME.
>> OH.
AND HE MADE THE BASKET.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS ALL GOOD.
OKAY.
EXACTLY WHAT YOU WANT TO SEE IF
YOU GO FOR A WALK IN YOUR
NEIGHBORHOOD, RIGHT?  THE BEAR
ROAMING AROUND MONROVIA
CALIFORNIA THIS MORNING.
LOOK AT THIS GUY.
IT SPENT ITS TIME MOVING BETWEEN
HOUSES AND NOBODY WAS HURT.
WILDLIFE OFFICIALS EVENTUALLY
TRANQUILIZED THE BEAR AND MOVED
IT OUT OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT IS STILL UNCLEAR RIGHT NOW IF
THIS IS THE SAME BEAR SPOTTED
ROAMING THE AREA LAST NIGHT.
THE NEIGHBORHOOD BEAR.
>> I HOPE HE DOESN'T KEEP COMING
BACK BECAUSE THEN THEY HAVE TO
TAKE MORE DRASTIC MEASURES.
>> HE WASN'T BOTHERING ANYONE.
>> FOR NOW.
>> GO HOME.
>> BEARS CAN'T JUST ROAM
NEIGHBORHOODS FOREVER AND NOT
BOTHER ANYONE.
>> CAN YOU SEE HOW BIG IT IS
THOUGH.
>> CELEBRITIES AROUND THE WORLD
ARE RALLYING AROUND A YOUNG BOY
WHOSE BULLYING VIDEO IS GOING
VIRAL.
>> PLUS FIND OUT WHY HOCKEY STAR
ALEXANDER OVECHKIN HAD A RUN IN
WITH THE FAIRFAX COUNTY FIRE
DEPARTMENT.
>> LIVE LOOK AT TRAFFIC AROUND
THE DMV AS RUSH HOURS RAMPS UP
ON THIS FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
♪
NOON.
♪♪
We made USAA Insurance for
members like Martin.
An Air Force veteran made of
doing what's right,
not what's easy.
So when a hailstorm hit, USAA
reached out
before he could even inspect the
damage.
That's how you do it right.
USAA insurance is made just the
way Martin's family needs it -
with hassle-free claims, he got
paid before
his neighbor even got started.
Because doing right by our
members, that's what's right.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK.
STARS AROUND THE WORLD ARE
RALLYING AROUND A BULLIED BOY IN
AUSTRALIA WHO WAS BORN WITH A
FORM OF DWARFISM.
HIS STORY WENT VIRAL AFTER HIS
MOTHER POSTED THIS VIDEO OF HIM
IN TEARS OVER THE KIDS BULLYING
HIM AT SCHOOL.
THE VIDEO STRUCK A NERVE WITH
SEVERAL CELEBRITIES WHO ARE NOW
RETAILING AROUND KAYDEN
INCLUDING HUGH JACK MAN WHO
WROTE A MESSAGE SAYING KAYDEN
YOU ARE STRONGER THAN YOU KNOW
MATE.
IT ALSO CAUGHT THE EYE OF BRAD
WILLIAMS WHO WAS BORN WITH A
FORM OF DWARFISM.
HE SET UP A GOFUNDME FOR THE BOY
FOR THEM TO GO TO DISNEY LAND
WHICH HAS RAISED $358,000.
WE'LL HAVE MORE COMING UP ON TMZ
IN THE NEXT HALF HOUR.
>> I HAVEN'T WATCHED IT.
I SAW THE STILL SHOT AND I KNEW
I COULDN'T HANDLE IT.
>> BREAKS YOUR HEART.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE US
WOMEN'S NATIONAL TEAM FIGHT FOR
EQUAL PAY.
THAT CONTINUES.
PLAYERS ARE SEEKING MORE THAN
$66 MILLION IN BACK PAY AS PART
OF THEIR GENDER DISCRIMINATION
LAWSUIT AGAINST THE US SOCCER
FEDERATION.
THE PLAYERS SUED THE FEDERATION
LAST MARCH OVER THE PAID
DIFFERENCES BETWEEN THE MEN'S
AND WOMEN'S TEAMS.
THE FEDERATIONS ARGUE THAT THE
PAY STRUCTURE FOR THE TWO TEAMS
IS DIFFERENT T JUDGE HAS SET A
TRIAL DATE OF MAY 5TH UNLESS THE
TWO PARTIES CAN COME TO AN
AGREEMENT.
>> WOW, THEY JUST KEEP THIS
GOING.
IT'S IMPRESSIVE.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
LET GO.
>> AND THEY KEEP GETTING
PROMISES AND A LITTLE LIP
SERVICE IF YOU WILL FROM THE
U.S. FEDERATION AND EVERY TIME
THEY'RE GIVEN SOMETHING, THEY
SAY NO, THIS IS WHAT WE ARE
DEMANDING AND NOT GOING TO
ACCEPT ANYTHING LESS.
>> I DON'T THINK AN AGREEMENT IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
I THINK THEY KEEP PUSHING
FORWARD WITH THIS.
>>> THE SLUMP IS OVER ALEXANDER
OVECHKIN ENDING THE LONGEST
NON-SCORING DROUGHT OF HIS
CAREER WITH HIS 41ST GOAL OF THE
SEASON AGAINST THE MONT TROLL
CANADIANS.
HE NOTCHED HIS 699TH CAREER
GOAL.
OF COURSE THAT'S ONE GOAL FROM
THE EXCLUSIVE 700 CLUB WHICH
INCLUDES JUST SEVEN PLAYERS.
DESPITE THE CAREER MILESTONE FOR
OVECHKIN THE CAPS LOST GELLING
FALLING 4-3 IN OVERTIME.
>> MAN.
>>> SINCE WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
OVY THE CAPS STAR TOOK TIME TO
VISIT WITH FAIRFAX FIRE AND
RESCUE CREWS.
THEY WERE ON A FALSE ALARM CALL
AND OVECHKIN CAME OVER.
FIRE FIGHTERS SAID HE WAS NEXT
DOOR AND WANTED TO MAKE SURE ALL
WAS WELL WITH THE CREW.
SO THAT'S PRETTY NICE.
>>> A BALTIMORE RAVENS PLAYER
CRUSHING THE COMPETITION OFF THE
FIELD TACKLING A FOOD EATING
CHALLENGE.
OFFENSIVE LINEMAN BRADLEY BOWMAN
WAS AT A TEXAS ROAD HOUSE AND
TOOK PART IN THE STEAK
CHALLENGE.
>> I'VE BEEN THERE.
>> HAVE YOU DONE THE CHALLENGE?
>> NO, BUT I WANTED TO DO.
I'VE SEEN SOMEBODY TRY IT.
>> I WANT TO TRY IT.
IT ENTAILS A 72 OUNCE STEAK I
CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
>> IT'S MASSIVE.
LOOK AT IT.
>> SHRIMP COCK TAME, BAKE POE AT
A TIME ODD, SALAD, BUTTER ROLL
AND EAT IT UNDER AN HOUR.
THE PRICE IS A T-SHIRT.
HE WAS IN TEXAS FOR HIS WIFE FOR
A SPEAKING TOUR ABOUT THE
EFFECTS OF BULLYING.
I WOULD LOVE TO TRY THAT.
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WIN?
>> HUH?
>> YOU WIN THE MALE, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO PAY FOR IT.
>> SO YOU PAY FOR IT IF YOU
DON'T --
>> IF YOU DON'T FINISH IT.
>> THAT'S INCENTIVE TO FINISH
IT.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
VERY COOL.
OKAY, SEE, I LOOK AT WHAT'S
BEHIND YOU THERE.
I BELIEVE THAT'S BEAUTIFUL
LEONARDTOWN.
>> IT IS.
>> I THINK, OH, LET'S GET THE
WIND BREAKING ON AND ENJOY THIS
SPRING DAY IN FEBRUARY.
>> CAITLIN I WAS DRINKING COFFEE
ON MY COUCH BY THE WINDOW.
IF YOU'RE BY THE WINDOW IN THE
SUN, LIKE A CAT OR DOG LAYING
THERE IT'S NICE AND WARM.
>> FROM THE COMFORT OF YOUR HOME
ALL IS GREAT.
>> THEN YOU OPEN THE DOOR AND
IT'S LIKE, HI FEBRUARY.
>> IT'S BRISK, YES.
THAT'S SOMETIMES HOW IT IS.
OUR COLDEST DAYS ARE THE BEST
LOOKING, BEAUTIFUL ARCTIC HIGH
PRESSURE OVERHEAD DELIVERING
NOTHING BUT BLUE SKY TODAY.
BUT IT'S BEEN COLD, NO DOUBT
ABOUT IT.
ONE OF THE CHILLIEST DAYS WE'VE
HAD ALL WINTER AS HIGH
TEMPERATURES HAVE FAILED TO HIT
40 DEGREES.
CLEAR SKIES TONIGHT AND VERY
COLD AS WE FALL INTO THE 20S,
TEENS OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY.
IT WILL BE MILDER THIS WEEKEND
WITH PLENTY OF SUNSHINE.
MILDER THOUGH IN THE AFTERNOON
HOURS, STILL LOOKING AT SOME
COLD MORNINGS AND LATE NIGHTS.
SHOWER CHANCES ARRIVE NEXT WEEK,
SO WE'RE GOING TO GET THROUGH
THE WEEKEND, THOUGH, WITH
BEAUTIFUL BLUE SKIES AND
SUNSHINE, LIKE THAT SHOT OF
NORTHWEST DC RIGHT BEHIND ME.
NICE NEIGHBORHOOD THERE, FORT
RENO PARK IN THE BACKGROUND.
DOES LOOK LIKE A NICE DAY FOR
THE PARK BUT FEELS PRETTY
COOLED.
39 DEGREES RIGHT NOW, FEELS LIKE
33 WITH A LIGHT NORTHWEST WIND,
SO WE DO STILL HAVE SOME WIND
CHILLS.
A LOT OF FEBRUARY-LIKE WEATHER
ON THE MAP HERE TODAY.
30 IN BOSTON, 29 IN BUFFALO, 37
IN WILMINGTON, 43 IN NASHVILLE.
SO, YES, EVEN ALL OF OUR
SOUTHERN STATES GETTING IN ON
THIS COLD AIR.
37 IN CHICAGO, MINNEAPOLIS, 51
IN LINCOLN.
SO HIGH PRESSURE OVERHEAD, IT'S
REALLY BEEN A QUIET DAY COAST TO
COAST.
AND IT WILL BE THIS WEEKEND.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO BE DRY WITH
PLENTY OF SUNSHINE WITH HIGH
PRESSURE JUST TO OUR SOUTH IN
THE AFTERNOON, WE'LL GET A BIT
OF A WARM-UP.
CERTAINLY COLD IN THE MORNING
EACH DAY, WE START OFF CHILLY,
20S TOMORROW, PROBABLY 30S
FOR -- LOW 30S FOR SUNDAY.
BUT EACH AFTERNOON WE SHOULD
CLIMB INTO THE 50S.
SO YOU MIGHT NEED ALL THE GEAR
EARLY BUT BY AFTERNOON YOU CAN
START TO TAKE OFF A LAYER OR
TWO, IT WILL FEEL A LITTLE BIT
MORE COMFORTABLE.
THE NUMBERS FOR YOUR WEEKEND, 52
DEGREES ON SATURDAY, GREAT TO
BREAK OUTSIDE AND 55 ON SUNDAY
WITH JUST A FEW MORE CLOUDS,
BEAUTIFUL.
TEMPERATURE TREND PRETTY STEADY
THE NEXT FEW DAYS, WE'LL REMAIN
IN THE 50S SLIGHTLY ABOVE
AVERAGE AS WE HEAD INTO EARLY
NEXT WEEK.
THAT'S THE NEXT FEW DAYS.
YOUR FULL SEVEN-DAY FORECAST
STILL AHEAD COMING UP IN A
LITTLE BIT.
BLAKE AND ANGIE BACK OVER TO
YOU.
>> THANKS CAITLIN.
>>> STILL TO COME, HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO BE ABLE TO SUMMON A
SERVER WITH THE CLICK OF A
BUTTON.
A DC HOTEL IS LETTING CUSTOMERS
DO JUST THAT BUT THE NEW
TECHNOLOGY HAS SOME PEOPLE
TALKING AND DEBATING THIS.
>> WHERE IS THAT HOTEL, TOO,
THAT LOOKS NICE.
>> STICK AROUND.
>> LIVE LOOK ALONG THE BELTWAY
NEAR THE AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE,
IT IS HEAVIER THAN NORMAL
TRAFFIC.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪
>>> A LOOK NOW AT WHAT IS
TRENDING ON THIS FRIDAY, CAITLIN
JOINING US FOR THESE.
FIRST UP TALKING ABOUT DRINKING
WHILE SHOPPING.
SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD TIME TO ME.
YOU MAY HAVE SEEN A BAR IN A
GROCERY STORE BEFORE.
YOU CAN NOW SHOP THOUGH AT
PLACES -- OR DRINK AND SHOP AT
PLACES LIKE NORDSTROM'S FLAGSHIP
STORE IN MANHATTAN.
THE STORE IN CHICAGO HAS IT IN
THE MIDDLE.
CRATE AND BARREL, LULULEMON NOT
ONLY ALLOWING YOU TO HAVE A
DRINK INSIDE THEY ENCOURAGE IT.
THE MORE YOU DRINK THE MORE YOU
SPEND, A SURVEY SAYS THE DRUNK
SHOPPING MARKET IS A $45 BILLION
A YEAR INDUSTRY.
I IMAGINE MOST OF THAT IS DRUNK
SHOPPING ON LINE AT HOME.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, AT NIGHT.
>> INHIBITIONS HAVE BEEN
LOWERED, SO PLACE ORDER, PLEASE.
>> YEAH, I HOPE THAT THESE
PEOPLE ARE UBERING TO THE MALL.
>> THIS IS NEW YORK CITY SO
THEY'RE PROBABLY NOT DRIVING
THEMSELVES.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT ACTUALLY THE GIANT
GROCERY STORE ON WISCONSIN
AVENUE HAS A BAR IN IT.
THE ONE ON CATHEDRAL COMMONS SO
THAT'S FASCINATING IT'S GROCERY
SHOPPING.
>> THE WEGMANSS IN LOUDOUN
COUNTY HAS THE SAME THING, A
REALLY NICE BAR.
>> I FEEL LIKE GO INTO THE
GROCERY STORE YOU'RE GOING TO
BUY A LOT NO MATTER WHAT,
CLOTHES SHOPPING IS DIFFERENT
BUT MAYBE IT'S JUST SOME
ENTERTAINMENT AS YOU GO THROUGH
THE GROCERY AISLE.
>> AFTER BRUNCH ON 14TH STREET
THE OTHER WEEKEND I WENT TO A
FURNITURE STORE AND THEY WERE
GIVING OUT MIMOSAS WHILE PEOPLE
WERE SHOPPING.
I WAS LIKE WHY DID I BOTHER
BUYING THEM AT BRUNCH WHEN I
COULD GET THEM 43 AT THE
FURNITURE STORE.
>> DID YOU END YOU HAVE BUYING
FURNITURE.
>> WE'RE ON THE E-MAIL LIST NOW
SO WIN WIN.
>> IT ADDS TO THE EXPERIENCE.
CRATE AND BARREL I WOULD LOVE TO
TRY THEIR WINE GLASSES OUT.
>>> GONE ARE THE DAYS OF TRYING
TO WAVE OR SHOT ACROSS THE ROOM
TO GET YOUR SERVER'S ATTENTION
AT A RESTAURANT.
INSTEAD THE NEW AC HOTEL IN
DOWNTOWN DC HAS A BUTTON YOU CAN
PUSH AT EACH TABLE THAT ALERTS
YOUR SERVER.
THEY'LL RECEIVE THE MESSAGE ON A
VIBRATING LIGHT-UP SMART WATCH.
IF YOU WANT TO CLOSE YOUR TAB
THERE'S CHECK BUTTON SO THEY CAN
BRING THE CHECK RIGHT OVER.
SOME THINK IT'S COOL OTHERS
THINK IT IS A DEHUMANIZING AND
TAKES AWAY FROM THE SERVER
PATRON EXPERIENCE.
>> INTERESTING.
KIND OF LIKE BEING ON AN
AIRPLANE JUST RING THE CALL
BUTTON.
>> I LIKE IT IN A HOTEL BECAUSE
OFTEN TIMES THEY'RE NOT AS
ATTENTIVE AS YOU WOULD BE IN A
RESTAURANT BECAUSE A LOT OF
PEOPLE SIT DOWN AT THOSE TABLES
AND NOT NECESSARILY ORDER
ANYTHING, SO THIS WAY YOU CAN
GET A SERVER OVER THERE QUICKLY
IF YOU DO WANT SOMETHING.
>> BUT AS A FORMER SERVER I FEEL
LIKE THAT THAT IS JUST A WAY TO
LET YOUR GUARD DOWN, YOU KNOW,
WHEREAS A SERVER YOU'RE JUGGLING
SO MUCH ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVE A
BIG SECTION AND IT'S YOUR JOB TO
BE ON YOUR GAME AND IF YOU KNOW,
WELL, I JUST HAVE TO WAIT FOR
THE BUTTON, I FEEL LIKE IT TAKES
AWAY A LITTLE FROM THE JOB AS
WELL.
>> A LOT OF SERVERS PRIDE
THEMSELVES ON THEIR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THEIR CUSTOMERS AND HOW
ATTENTIVE THEY ARE AND LET'S
FACE IT, THE MORE ATTENTIVE AND
MAYBE YOU'RE REALLY BEING
HELPFUL, IT CAN HELP YOU GET A
BIGGER TIP, WHATEVER.
BUT THEY COUNT ON THOSE
RELATIONSHIPS.
SO THAT KIND OF TAKES IT AWAY
FROM THEM.
>> ALL I KNOW I COULD NEVER DINE
THERE WITH MY KIDS BECAUSE THEY
WOULD BE LIKE, YOU KNOW, JUST
TRYING GOING IN AN ELEVATOR WITH
THEM.
>> I HAVE A LOT OF RESPECT FOR
SERVERS, TOO.
HAVING ONCE DONE IT MYSELF AND
NEVER GONE BACK, IT'S HARD WORK.
>> VERY HARD WORK.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THIS.
DOES USING TECHNOLOGY TO DEMAND
SERVICE, I DON'T KNOW IF DEMAND
IS THE RIGHT WORD BUT TO ASK FOR
SERVICE, TO CALL THEM OVER, DOES
IT DEHUMAN EYES SERVERS.
THAT'S OUR LIVE INSTAPOLL, YOU
CAN VOTE ON FOX5DC.COM OR THE
FOX5 DC APP LET US KNOW WHAT YOU
THINK.
PEOPLE ARE SPLIT SO FAR.
>> YEAH.
>>> STILL TO COME HERE FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN YEARS, VIRGINIA'S
WORKERS MIGHT BE GETTING A RAISE
AND EVEN MORE INTERESTING
DIFFERENT REGIONS OF THE
COMMONWEALTH WILL HAVE THE
ABILITY TO MAKE THEIR OWN
ADJUSTMENTS.
♪
NTS.
♪♪
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[ fast-paced drumming ]
♪
>> BACK NOW WITH A LOOK AT SOME
OF THE OTHER TOP STORIES WE'RE
FOLLOWING.
FOUR FIRE FIGHTERS SENT TO THE
HOSPITAL THIS MORNING IN PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY ARE BACK HOME
TONIGHT.
THREE SUFFERED MINOR BURNS
BATTLING A HOUSE FIRE ON DOWER
HOUSE COURT IN UPPER MARLBORO.
THE FOURTH WAS CHECKED OUT FOR A
NON-FIRE RELATED ISSUE.
STILL NO CAUSE OF THE FIRE WHICH
DID A HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS
IN DAMAGE.
>>> NOW TO A BIZARRE ASSAULT
OUTSIDE A MARYLAND GROCERY
STORE.
POLICE ARE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR
THE MAN YOU SEE RIGHT HERE ON
THE SCREEN.
TAKE A GOOD LOOK IF YOU CAN.
THEY BELIEVE HE POKED A WOMAN
WITH A SYRINGE AS SHE WAS
WALKING THROUGH THE PARKING LOT.
SHE WAS ON SHADY SIDE ROAD IN
CHURCH TON.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO ALSO CAPTURED
HIM WALKING NEAR THE VICTIM AND
BUMPING INTO HER.
>>> SALISBURY UNIVERSITY POLICE
HAVE IDENTIFIED A SUSPECT IN
CONNECTION WITH TWO RACIST
GRAFFITI INCIDENTS ON CAMPUS.
POLICE HAVE NOT RELEASED THE
SUSPECT'S NAME BUT SAY THE
PERSON IS NOT A STUDENT OR A
STAFF MEMBER.
SOME OF THAT GRAFFITI WAS FOUND
ON A STAIRWELL ON THE SCIENCE
BUILDING AND CALLED FOR VIOLENCE
AGAINST MINORITIES.
THE FBI IS INVOLVED IN THIS
CASE.
>>> A NORTHERN VIRGINIA MAN IS
IN CUSTODY AND CHARGED WITH
THREATENING THE SPEAKER OF
VIRGINIA'S HOUSE OF DELEGATES,
EILEEN FILLER-CORN OF FAIRFAX
COUNTY.
AUTHORITIES ARRESTED STEPHEN
HARTZELL LAST NIGHT.
THEY SAY HE ISSUED THE THREAT ON
FILLER-CORN'S FACEBOOK LAST
WEEK.
THAT POST HAS SINCE BEEN
REMOVED.
IF CONVICTED HARTZELL FACES UP
TO TEN YEARS IN PRISON.
>>> WELL, SOME OF YOU COULD BE
SET TO EARN MORE MONEY AS SOON
AS THIS SUMMER AND THAT'S
BECAUSE MINIMUM WAGE COULD GET A
BOOST IN VIRGINIA.
A BILL TO BUMP IT TO $15 AN HOUR
BY 2025 WORKING ITS WAY THROUGH
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY AND THE
FIRST INCREASE WOULD HAPPEN THIS
JULY.
FOX5'S TISHA LEWIS IS IN
ALEXANDRIA WITH MORE ON THIS
NEWS.
HI, TISHA.
>> HI THERE.
ALSO KNOWN AS THE HEARTBEAT FOR
MOM AND POP SHOPS ACROSS THE
COMMONWEALTH, HERE IN
ALEXANDRIA.
NOW THERE'S MIXED REACTION FROM
BUSINESS OWNERS AND WORKERS
ABOUT ALL OF THIS, REEKS ON BOTH
SIDES, THE BILL INTRODUCED BY
SENATOR RICHARD WOULD BOOST
MINIMUM WAGE OVER THE NEXT FOUR
YEARS, HERE'S HOW IT WOULD WORK.
STARTING THIS JULY 2020, YOU GO
FROM 7.25 AN HOUR TO $10 AN
HOUR, UP $11 THE NEXT YEAR AND
BY 2025 IT WOULD GO UP TO $15 AN
HOUR.
SO, AGAIN, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A
DOLLAR INCREASE OVER THE NEXT
FEW YEARS.
NOW, THE BILL WHICH WAS PASSED
BY THE SENATE BY A VERY SLIM
MARGIN WOULD THEN CONTINUE TO
ADJUST MINIMUM WAGE AFTER 2025
TO KEEP UP WITH INFLATION.
THE BILL ALSO DISCUSSES A PLAN
TO RAISE MINIMUM RAGE BY REJOHNS
ACROSS THE COMMONWEALTH.
THE HOUSE AND SENATE WILL
RECONCILE ON THE BILL BEFORE
FINAL VOTES IN A FEW WEEKS.
ANGIE.
>> I KNOW YOU TALKED WITH SOME
BUSINESS OWNERS OUT THERE, WHAT
ARE THEY SAYING?  ARE THEY FOR
THIS?  AGAINST IT?
>> Reporter: WELL, THAT'S A
GREAT QUESTION ANGIE.
REACTION REALLY IS SPLIT.
IT'S MIXED.
SOME ARE FOR IT SOME FOLKS ARE
AGAINST IT.
I WILL TELL YOU THE FOLKS THAT
ARE AGAINST IT ARE CONCERNED
THAT THE MINIMUM WAGE BOOST
WOULD FORCE THEM TO INCUR THE
COST ELSEWHERE.
THEY ESSENTIALLY WOULD HAVE TO
INCREASE PRICES FOR CUSTOMERS
AND THEN CUSTOMERS MAY DECIDE TO
GO TO ANOTHER BUSINESS.
AND, QUITE HONESTLY, SOME OF
THESE SMALLER BUSINESSES JUST
CANNOT SHOULDER THE IMPACT OF
BOOSTING MINIMUM WAGE.
IN FACT, THE FOLKS THAT ARE
AGAINST IT ARE NOT ALONE.
MANY REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS AGREE
WITH THEM SAYING THAT THEY'VE
SPOKEN WITH SEVERAL IN THE SMALL
BUSINESS COMMUNITY, FOLKS WHO
SAY THEY CANNOT AFFORD TO DO
THIS AND THEY CALL THIS YET
ANOTHER FAR REACHING RADICAL
POLICY SHIFT ACROSS THE
COMMONWEALTH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TISHA FOR US BRINGING US UP TO
SPEED.
THANKS SO MUCH.
>>> STILL TO COME, DITCHING THE
AIR BRUSH.
ANOTHER MAJOR BEAUTY BRAND IS
BANNING PHOTO SHOP AND MAKING
THEIR INFLUENCERS, YOU KNOW THE
ONES THEY REACH ON SOCIAL MEDIA
TO POST ABOUT THEM, THEY'RE
MAKING THEM DO IT, TOO.
>> I THINK IT'S' SMART MOVE,
RIGHT?
>> WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT COMPANY'S
DOING IT.
>> AND WE WANT TO TAKE A LIVE
LOOK ON I95 IN ALEXANDRIA
VIRGINIA, NO FILTER HERE WHAT
YOU SEE IS WHAT YOU GET.
TRAFFIC IS MOVING SLOWLY HERE
THROUGH ALEXANDRIA.
WE'RE BACK AFTER THIS.
♪
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
♪
>> SKIN CARE BRAND OH LAY HAS
MADE IT OFFICIAL.
THEY WILL NO LONGER AIR BRUSH
THEIR ADVERTISEMENTS BY 2021 SO
NEXT YEAR.
THE NEW CAMPAIGN WILL BE CALLED
MY OH LAY AND FEATURE SEVERAL
MODELS WITH UNTOUCHED FACES,
OLAY SAYS IT WILL ALSO ASK
INFLUENCERS WHO ADVERTISE THEIR
PRODUCTS ON SOCIAL MEDIA TO MAKE
A SKIN PROMISE TO GUARANTY THEIR
POSTS ARE NOT RETOUCHED.
OTHERS HAVE ALREADY DITCHED THE
AIR BRUSH INCLUDING DO HAVE AND
CVS.
OF COURSE THEY'RE STILL USING
MODELS SO THEY'LL HAVE GOOD SKIN
BUT A NICE STEP FORWARD.
>> IS THIS JAMES BLUNT.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> HE'S STILL PERFORMING YOU
KNOW THAT?
>> IS HE.
>> YEP.
>>> WE HAVE A LICENSE TO EAT,
DRINK, DANCE AND BE MERRY.
ON TROMBONE, GIVE IT UP FOR I
NEVER WAS FIRST CHAIR BECAUSE I
SAT WHERE I WANTED IN BAND
CLASS, BRITNEY JOHNSON.
SPECIAL GUEST HOSE JENNIFER
LOPEZ, NOT THE JENNIFER LOPEZ
BUT MY FRIEND REALLY NAMED
JENNIFER LOPEZ WHO'S GIVING AN
ALL NEW MEANING TO HOW LOW CAN
YOU GO J-LO ON THE TUBA?  AND
THAT'S ME, I'M YOUR HOST ANGIE
GOFF KILLING IT ON THE WASH
BOARD.
THIS TERRIFIC TRIO IS THE BAND
KNOWN AS JUST BEAD IT.
>> OKAY, SO WE ARE READY TO CUT
THE KING CAKE ON THE ALL NEW OH
MY GOFF SHOW OUT NOW.
WE GET OUR PARTY GRAS ON WITH A
HURRICANE COCKTAIL COMPETITION.
ALSO MY FRIEND J-LO REALLY KNOWS
HOW TO SHAKE IT.
LOVE, CAREER, LIFE COULD ALL BE
IN THE CARDS, A TAR ON READER
ALSO STOATS  STOPS BY.
SO CATCH THE NEW OH MY GOFF SHOW
ON APPLE POD KISSES AND YOUTUBE.
NEXT TUESDAY IS FAT TUESDAY.
>> WE DIDN'T PLAN THIS BUT WE'RE
WEARING MARRED GRAY COLORS.
>> THIS IS THE PREGAME.
AND ALSO IF YOU'RE INTO DRINKING
WHICH MARDI GRAS IS ALSO
ASSOCIATED WITH, WE DID THIS
ROSE GOLD DAIQUIRI AND GINA
PARTY GIRL EXTRAORDINARY.
>> ROSE GOLD.
>> SHE USED FLAKES OF ROSE GOLD
THAT MAKES IT BEAUTIFUL.
>> DO YOU KNOW I FEEL FANCY IF I
HAVE LA CROIX FOR PEOPLE TO MIX
WITH AND SHE HAS ROSE GOLD.
>>> STILL TO COME AN OUTPOURING
OF SUPPORT FROM AROUND THE WORLD
FOR A YOUNG BULLIED BOY.
TALKING TO TMZ ABOUT ONE OF THE
GENEROUS OFFERS HE RECEIVED.
>> PLUS AN UPDATE ON ACTOR
ORLANDO BLOOM'S NEW INK AFTER
FANS POINTED OUT THE TATTOO OF
HIS SON'S NAME WAS SPELLED
WRONG.
>> WELL, HE DID IT IN MORES
CODE.
>> HOW DID ANYONE KNOW.
>> NOBODY SPEAKS MONTHERS CODE
BUT WHO KNOWS IT AND IF YOU'RE
GOING TO GET A TATTOO WITH MORES
CODE WOULDN'T YOU DOUBLE-CHECK
IT?
>> YOU WOULD THINK.
BUT I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I WOULD
FIX IT BECAUSE IT'S MORES CODE.
>> AND HONEST WILL I NOBODY'S
GOING TO KNOW.
>> IS IT WORTH IT?  CAN'T REALLY
TELL.
>> KEEP IT, GIVES IT CHARACTER.
>> HE IS.
>>> HEADING INTO THE WEEKEND,
WOO, IT IS FRIDAY, YES, IT'S
COLD BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
BECAUSE IT'S STILL FRIDAY, THE
WEEKEND IS RIGHT UPON US.
WE'LL HAVE A LOOK AT THAT
FORECAST AND WARMER TEMPERATURES
IN IT THAT'S COMING UP WHEN FOX5
RETURNS RIGHT AFTER THIS.
♪
TER THIS.
♪♪
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
♪
>> WE OF COURSE HAVE A LOT OF
FREE MUSEUMS IN OUR AREA TO
VISIT BUT ONE YOU MAY NOT KNOW
ABOUT IS MAKING BIG WAVES.
>> SARAH SIMMONS HAS MORE ON
THAT AND WHAT ELSE THEY'RE
WORKING ON FOR THE NEXT HOUR.
HI SARA.
>> HI GUYS ALL NEW AT 5:00 THE
HISTORY OF SEA POWER.
WE WILL TAKE YOU TO ANNAPOLIS
FOR A BEHIND THE SCENES TOUR OF
THE US NAVAL ACADEMY MUSEUM AND
SHOW US SOME OF THE PIECES
THEY'RE TRYING TO RESTORE THERE.
AND NEARLY THREE YEARS AFTER
BEING BAGGED FOR STOMACH TURNING
VIOLATIONS, A POPULAR GROCERY
STORE IN THE AREA IS COMING
BACK.
WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE RETURN OF
THE WHOLE FOODS IN GLOVER PARK.
THAT'S ALL NEXT AT 5:00.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SARAH, THANK YOU.
>>> OKAY, SO HERE'S THE
QUESTION.
DO YOUR FAMILY MEMBERS BEG YOU
TO MAKE YOUR FAMOUS SWEET POTATO
APPLY EVERY THANKSGIVING.
CONSIDER APPLYING FOR THE GREAT
AMERICAN BAKING SHOW THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR ALL STAR BAKERS AND
ARE ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS NOW
FOR SHOWS AIRING LATER THIS
YEAR.
TO APPLY YOU HAVE TO BE A U.S.
RESIDENT 18 YEARS OLD AND AN
AMATEUR BAKER.
THE SHOW IS ACCEPTING
APPLICATIONS THROUGH NEXT
FRIDAY, AND I MIGHT BE ABLE TO
DO THIS.
I CAN'T COOK, BUT I CAN BAKE.
AND AMATEUR, THAT MEANS LIKE
OKAY, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, BUT YOU SHOULD AT LEAST
KNOW HOW TO TURN ON THE OVEN,
ANGIE.
>> NO, I DO.
I JUST -- BAKE AND BROIL, WHAT'S
THE DIFFERENCE?  THAT'S OKAY.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW EITHER.
>> I HAVE MORE RESEARCH.
I'M MORE THE ONE WITH THE REALLY
BAD BAKERS.
>> WHY DON'T WE LET EVERYONE
ELSE HANDLE THE BAKING.
>>> SINGER SELENA GOMEZ RECENTLY
RELEASED AN ALBUM AND ALREADY
DROPPING BONUS TRACKS.
TODAY SHE RELEASED THE SONG FEEL
ME.
IT'S A FAN SONGS HAVE LONG BEEN
WAITING FOR.
SHE FIRST SANG IT LIVE DURING
HER WORLD TOUR IN 2016.
RARE HAS ALREADY HIT NUMBER ONE
ON THE CHARTS WHEN RELEASED LAST
MONTH.
>>> A QUICK STORY TO THE STORY
WE TOLD YOU EARLIER THIS WEEK
ORLANDO BLOOM'S TATTOO IS FIXED.
HE GOT NEW INK THAT WAS SUPPOSED
TO SPELL HIS SON'S FLYNN NAME IN
MORSE CODE.
THE TATTOO GOOFED AND IT READ
FRINN NOT FLYNN.
THE MISSING DOT HAS BEEN ADDED
AND NOW READS THE CORRECT NAME.
>> AT LEAST IT'S MORSE CODE IT'S
EASY TO TAKE OFF A DOT OR TWO.
BETTER THAN HIS FACE.
>> YEAH, OR THAT'S MORE SGLAELD
ALL OVER SOCIAL MEDIA, A HEART
BREAKING VIDEO OF A YOUNG BOY
WITH DWARFISM IN TEARS BECAUSE
OF KIDS WHO BULLIED HIM IN
SCHOOL HAS RECEIVED AN
OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT AND EVEN
AGREED TO ACCEPT SOME FREE MMA
TRAINING FROM A TOP
ORGANIZATION.
LOREN LoROSA JOINS US LIVE FROM
TMZ'S HEADQUARTERS.
LAUREN, I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU,
THIS VIDEO'S BEEN EVERYWHERE AND
I HAVE A SEEN THE SCREEN SHOT ON
MY SOCIAL MEDIA BUT I CAN'T
BRING MYSELF TO WATCH IT.
IT'S HEART BREAKING.
I CAN ALREADY TELL.
>> I ACTUALLY WATCHED IT AND I
COULDN'T FINISH IT.
IT DOES, I MEAN, IF IT DOESN'T
BRING YOU TO TEARS, I DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHAT TYPE OF PERSON
YOU ARE BECAUSE IT'S JUST REALLY
REALLY SAD.
HE LITERALLY IS BARELY ABLE TO
SPEAK BECAUSE HE'S JUST SO FULL
OF EMOTION AND HE'S CRYING,
VERY, VERY UPSET.
AND YOU HEAR HIS MOM IN THE
BACKGROUND SAYING, I WANTED TO
SHOW THIS BECAUSE SCHOOLS AND
EDUCATORS AND JUST PARENTS, DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS, NO KID
SHOULD FEEL THIS WAY.
BUT GOOD NEWS IS IS THAT, YOU
KNOW, THE WORLD HAS BEEN
EMBRACING QUADEN.
ONE CEO OFFERED MMA LESSONS AND
ONE IS ONE OF THE TOP MMA
ORGANIZATIONS IN THE WORLD.
HE INVITED HIM TO SINGAPORE FOR
AN ALL EXPENSE PAID VACATION SO
THAT QUADEN CAN LEARN MATERIAL
ARTS AND HE CAN IS SET TO MAKE
AN ALL EXPENSE PAID TRIP TO
DISNEY LAND IN THE COMING MONTHS
AFTER A GOFUNDME FOR HIM WAS SET
UP AND RAISED MORE THAN $230,000
IN LESS THAN A DAY.
SO MANY BIG NAMED CELEBRITIES
ARE JUST COMING OUT AND SPEAKING
POSITIVE THINGS TO QUADEN AND
BACKING THE FUND RAISERS AND
DIFFERENT THINGS SO IT'S AMAZING
TO SEE THE OUTPOURING OF LOVE
FOR A KID THAT NEEDS IT.
>> I KNOW THE GOFUNDME PAGE WAS
SET UP TO PROVIDE A TRIP TO
DISNEY LAND FOR HIM AND BOOST
HIS SPIRITS.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY RAISED WAY MORE
MONEY THAN THEY POSSIBLY NEED
FOR THAT.
DO WE KNOW WHERE THE REST OF THE
MONEY WILL GO.
>> NO, WE HAVE NOT GOTTEN TO THE
BOTTOM OF THAT YET BUT
DEFINITELY HE'LL MAKE IT TO
DISNEY LAPPED BECAUSE 230 K.
AT LEAST 30,000 TIMES. Y WORLD -
>> IN A PRIVATE JET PROBABLY.
>> RIGHT, YEAH.
SO NO WORD EXACTLY AS TO LIKE
WHERE ELSE HE WILL BE SPENDING
THE MONEY, BUT HE'LL DEFINITELY
MAKE IT TO DISNEY LAND AND WE'LL
KEEP IN CONTACT FOR UPDATES.
>> LOREN LoROSA LIVE FROM TMZ,
THANK YOU AND HAPPY FRIDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> TMZ AIRS AT 7:30 HERE ON FOX5
AFTER LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> HELLO?  YES, HI.
>> HOW YOU DOING.
>> LOREN LoROSA PICKED UP THE
PHONE RIGHT AFTER.
>> THAT'S FIVE AT 4:00 HOW CAN I
HELP YOU.
OH, YOU WANT SOME NICE WEATHER?
YEAH, LAUREN CHECK IT OUT.
OPEN UP THE DOOR OUTSIDE, WE
HAVE SUNSHINE JUST BLANKETING
THE SKY BUT DON'T BE FOOLED,
RIGHT CAITLIN?  IT'S PRETTY COOL
OUT THERE.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR CALLING OUR 1-800
NUMBER FOX5 AT 4:00, THANKS
ANGIE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL OUTSIDE,
BEAUTIFUL LOOKING, BUT IT SURE
IS COLD.
IT'S GOING TO BE A CHILLY NIGHT,
BUNDLE UP IF YOU'RE HEADED OUT
NOT EXPECTING IT TO DO ANYTHING
BUT FALL FARTHER OVERNIGHT
TONIGHT WHEN IT COMES TO OUR
TEMPERATURES.
FOR THE WEEKEND WE KEEP THE
SUNSHINE.
IT WILL BE A LITTLE BIT MILDER
BUT MILDER ONLY DURING THE
AFTERNOON HOURS.
SO IF YOU'RE UP EARLY OUT LATE
STILL COUNT ON IT BEING VERY
CHILLY AND WE'LL GET THAT NICE
WARM-UP IN THE AFTERNOON WHEN
THE SUN'S REALLY SHINING.
AND THE SUN'S BEEN SHINING
LONGER, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE
NOTICED OR NOT BUT WE'RE REALLY
STARTING TO EXPAND THAT DAYLIGHT
WITH THE SUN NOW SETTING ENCLOSE
IS TO 6:00 P.M.
SO FOR TOMORROW, SUN COMES UP AT
SIX:51 SETS AT 5:53 NOW CROSSING
THE 11-HOUR THRESHOLD.
IT'S ALL THESE LITTLE THINGS
THAT START TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE,
LIKE YOU'RE HEADED TOWARDS
SPRING EVEN THOUGH IT'S STILL
COLD OUT AND I BELIEVE WE SPRING
FORWARD IN JUST A FEW WEEKS SO
THEN WE GET A WHOLE EXTRA HOUR
IN THE EVENING.
39 DEGREES WAS OUR HIGH
TEMPERATURE AT REAGAN TODAY, 38
AT DULLES, 39 AT BWI.
A RARE FEBRUARY DAY WHERE OUR
HIGH TEMPERATURES WERE WELL
BELOW NORMAL.
THAT NORMAL HIGH FOR LATE
FEBRUARY, 48.
SO REAL DIP IN THE JET STREAM
PROVIDED THESE COLDER
TEMPERATURES THAT STARTED
OVERNIGHT, EVEN BROUGHT US A FEW
SNOW FLURRIES TO REAGAN NATIONAL
AND NOW NOTHING BUT SUNSHINE
WITH THOSE CHILLY TEMPERATURES.
SO LOOKS LIKE NO ONE HIT 40
DEGREES TODAY, 37 IN ANNAPOLIS
RIGHT NOW, 34 IN LEONARDTOWN, 39
IN QUANTICO, 37 OUT OF DULLES
AND 38 IN MARTINSBURG.
STILL A BIT OF A WIND CHILL EVEN
THOSE THE WINDS HAVE BEEN
DIMINISHING A BIT FEELS LIKE IN
THE LOW 30S, SO COLD TONIGHT,
CLEAR SKIES, NOT MUCH TO SEE
HERE, SATELLITE AND RADAR COULD
NOT BE QUIETER AS HIGH PRESSURE
IS DOMINATING OUR FORECAST
TONIGHT AND THROUGH THE WEEKEND.
25 DEGREES IN THE CITY, WOULDN'T
BE SURPRISED TO SEE SOME TEENS
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING AS WE KICK
START YOUR SATURDAY, WHICH WILL
BE WARMER LATER ON IN THE DAY.
SO IF YOU HAVE THINGS PLANNED,
OUT AND ABOUT IT WILL FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE COME THE AFTERNOON
HOURS, 52 DEGREES THE HIGH
TEMPERATURE AS WE RISE FROM THE
20S INTO THE 50S.
HIGH PRESSURE REMAINS IN CONTROL
THROUGH SUNDAY.
TEMPERATURES UP A LITTLE BIT.
SO I THINK BY SUNDAY MORNING
WE'LL START IN THE 30S.
AFTERNOON WILL ONCE AGAIN BE IN
THE 50S AND WE'LL HAVE PLENTY OF
SUNSHINE SO PRETTY NICE LOOKING.
NUMBERS FOR YOU, 52 TOMORROW.
YOU KNOW THAT.
SUNSHINE AND A FEW CLOUDS ON
SUNDAY, 55.
THOSE MORNINGS AND THE NIGHTS
WILL BE COLD.
STILL TRACKING OUR LACK OF SNOW
THIS WINTER.
YOU KNOW, WE GOT A TRACE LAST
NIGHT AT REAGAN NATIONAL SO WE
CAN OFFICIALLY SAY WE'VE HAD
SOME SNOW IN FEBRUARY BUT WE ARE
STILL ON TRACK TO BE THE THIRD
LEAST SNOWIEST WINTER EVER WITH
A WHOOPING SIX TENTHS OF AN INCH
OF SNOWFALL THAT'S ACCUMULATED.
JUST A TRACE YESTERDAY DOESN'T
COUNT, IT NEEDS TO BE MEASURABLE
TO ADD TO OUR TOTALS.
TWO CAREERS BEFORE THIS WHERE WE
GOT EVEN LESS, JUST A TENTH OF
AN INCH OF SNOW, 97/98 AND 72/73
AND CLOSE TO TWO OTHER YEARS,
ONE RECENT 2011/2012 AND ONE
BACK IN THE 70S WITH TWO INCHES
OF SNOW BUT STILL NOT NORMAL TO
GET THIS LITTLE SNOW AROUND
HERE, AVERAGE IS JUST OVER 15
INCHES AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY.
NO SNOW IN THIS ONE, NEXT WEEK,
50S, SHOWER CHANCES.
THEY'LL BE INCREASING MONDAY
NIGHT INTO TUESDAY, SECONDARY
LOW WILL BRING SHOWERS ON
WEDNESDAY AND THEN WE CLEAR OUT
AND TURN COLDER ONCE AGAIN KIND
OF IN THIS PATTERN AS WE
APPROACH NEXT WEEKEND.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN DAY, ANGIE,
BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
CAITLIN YOU NEED TO LISTEN TO
THIS NEXT STORY, OKAY?  BECAUSE
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT BRIDES AND
WE KNOW YOU'RE A BRIDE TO BE.
LOOKING AT FOX5'S LIKE IT OR
NOT, THERE ARE SEVERAL WEDDING
GUESTS DOS AND DON'T.
YOU DO SHOW UP ON TIME, YOU
DON'T BRING SOMEONE NOT INVITED
AND YOU DEFINITELY DON'T WEAR
WHITE THEY SAY.
ONE GUEST DIDN'T FOLLOW THAT
RULE AND THE BRIDE SENT THIS
PETTY THANK YOU CARD HER WAY.
THANK YOU FOR ATTENDING OUR
WEDDING, IT WAS AN HONOR TO
SHARE THE ENTITLEMENT OF WEARING
A WHITE DRESS WITH YOU.
BEST WISHES.
WE HAD SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT
THIS.
>> I THINK DOMINIQUE HAS A
PICTURE FROM MY WEDDING, RIGHT?
LOOK, EVERYONE'S IN WHITE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE PUT SO
MUCH ON THAT.
ALL THIS SYMBOLISM IS GREAT AND
WE HAVE THESE FANNED FANTASIES
IN OUR HEAD BUT AT THE END OF
THE DAY, DID YOU HAVE A GOOD
TIME, WAS THIS A MEMORABLE
MOMENT, DOES IT MAKE YOU FEEL
THAT MUCH BETTER, DID SHE REALLY
STEAL THE BEAUTY OF THE MAGIC OF
THE DAY.
>> IT IS MY DAY.
YOU WILL NOT WEAR WHITE TO MY
WEDDING.
>> IT IS YOUR DAY SO WHY EVEN
GIVE HER THE ATTENTION.
>> BECAUSE YOU SHOULD NO BETTER.
>>> OKAY.
WELL, TONIGHT ON LIKE IT OR NOT,
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT DOG
COLLARS.
A DOG COLLAR THAT ACTUALLY
TRANSLATES BARKS INTO SWEAR
WORDS.  UH-HUH.
IT'S CALLED THE CURSE COLLAR.
THE COMPANY BEHIND IT SAYS IT'S
NOT INTENDED FOR ANTI BARK
TRAINING, IT'S MORE OF A GAG
GIFT IF ANYTHING.
IT'S ALREADY SOLD OUT.
PEOPLE WANT THIS THING.
OR GOING TO HEAR OUR THOUGHTS ON
THIS COMING UP AT 7:00.
I NEED TO HEAR THIS DOG COLLAR.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF -- ARE
THERE DIFFERENT LEVELS OF SWEAR
WORDS?  THAT WOULD BE REALLY
INTERESTING.
>> JUST GET A PAIR ROT WILL
SWEAR.
>> PRODUCER DOMINIQUE FROM FOX5
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> SHE DIDN'T KNOW THE PARROT
COULD TALK, THEY HAD IT FOR SIX
MONTHS AND THEY WERE SWAYING AND
SWEARING AND SWEARING AND THEY
COME HOME AND THE PAR ROT WAS
SWEARING AT THEM.
>> IN THEIR VOICE.
>> SCARY.
JOIN US TONIGHT TO TALK ABOUT
IT.
>>> STILL TO COME THREE MORE
ICONIC WOMEN BEING ADDED TO
BARBIE'S INSPIRATIONAL WOMEN'S
SERIES.
FIND OUT WHO'S JOINING THE
COLLECTION.
♪
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪
>> CHECKING IN WITH THE FOX5
INSTAPOLL, DOES USING TECHNOLOGY
DEMANDING IMMEDIATE SERVICE
DEHUMANIZE SERVERS, IT IS THE
FOX5 LIVE INSTAPOLL QUESTION OF
THE DAY.
LOOKS LIKE THE YES VOTES ARE
WINNING BY A SLIM MAJORITY.
KEEP VOTING AT FOX5DC.COM OR THE
FOX5 DC APP.
>>> SO NEW DOLLS ARE COMING TO
THE BARBIE INSPIRING WOMEN'S
SERIES.
TENNIS STAR BILLIE JEAN KING,
QUEEN OF JAZZ ELLA FITZGERALD
AND THE FOUNDER OF MODERN
NURSING FLORENCE NIGHTENGALE ARE
ALL GETTING BAR BUSINESS, ALL
PART OF THE MISSION TO CLOSE THE
DROME GAP, A GLOBAL INITIATIVE
THAT RAISES AWARENESS ONORS THAT
LIMIT GIRLS FROM RAISING THEIR
FULL POTENTIAL.
>> VERY COOL.
>>> THIS PUP DOES NOT WANT TO
TAKE A BATH.
THE OWNER SHOWED WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THEY TRY TO GIVE HIM A
BATH.
FIRST, HE REFUSES.
>> OH, STOP.
>> HE WON'T EVEN LOOK AT THEM.
>> HE'S PLAYING DEAD.
>> HE HIDES BEHIND A WALL, THEY
CAN'T SEE ME, RIGHT.
THEN HE TRIES TO CONCEAL HIMSELF
BEHIND THE TOILET.
>> I HAVE TO SEE THIS.
>> LOOK AT HIM.
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS AN ALASKAN MALL MUTE
WHICH ON AVERAGE WEIGHS ABOUT 85
POUNDS SO IT'S PRETTY HARD FOR
THEM TO HIDE.
NO WORD IF HE ACTUALLY MADE IT
INTO THE BATHTUB.
>> IS A PUPPY, DO YOU KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LITTLE BABIES UP UNTIL THE
AGE OF THREE WHEN THEY CLOSE
THEIR EYES THINK THEY BECOME
INVISIBLE SO YOU MIGHT THINK
RIGHT THERE, THEY CAN'T SEE ME,
I'M NOT GETTING THIS BATH.
SO ADORABLE.
PERFECT WAY TO ROUND OUT THE
SHOW.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US AT
4:00.
>> THE NEWS AT
>> LOCAL TEENAGER SON, TWO
MORE SUSPECTS UNDER ARREST,
NEW INFORMATION THE JOY IN THE
HARVEY STYLE REACHES VERDICT
ON SOME OF THE SEXUAL ASSAULT
CHARGES, DELIBERATIONS AREN'T
OVER YET.
>> MICHAEL BLOOMBERG ON STOP
AND FRISK, YOUR NEWS STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> AND WE START WITH BREAKING
NEWS OFF THE TOP AT 52:00 MORE
TEENS UNDER ARREST AND CHARGED
IN THE MURDER OF 17 YEAR OLD
BRADLEY BROWN, THAT ANNOUNCED
YESTERDAY.
>> INVESTIGATORS SAY BROWN HAD
ADVERTISED DRUGS FOR SALE, ON
SNAP CHAT.
AND WAS SHOT AND KILLED IN THE
DRIVEWAY OF HIS HOME.
>> COURT RECORDS ARE VOGUE ONE
OF THE THREE HAS CONFESSED,
PAUL WAGNER LIVE IN WALDORF
TONIGHT WITH THE LATEST ON THE
BREAKING STORY.
PAUL?
>> JIM, WE WORRY, LOOKING AT
SOME OF THE COURT RECORDS LATE