>> AND SHE CAN PICK UP
A STROKE, SHE WOULD
CERTAINLY LIKE TO PICK
UP AT THIS POINT
I THINK THIS PLAYER
MUST HAVE WHAT I HEARD
OTHER PEOPLE SAY FACE
AWARENESS.
I KNOW WHEN WE ARE ALL
PLAYING PRETTY WELL,  S
HOW SHE IMPRESSES ME
BECAUSE SHE RARELY
HITS A BALL SERIOUSLY
OFFLINE.
>> AND WITH DECENT
POWER, AS WELL
IT'S A VERY STRAIGHT
BALL
FLAT ALMOST EVERY
TIME
>> BOY, SHE THOUGHT
SHE MADE THAT.
>> FIRST DROPPED SHOT
OF THE DAY
>> THAT'S A BIG CHANCE
THAT WENT BY THE
WAYSIDE.
>> INCREASES THE
CHANCES OF FENG,
WHAT'S GOING ON
BEHIND.
>> 170, 6 IRON IN
HAND
THERE IS A LITTLE BIT
OF ROOM OUT THAT WAY
THAT STARTED RIGHT AND
IT'S NOT DRAWING
>> IT'S NOT MOVING
EITHER
WOW.
I THINK IT MIGHT BE IN
ITS OWN PITCH MARK
>> THIS TO DROP JUST
ONE HERE FOR KIM
OKAY
BUT DOESN'T GIVE
GROUND BECAUSE JIN
YOUNG KO ALSO MADE
BOGEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT
SUNG-HYUN PARK DID,
TOO.
A TWO-SHOT LEAD FOR
KIM.
You wouldn't do only
half of your daily routine
So why treat your
mouth any differently?
LISTERINE® completes the
job by preventing plaque,
early gum disease, and
killing up to 99.9% of germs.
Try LISTERINE®.
Need stocking stuffers?
Try LISTERINE® READY! Tabs™.
>>> THE LEADER IS HYO
JOO KIM.
TEE SHOT AT THE 13th
>> SMOOTH LOOKING
SWING THAT ONE FROM
KIM.
NO NEED TO LOOK.
>> THAT IS IN THE
FAIRWAY.
LITERALLY IN THE
WELL, DON'T YOU THINK?
>> NOT ALL IN THE
FAIRWAY, BUT IN THE
FAIRWAY.
>> ALTOMARE FOR PAR AT
>> WELL.
>> SHE WIWE DIDN'T SHOW
HER --
>> YOU THINK YOU ARE
BULLETPROOF.
>> I KNOW.
>> OFF THE BACK OF A
FIRST DROPPED SHOT OF
THE DAY TO A HOLE
SHE'S BOGEYED EVERY
DAY.
>> THAT MAY NOT BE THE
ONLY ONE
>> GREAT START THERE
THOUGH
THAT'S IN THE
NARROWEST PART OF THE
FAIRWAY AS WELL.
>> SO WITH THREE SHOTS
AND TWO HOLES, I
WONDER IF IT'S GOING
TO BE A RATHER
CAREFREE SUNG HYUN
PARK OVER THIS
STRETCH.
>> SHE IS DISAPPOINTED
AND MAD AT HERSELF.
ALSO A LITTLE SAD.
SHE WALKED OFF WHILE
THEY WERE DOING THEIR
THING AND SHE STOOD
WELL IN FRONT OF THE
GREEN ALONE WITH HER
THOUGHTS
IT WASN'T EVEN THE
PATH YOU WOULD TAKE TO
GET TO THIS TEE BOX.
STARTED OFF UP THE
LEFT CENTER.
STAYED THERE
>> YOU KNOW, A LOT OF
PLAYERS ARE VERY HARD
ON
ON THEMSELVES.
I THINK YOU SEE THAT
IN HER FACE.
>> PARK NOW FOR
BIRDIE.
>> HIT A 5 WOOD HERE
FROM 194 YARDS
IT WAS A GOOD ONE.
THIS LITTLE DOUBLE
BREAK, A LEFT TO
RIGHT, AND SHOULD
STRAIGHTEN UP.
>> THAT'S A BIG BONUS.
EVEN WHEN SHE ROLLED
THAT ONE IN AT 11, YOU
KNEW TOO ITTLE, TOO
LATE
BUT STILL.
KUPCHO MAY BE ABLE TO
POST A NUMBER.
>> SHE MIGHT, IF SHE
JUST REALLY TAGS ONE,
HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
HOME AT 18.
>> ARIYA JUTANUGARN
WITH A BIRDIE
OPPORTUNITY TO GET IT
AT DOUBLE FIGURES HERE
AT 14.
REACH.
WELL, IT GOT THERE
>> IT'S LIKE THIS
SECOND PUTT THAT MAY
ME THINK SHE CAN PLAY
GOLF AS LONG AS SHE
WANTS TO BECAUSE IT'S
ONE OF THE MARKS WHY
SHE IS SUCH A GOOD
PUTTER
SHE RARELY LEAVES
HERSELF WITH A LOT OF
WORK WITH A SECOND
PUTT.
>> CHECKING IN AT
NUMBER NINE IN THE
ROLEX RANKINGS
HYO JOO KIM COMING OFF
A BOGEY.
IT'S A TWO-SHOT
ADVANTAGE FOR THE
PLAYER WHO WON HERE
BACK IN 2014
AND POSTED A 61.
LOWEST ROUND BY ANYONE
IN MARRIAGE.
ON HER WAY TO DO THAT.
SALAS WITH A 68.
POSITIVE THOUGHTS.
LOOKING AHEAD TO NEXT
WEEK
WOMEN'S BRITISH OPEN
FEMALE ANCHOR: It's 6:39, time
for 'News Update'
MALE ANCHOR: ...an update on the
cat who captured our hearts.
FEMALE ANCHOR: How often should
you clean your fridge?
Stay tuned to find out.
MALE ANCHOR: ...this year's
most buzzed about premieres...
FEMALE ANCHOR: Makes it
red-carpet official with...
MALE ANCHOR: 50 5-star products
you can buy online right now
MALE ANCHOR: Tributes pouring
in from fans...
FEMALE ANCHOR: Her hot new
album is just
one of the things
we talked about.
MALE ANCHOR: Beats the odds
at the Box Office
to become a rare
non-franchise hit.
[Anchor voices ramp up together
becoming indiscernible]
You can provide the help
and hope that survivors need.
>>> OUT TO THE PAR 5
15th
UP THE HILL, BIRDIE
PUTT FOR MORIYA
JUTANUGARN
YEAH, THE PLAYERS
CHASING COULDN'T
AFFORD MISTAKES LIKE
THE ONE SHE MADE AT
>> INBEE PARK COMING
OFF THAT LONG PUTT ON
THE TEE AT 14.
>> 187 YARDS
I IMAGINE YOU ARE
LOOKING AT THINKING
ABOUT, YOU KNOW, 180
FLY THE BALL ALL THE
WAY TO THE HOLE.
MAYBE EVEN A LITTLE
LESS THAN THAT, BUT
THAT'S CLOSE TO THAT
20-FEET HOLE HEIGHT TO
THE LEFT, ALTHOUGH
IT'S GETTING BETTER
AND BETTER ALL THE
TIME
IT'S INSIDE OF
20 FEET.
GOOD SHOT.
>> GOT TO MAKE ALL OF
THESE.
>> NOT SURE SHE
THOUGHT SHE MADE THAT
ONE, BUT IN IT GOES.
REMEMBER, TOLD YOU
ABOUT HER EARLIER, A
TWO-THREE FINISH,
EAGLE-EAGLE.
STRANGER THINGS HAVE
HAPPENED
SHE GETS HERSELF TO 11
UNDER PAR.
FOURTH IN A ROW.
FOUR SHOTS BACK.
SO THIS THE 13th HOLE.
TWO SHOT FROM SUNG
HYUN PARK.
PRETTY GOOD.
STILL A LONG WAY IN
FOR THE LEADER
HEF HER DAD AND SISTER
HERE THIS WEEK
SUNG HYUN PARK IS
GOING TO PLAY HERE
FIRST.
>> YEAH, WELL, HAD TO
TAKE A LITTLE BREAK
AFTER THE TEE BALL AND
WAS QUITE THE LEG
COMING UP THE FAIRWAY.
AND SUNG HYUN PARK IS
IN A MINDSET RIGHT
NOW, SHE DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE WAITING
THAT'S A HOOKING IRON
TO THE HOLE.
>> IT IS REALLY GOLF
NOWADAYS
I MEAN, THEY HAVEN'T
EXACTLY BEEN QUICK
AROUND THERE, JUDY,
TODAY.
>> YOU MAKE CERTAIN
ACCOMMODATIONS
>> ALMOST FOUR HOURS
INTO THE ROUND.
>> THIS, I BELIEVE,
BEST OF MY MEMORIES,
FIRST OR SECOND HOLE
THAT THEY GOT THEIR
BALL ON THE GREEN AND
IT WAS CLEAR
THEY HAVE WAITED A
TON.
BE THAT AS IT MAY,
THIS IS A DIFFICULT
SHOT
198 FROM A HOOK LIE TO
A BACK RIGHT HOLE
LOCATION WITH A
HYBRID
TAKE FOUR AND RUN
RIGHT HERE, JUDY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> YES, I DO
I THINK MIDDLE OF THE
GREEN WOULD BE A
BEAUTIFUL PLACE.
EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
SO MANY PLAYERS,
PARTICULARLY THOSE
STRIKING THE BALL
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU
JUST HAVE A RADAR FOR
WHERE THE FLAGSTICK
IS
>> SOMEHOW GOT THAT
BALL TO FADE OFF OF
THAT LIE CENTER OF THE
GREEN.
MAYBE BETTER THAN
THAT
>> GOOD SHOT
WELL SHORT
BALL WELL ABOVE HER
FEET
NICE EXTENSION THROUGH
THERE.
>> THE STRETCH OF THE
GOLF COURSE, 13 TO PAR
4, 12, 13, 14, GOOD
LUCK GETTING THROUGH
THAT SECTION
FENG
>> IT'S GOOD.
>> JUST ENOUGH
OKAY
YOU TAKE IT.
SECOND TOUGHEST HOLE
THROUGHOUT THE WEEK.
>> JIN YOUNG KO, EVEN
THOUGH WITH
SIGNIFICANT POWER,
ALSO IN NEED OF A
HYBRID ON THIS GREEN
NOT AS SEVERE AS THE
LIE, BUT STILL IS
ABOVE HER FEET
VERY SIMILAR LOOKING
LINE TO THE OTHER TWO.
>> YEAH, YOU WOULDN'T
THINK THEY HAVE A
GREAT CHANCE TO ADD TO
ONLY THE THREE BIRDIES
WE HAVE SEEN AT THIS
HOLE SO FAR TODAY.
>> SO WE GO TO 16, THE
PAR 3.
JENNIFER KUPCHO COMING
OFF THE BIRDIE AT 15.
>> THIS IS THE
SHORTEST, THIS LITTLE
PAR 3 HAS PLAYED THIS
WEEK
124 YARDS.
FRONT RIGHT HOLE
>> HANG ON
SOFT ENOUGH.
I THINK.
YES.
>> AND IT KIND OF
TUCKS UP AGAINST THAT
CUT OF ROUGH
IT COULD BE A PROBLEM
FOR THE TOE OF THE
PUTTER.
>> WHAT A PERFORMANCE
THROUGHOUT THE WEEK
THOUGH
YOU COME OUT HERE
MIDWAY THROUGH THE
SEASON, YOU TURN
PROFESSIONAL, YOU
JOIN, YOU PLAY A
COUPLE OF MAJORS, YOU
GET IN THE FIELD HERE
AND YOU ARE IN THE TOP
FIVE, IS KUPCHO.
♪
Everything your trip needs
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
I see what's possible,
instead of what's here.
for everyone you love.
Others see cracked concrete,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
That's why I made
Project Backboard
and a site with GoDaddy.
How will you make your mark?
Make the World You Want
>>> REALLY GOOD SHOT
ONE OF THE BEST WE'VE
SEEN THERE
IT IS GREAT TO WATCH
SHE AND HER SISTER
ARIYA OUT HERE
ARIYA WAS THERE, JUST
TOP OF THE WORLD, AND
THEN WATCH MORIYA WIN
FOR THE FIRST TIME
LAST YEAR AT WILSHIRE
COUNTRY CLUB IN L.A.
IT WAS SOME SCENE.
>> YEAH.
NO
I HAVE OFTEN SAID THEY
ARE MUCH LIKE TWINS.
MORIYA IS THE OLDER OF
THE SISTERS, BUT THEY
ARE AS CLOSE AS
SISTERS CAN POSSIBLY
BE
THEY ARE A LITTLE BIT
COMPETITIVE WITH EACH
OTHER, BUT THEY ALSO,
YOU KNOW, WHEN ONE IS
DOING WELL, THE OTHER
ONE IS LIVING AND
DYING EVERY SHOT.
>> YOU CAN BE AS CLOSE
IF SHE MAKES THAT PUTT
TO GET ON THE
LEADERBOARD, TOO
BOTH 9 UNDER
MIRIM LEE'S THIRD AT
SHE GOT HERE IN TWO.
YOU CAN DO IT.
AND THEY MOVED THE TEE
UP
IT'S 454
HOWEVER, WITH THE
CONDITIONS, YOU HAVE
TO PUT IT IN THE
FAIRWAY AND YOU ARE
GOING TO GET NO ROLL.
>> THERE WAS A POINT
IN TIME TODAY IN THIS
ROUND, MAYBE TWO HOURS
AGO, WHEN NO ONE HAD A
CHANCE TO GET THERE IN
TWO.
>> ORDINARILY, YOU SEE
TWO GOOD PUTTS FOR
PAR, BUT THIS IS HYO
JOO KIM WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT.
>> THIS IS UPHILL
INITIALLY AND THEN THE
SECOND HALF IS
DOWNHILL
TOUGHEST PUTT TO
JUDGE, THE SPEED IN
ALL OF GOLF.
TURNING LEFT AS WELL.
>> YOU JUST DON'T WANT
A DIFFICULT PUTT, DO
YOU, JERRY
>> NO, YOU NEVER DO.
>> UP AT 18,
VALENZUELA, THIS TO
SAVE PAR FOR THE
AMATEUR.
WENT TO STANFORD
IS AT STANFORD
BEEN WATCHING YUKA
ALSO PLAY.
SHE IS PLUS 1.
YOU HAVE FIVE AMATEURS
START THE WEEK.
>> AS ANOTHER EXAMPLE
OF THE YOUNG AMATEURS
WHO ARE SO WELL
PREPARED TO COME TO
PROFESSIONAL GOLF.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE
SEEING WITH KUPCHO.
>> 14.
THIS IS WHERE SHANSHAN
FENG'S TEE SHOT ENDED
UP
THIS FOR BIRDIE.
>> ROLLED ABSOLUTELY
STRAIGHT
>> BACK TO 13 THEN
IN NEED OF A
PICK-ME-UP.
>> AND THAT WOULD BE
UNEXPECTED FROM HERE,
BUT DESPERATELY IN
NEED
A LITTLE RIDGE WILL
THROW IT RIGHT AND
THEN IT WILL LEVEL OUT
NEAR THE HOLE.
>> SO I MENTIONED
YASUDA
HER THIRD AT 18.
LOOKING FOR A BIRDIE
TO TIE THE LOW AMATEUR
FOR THE TOURNAMENT
I BELIEVE SHE HAS A
CHANCE
>> LOOKING PRETTY
GOOD
>> THAT NOT PLAYING IN
THE WOMEN'S BRITISH
OPEN NEXT WEEK, BUT
YASUDA WILL BE IN THE
FIELD.
>> I SUPPOSE IT'S
SUNDAY, BACK NINE OF A
MAJOR, FEELS A LITTLE
TENSE OUT THERE AT THE
MOMENT, JERRY.
>> YES, INDEED
YOU CAN FEEL IT IN THE
AIR.
ABSOLUTELY
AND THE MANDELA, THE
SUNG HYUN PARK FAN
CLUB IS QUIET AT THE
MOMENT, BUT THEY ARE A
VERY GOLF
KNOWLEDGEABLE AUDIENCE
AND APPRECIATIVE OF
THE PLAY
THEY HAVEN'T HAD MUCH
TO CHEER ABOUT IN A
WHILE.
THIS WOULD BE BIG
RIGHT HERE
>> GREAT SHOT.
STRAIGHT LOOK.
IN IT GOES
>> YOU WERE ABSOLUTELY
BETTER OFF TO BE
BEYOND THE HOLE AT 13
TODAY.
YOU COULD SEE THAT
WITH THAT PUTT
IT ROLLED EXACTLY THE
WAY YOU THOUGHT IT
WOULD.
JUST BROKE MAYBE AN
INCH OR TWO RIGHT TO
LEFT AND IT WAS
SLIGHTLY BACK UP THE
HILL
IT'S RARE THAT YOU
THINK GETTING BEYOND
THE HOLE IS THE BEST
PUTT.
>> BIG PUTT IN MANY
WAYS
>> THE GAP IS ONE.
>> INBEE PARK BIRDIED
THE 13th
LOOKING TO GO BACK TO
BACK
TRIED TO COME BACK,
DIDN'T IT?
>> IT KIND OF
SURPRISED ME IT WENT
TO THE RIGHT, TO TELL
YOU THE TRUTH.
>> SHE IS FOUR SHOTS
NOW BEHIND SECOND
PLACE.
>> HERE AT 16, KUPCHO
RIGHT ON THE EDGE.
THIS FOR BIRDIE.
SEE WHERE SHE IS
PUTTING FROM
THAT CLOSELY MOWED
AREA
GOT A BREAK.
>> I WAS WORRIED ABOUT
THAT CUT OF THE ROUGH,
BUT SHE IN FACT COULD
LIFT AND CLEAN THE
BALL
AND GET THAT LITTLE
AGGRAVATION OUT OF THE
SHOT
>> ARIYA JUTANUGARN TO
GET IT TO 9 UNDER.
MORIYA JUTANUGARN.
WELL DONE.
SO SHE AND HER SISTER
ARE AT 9 UNDER
6 OFF THE LEAD
GOT INBEE PARK THERE
AS WELL.
SHANSHAN FENG FOR PAR
AT 14.
STAYS IN SOLO THIRD.
THREE BACK
NOT DONE YET
MAJOR CHAMP HERSELF.
INBEE PARK, OF COURSE,
HAS WON HERE BEFORE AS
WELL, BUT NTHAT WAS
BACK IN 2012
LAST TIME IT WAS A
NON-MAJOR.
♪ ["Stuck in the Middle
with You" by Stealers Wheel] ♪
♪  ♪
♪ Well I don't know why
I came here tonight ♪
♪ I got the feeling that
something ain't right ♪
♪ I'm so scared in case
I fall off my chair ♪
You can't always
choose how you travel
But now, you can choose
a little extra comfort
♪ Jokers to the right, here I am
stuck in the middle with you ♪
>>> FINAL GROUP ON THE
TEE AT THE PAR 3 14th.
>> JIN YOUNG KO WITH A
6 IRON HERE.
IT TAKES A GREAT SHOT
AND A LITTLE BIT OF
CREATIVITY TO GET IT
CLOSE.
I THINK THE LINE IS
ABOUT TEN YARDS LEFT
OF THE FLAGSTICK AND
ABOUT TEN YARDS SHORT.
JUST GET IT OVER THAT
RIDGE AND LET THE
CONTOUR TAKE CARE OF
THE REST
>> SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE
HAS A LOT OF LOFT.
>> IT'S A 6 IRON,
JUDY
YEAH.
>> WOW.
>> SHE IS PLAYING THAT
RIGHT WHERE IT WAS
AIMING IF IT CARRIES
THAT SLOPE
STICKS RIGHT, OR IT
LANDS.
>> HYBRIDS HERE, JUDY.
>> YEAH, 6 IRON, SHE
REALLY HAD TO STRETCH
IT, JERRY.
>> YEAH.
>> YUKA YASUDA FOR
BIRDIE
TIED FOR LOW AMATEUR
THE 18-YEAR-OLD FROM
KOBE, JAPAN.
THERE YOU GO, THE
WOMEN'S ASIA-PACIFIC
AMATEUR CHAMPION,
EARNED A SPOT IN THE
FIELD WITH THAT WIN.
75 HERE IN THE FINAL
ROUND.
>> THE LEADER BY 1,
GETTING READY ON THE
TEE AT 14.
>> DEFINITELY GOING TO
BE A HYBRID.
HER 5 HYBRID
THIS IS WHAT WE USED
TO CALL UTILITY CLUBS,
DIDN'T WE, JUDY?
AND IT HAS BEEN USED
IN THAT MANNER BY HER
MAGNIFICENTLY THIS
WEEK
SHE HIT SO MANY
DIFFERENT SHOTS WITH
IT
SHE MIGHT NEED TO
CHANGE THE GRIP BEFORE
NEXT WEEK STARTS
>> IT'S BEEN A GREAT
ADVANTAGE TO GOLFERS
TO HAVE THESE CLUBS.
>> I'M NOT SURE IT WAS
MEANT TO GO THERE.
THAT'S RIGEDGE OF THE
GREEN.
NOT GOING TO CARRY.
>> THAT COULD BE
TROUBLE DEPENDING ON
THE LIE.
>> SHE IS RIGHT THERE,
WHAT ANALYSTS MEAN
WHEN THEY SAY A PLAYER
IS STAYING CONNECTED
NO PART OF HER BODY OR
HER ARM SWING EVER GOT
FAR APART.
AND SHE DID HIT A SHOT
ALMOST EXACTLY ON
LINE, BUT NOT ENOUGH
MEAT
>> YOU KNOW, GOOD ON
YOU IF YOU CAN GET IT
CLOSE TO THE HOLE.
ONCE AGAIN, THAT
20 FEET TO THE LEFT OF
THE HOLE LOOKS GOOD TO
ME
>> NEVER EVER SEEN
THAT OUT OF HER
BEFORE.
>> SHE WAVED HIM OFF
>> YEAH.
SHE WENT TO ONE MORE,
JERRY?
>> I THINK JUST THE
OPPOSITE
I'M NOT SURE
NO SIGNAL YET.
BUT HE TALKED HER INTO
WHATEVER IT WAS.
>> THAT'S THE RIGHT
ONE.
TRUST IT.
>> SHE BACKED IT UP
THE TWO CLUB LENGTHS
SHE COULD.
>> OH, SHE WENT TO 5
THAT'S A LOT OF CLUB.
>> THAT'S WHAT MY
GUESS IS
>> RIGHT OF THE HOLE
>> SAFE TO SAY THERE
WAS PLENTY OF DOUBT IN
THAT SWING
>> YEAH, AND IT'S
DIFFICULT IN ANY
CIRCUMSTANCES, BUT AS
HARD AS THAT HOLE IS,
REALLY DIFFICULT
>> BIRDIE FOR ARIYA,
EVEN THOUGH SHE IS
JUST OFF THE PUTTING
SURFACE, MOVED IN THE
FRINGE, NOT AS SHE
EXPECTED
FENG BACK ON THE TEE
THAT WILL DO
>> YEAH, IT'S ALMOST A
BREATHER TEE SHOT
TODAY BECAUSE CHANCES
ARE, UNLESS YOU ARE
ONE OF THE REALLY HUGE
HITTERS, YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO GET THERE IN
TWO.
>> A LITTLE TOO FAR
RIGHT THAN WHERE SHE
WANTS TO BE, JENNIFER
KUPCHO
SHE IS GOING TO HAVE
TO COME UP AND OVER
THE TREES.
>> LEFT HAND HOLE
LOCATION HELPS A BIT
IF IT SETTLES, QUITE
GOOD
>> GIVEN WHAT HAPPENED
IN 2016, JUDY, AT THE
WOMEN'S BRITISH OPEN,
HOW WELL SHE PLAYED
THIS WEEKEND, SHE IS
AMONGST THE FAVORITES,
ISN'T SHE?
>> SHE HAS NOTHING BUT
GOOD MEMORIES FROM
MELBOURNE.
>> TIED WITH HER
SISTER AT 9 UNDER.
>> RICHARD, SPEAKING
OF THE WOMEN'S BRITISH
OPEN, THE AMATEURS
FINISHED YOU WILL,
ALBANE VALENZUELA IS
ENTERED TO QUALIFY
TOMORROW.
>> YEAH, SO SHE HAS TO
GET QUICKLY OVER TO
MAKE IT IN TIME.
YOU WOULDN'T RULE HER
OUT COMING THROUGH
THAT QUALIFIER
TIED AT THE TOP, ISN'T
IT
KIM IN THE BUNKER AT
FENG NICELY DOWN THE
FAIRWAY AT 15.
AND FOUR OF HER BEST
FINISHES HAVE COME IN
THE MAJORS
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
LITTLE HARDER THAN IT
WAS.
MEGAN KHANG READY AT
THE PAR 3.
SEEN SOME GOOD ONCE IN
HERE, MUCH LIKE MORIYA
JUTANUGARN RIGHT IN
THAT AREA.
THE RAIN JUST A
NUISANCE THROUGHOUT
THE AFTERNOON.
OH, THAT'S MORE THAN A
NUISANCE
HYO JOO KIM.
SO SUNG HYUN PARK A
MUCH BETTER SITUATION.
BUT IN THE BUNKER FOR
HER SECOND.
>> AND STILL VERY
ANNOYED.
ALL OF HER GESTURES
WITH DAVID SHOW
FRUSTRATION.
I MEAN, TO THE POINT
WHERE OUT OF HER,
BEING SO STOIC, THAT'S
THE EQUIVALENT OF ONE
OF US BREAKING GOLF
CLUBS IN OUR BAG.
>> HAVE YOU DONE THAT?
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU HAVEN'T?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> OH, AND IT'S IN
ANNOYED NO LONGER.
>> GOING 100 MILES AN
HOUR
MAYBE YOU NEED A
LITTLE POSITIVE, A
LITTLE GOOD BREAK.
SHE DIDN'T THROW IT UP
REAL HIGH.
>> HIT THE LIP
HIT THE LIP AND CAME
UP.
>> JUST TRAVELING.
BACKSTOP
LET'S GET A CLOSER
LOOK
IT'S BETTER IN REAL
SPEED.
OH, OKAY
>> NOW, THERE IS A
TECHNIQUE FOR HYO JOO
KIM THAT WORKS REALLY
OFTEN, AND WE'LL SEE
WHAT SHE DOES, BUT IF
SHE OPENS THE BLADE
AND HITS BEHIND THIS
BALL AS HARD AS SHE
CAN AND JUST LEAVES
THE CLUB IN THE SAND,
THE BALL WILL POP UP
PRETTY HIGH AND NOT
RUN AWAY FROM HER.
THAT'S THE ONLY
TECHNIQUE I KNOW THAT
WOULD WORK IN THIS
CASE, JERRY.
>> YEAH, NOT GOING TO
DOUBT YOU.
THE ONLY THING IS THIS
SUCH A SEVERE UPSLOPE.
GETTING THE BALL TO
HERE FROM THE TOP OF
THE HILL TO THERE IS
NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE.
>> THAT'S WHY I SAY
SHE HAS TO OPEN THE
BLADE AND HIT BEHIND
THAT BALL AS HARD AS
SHE CAN.
>> THIS, JUDY, COULD
BE THE MOMENT HERE ON
THE BACK NINE.
I MEAN, BECAUSE YOU
ARE IN A SITUATION
RIGHT NOW WHERE A BIG
NUMBER COMES INTO
PLAY.
>> YES
WELL, EVEN A LOT OF
VERY ACCOMPLISHED
PLAYERS DON'T TOTALLY
KNOW THE TECHNIQUE OF
PLAYING THIS SHOT, BUT
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
AND IT'S PRETTY --
IT'S GOING TO BE
PRETTY SIMPLE RIGHT
HERE THAT YOU DON'T
TRY TO TAKE THE CLUB
THROUGH THE SAND
LEAVE IT IN THE SAND.
>> IF SHE COULDN'T, IT
WOULDN'T GET PAST THE
LIP ANYWAY.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF IT ROLLS BACK IN
THE BUNKER, IT'S GOING
TO COME BACK TO A FLAT
LIE AND LEAVE A
DEVILISH SHOT JUST
LIKE SUNG YUN JUST
HAD.
>> LOOK OUT.
MY GOSH.
SO MUCH FOR THE FLAT
LIE.
>> NOW YOU GET THE
BALL ON THE GREEN,
YOU'RE HAPPY
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I THINK YOU HAVE TO
PLAY THIS LIKE IT'S
BURIED ALSO, DON'T
YOU, JERRY
>> CAN'T SEE THE LIE,
BUT ABSOLUTELY.
>> RIGHT IN HER
FOOTPRINT.
>> BIG TIME RIGHT IN
HER FOOTPRINT.
>> THOSE AREN'T
SHALLOW PRINTS WHEN
YOU GET ON THE FACE OF
THE BUNKER
WOW.
>> I DON'T THINK THE
FACE WAS NEARLY OPEN
ENOUGH.
>> CLOSED RIGHT AWAY,
DIDN'T IT?
>> YEAH, THIS IS A
SHOT I LEARNED A LOT
OF YEARS AGO FROM A
FORMER PGA TOUR
PLAYER, AND IF YOU DO
WHAT I JUST SUGGESTED
IT WORKS
>> TOOK NO TIME, AND
THAT WAS HER THIRD
>> AND NOW YOU WERE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
THIS IS THE MOMENT.
>> AND SUNG HYUN PARK
BACK IN THINGS NOW
>> SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKELY A THREE-SHOT
SWING.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS IS A CRAZY
GAME YOU PLAY, YOU
KNOW
>> WHO IS THE FELLOW
WITH THE OPEN
CHAMPIONSHIP, JERRY,
WHO TOOK THE SWIPE AT
ONE, HE WAS REALLY OFF
BALANCE AND FELL IN
THE BUNKER AND HE
TWEETED OUT, THIS IS A
HARD GAME, AND A
PICTURE OF HIMSELF.
>> IT WAS A SOUTH
AFRICAN GOLFER.
>> JUSTIN SOMEBODY
>> JUSTIN HARDING.
>> OKAY.
ANYWAY, IT PUT A
LITTLE BIT OF HUMOR
INTO A RIDICULOUS
DIFFICULT SITUATION.
>> WELL, AFTERWARD IT
DID.
>> YEAH, NOT AT THE
TIME
>> SO WHAT AN
OPPORTUNITY NOW AS THE
RAIN DOES FALL A
LITTLE HARDER FOR JIN
YOUNG KO.
>> YEAH, SHE IS REALLY
SITTING IN A GOOD SPOT
RIGHT NOW.
>> JUST A LITTLE
GENTLY DOWNHILL FROM
HERE
NOT TOO BAD.
I THOUGHT SHE LEFT
THAT SHORTER THAN SHE
DID.
>> MUCH BETTER THAN IT
LOOKS, RIGHT, JERRY?
>> YES.
>> IN THE END, THAT
WAS TERRIFIC.
>> DON'T FORGET ABOUT
FENG
SHE CAN GET THIS ONE
DANCING AROUND
INBEE PARK'S BALL JUST
A LITTLE CLOSER.
>> YOU THINK THE 9
UNDERS WOULD HAVE A
TOUGHHEIM HERE
IF ARIYA JUTANUGARN
GETS IT TO 10 UNDER
HERE
WELL, JENNIFER
KUPCHO'S GOT THE
ABILITY TO HIT THE PAR
5 18th TO GET TO 12
UNDER.
SHE HAS BEEN WAITING
FOR THAT
SO MANY NEAR MISSES.
HER TIMING IS GREAT.
12 UNDER
SHE WILL BE UNAWARE OF
WHAT'S HAPPENING
BEHIND, BUT SHE IS IN
WITH A SHOUT NOW
>> A SHARE OF THIRD
PLACE RIGHT NOW.
AT THE MOMENT 3 BACK
HOWEVER, THAT'S
CHANGING AS WE SPEAK
SO THIS IS THE FOURTH
FOR KIM, JERRY.
>> YEAH, LOOKS TO
GATHER HERSELF QUITE
WELL, WHICH IS
IMPORTANT HERE
OH, WOW, WHAT A GREAT
PUTT
>> A LITTLE BIT LEFT
THOUGH
MORE THAN A LITTLE
BIT.
>> AND THE LEAD IS
GOING TO CHANGE HANDS
AS WE GO UP TO 16.
MEGAN KHANG FOR
BIRDIE
HAD A CHANCE
HAVE A SHARE OF SIXTH.
CURRENTLY IN NINTH
PLACE.
BUT THAT FINAL GROUP
BACK AT 14 GOT A
DOUBLE-BOGEY PUTT
COMING UP FOR HYO JOO
KIM AS JIN YOUNG KO
SITS AT 14 UNDER
>> SWITH EACH PASSING
HOLE, THE PRESSURE
MOUNTS, ESPECIALLY
WHEN IT'S FOR DOUBLE
>> YEAH, YOU CAN'T
HELP BUT BE A LITTLE
BIT RATTLED.
>> WOW.
>> QUICK STROKE,
JERRY.
>> YEAH, VERY QUICK.
>> JUDY, AS SOON AS WE
GOT UP THERE AND SAW
THAT LIE IN THE
BUNKER, YOU KNEW THAT
IT WAS THE TIME.
MAYBE A DICEY
SITUATION.
SO YOU HAVJIN YOUNG KOU
HERE AT THE EVIAN
CHAMPIONSHIP
♪ I got the feeling that
something ain't right ♪
♪ I'm so scared in case
I fall off my chair ♪
You can't always
choose how you travel
But now, you can choose
a little extra comfort
♪ Jokers to the right, here I am
stuck in the middle with you ♪
I see what's possible,
instead of what's here.
Others see cracked concrete,
broken backboards,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
Art can change it all.
Bright colors, a bold vision,
and it can be somewhere that
brings people together.
For games or hangouts
or whatever.
A place that makes people proud
like "this is my neighborhood."
That's why I made
Project Backboard
and a site with GoDaddy.
How will you make your mark?
Make the World You Want
>>> TENTATIVE.
SHE'LL STAY TWO SHOTS
BACK
AND BACK TO THE TEE
WITH OUR NEW LEADER,
JIN YOUNG KO
SHOULD BE FINE
FOUR WINS AT THE AGE
OF 24.
LOOKING FOR HER SECOND
MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIP OF
THE SEASON
WON THE A AND A
INSPIRATION IN THE
SPRING
INBEE PARK ON THE TEE
AT 16.
MISSED THAT RIDGE.
NOT GOING TO COME
BACK
>> TOUGH OPENING NINE.
IN 3 OVER 38
SHANSHAN TWO BACK.
JUST MAKING SURE YOU
CARRY THAT, I GUESS.
>> YEAH, SO MANY TIMES
IF YOU HAVE THIS CLUB
IN YOUR HAND, YOU
REALLY EXPECT TO HIT
IT, YOU KNOW, IN SORT
OF THAT EIGHT-FOOT
CIRCLE, BUT AT THIS
HOLE IT'S A LITTLE
INTIMIDATING
IT'S HARD TO DO.
>> DO YOU BUY SHE
DOESN'T KNOW WHERE SHE
STANDS ON THE
LEADERBOARD?
>> I GUESS I DO.
>> I CAN'T IMAGINE THE
BACK NINE OF A MAJOR
COMING DOWN THE
STRETCH --
>> WELL, I AGREE.
>> HERE WE ARE WITH
THE FINAL THREE BALL
I MEAN, NOT ANYONE
OBVIOUSLY ISSUES ANY
ILL ON KIM
BUT IT WHAT HAPPENED
AT THE LAST HOLE HAS
REALLY SPARKED LIFE
INTO A GLOOMY DAY.
IT'S FEEL LIKE IT'S
BEEN A BIT OF A
STRUGGLE
BUT IT'S GOTTEN VERY,
VERY INTERESTING
WELL, FROM A TWO-SHOT
LEAD NOT LONG AGO, NOW
TWO BEHIND
>> NICE AND STRAIGHT
SET UP FOR A SHORT
SHOT IN, GIVE HERSELF
THAT BIRDIE
OPPORTUNITY THAT SHE
BADLY NEEDS RIGHT NOW
TO BOUNCE BACK
>> THIS HOLE OUT OF
REACH, JERRY, FOR THEM
TODAY?
>> YES, INDEED
266 TO THE HOLE FOR
JIN YOUNG KO
PLAYS PRETTY WELL
UPHILL FOR THE MOST
PART, THIS SECOND
SHOT
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO
GET THE ROLL YOU HAVE
BEEN ACCUSTOMED TO
I THINK EVEN WITH A
DRY FAIRWAY, THAT WAS
OUT OF REACH
NOT EVEN CONSIDERING
TRYING TO SEE IF SHE
CAN GET IT UP THERE TO
THE HILL
IN A POSITION NOW
WHERE THE OTHERS HAVE
TO BEAT HER IF SHE
DOESN'T MAKE MISTAKES.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT
SOME OF THE BEST
PLAYERS IN THE GAME
DO
EXACTLY WHAT SHE HAS
DONE TODAY
THEY HANG AROUND, HANG
AROUND, HANG AROUND
JUST IN CASE SOMETHING
HAPPENS.
AND LOOK WHERE SHE
SITS AT THE MOMENT.
>> YES
SOME GUY NAMED
NICKLAUS DID A GOOD
JOB OF THAT.
>> ISN'T THAT THE
TRUTH?
>> 18 TIMES.
>> INTERESTING CHOICE
OF CLUBS HERE, JERRY,
FROM SUNG HYUN PARK.
>> LIE WASN'T TOO BAD.
THAT DIDN'T PAY OFF.
THAT'S ALMOST A TOP
KNUCKLEBALL IN SOME
DEEP, DEEP ROUGH
>> UP TO THE PAR 5
18th, RIGHT ROUGH,
JENNIFER KUPCHO.
IS SHE GOING FOR THE
GREEN?
>> LOOKS LIKE A LONG
CLUB
>> ONLY TWO OFF THE
LEAD
I SEE A GOLF BALL
THERE.
>> I THINK THE BALL
HAS PLUGGED ABOUT TWO
FEET PAST THE PENALTY
AREA LINE.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
>> I SAID THAT
CORRECTLY.
PENALTY AREA.
>> STAY AWAY FROM
HAZARD
THAT WAS A PRETTY
BRAVE SHOT.
>> IT WAS, WASN'T IT
>> WOW.
>> YEAH, SHE HAS GOT,
IT SEEMS, THE
MENTALITY TO BE A
BIG-TIME PLAYER.
HERE AT 17 FOR ARIYA
JUTANUGARN
>> TO HER SISTER,
MORIYA'S THIRD AT 18
BRILLIANT.
AND IT WORKS AS A
THREE-SHOT HOLE, TOO
SO JUST A LITTLE MORE
THAN A TAP IN ON HER
BIRTHDAY TO FINISH UP
AT 10 UNDER AND HAVE A
CHANCE AT A TOP FIVE
FINISH.
>> YEAH, HAPPY
BIRTHDAY
25 YEARS OLD.
>> YEAH.
SHANSHAN FENG HERE IN
THE RAIN AT 16 FOR
BIRDIE
>> BOY, IT'S GOING TO
MOVE TO THE RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK VERY
SEVERELY
>> THIS TO GET WITHIN
ONE.
>> OH, SHE READ IT
BEAUTIFULLY AND DIDN'T
HIT IT
>> TEN-TIME WINNER ON
THE LPGA TOUR 12 YEARS
OUT HERE
MAJOR CHAMPION
HERSELF, THE WOMEN'S
PGA CHAMPIONSHIP BACK
IN 2012.
DROPPED BACK NOT FAR
BACK HERE TO 15.
>> DOESN'T LOOK
PARTICULARLY FUN HERE
FOR PARK
>> SHE DOESN'T SAY
MUCH BECAUSE IT'S A
LANGUAGE THING
THE OTHER PLAYERS,
JUDY, SAY SHE DIDN'T
SPEAK MUCH IN KOREAN
EITHER
>> SHE CAN CERTAINLY
SEE SHE UNDERSTANDS
ENGLISH QUITE WELL.
>> YEAH.
>> 122 TO THE HOLE
SHE IS GOING WITH A 9
IRON
NOT THE LONGEST ROUGH,
BUT VERY, VERY WIRY
AND LYING A LITTLE
INTO THE GREEN
TOUGHEST HOLE LOCATION
ON THE GREEN TO GET IT
CLOSE TO
THAT'S GOING TO BE
RIGHT OF IT.
AND DOESN'T GET A
BOUNCE
THAT IS JUST
DEPEN
DAEDSVILLE THERE.
>> THE OTHER THING
THAT HAPPENS WHEN YOUR
BRAIN IS A LITTLE BIT
SCRAMBLED IS YOU DON'T
MAKE GOOD DECISIONS.
>> YEAH, THE SECOND
SHOT, JUDY, WHAT DID
YOU THINK?
>> THERE WAS NO POINT.
SHE SHOULD HAVE DONE
SOMETHING A LITTLE BIT
SAFER AND LEFT HERSELF
A FULL WEDGE INTO THE
GREEN.
>> SHE HAS BEEN GIVEN
AN OPPORTUNITY THAT
SHE NEVER THOUGHT
WOULD COME AWAY.
>> YOU KNOW, AS BAD OF
LUCK AS IT SEEMED SHE
HAD FOR THE BALL TO GO
BACK IN HER OWN
FOOTSTEPS AT 14, THINK
OF THE GREAT GOOD LUCK
THAT SUNG HYUN PARK
HAD AND NOW SHE IS NOT
ALLOWING HERSELF TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT
>> PLAYING A LITTLE
INTO THE BREEZE.
SEVERE UPHILL LIE.
I STOOD NEXT TO THE
BALL, I COULD SEE THE
FLAG ON THE FLAGSTICK
AND I'M A LOT TALLER,
SO PRETTY MUCH A BLIND
SHOT
JUST CAN'T SPIN THIS
TOO MUCH
>> JERRY, SHE SURE
NEEDS THAT BOUNCEBACK
BIRDIE.
>> TOOK THE RIGHT
APPROACH WITH A LOW
SPINNING SHOT.
>> JUST OFF THE EDGE
MAKEABLE, BUT NOT
SIMPLE
>> SO THE BIRDIE PUTT.
MORIYA JUTANUGARN.
VERY GOOD FINISH
3 UNDER ON THE DAY
68, 10 UNDER, JUST
OUTSIDE THE TOP FIVE
>> THE LEADER BY 2
NEITHER OF HER PLAYING
PARTNERS ON THE GREEN.
>> GOING WITH A SMOOTH
PITCHING WEDGE
ALSO GOING TO TRY TO
LIMIT THE SPIN
THE RAIN STARTING TO
FALL MUCH HARDER THAN
IT WAS FORECAST TO DO
RIGHT NOW.
PULLED IT A LITTLE
NOT MUCH
OH, WOW, HOLDING ITS
LINE NICELY.
>> WELL, SHE STARTED
THE MAJOR SEASON WITH
A VICTORY.
IS SHE HEADING FOR
ANOTHER HERE, JIN
YOUNG KO
17 Birdies
1 Hole in One
Wherever your love of golf
takes you.
Whoever it takes you with.
You can count on Ship Sticks
To take your clubs.
Just a few clicks
and a couple of minutes
Ship Sticks will ship your clubs
from your home
To your golf destination.
Make it simple.
Make it Ship Sticks
Sorry, sorry.
It's okay.
Man, this guys gotta get off the
green.
You know what? You should
just...
He's letting them play through.
Nice touch.
Here pal.
Oh wow! That's so nice of you!
Thank you.
Classy move.
How do we get out of here?
I have no idea.
Watch out.
Tap with your Mastercard.
The simple, secure way to pay.
And Start Something Priceless.
>>> OKAY
AT 18, THE THIRD FOR
JENNIFER KUPCHO.
OH, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
TO CLOSE
GIVE YOURSELF A
CHANCE
WILL IT COME BACK
USING THAT SLOPE
>> LOOKING PRETTY
GOOD.
>> YES.
>> NOT QUITE FINISHED,
BUT SURE LOOKING GOOD.
>> WHAT A WEEK
THE 22-YEAR-OLD FROM
COLORADO WE SAW HER
WIN THE AUGUSTA
NATIONAL AMATEUR OVER
MARIA FASSI.
67, AN EAGLE AT 13,
BIRDIES ON HER LAST
FOUR HOLES
COMES OUT, SHE HAS
PLAYED IN THE MAJOR,
BUT RIGHT THERE.
WHO KNOWS?
WITH A CHANCE.
SO THIS THE FOURTH
MA
MAJOR OF THE SEASON.
ONE MORE NEXT WEEK AT
WELL BURN.
THE WOMEN'S BRITISH
OPEN
THE ROLEX ANNIKA MAJOR
AWARD, JEONGEUN LEE6
MISSED THE CUT BY 1.
THERE IS JIN YOUNG KO
IN THE RUNNING WINNER
OF THE ANA INSPIRATION
TO START THE SEASON.
FIRST MAJOR OF THE
YEAR
ALEXIE THOMPSON
STRUGGLED THIS WEEK
THE FIRST TWO DAYS AND
MISSED THE CUT
>> NOTHING THAT
ANOTHER CHIP-IN
WOULDN'T SOLVE
>> BE THE ONLY WAY TO
GET IT CLOSE
NEEDING ANOTHER
MIRACLE HERE
JUST GETTING IT ON THE
TIER
AND ON THE PUTTING
SURFACE WHERE THE
FLAGSTICK IS WOULD BE
A HUGE VICTORY
EVERYTHING SLOPES AWAY
EXCEPT THE PORTION
WHERE SHE'D LIKE TO
LAND IT SHORT, SLOPES
TOWARDS HER.
AND IT'S A BIT OF A
DOWNHILL LIE
>> AYE-YAI-YAI
>> KUPCHO AT 18 TO
FINISH UP AT 13 UNDER.
THAT COULD BE.
YOU NEVER KNOW, JUDY
POST A NUMBER, AND SHE
JUST DID
SENSATIONAL FINAL
ROUND.
5 UNDER 66 AND IS
GOING TO WAIT AROUND
TO SEE.
>> YOU BET SHE IS
GOING TO WAIT AROUND.
>> ONE OFF THE LEAD.
AND JUST THE MINDSET
AT 18 TO GO FOR IT IN
TWO.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF
THAT WAS TO BRAVE OR
MAYBE THAT WASN'T ALL
THAT SMART
I'M NOT SURE
BUT IT CERTAINLY
WORKED OUT.
>> IT WILL BE FUN TO
WATCH FOR A NUMBER OF
YEARS.
>> SHOT NUMBER FIVE
NOW AT THIS PAR 5.
>> AND STILL VERY
SLIPPERY
VERY, VERY SLIPPERY.
>> ALMOST.
>> I'M NOT SURE THAT
STAYS ON THE PROPER
TIER IF IT MISSES.
>> IT WAS TRICKLING A
LITTLE QUICKLY, WASN'T
IT, JERRY?
>> SUCH A SEVERE
SLOPE.
>> ANOTHER THING THAT
THEY HAVE PROBABLY
LOOKED AT WHEN THEY
SET UP THE GOLF COURSE
TODAY WAS SOME OF THE
HOLE LOCATIONS THAT
WOULD FEEL A LITTLE
HIGHER ON THE GREENS
JUST IN CASE THE
DOWNPOURS CONTINUED,
AND THAT'S ONE REASON
PROBABLY THIS HOLE
LOCATION IS AS TOUGH
AS IT IS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
JUDY INKSTER, MAKING
JENNIFER KUPCHO'S
FINISH TODAY
>> I THINK IT PUTS
EVEN A LITTLE MORE
PRESSURE ON.
>> YOU THINK OF RYANN
O'TOOLE, NOT LIKE
SOMEONE HASN'T BEEN
PICKED BEFORE.
>> WELL, NO DOUBT.
SHE IS FRESH FROM
PLAYING QUITE A LOT OF
MATCH PLAY
SO, YOU KNOW -
>> DEPENDS WHAT ELSE
IS ON FOR HER, I
SUPPOSE.
>> YES.
>> SHE IS INTO THE
CHANCE OF STILL
WINNING THIS
JIN YOUNG KO OF COURSE
OR LEADER.
STARTED THE DAY 4
BACK
HER FIRST WIN OF THE
YEAR WAS THE FOUNDERS
CUP.
4 BACK GOING INTO THE
FINAL ROUND THERE.
>> SHE TOOK IT A CLUB
LENGTH LEFT TO TAKE A
LITTLE SPEED OUT OF
IT, BUT IT ADDED A
FAIR BIT OF BREAK.
>> NOT THE BOUNCEBACK
BIRDIE THAT SHE WOULD
HAVE BEEN HOPING FOR
HERE AT THIS PAR 5
A CHANCE COMING UP TO
REESTABLISH THAT
TWO-SHOT LEAD FOR JIN
YOUNG KO
BACK TO THAT IN A
MOMENT
UP TO 17
OH, JUST LOOKING AT
THOSE TREES.
GOOD.
>> YEAH, IF IT
SETTLES, THAT'S A GOOD
PLACE FROM WHICH TO
PUTT.
>> WHERE JENNIFER
KUPCHO WAS, WASN'T IT?
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY THE
14th GREEN VERY
SIGNIFICANT, BUT THIS
COULD BE ANOTHER BIG
MOVE TO THE TITLE FOR
JIN YOUNG KO
>> SLOW ONE UP THE
HILL
NOT MUCH BREAK
EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD
LOOK FOR
THAT WOULD HAVE MADE
IT A LITTLE EASIER TO
PLAY CONSERVATIVE GOLF
ON THE WAY IN.
>> REMEMBER, ONE IN
THE CLUBHOUSE ALREADY
AT 13 UNDER PAR,
JENNIFER KUPCHO WITH
THE CLUBHOUSE LEAD
JIN YOUNG KO 1 AHEAD
OF HER
BOGEY-FREE 66.
>> SECOND SHOT, 18,
ARIYA JUTANUGARN
WENT AFTER IT.
AND GOT IT THERE.
>> BEAUTY.
>> EVEN BETTER.
>> ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFUL.
>> THAT FOR AN EAGLE
IN THE HEAVY RAIN NOW
HERE AT THE EVIAN.
card.
Yea but she's got help.
Hi, I'll take care of this.
Oh. Thank you so much!
No problem!
Thank you!
Good solid etiquette right
there.
Can't teach that to the
youngsters.
mhmmm
Tap with your Mastercard.
The simple, secure way to pay.
And Start Something Priceless.
♪
So Josh, you going for our
Drive Safe and Save discount?
Yup, using the app.
Driving safe. Heh.
You wanna go? Wanna go bro?
Hey, uh, do not mess
with my discount.
Woooo!
You could save up to 30%.
Let's go!
Nice to meet you,
go get 'em tiger!
Woooo!
Sounds like you've got this?
Yeah. Definitely.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe and Save™
from State Farm.
You wouldn't do only
half of your daily routine
So why treat your
mouth any differently?
LISTERINE® completes the
job by preventing plaque,
early gum disease, and
killing up to 99.9% of germs.
Try LISTERINE®.
Need stocking stuffers?
Try LISTERINE® READY! Tabs™.
>>> SO THREE HOLES TO
PLAY FOR THE FINAL
GROUP, AND IT'S JIN
YOUNG KO WHO LEADS BY
ONE.
BIRDIES HERE ALL THREE
DAYS
>> WELL, MEASURES 124.
124 OR LESS, YOU CAN
ONLY MISS IT A LITTLE
BIT RIGHT AND BE SAFE.
SHE IS GOING WITH A 9
IRON
PLENTY OF CLUB
IT WILL BE AN EASY
ONE, BUT I THINK IT
TAKES THE WATER OUT OF
PLAY.
>> JERRY, THE SHOTS
WE'VE SEEN GIVE A
PLAYER A SHORT PUTT,
LAND ON THAT RIGHT
FRINGE.
>> YEAH.
BUT IF YOU HIT IT THE
RIGHT -- AND YOU PULL,
THAT'S RIGHT, A LITTLE
LONG
NOT MUCH
WHAT A SHOT.
>> FOUR BWINS ON THE
LPGA
THE WINNER OF THE ANA
INSPIRATION.
FIRST MAJOR OF THE
YEAR
>> SO FAR SHE SHOT THE
LOWEST ROUND OF THE
DAY BY TWO SHOTS
SHE SAID AT THE START
AFTER YESTERDAY'S
ROUND THAT SHE, HER
GOAL WAS TO KEEP HER
CARD
I THINK SHE'S DONE
THAT.
>> HYO JOO KIM
>> SOUNDED A LITTLE
LOUD
IT'S HEADED AT THE
JU MISSES THAT AREA, JI
ABOUT.
HORT >> S DISNCFROM
TO 18, THE THIRD
BAP, IT WILL COME
SO THAT TO FINISUP
9NDER
DO YOU  RAIN, TOO, AS  GET
IER AND HEAVIER?
DONE FORAY THE D
>> ANDAYBE NOT
>> IEN ROUTE, A  LITTLE RIG OFT
>> TT'S THAT ONE
'VE SEEN
D WH I SAY MAY
NOT, MEA MAYBE NOT
THERE COULD BE MORE
HOLES T >>HAT IS TRUE.
IN THE CLUBHOUSE, 13
UNDER.
KO UP BY ONE
May your holidays glow bright
and all your dreams
take flight.
Lease the C 300 Sedan
for just $399 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Winter Event.
Hurry in today.
>>> SHANSHAN FENG FOR
BIRDIE AT 17 TO PULL
WITHIN ONE
AND SHE DOES
TIES HER WITH KUPCHO
WHO IS THE LEADER IN
THE CLUBHOUSE AT 13
UNDER.
TO 18 NOW.
ARIYA JUTANUGARN FOR
EAGLE.
WHAT A FINISH.
THE FORMER WORLD
NUMBER ONE
HYO JOO KIM JUST OFF
THE GREEN AT 16.
THAT TRIPLE-BOGEY ON
THE 14th HOLE, 12
UNDER.
TRYING TO MAKE
SOMETHING HAPPEN LATE
HERE
IT'S LEFT.
STAYS TWO BACK
WE GO UP TO THE TEE AT
AND SHANSHAN FENG ONE
OFF THE LEAD
AND THE DRIVE,
OBVIOUSLY, WILL
DICTATE A LOT HERE
>> YEAH, NO CHANCE TO
GO IN TWO.
JUST GET IT IN THE
FAIRWAY WHERE YOU CAN
PLAY THE PERFECT
LAYUP.
GOOD SHOT.
ABSOLUTELY STRAIGHT.
IT'S HARD TO HIT THAT
SHOT WITH NO CURVE
YOU KNOW THAT
ABSOLUTELY STRAIGHT
BALL
>> I AM STILL
SEARCHING FOR ONE.
>> THAT'S OUR ANNIKA
SORENSTAM PLAYED
ALL SHE HAD TO KNOW
WHAT TO DO IS AIM.
THERE WERE NO CURVES
IN HER GOLF GAME.
>> DAVID BROOKER SAYS
THE SAME ABOUT JIN
YOUNG KO
VERY SIMILAR
THIS PUTT TURNING
RIGHT.
PRETTY LEVEL SPEED
WISE
MAYBE A CUP OUT ON THE
LEFT
>> AND THE SPEED.
>> YEAH, GAVE IT A
GOOD RUN
>> THAT PACE JUST
STAYED RIGHT THERE
ALL RIGHT.
STILL UP ONE
CROSS OFF ANOTHER
HOLE
AND PARK, THE LAST OF
THE THREE TO GO HERE,
WITH AN OPPORTUNITY.
>> IF SHE IS THINKING
CLEARLY, JUDY, IN HER
MIND,
BIRDIE-BIRDIE-EAGLE.
YOU NEVER KNOW
SHE'S GOT THE
FIREPOWER.
THREE OFF THE LEAD
MAYBE NOT LIKELY, BUT
CERTAINLY NOT DONE.
>> YEAH, AT LEAST THE
BEGINNING OF THE
RECOVERY THAT SHE
NEEDS.
>> HYO JOO KIM TO
CLEAN THIS UP.
>> JUST A LITTLE BIT
OF A PAY ATTENTION
PUTT
>> BUT ONE OF THOSE
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
JUST ENOUGH IN IT.
YOU SAW HOW FIRMLY SHE
HIT IT
DIDN'T TAKE THE OUT.
TWO OFF THE LEAD
YOU HAVE GOT SHANSHAN
FENG PLAYING 18.
KUPCHO ALREADY IN THE
CLUBHOUSE AT 13 UNDER.
JIN YOUNG KO WITH A
PAR 4 STRAIGHT AHEAD
AND A FINISHING PAR 5.
BUT EVEN, MAY HAVE
WENT UP A LITTLE BIT
AT THE MOMENT.
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES AGO
IT WAS HARD ENOUGH
WHERE YOU WERE NOT
THINKING ABOUT GETTING
THERE AT 18.
WE'LL SEE.
THE CHANGE TO A PAR 5
THOUGH HAS CERTAINLY
CHANGED THE FINISH OF
THIS GOLF COURSE AND
MADE THAT STRETCH 12
THROUGH 14 EVEN THAT
MUCH MORE DIFFICULT
WHEN 13 IS A PAR 4.
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY
SO ON THIS GOLF COURSE
REALLY 10 SHOULD NOT
PLAY AS A HARD, HARD
HOLE ON THIS GOLF
COURSE, AND NEITHER
SHOULD 11.
BUT WHEN YOU START AT
12, ALL OF THE WAY IN
YOU PLAY VERY
DIFFICULT HOLES OR YOU
PLAY HOLES WHERE THERE
CAN BE A SIGNIFICANT
CHANGE, AND THAT'S WHY
IT'S A GOOD FINISH
>> WELL, THE CLOSEST
CHALLENGER TO JIN
YOUNG KO, JENNIFER
KUPCHO AND SHANSHAN
FENG
BOTH BIRDIED THIS
17th, BUT OFF THE BACK
OF HER BIRDIE AT 16,
IT'S SUNG HYUN PARK.
>> NOT THAT EASY TO
SEE OUT HERE RIGHT
NOW.
IT'S GETTING A LITTLE
DARKER
THE CLOUDS ARE GETTING
THICKER.
THE RAIN CERTAINLY
DOESN'T MAKE IT ANY
EASIER
YOU COULD HEAR HER
CADDIE SAYING IT'S
COMING BACK, IT'S
FINE
SHE WILL HAVE TO COME
OVER THE TREES THERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF
IT'S FINE, BUT I THINK
THERE IS A SHOT TO BE
PLAYED
>> I AM NOT SURE IF
SHE WAS DOING THIS ALL
THE WAY AROUND, BUT
JIN YOUNG KO HAS BEEN
CHEWING ON THE GUM
WE SAW THAT FROM A
COUPLE OF PLAYERS,
DIDN'T WE, EARLIER IN
THE YEAR
>> IT'S BECOMING MORE
AND MORE POPULAR
>> MAYBE A STRESS
RELEASE.
>> YOU ARE LOOKING FOR
THE CENTER OF THE
FAIRWAY OR REALLY
WHAT'S PERFECT IS LEFT
CENTER
>> SHE LIKED IT
IMMEDIATELY.
>> YOU KNOW, IF I
COULD GO BACK TO
SOMETHING THAT KAREN
WAS TALKING ABOUT
EARLIER TODAY, SHE WAS
TALKING ABOUT HOW GOLF
COURSES IN KOREA TEND
TO NOT HAVE ANY FLAT
LIES, THAT YOU PLAY ON
THE SIDE OF HILLS AND
MOUNTAINS AND SO ON.
IF THERE IS ONE THING
THAT'S COMMON TO ALL
OF THE PLAYERS FROM
KOREA THAT I HAVE
WATCHED IS THEY HAVE
GREAT BALANCE IN THEIR
GOLF SWINGS.
HERE IS SHANSHAN
>> 240 WAS THE NUMBER
THERE.
AND PLAYING JUST
SHORT.
A LAYUP.
>> SHE MADE A LITTLE
DARING LAYUP OUT OF
IT
TOOK IT WAY DOWN
THERE.
>> A LONG-TIME LEADER,
TWO BACK NOW
>> ANYWAY, I HAVE
NEVER SEEN A KOREAN
PLAYER LOSE THEIR
BALANCE IN THE GOLF
SWING.
>> THAT ONE THERE IS
GOING TO BE WELL BACK.
BUT WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT THE KOREAN
DOMINANCE AT THE TOP
OF THE LEADERBOARD
IT'S NOW, WELL, A
KOREAN ON TOP, BUT
TIED FOR SECOND AND AN
AMERICAN AND CHINESE
PLAYER
THERE IS THE AMERICAN,
JENNIFER KUPCHO.
WELL, IF HER GOAL AS
SHE STATED YESTERDAY
WAS TO SEEAVE THE CARD
WELL, JOB NUMBER ONE
DONE
SHE IS DEFINITELY
GOING TO HAVE HER
PLAYING RIGHTS FOR THE
2020 SEASON.
>> WELL, SHE PLAYED
THE ROUND SHE NEEDED
TO PLAY AND THE ROUND
SHE REALLY REALLY
WANTED TO PLAY
SO REGARDLESS OF HOW
IT COMES OUT, THAT IS
SUCH A FEATHER IN HER
CAP.
>> SHE IS ON THE MOVE.
SHE SHOULDN'T GO FAR
BOGEY-FREE ROUND OF
BEST OF THE DAY.
SHANSHAN FENG ALSO
ALONGSIDE HER.
A SHOT BACK.
having your clubs lost or
damaged by the airlines.
Sending your
own clubs ahead
with
ShipSticks.com
makes it
fast & easy
to get to your golf destination.
With just a few clicks
or a phone call,
we'll pick up and deliver
your clubs on-time,
guaranteed,
for as low as $39.99.
ShipSticks.com saves you
time and money.
Make it simple.
Make it Ship Sticks.
>>> INE PA, THIS
AT8, HER THIRD, PAR
WAS ING LA
NIT ABFNHOW
DIFFULT ANLOW SHE
WAS ING  HAVTO
GOO HAVEHANC
TODAY, AND DIDN'T VE
N TH IT OOPENING
NISTORY.
OT YEA NOT IN TH ID
THE OTHETW HAVE A
KIM TO GO FIRST
LEAN LINE TO THE
LE
137  THE TOTAL
NUMB
SIGNIFICANTLY OM
ANOTHER HOOK LIE
PICKED VY CLEANL
ONCE AGSTRAIG PT WE HAVE  THE
SEEN FROM BELOW E
HOLE, BUT IT'S A GSHOT
>> SHE IS GOING TO
METHING VERY SCIALE
SHNARROWLYISSES
ANCHES OF THAT
RST FL,TREE, E CAN
GET  CSE TO THE
FLAG
JUST A YARD  TWO,
SHE'D HAVE A CHANCE TO
GET IT CLOSE.
>> WEDGE OR A 9 IRON,
JERRY?
>> YEAH, I DIDN'T GET
THE SIGNAL FROM DAVID.
I CAN'E HIT SERIGHT
NOW.
IT'S PRETTY DARK.
>> REALLY HARD TO CUT
A VERY LOFTED CLUB.
>> YEAH.
CLEAN PAST THE TREES,
WHICH MEANS IT HAS TO
BE LEFT OF THE HOLE.
>> YEAH, IT LANDED
JUST LEFT OF THE
GREEN, JERRY
CAUGHT THE SLOPE AND
NOW IT'S WELL DOWN
BELOW.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THE
CHURCH BELLS ARE
GOING.
>> I THINK IT'S A
DINNER BELL.
>> IT IS 7:00 AT
NIGHT.
>> 121 UP THE HILL
9 IRON
DEFINITELY GOING TO BE
RIGHT OF THE FLAG,
ISN'T IT, JUDY
>> WELL, YOU WOULD
THINK SO
>> THAT'S THE
INTENTION.
>> YEAH, IF SHE HAS
THE SPACE TO DO IT,
THAT IS THE SMART SAFE
PLAY>> THE SPACE TO DO.
THIS ISN'T RIGHT OF
THE FLAG
>> BEYOND THE FLAG
>> SHE WENT WITH A 9
IRON THERE, BUT SHE'S
PUTTING.
SHE HAS THE LEAD FOR
NOW.
OF COURSE, THE FLAG AT
18 MIGHT CATCH HER
JUST YET
>> SHANSHAN TRYING TO
GET IT CLOSE, MAKE THE
PUTT, GET IT TO 14
UNDER AND POST.
>> WHAT AN IMPORTANT
SHOT RIGHT HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'VE SEEN SO MANY
GOOD ONES IN THE LAST
30 MINUTES.
>> YEAH, I DON'T THINK
SHE'D GIVE HER -- A
POSITIVE TALK, THOUGH,
AND THOUGHTS
SHANSHAN, THE VETERAN,
29 YEARS OF AGE FROM
CHINA.
12 YEARS OUT ON THE
LPGA TOUR.
TEN WINS OVERALL AND A
MAJOR.
>> SHE IS JENNY TO HER
CLOSE FRIENDS OUT
HERE
SHE SOMETIMES KIDS
AROUND AND CALLS
HERSELF JENNY MONEY.
>> A REALLY POPULAR
PLAYER OUT HERE.
>> YEAH, SUCH A GOOD
GAL.
SHE IS SUCH A
CHARACTER.
SHE NEVER, I HAVE
AST LPGA STA WASOWN.
WITH A WIN AT THE
THORNBERRY CRE
>> YEAH, A GOLF COURSE
WHERE THE SCORES ARE
VERY LOW, AND SHE, OF
COURSE, SHOT SOME VERY
LOW SCORES
>> HOW ABOUT 29 UNDER?
>> YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY
GOOD.
>> THAT'S LOW.
>> YEAH.
>> SECOND LOWEST
72-HOLE SCORE IN LPGA
HISTORY.
AND THINKING ABOUT
THIS PUTT NOW, WHICH
WOULD TIE JIN YOUNG
KO, BE IN THE
CLUBHOUSE AND WAIT TO
SEE WHAT KO DOES
NOT A GIMME TWO-PUTT
BACK AT 17
AND THE WEATHER HAS
CERTAINLY PLAYED A
ROLE IN THIS
TOURNAMENT THROUGH THE
YEARS.
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO
WE HAD HAIL WHEN THEY
WERE FINISHING UP AT
NOT NEARLY THAT TOUGH
TODAY.
>> AND IT WAS ABOUT 30
DEGREES >> I KNOW, IT WAS
CRAZY.
>> WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
>> ALWAYS THE
OPTIMIST
>> KEEPS GIVING
HERSELF SOME TOUGH
CHIPS, SUNG HYUN PARK,
RECENTLY.
>> THIS IS REALLY
TOUGH.
SHE DOES NOT OPEN THE
BLADE AS MH AS MOST
PLAYERS WOULD.
>> BUMP-AND-RUN IT, IT
LOOKS LIKE.
>> SUCH A TIGHT LIE.
DN'T HAVE MUCH
OPTION
BEAUTIFULLY DONE
>> WE'VE TALKED A LOT
ABOUT HER AND A LO
DIFFERENT THGS ABOUT
ABSOTE TTH WITH
ALL OF THE GOOD
PLAYERS OUT HE, SHE
REALLY STILL HAS A
CHANCE TO BE A VERY
DOMINATING PLAYER.
>> NOT WASTING MUCH
TIME
SHANSHAN FENG, THIS
FOR BIRDIE TO SHE  THE LEAD
>> SHE TRIED
>> MY GOODNESS
>> ITRIED TO
PUTT TNOT GO IN E
HO
>> JEN MON, AND
TH WAS  OST  YEANEY.
>>HAWAS RIGHTHERE.
68, FINISHES U 13
UNR.
>>OR BIRDIE FOR JI
YOUNG KO
RETTY MUCH S
IFT DRS.
TUING LITT
RIT.
>> SHE'S GOT IT.
THATIGHT BE THE
YOG KOENT FOR JIN
>> YEAH,HEAME TO
THE LPGA TR PLAYG
RELYELL. W
THG TOF THE YEAR
BE ANY SWING HER
DOWN, N'THINK.
EN YOUAVE WHAT YOU
AN THIS I T
OVERSTATEMT, BUT
IT'S LITTLE BITHE
WASHE PLAY A
MIPROOSTAKE-GAME
SHE DOESN'ALLOW
BIG NUMBER MAKE
THMISTA WRONG TI
KIND OF CREEPS UP ONIS
SHEDHERE, GETS T
HER BUNESS. T
JOO KI WHO IS YO
PUTTING FOR BIIE
HERSF.  >>O HAVE
H FEELIN HER
STOMACH RIT NO
YH, FST PUTT I
VE SEEN OUT OF HYO
JOO M WHERSHE
COILED
SHE S BEEN SOKING
IT SO MAELOUSLY.
SHE MUST BE TTLE
>> OUT OF GAS.
U KNOW, U KNOW
CONSCIOUSLY THATOU
KEEPRYING,UT WHEN
YOU HAVE ACTLLLOSTY
WH YOU WOULD-
WERE HAD, IT'S
RY HD.
>> BIRDIE PUTT, IN
PARK TSH UO FINIAT
10 UND
REER NOT DONT,
HALL OF FA
YMPIC GOLD
SHE'LL EP AR
IGHTH AT LST
THE REEN HAS BUT
BENGED T KO ANDH IT
PONTIALLY IS E
CHAMPISHIP
I sewhat's possiblinstead .
Others see cracked concrete,
broken backboards,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
Art can change it all.
Bright colors, a bold vision,
it can be somewhere that
brings people together.
For games  hangout
or whatever.
A place that makeople proud
li "this imy neighborhood."ade
For games  hangout
oj    or whatever.
and site with GoDay.
How willou make ur mar
Make the Wld You Wt
>>> SO THE PAR 5,
PLAYING 454 YARDS
Y. TODA
IT HAS BEEN THE
EASIEST OUT THERE.
BUT THE TWO-SHOTOWN,
CUSHION IS QUITE A
RELIEF RIGHT NOW
LL, RELIEF IS NOT
E RIGHT WORD
NE, BUT THE L YOU ARE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
WHERE SHE WAS FIVE
HOLES AGO.
THIS IS DRAMATIC, THIS
TURNAROUND.
>> VERY DRAMATIC
LAST YEAR WHEN SHE WAS
THE ROOKIE OF THE YEAR
SHE WAS NUMBER ONE IN
GREENS IN REGULATION
ON THIS TOUR AND SHE
WAS NUMBER TWO IN
DRIVING ACCURACY
HOW CAN YOPLAY A BAD
ROUND OFOLF?
>> WELL, 3 WOOD IN
HANDS, SHE KNOWS SHE
HAS A TWO-SHOT LEAD.
THAT CONVERSATION TOOK
PLACE.
NO OTHER EXPLANATION
SHE COULD HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET HOME IN
TWO WITH A DRIVER.
H,O. I THI HE WOULD
SHE WAS ABLE TO HIT
.
>> GOING NA A COUGHING
FIT.
>> HA M ALDAY.NE
>>HAT IS RIG DOW
BROADWAY
>>S ORDERED.
>> WT OUR FRIE
SAYS IN THE MAYOR'
OFFICE
>> IS THAT LIKE THE
PRINPAL'S OFFICE
>> I DON'THINK SO.
I THINK THE MAYOR'S
OFFICE IS A BETTER
PLACE.
>> YOU KNOAT ONE
WELL
>> AND THE SWING'T CHAA
NO, NO, NO.
SHGETS THE WEIGHTO
A LITTLE SPEED GOING,
STAYS IN THE SHOT
BEAUTIFULLY.
FINISH TO A NICE HH
YOU'VE GOT TO LOVE IT.
>> THAT'S REALLYICE, N
THE TEE SHOT OUT OF
SUYUN PARK
>> IIT WAS ALREADY
ON HER MIND, THE LEAD,
PLAYING IN THE FIN
GROUP  AAJOR M
CHAMPIIP AND NOT
COMING THROUGHWHAT
DOES THIS DO TO HER?>>I
S JUST, YOU
KNOW, IT ONE MORE
TIME THAT SHE'S PUT
HERSELF IN THI
POTION AND PROBABLY
T RFORMED THE WAY
WAY WE KNOSHW E N.HE
YOU JUST KEEP
TRYING TO WHIP IT, AND
SHWILL
AND SHHAS ONY
>>ERE  WELL.> YEAH.
>> HYO JOO KIM HAS WON
HERE BEFORE.
HAD THE LEAD COMING TO
THAT PAR 3 14th IN THE
BUNKER
A HORRIBLE LIE
LEFT IT IN THE
FOOTPRINT, AND THE
DOUBLE
THE FINAL DAY AT THE
EF I DON'T KNOW
CHAMPIONSHIP
VIANHAMPIO.
Greariches wl fi youwh Liber
so you oy pay
caI ev you?
what youWo Thank Zol Hw
Mae yo
Liberty. L.
On pay for what you need.Libet
, lady. Taxi
Sorry,or
It's okay
Man, this guys gotta gff
green.
know wha You should
just...
H's letting them pthrough.
know wha YNicechuld
just...
Here p.
wow! That's soic you!
ank you.
Clsy move.
How do we get t of here?idea.
Wah out.
Taour Map with ycard.
TH-YEAR-OLD,
SEATIOL YEAR
N
MENTNED MAR.
INMULTIP  TOOD LEADING E TOUR
IN SCORING
CME GLOBE.
THE LPGA TOUR.
ALL GHTHEREIN E IRWAY
>> JLAYINGP WITH
CAN'T LY HIT MH
REHAAT DONE.
YOU'VE GOT TFE FOR
HER, JUDY.PL
SILLIANTLY R SO
LO ANDN E
AWFUUL BREAK.
>> YH,T  JUS
HAS PLAYED SOME
'S THE NATURE OF T
GAME TUGH WHEN THI
MA PEOE ARE THIS
GOOD
YOU CAT MA
MISTAKE.
AN'T FORGET R
BIIE AT , TO
A DIULT PA4.
ITAS A BIGUTT SH
MADEMIFF BOG
AT 12.
INACT, BOTH MADE
GEBACK AT 12
ANTHREE RAIGHT
PARS AND THE BIRDIE ON
THE LAST WITH THE
TWO-SHOT CUSHION.
>> I THINK THE BACK
NINE HAS EARNED A LOT
OF RESPECT THIS WEEK
>>S EVENTFOR
THANTHING ELSE
SO MUCCAN HAEN
LIOKS LIKE A LEVEL
AN RHTSSHANON
MIGHEV >> AOTNG BERIGHT
TROUBLE.
>>EL 1UNDER AN NOT,
THAT IS REOUGHLY A T
ASK.
SO JIN YNGO
STRIDE TO HER
NOT NEEDINANYTHI
T A PAR, ITHAT
>> YEAWOLAYERS
THE CLUBHOU
>> JIN YOUNG KO AND
SHANSHAN FENG. JUST LO
SOMEWHAT DRY AREA.
>> ON A DAY LIKE THIS,
CERTAINLY WORTH A SHOT
OR TWO
SHEAS HIT I96
YARDS, WEDGER.
NOT ENOUGHIME FOR
SLIPPE TO GET
ONAY SOULDT
WIN.
>> HER WAGGLIS
ALWAYS THE LTLE
PRE-ROINE THATHE
TAKEAWDOES W
>> ON THE GREEN AND
THAT'S ALL SHE NEEDED.
>> COULD HAVE BEEN
VERY CLOSE, BUT SHE
ACTUALLY JUST STRUCK
IT A LITTLE BIT TOO
WELL.
>> YEAH.
A LITTLE BIT OF RISE
BEYOND THE PIN
SHANSHAN REALIZING
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
WAS HANGING AROUND,
BUT IT WILL BE A SHARE
OF SECOND PLACE.
>> TWO PRETTY GOOD
WEEKS FOR SHANSHAN
A WIN AND A TIE FOR
SECOND
>> AND ANOTHER MAJOR
NEXT WEEK.
>> HYO JOO KIM NEEDS
BIRDIE TO GET INTO
THAT TIE FOR SECOND.
>> JENNIFER KUPCHO
ALSO REALIZING THAT 13
IS GOING TO COME UP
SHORT.
>> WELL, TALK ABOUT
HER BEING ON THE LPGA
TOUR JUST A FEW
SEASONS.
FOUR WINS ALREADY.
THIS WILL BE A SECOND
MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIP,
BUT SHE BWON TEN TIMES
ON THE KOREAN LPGA
TOUR AS WELL
THIS IS A PLAYER WHO
IS ONLY 24 YEARS OLD,
BUT SHE IS A VETERAN
NOW AND SHE IS MAYBE A
LONG WAY FROM BEING
DONE
THERE ARE A LOT OF
WINS IN HER FUTURE.
>> AND IF YOU GET TO
MEET HER, YOU GET TO
KNOW HER
EVEN IF YOU JUST WATCH
HER IN GOLF
TOURNAMENTS AND ON
YOUR TELEVISION
SCREEN, SHE IS VERY
MATURE
SHE HAS GROWN UP
SHE TAKES THINGS SORT
OF AS THEY COME.
SHE DOESN'T GET TOO
HIGH OR TOO LOW, WHICH
IS USUALLY THE MARK OF
SOMEBODY WHO IS GOING
TO LAST A LONG TIME.
>> TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT EXACTLY WHERE SUNG
HYUN PARK ENDED UP.
>> SHE IS IN THE
FLATBED AND STANDING
ON A ROCK.
>> EVENTFUL TO THE
END.
Everything your trip needs,
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
♪ ["Stuck in the Middle
with You" by Stealers Wheel] ♪
♪  ♪
♪ Well I don't know why
I came here tonight ♪
♪ I got the feeling that
something ain't right ♪
♪ I'm so scared in case
I fall off my chair ♪
You can't always
choose how you travel
But now, you can choose
a little extra comfort
♪ Jokers to the right, here I am
stuck in the middle with you ♪
Apparently we come from
a long line of Haberdashers.
We chose Eleanor.
It was
great-grandma's name.
So we're in this little
town near Salerno
and everyone has
Dad's eyebrows.
Help your family discover
their unique story,
with a gift from Ancestry.
>>> JERRY, HAVE THEY
FIGURED THIS OUT FOR
PARK
>> YEAH, THEY CALLED
FOR A RULING TO SEE IF
THEY COULD MOVE A
LOOSE IMPEDIMENT, AND
THEY COULD, AND SHE IS
ALLOWED TO TAKE
PRACTICE SWINGS.
I HATE TO MAKE LIGHT
OF A SERIOUS
SITUATION, BUT IT'S
GOING TO BRING A LOT
OF PEOPLE THIS THINK
ABOUT "CADDYSHACK"
RIGHT HERE
>> THE FLOWERS
>> DON'T DO THIS,
JUDY, WHEN YOU PLAY ON
THE WEEKEND, OKAY?
>> CERTAINLY A SHOT
YOU HAVE PROBABLY
NEVER PRACTICED IN
YOUR ENTIRE LIFE.
>> LOOK AT THE STANCE.
MY GOSH.
>> SPEAKING OF GREAT
BALANCE.
OH, BOY.
>> YEP
ONE OF THOSE DAYS.
AND IT HAPPENS EVEN TO
THE NUMBER ONE PLAYER
IN THE WORLD
>> WELL, IT'S A HARD
ASK, BUT SHE COULD
STILL MAKE PAR
>> WHICH WOULD PUT HER
AT 11 UNDER, A SHARE
OF FIFTH PLACE WITH
ARIYA JUTANUGARN
THIS LONG WAIT FOR JIN
YOUNG KO, YOU ARE
GOING, I'M GLAD I'M UP
BY TWO
OTHERWISE, THIS WAIT
WOULD BE AN ETERNITY
>> DOWNHILL LIE, DEEP
WET ROUGH.
NOT A LOT OF GREEN TO
WORK WITH, BUT THE
CONTOUR IS NOT GOING
TO HURT HER TOO MUCH
SHE COULD GET THIS
CLOSE.
>> THE LAST SEVERAL
HOLES, THOUGHT SHE WAS
DONE
SHE HAD FALLEN TOO FAR
BACK
THEN SHE HOLES THE
BUNKER SHOT AT 14.
SHE IS NOT ABLE TO
CAPITALIZE ON THAT
CAME BACK, MADE BOGEY
AT THE PAR 5 15th.
>> WELL, THAT 14th,
THE PAR 3, AT SOME
POINT, AND MAYBE MORE
THAN ONCE THIS WEEK,
PLAYED AS THE HARDEST
HOLE ON THE GOLF
COURSE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IT SURE PROVED
ITS POINT TODAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS, I
GUESS YOU HAD TO PLAY
A VERY SMART SHOT.
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS A
QUITE DIFFICULT HOLE
LOCATION
ONCE AGAIN, A LOT OF
HOLES HAD TO BE PLACED
ON HIGH GROUND
>> FORTUNATE JUST TO
GET THIS ROUND IN
TODAY AND NOT GO TO
MONDAY
ALL RIGHT.
DOESN'T NEED IT,
OBVIOUSLY, BUT FINISH
IN STYLE
I ASKED YOU ABOUT PARK
AND WHAT KIND OF
EFFECT COMING UP
SHORT, NOT GETTING IT
DONE, NOT JUST COMING
UP SHORT, BUT PLAYING
LIKE SHE DID TODAY,
HOW ABOUT HYO JOO KIM?
WITH THE DRAMATICS,
YOU KNOW, ALL THE
DRAMA OF 14, HAVING
THE LEAD.
>> I THINK HYO JOO KIM
IS GOING TO HAVE TO
JUST HAVE A TALK WITH
HERSELF AND SAY THIS
WAS, YOU KNOW, AN
ANOMALY.
THIS WAS JUST ONE HOLE
THAT JUST, YOU KNOW --
AND IT ALL WENT WRONG
ON THAT ONE HOME
BUT I REALLY PLAYED A
GREAT TOURNAMENT
I THINK THAT'S HOW SHE
HAS TO DEAL WITH THIS.
>> 73 IN THE FINAL
ROUND.
A SHARE OF SECOND
PLACE.
>> SO AFTER THE
TRIPLE, SHE PLAYED THE
GOLF COURSE 1 UNDER
PAR.
SO THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
GETTING A HOLD OF
YOURSELF
>> PARK FOR PAR AND A
TOP FIVE FINISH.
AND THE MOVIE STAYS
THE SAME
>> WITH AN ENDING SHE
DIDN'T ENVISION.
>> IT WILL BE VERY
INTERESTING NOW TO SEE
IF SHE WILL BE A
CONTENDER NEXT WEEK AT
WELL BURN IN ENGLAND
SHE CONTENDS SO VERY
OFTEN THAT IT'S HARD
TO BELIEVE SHE
WOULDN'T BE.
BUT SHE'S GOING TO
HAVE TO HAVE SOMEBODY
GIVE HER A LITTLE PEP
TALK AFTER THIS.
>> YEAH, MIGHT HAVE A
LASTING EFFECT
AND THAT'S ALL
RELATIVE WHETHER
THAT'S DAYS, WHETHER
THAT'S WEEKS, BUT
NUMBER ONE PLAYER IN
THE WORLD AT THE
MOMENT AT LEAST.
75, PLAYING IN THE
LAST GROUP ON THE
FINAL DAY.
AND NOW JIN YOUNG KO
TO MAKE IT OFFICIAL.
JIN YOUNG KO IS A
MAJOR CHAMPION AGAIN
SECOND MAJOR OF THE
SEASON
MIGHT NOT BE DONE YET.
THERE IS ANOTHER ONE
NEXT WEEK.
>> THERE SHE IS, THE
NEW NUMBER ONE PLAYER
IN THE WORLD, SECOND
MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIP AT
THE AGE OF 24, JIN
YOUNG KO, FINAL ROUND
OF 67 AND A TWO-SHOT
VICTORY OVER JENNIFER
KUPCHO
SHANSHAN FENG AND HYO
JOO KIM, TWO MAJORS
THIS SEASON.
THREE WINS IN ALL.
EI