GREAT EXPERIENCE,
BUT I'D LOVE TO STAY HERE AND
HANG OUT WITH YOU FOR LONGER,
BUT WE GOT TO HEAD
BACK TO VEGAS.
DUDE, BUT THAT WAS
A GREAT INSTALL.
THAT WAS GREAT.
HE'S SO MUCH FUN, THOUGH.
YEAH, HE'S A GREAT GUY.
♪
Brett: YEAH, THAT WAS
A LOT OF FUN, MAN.
OH, IT WAS
DEFINITELY COOL.
WHAT THE [BLEEP]?
STOP THE CAR!
OH, MY GOD!
AAH, SNAKE!
[ LAUGHS ]
I GOT YOU BACK, BRETT!
YEAH!
Brett:
ON THIS EPISODE OF "TANKED"...
BASKETBALL SUPERSTAR
HASSAN WHITESIDE
FROM THE MIAMI HEAT
WANTS A TANK.
SO YOU'RE THINKING BIG.
NO, I'M THINKING BIG.
HOW ARE WE GETTING IT
IN HERE?
A BOAT.
[BLEEP]
-DON'T EVEN BOTHER.
-WHAT?
THIS TANK AIN'T GOING IN.
BOTTOM'S BLOWN OUT.
Brett:
BOTTOM OF THE TANK IS CRACKED.
[BLEEP]
IT'S NOT GOING ON THE BOAT,
IT'S NOT GOING ACROSS THE CANAL,
AND IT'S NOT GOING IN.
I'VE NEVER
SEEN THIS HAPPEN.
I KNOW.
ME NEITHER.
WE CAN'T
PUT THE TANK IN TODAY.
Y'ALL NOT KIDDING?
DOES HE REALLY?
NO, WE'RE NOT KIDDING.
WE'RE 100% SERIOUS.
LIKE, DEAD SERIOUS.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I ACTUALLY FELT LIKE
ATM LET SOMEBODY DOWN.
Wayde: I'M WAYDE KING.
Man: YEAH!
Brett: I'M BRETT RAYMER.
JACKPOT, BABY!
WE'RE TWO NEW YORKERS
WHO MOVED TO LAS VEGAS
TO FOLLOW OUR DREAMS...
TO CREATE UNDERWATER WORLDS
LIKE NO ONE'S EVER SEEN.
WOW!
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
OUR FAMILY IS THE NUMBER-ONE
AQUARIUM BUILDER IN THE WORLD.
I WAS FORCED
INTO THIS RELATIONSHIP.
I MARRIED BRETT'S SISTER.
I LOVE YOU.
Brett:
AND MY DAD RUNS OPERATIONS.
WE CALL HIM "THE GENERAL."
THIS IS THE WAY I ROLL!
WE MAY FIGHT,
BUT SOMEHOW WE MAKE IT WORK.
AAH!
LISTEN, YOU GUYS
ARE THE EXPERTS.
IT'S GONNA BE AMAZING.
IF YOU CAN DREAM IT...
...WE CAN BUILD IT.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
DISCOVERY COMMUNICATIONS
♪
WE'RE ON OUR WAY
TO MIAMI, FLORIDA, TODAY
TO MEET
A BRAND-NEW CLIENT.
MIAMI HEAT PLAYER
HASSAN WHITESIDE.
YEAH!
HASSAN WHITESIDE HAS BEEN
RISING THROUGH THE RANKS
TO BECOME A NEW SUPERSTAR
AND SIGNED WITH THE MIAMI HEAT
IN 2014.
-CRAZY, HUH?
-AT LOT OF WORK GOING ON.
A LOT OF CONSTRUCTION.
-WOW, LOOK AT THE CARS.
-NICE.
-THERE'S MY CAR.
-YEAH, NICE.
-IS THAT HIM?
-I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
PLAYING BY THE POND?
HEY, HEY,
WHAT'S UP, FELLAS?
HEY!
HEY, HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS IS MY COUSIN DAWUD
RIGHT HERE.
HEY, DAWUD, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
BRETT, LOOK LIKE
THE OLDER ONE, MAN.
YOU LOOK OLDER IN PERSON.
-I LOOK OLDER IN PERSON?
-YEAH.
DUDE, I THINK
IT'S THE GRAY HAIRS.
WHATEVER. GRAY HAIRS?
I DON'T HAVE ANY HAIR.
DID YOU JUST MOVE IN
OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, I JUST MOVED IN
A MONTH AGO.
YOU KNOW,
AS YOU CAN SEE,
IT'S CONSTRUCTION
GOING ON EVERYWHERE.
I WANT TO GET A TANK
INSIDE THE HOUSE.
I SEEN Y'ALL GUYS
DO SHAQ.
YOU GUYS GONNA MAKE ME CRY --
ON THE INSIDE, OF COURSE.
DO DWIGHT HOWARD'S TANK.
OH, MY GOD.
[ Laughing ] WHOO!
I WANT SOMETHING AMAZING.
I LOVE IT. IT'S GETTING
AROUND THE NBA. I LOVE IT.
SO, YOU'RE INTO FISH,
I SEE THAT, HUH?
I LOVE FISH.
WE GOT THE FISH RIGHT HERE.
-YOU GOT FISH?
-YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
OH, YOU GOT SOME GOLDFISH
AND STUFF, HUH?
I'M GONNA PUT THEM
IN HERE.
YOU PUT THEM IN THE POND?
YEAH, YOU SEE THEY GOT
THAT LITTLE FOREST GOING ON.
YOU GOT THE LITTLE MOAT
GOING AROUND THE HOUSE, HUH?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
I'M TRYING TO GET IT RIGHT.
IT'S NOT A MOAT YET UNTIL
WE GET SOME SHARKS IN THERE.
YOU KNOW, OUTSIDE'S
NOT THE GREATEST FOR SHARKS.
DO YOU REALIZE
WHAT YOU JUST SAID?
WHAT?
OUTSIDE ISN'T THE GREATEST
FOR SHARKS?
THEY LIVE OUTSIDE
NATURALLY IN THE OCEAN.
GOT IT.
I WANT A GREAT WHITE.
GREAT WHITE
WOULD NOT GO IN THERE.
NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
THEY CAN'T KEEP GREAT WHITES IN
CAPTIVITY IN A PUBLIC AQUARIUM,
LET ALONE
IN A HOME AQUARIUM.
-SO, NO GREAT WHITES?
-YOU WANT A FISH TANK, RIGHT?
YEAH, LET'S GO.
LET'S CHECK THE HOUSE OUT.
BUT THEY "TANKED."
Brett: WOW!
I THINK I KNOW WHY
YOU BOUGHT THIS HOUSE, MAN,
'CAUSE THIS IS THE FRONT DOOR
THAT YOU CAN WALK INTO
WITHOUT DUCKING.
LET'S GO UPSTAIRS.
WHAT DO WE GOT HERE, FELLAS?
WHAT ROOM IS THIS?
-BEDROOM.
-MASTER BEDROOM.
ALL RIGHT, SO,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
I WANT TO PUT A TANK
OVER HERE.
MAYBE OVER HERE
OR OVER HERE.
WHERE'S THE TV GONNA GO,
AND WHERE'S THE BED GONNA GO?
I'M GONNA JUST CHOOSE
THE OPPOSITE.
GOTCHA. SO, I WOULD RECOMMEND
MORE THE BED ON THIS SIDE,
BECAUSE IF THE SHOWER'S RUNNING
AND YOU'RE SLEEPING,
YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR
THE WATER RUNNING.
HE WAS NOT ASKING YOUR OPINION
WHERE TO PUT HIS BED.
I WAS JUST OFFERING.
LISTEN TO ME.
WE CAME HERE TO BUILD A TANK.
FOCUS.
YOU WANT
SOMETHING SMALL, BIG?
I MEAN,
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
-BIG.
-I KNEW YOU WERE GONNA SAY THAT.
I HAD A FEELING
"BIG" WAS COMING.
IF YOU WANT SOMETHING BIG,
I WOULD SAY THE BEDROOM'S
PROBABLY NOT THE SPOT
BECAUSE NUMBER ONE,
WE'RE ON THE SECOND FLOOR,
OKAY, AND IT'S GONNA BE
A LOT OF WEIGHT.
SO IF YOU HAVE
A LOT OF WEIGHT,
POTENTIALLY, YOU'D HAVE TO
SHORE UP THE FLOORS.
IT'D PROBABLY BE A NIGHTMARE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
AND TO GET IT UP HERE
WOULD JUST PROBABLY BE A PROBLEM
CONSIDERING THE STEPS.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M HERE FOR.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I GOT A SPOT FOR THIS.
I GOT SPOT.
-YOU GOT A SPOT?
-I GOT A SPOT.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO CHECK IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT THE VIEW?
COOL, I LIKE IT.
WOW, NICE.
I SEEN A DOLPHIN FLIP
OUT THERE THE OTHER DAY.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
PUTTING A FISH TANK RIGHT HERE.
NEXT TO THE HOT TUB.
IT GOT SPEAKERS.
BRETT, YOU COULD SHOW ME
YOUR FAVORITE DANCE MOVES.
-OH, MAN.
-HEY.
SO YOU WANT TO CHILL
IN THE HOT TUB,
HAVE A NICE TANK OUT THERE,
AND ENJOY.
THINK OF SOMETHING
THAT'S AWESOME,
AND THEN TIMES THAT
BY 5.
AND THAT'S THE IDEA.
Both: SOMETHING AWESOME.
HMM.
MY ONLY CONCERN UP HERE --
ONE, IT'S OUTSIDE.
YOU GOT TO TEMPERATURE CONTROL
DURING THE WINTER AND SUMMERS.
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF ANY MORE WEIGHT UP HERE
IS GONNA BE GOOD.
WE COULD THROW YOU OFF.
I'M JUST SAYING THERE'S A LOT
OF WEIGHT UP HERE IN GENERAL.
SO, LET ME ASK A QUESTION.
WHY DO YOU WANT A FISH TANK?
I LOVE FISH TANKS, YOU KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S ART.
AND I HAD ONE
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
YOU KNOW,
I HAD A SALTWATER TANK.
IT WAS LIKE 100 GALLONS.
SO I REALLY JUST -- I MISS IT.
YOU LIKE SALTWATER FISH.
I LOVE --
I LOVE SALTWATER FISH.
ALL RIGHT,
YOU KNOW WHAT, FELLAS?
I LOVE YOUR IDEAS, BUT LET'S
GO CHECK OUT THE OTHER SPOT.
I THINK IT'S GONNA
WORK OUT BEST.
YOU GOT TO GET ME SOMETHING.
THEY DON'T LISTEN TO US.
YOU GOT TO GET US
SOME SHARKS IN HERE.
-I'M TRYING.
-I NEED THE SHARK.
♪
-WE GOT A SPOT OVER HERE.
-ALL RIGHT, LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I GOT A CHEF OVER HERE COOKING
IT UP RIGHT NOW.
-CHEF RUDY.
-WHAT'S UP, CHEF?
SO I WAS THINKING
OF THIS SPOT.
THAT'S NOT A SPOT.
THIS IS A WALL.
IT'S A GOOD SPOT.
I LIKE IT.
IT'S BIG.
IT'S OPEN, AND YOU CAN
SEE IT FROM ANY PLACE
IN THE HOUSE HERE.
MOST PEOPLE SPEND MOST
OF THEIR TIME IN THE KITCHEN.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
-TRUE.
SO YOU'RE THINKING BIG.
NO, I'M THINKING BIG.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
THIS IS
A REALLY BIG CORNER.
YOU GOT TWO WALLS,
ACTUALLY.
YOU'RE ON FIRE TODAY.
SHARKS DON'T LIKE
TO LIVE OUTDOORS.
THE SPECIAL CORNER'S
MADE UP OF TWO WALLS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT YOU COME UP WITH NEXT.
MAYBE WE DO
WHERE IT COMES FROM HERE,
COMES OUT,
AND THEN IT BOWS.
IT'S A BIG BOW FRONT.
-SO THE WHOLE CORNER?
-THE WHOLE CORNER.
HOLD ON.
YOU'RE THINKING OF BACK PANEL,
BACK PANEL,
AND THEN SOME SORT
OF A RADIUS FRONT.
BIG, HUGE, RADIUS FRONT.
AND THEN BIG.
IS IT GONNA BE 7 FOOT LIKE HIM
OR 6'4" LIKE ME?
NO, IT'LL BE AT LEAST 7 FOOT
ON THE STAND.
I LIKE THAT.
WHAT ABOUT FEEDING THE FISH?
YOU'LL HAVE NO PROBLEM
WITH THAT.
JUST GO LIKE THIS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHAT DO WE WANT TO DO
ABOUT THEMEING?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING IN MIND
THAT YOU WANT TO DO?
I REALLY LOVE BASKETBALL,
SO I WANTED TO ADD
BASKETBALL TO IT.
IT'S A REALLY MODERN HOUSE.
I WANTED THE STAINLESS STEEL
TO MATCH THE POOL TABLE.
Wayde: OKAY, SO THE POOL TABLE'S
RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, THAT'S LIKE
A HIGH-FINISHED MIRRORED LOOK.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, IT'S YOUR TANK,
BUT I DON'T LIKE IT.
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO.
I DON'T CARE NONE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
-I LOVE IT.
-JUST IGNORE HIM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, SO YOU WANT
THE FACADE AND THE CANOPY,
THE EXTERIOR
TO MATCH THE POOL TABLE.
AND THEN ON THE INTERIOR,
YOU WANT US TO DO SOMETHING
BASKETBALL-THEMED.
PUT YOUR OWN SPIN ON IT.
I REALLY WANT YOU GUYS
TO JUST DO WHAT Y'ALL DO.
THIS IS A BIG TANK.
HOW ARE WE GETTING IT IN HERE?
A BOAT.
A BOAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN A BOAT?
I GOT TO BRING IT IN BY BOAT
'CAUSE THE DOORS ARE NARROW.
SO THAT'S WHY I HAVEN'T GOT
MY FURNITURE IN HERE.
YOU LOAD IT SOMEWHERE,
PUT IT ON A BOAT,
AND THEN BRING IT ON THE DOCK
THAT YOU GOT OUT THERE?
ARE YOU, LIKE,
BEING SERIOUS?
VERY SERIOUS.
WE'RE IN FLORIDA
MEETING WITH MIAMI HEAT PLAYER
HASSAN WHITESIDE,
AND HE WANTS A TANK.
YEAH, HE'S A BIG GUY,
AND HE WANTS A HUGE TANK.
NOT ONLY I WANT IT WIDE,
I WANT IT TALL.
-THAT'S PRETTY TALL.
-THAT'S TALL.
SINCE THE TANK WILL TOO BIG
TO FIT THROUGH HIS DOORS,
HE BROUGHT UP A CHALLENGE
WE NEVER FACED BEFORE.
HOW ARE WE GETTING IT
IN HERE?
A BOAT.
A BOAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN A BOAT?
THAT'S HOW I GOT
MY FURNITURE IN HERE.
-YOU BEING SERIOUS?
-VERY SERIOUS.
Wayde: YOU'RE SAYING
YOU CAN'T GO AROUND
TO THE BACKYARD
OR ANYTHING?
YEAH, IT'S KIND OF LIKE
WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
A REGULAR TANK.
-WE TALKING ABOUT A...
-BIG TANK.
SO YOU WANT SOMETHING
LIKE RIGHT HERE.
BIG.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
I'M TOO SHORT.
[ LAUGHS ]
SO, LIKE RIGHT HERE,
JUST TAKE UP THIS WHOLE --
ALL THIS.
YOU HAVE TO LOAD IT SOMEWHERE,
PUT IT ON A BOAT,
AND THEN BRING IT ON THE DOCK
THAT YOU GOT OUT THERE?
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
-I NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE.
-ME EITHER.
IF IT CAN BE DONE,
ATM's GONNA GET IT DONE.
-ANY FAVORITE FISH?
-CLOWNFISH.
EVERYBODY LOVES
THE CLOWNFISH.
'CAUSE THEY TELL
GOOD JOKES.
OH, YOU GOT A JOKE?
WHAT KIND OF JEANS
DOES MARIO WEAR?
DENIM, DENIM, DENIM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YO, I TELL THE SAME JOKE
ALL THE TIME.
FISH WALKS INTO A BAR.
BARTENDER GOES,
"CAN I HELP YOU?"
FISH GOES, "WATER!"
YOU TELL THAT JOKE
ALL THE TIME?
-I GET A LOT OF LAUGHS.
-NO, HE DOESN'T.
-IT GROWS ON YOU.
-YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'RE GONNA HEAD BACK TO VEGAS.
GIVE US A DAY.
WE'LL PUT SOMETHING TOGETHER,
MAKE SURE YOU BOTH LIKE IT.
WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
I NEED IT
BEFORE BASKETBALL SEASON.
OKAY.
WHICH IS REALLY SOON.
-I KNOW. HOW SOON?
-SOON, VERY SOON.
-SOON? CAN WE BUILD IT --
-FELLAS, WE GOT YOU COVERED.
YO, SHARKS AROUND
THE WHOLE PROPERTY.
I HEAR YOU,
BUT I DON'T HEAR YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
GREAT WHITE SHARKS.
WE FLEW HOME
AND DIDN'T DILLY-DALLY
ON THE START OF HIS TANK.
TO BRING A SLICE OF THE OCEAN
INTO A CORNER OF HASSAN'S HOME,
WE'LL MOLD A 7-FOOT-TALL,
8-FOOT-WIDE
BOW-FRONT PIECE OF ACRYLIC
FOR HIS PIE-SHAPED STAND
AND AQUARIUM.
A STAINLESS-STEEL FACADE
WILL MATCH HIS MODERN DECOR.
THE 1,000-GALLON
SALTWATER AQUARIUM
WILL BE TEEMING
WITH COLORFUL FISH,
AND THE CORAL INSERT
WILL FEATURE A SPECIAL
BASKETBALL-THEMED PROP.
♪
THE SHOP DOVE RIGHT INTO
THE HASSAN WHITESIDE PROJECT.
BECAUSE IT'S SUCH A BIG TANK,
WE'RE WORKING WITH A MASSIVE
4-INCH-THICK PIECE OF ACRYLIC.
SO SHAPING IT IS REALLY TRICKY.
WE GOT TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE HAVE A CENTER POINT HERE
AND A CENTER POINT THERE,
SO WHEN IT DRAPES DOWN
IT DRAPES EVENLY
AND WE CAN MATCH THE LINES.
'CAUSE IF THAT'S OFF
A LITTLE BIT,
THAT MEANS LATER ON
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO CUT MORE
AND SAND A LOT MORE.
AND WE DON'T
WANT TO DO THAT.
THIS IS NO BARBECUE, REDNECK.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WE GOT TO MAKE SURE
WE COOK THIS JUST RIGHT.
♪
CHUY, LET'S GET
THE FORKLIFT GOING.
♪
THE STAND IS IN PRODUCTION,
AND THE INSERT TEAM
ALREADY BUILT THE INSERT
FOR HASSAN'S TANK.
YOU GO LOW.
I'LL GO HIGH, ALL RIGHT?
-BLAH!
-REDNECK!
-WHAT'S UP, RED?
-WHAT UP, RED?
WHAT ARE
YOU TWO GOOFBALLS DOING?
MAKING SURE
YOU'RE DOING YOUR WORK.
I'M CLEAR-COATING.
YOU JUMPED, DIDN'T YOU?
UH-HUH, WE SCARED
THE RACCOON OUT OF HIM.
[ LAUGHS ]
THEY BOTH MUST'VE GOT PICKED ON
A LOT IN SCHOOL, RIGHT?
-LOOKING GOOD.
-THIS IS LOOKING GOOD.
I LIKE THE COLORS.
WHAT DO YOU TWO WANT?
WE GOT TO CHANGE
SOME THINGS AROUND.
WE GOT TO SPOOF IT UP.
RIGHT? SPEEF, SPROOF, WHAT?
-SPRUCE.
-SPRUCE IT UP.
AND WAYDE MUST HAVE SLEPT
THROUGH ENGLISH CLASS.
AND YOU KNOW,
HE GAVE US FREE CREATIVE REIN,
SO WE STARTED
THINKING UP SOME IDEAS.
HE GAVE US COMP BLANCHE
TO WHATEVER WE WANT.
AND FRENCH CLASS.
WHAT ABOUT JUST DOING A LOGO
OR SOMETHING LIKE "MH."
MAYBE ON A BASKETBALL.
YOU WANT TO DO A BASKETBALL NOW,
AND YOU WANT TO PUT "MH" ON IT?
CORRECT.
I CAN DO THE BASKETBALL
OUT OF ACRYLIC,
AND I CAN DO THE LETTERS
OUT OF ACRYLIC.
YOU THINK THIS WOULD MAKE
A GOOD-SIZE BASKETBALL?
YEAH,
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD SIZE.
-PRETTY CLOSE.
-THAT IS PRETTY CLOSE.
YOU COULD PUT THE "MH"
ON THERE, TOO.
LETTERS ARE TOO BIG.
THEY CAN ALL BE
PROPORTIONALLY SIZED.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET
A REFERENCE
WHERE YOU WANT THIS TO GO.
THERE YOU GO.
RIGHT THERE, PERFECT.
OKAY.
♪
Wayde: BEFORE RED
CAN WORK ON THE BASKETBALL,
I NEED HIS HELP GETTING
THE ACRYLIC OUT OF THE OVEN.
OPEN HER UP.
THE ACRYLIC'S BEEN IN THE OVEN
OVER SIX HOURS NOW,
SO IT SHOULD BE READY
TO COME OUT.
DUDE, IT'S NOT EVEN HOT.
IT DIDN'T EVEN MOVE.
THIS OVEN HAS TO OPERATE.
DUDE, THIS THING'S
SUPPOSED TO BE BENT RIGHT NOW.
THIS OVEN IS
THE ALL-STAR OF OUR SHOP.
IF IT'S NOT WORKING PROPERLY,
ALL OUR PROJECTS COME TO A HALT,
INCLUDING
HASSAN WHITESIDE'S AQUARIUM.
♪♪
Applebee's New Irresist-A-Bowls
now starting at $7.99.
Now that's Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
Wayde: WE'RE BUILDING A TANK
FOR MIAMI HEAT STAR PLAYER
HASSAN WHITESIDE.
BUT HEAT IS SOMETHING WE HAD
A LITTLE TROUBLE WITH AT ATM.
DUDE, IT'S NOT EVEN HOT.
THIS OVEN HAS TO OPERATE.
WE GOT THE OVEN REPAIRED
AND THE ACRYLIC BENT INTO SHAPE,
BUT RIGHT NOW
WE'RE ON A TIME CRUNCH.
HOW WE DOING, RED?
♪
NOW I'M GRABBING
THE FRONT PIECE OF THE TANK
TO LAY ON THE OTHER PANEL
SO WE CAN PREP FOR GLUING.
GET YOUR EYES ON IT, REDNECK.
BE CAREFUL, GUYS.
A LOT OF WORK IN THIS PANEL.
ALL RIGHT, SO THE PANEL CAME OUT
OF THE OVEN PRETTY GOOD.
WE GOT THE SHAPE THAT WE WANT.
GOT THE OVERFLOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO THIS HAS TO
MATCH UP WITH THIS SIDE.
OH, BOY.
WE GOT A PROBLEM, REDNECK.
THIS PIECE IS GONNA HAVE TO
BE CUT ALL THE WAY DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA GET A CHUNK
OFF THIS MUCH,
AND THAT'S GONNA
HAVE TO BE PERFECT
TO MATCH THIS PIECE
AND GLUED.
NOW THE PIECE IS LAID OUT,
AND WE HAVE TO CUT A LOT OFF.
THERE'S A LOT OF PREP WORK.
IT'S GONNA TAKE HOURS.
GET CHUY AND ALL THE GUYS.
LET'S ROLL.
ALL RIGHT.
THE TEAM CUT, SANDED, AND GLUED
THE SIDES OF THE TANK.
SO IT ALL FITS TOGETHER
PERFECTLY.
NOW WE JUST HAVE TO
GIVE IT TIME TO BOND.
♪
THINGS ARE MOVING FORWARD,
BUT I CAN'T STEP AWAY
FROM THE SHOP,
SO I ASKED THE GIRLS
TO PICK OUT THE FISH
FOR HASSAN WHITESIDE'S TANK
AT SEA DWELLING CREATURES
IN L.A.
BEST PART OF OUR JOB.
IT REALLY IS.
-HEY.
-HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT'S GOING ON, GIRLS?
SO, WE'RE DOING A TANK
FOR HASSAN WHITESIDE.
HE'S FROM THE MIAMI HEAT.
IT'S AN 800-GALLON TANK.
HE DID HAVE ONE SPECIAL REQUEST.
WHAT'S THAT?
HE WANTS A CLOWNFISH.
OH, COOL.
LET'S GO FIND SOME GOODIES.
LET'S GO.
I LOVE ANEMONES.
BUT NOT AS MUCH
AS CLOWNFISH LOVE THEM.
ANEMONES ARE AN INVERTEBRATE,
AND SO MEANING NO SKELETON.
THEY ARE ALSO PREDATORS.
THOSE LITTLE TENTACLES
ARE FILLED
WITH MILLIONS
OF WHAT ARE CALLED NEMATOCYSTS.
NEMATOCYSTS ARE LIKE
A LITTLE, TINY HARPOON
WITH A TETHER ON IT.
AND SO, WHEN A FISH COMES OVER
AND TOUCHES THE ANEMONE,
MILLIONS
OF THESE LITTLE HARPOONS
ARE INJECTED
INTO THE FISH.
AND THEY'RE NOW STUCK
ON TO THE ANEMONE.
AND THE FISH THEN IS PUSHED
INTO THE CENTER OF THE MOUTH,
WHICH IS ALSO
THE STOMACH.
I KNOW THAT CLOWNFISH...
MM-HMM.
...LIVE IN ANEMONES.
YES, THEY DO.
THEY LOVE THEM.
HOW DO THEY NOT GET HURT?
MANY OF THEM USED CORALS
OR ANEMONES
AS THEIR SYMBIOTIC HOST.
THEY HIDE IN THEM FOR PROTECTION
AND AT THE SAME TIME,
BRING FOOD FOR THEIR ANEMONE
OR CORAL HOST.
SO THEY'RE PAYING THEIR DUES.
THEY'RE PAYING THEIR WAY.
Agnes: WE CAN'T HAVE
A LIVING ANEMONE IN OUR TANK
WITH ARTIFICIAL CORAL,
BUT WE'LL MAKE SURE
THE CLOWNFISH HAVE PLACES
TO HIDE AND FEEL SAFE.
LET'S GO.
A LIGHTNING
MAROON CLOWNFISH.
THAT'S A MAROON CLOWN?
WHEN THEY'RE YOUNG,
THEY TEND TO BE
KIND OF ORANGE-Y.
AND AS THEY MATURE,
THEY BECOME A DEEP MAROON RED.
I LIKE THE FACT THAT
IT KIND OF HAS THE HEAT COLORS.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE A FLAME.
PERFECT.
HOW BIG WILL THESE GUYS GET?
6 TO 7 INCHES
ON A REALLY BIG ADULT FEMALE.
THIS IS PERFECT.
OH, HEY.
MIAMI HEAT.
WHOA! I'VE NEVER SEEN A FISH
LIKE THAT.
THAT IS A MIDNIGHT ANGEL.
-OH, WOW.
-THAT IS AWESOME.
IS HE
AN AGGRESSIVE ANGEL?
NO, IT'S ONE
OF THE DWARF ANGELS,
SO IT'S NOT
GOING TO GET BIG.
WORKS WELL
IN MOST ALL COMMUNITY TANKS,
SO IT'S A GREAT FISH.
AND THEY'RE JUMPERS,
RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW
THAT HASSAN IS KNOWN
FOR BEING LIKE
A GREAT REBOUNDER.
WELL, THEN I DON'T THINK
WE COULD'VE PICKED
A BETTER FISH FOR HIM.
♪
Wayde: NOW THAT THE GLUE
IS DRIED ON THE TANK,
WE NEED TO FOCUS
ON THE TOP AND BOTTOM,
WHICH MEANS
WE HAVE TO FLIP IT OVER.
THIS THING'S 2,400 POUNDS.
IT'S NOT EVEN.
IT'S A RADIUS.
IT'S HARD TO PICK IT UP.
THERE'S MORE WEIGHT ON ONE SIDE,
AND IT HAS TO BE FLIPPED OVER
SO WE CAN BLOCK-SAND IT.
WHEN YOU'RE MOVING A TANK
LIKE THAT AND IT'S NOT SQUARE
AND YOU GOT STRAPS ON IT,
THIS THING COULD SLIDE OUT.
IT COULD HURT SOMEBODY.
IT'S VERY DANGEROUS.
SO WE GOT IT OVER.
NOW WE GOT TO BLOCK-SAND THAT.
AND THEN WE'VE GOT TO DO IT
AGAIN AND GLUE AND DO IT AGAIN.
SO THIS THING STILL HAS TO BE
MOVED THREE MORE TIMES.
♪
THE SHINY
STAINLESS-STEEL MATERIAL
FOR HASSAN'S FACADE CAME IN.
SO WE STOPPED OVER
TO CHECK IT OUT
WITH CARL
FROM XTREME METAL WORKS.
MAN, THIS IS EXACTLY THE FINISH
THAT HE'S GONNA WANT.
IT MATCHES THE POOL TABLE
PERFECTLY.
HE'S GOT THAT UNDER CONTROL,
AND THE TANK'S JUST ABOUT READY
TO HIT THE ROAD.
ONLY ONE PART TO FINISH.
-REDNECK.
-YEAH?
-WHAT'S GOING ON, BUDDY?
REDNECK IS CONFIGURING
THE AP LAZER MACHINE
TO CUT OUT OUR BASKETBALL
AND OUR LOGO INSERT.
LET'S CUT IT OUT.
LET ME SEE.
I WANT TO SEE THIS.
I'M GETTING EXCITED NOW.
LOOK HOW IT'S DOING
THE CIRCLE.
YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
LOOK AT THAT.
YOU KNOW THE LINES
ON THE BASKETBALL?
I'M GONNA DO THOSE
IN WHITE.
-WOW, LOOK, IT'S FINISHED.
-WOW.
PULL IT OUT.
YEAH, LET'S CHECK THAT OUT.
LOOK AT THAT.
-IS IT HOT?
-NO.
HERE YOU GO.
-DUDE, LOOK AT THAT.
-YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S PRETTY COOL, HUH?
YEAH, THAT'S AWESOME.
I LIKE THE BLACK ON BLACK,
BUT WE DEFINITELY NEED THE RED
FOR THE TEAM COLORS.
WE ALWAYS NEED
A LITTLE RED.
OH, MY GOD.
♪
THERE YOU GO.
LOOK AT THAT.
NICE.
IT'S DONE.
TAKE IT OUT.
-GO, RED.
-YEAH, RED!
HERE, LET ME SEE THIS.
OH, YOU WANT TO
PUT IT TOGETHER.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
OKAY.
SEE? NOW IT STANDS OUT.
IT'S UPSIDE DOWN.
SPIN IT.
THAT LOOKS G--
HEY, DID YOU SEE THAT?
TEAM INITIALS.
SPIN IT BACK A SECOND.
-YEAH, SPIN IT.
-TURN IT THE OTHER WAY.
THAT'S HIS INITIALS.
LOOK.
YEAH!
HASSAN WHITESIDE.
H.W.
WHY DON'T
WE JUST MAKE IT SPIN?
IF IT SPINS AND IT GOES
ONE WAY, ANOTHER WAY.
-YOU GOT TWO FOR ONE.
-THAT'S RIGHT.
I CAN MAKE IT SPIN.
PERFECT, BRO,
THAT WORKS OUT GREAT.
YEAH, REDNECK, WAY TO PUT A SPIN
ON MY IDEA.
YOUR IDEA --
I CAUGHT THAT.
OKAY.
YOU ALWAYS THINK
EVERYTHING'S YOUR IDEA.
RED, GOOD JOB, BRO.
Brett: AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR A QUICK FISH FACT.
HASSAN KNOWS A THING OR TWO
ABOUT BLOCKING,
BUT HE'S NOT THE ONLY ONE.
FIND OUT AFTER THE BREAK.