AROUND ME SCHOOL WAS LETTING
OUT.
NOW, YOU CAN SEE AGAIN THIS
WINDOW AT THE CAPITOL HILL
PREGNANCY CENTER HAS A BOARD
COVERING IT.
THERE'S ALSO BLOODSTAINS ON
THE WALL WHERE AUGUSTUS FELL
THROUGH TO THE BASEMENT.
WE'RE TOLD AN EMPLOYEE AND AN
INTERN WERE HERE AT THE TIME.
NO CLIENTS.
THIS WAS ALL BEFORE AUGUSTUS
REPORTEDLY WALKED OUT THE
CENTER DOWN THE STREET AND
RANDOMLY AMBUSHED A
FOUR-YEAR-OLD GIRL WHO WAS
WALKING WIND GUST HER MOTHER
NEAR MARYLAND AVENUE AND
EIGHTH STREET IN NORTHEAST.
GOOD SAMARITANS WHO SAW THE
ENCOUNTER IMMEDIATELY RUSHED
TO SAVE THE LITTLE GIRL.
>> I JUST WAS HOPING AND
PRAYING THAT HE DIDN'T, YOU
KNOW, KILL THIS LITTLE GIRL.
I KEPT SAYING DON'T KILL HER,
DON'T KILL HER.
I SAW BLOOD.
SHE WOULDN'T BE SAVED JUST
BECAUSE OF WHAT I DID OR WHAT
I DID BECAUSE THOSE MEN CAME
OUT OF THOSE CARS AND HELPED
TO FREE HER.
THAT'S WHAT REALLY SAVED THAT
LITTLE GIRL.
>> Reporter: THE GOOD
SAMARITANS THERE WANTED TO
REMAIN ANONYMOUS ONE TELLS US
SHE KICKED THE ATTACKER SO
HARD HER LEG WAS INJURED AND
SHE HAD TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
THANKFULLY THIS FOUR-YEAR-OLD
LITTLE GIRL SHE IS DOING JUST
FINE, ALL OF THIS HAPPENING IN
THIS HEAVILY TRAVELED
INTERSECTION WHICH MEANS THERE
WAS PLENTY OF WITNESSES AND
PLENTY OF HELP BLAKE AND
ANGIE, BACK TO YOU.
>> TISHA SO GLAD PEOPLE WERE
THERE AT THIS TIME.
DO WE KNOW IF THIS MAN HAD ANY
TYPE OF HISTORY WITH THIS
CENTER.
WHAT ARE WE FINDING OUT.
>> Reporter: WELL, YOU KNOW,
WHAT WE ARE LOOKING INTO THAT.
HE'S 28 YEARS OLD AND LIVES IN
SPRINGFIELD IN FAIRFAX COUNTY
AND HE DOES HAVE A SOCIAL
MEDIA PRESENCE.
WE'RE INVESTIGATING AND TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT MAY HAVE
TRIGGERED THIS.
SOME WITNESSES HAVE SOME
SUSPICIONS AND TELL US SOME
INFORMATION THAT POLICE TOLD
THEM BUT WE'RE STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT EXACTLY HOW THIS
ALL TRANSPIRED AND WHY IT
TRANSPIRED.
ANGIE.
>> SUCH A BIZARRE STORY.
TISHA THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE NOW ON
THIS THURSDAY.
THIS VERY RAINY THURSDAY.
GRAY SKIES, GLOOMY, WET.
>> IS THAT THE SAME SHOT WE
SAW YESTERDAY.
ARE WE JUST USING THE SAME
PICTURES?  I FEEL LIKE ALL
WEEK IT'S BEEN GLOOM AND DOOM.
>> ANGIE IT'S THE WHITE HOUSE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT US TO SHOW?
IT'S THE WHITE HOUSE CAMERA.
>> NOTHING HAS REALLY CHANGED.
>> IT'S JUST GROUND HOG DAY.
SAME THING OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
>> THAT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
>> SOMEONE PAINT THE WHITE
HOUSE TO MAKE IT LOOK
DIFFERENT.
>> I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
CONDITIONS.
>> YES.
THIS WILL MAKE YOUR HEART
WARMER ANGIE.
IT'S GOING TO BE DIFFERENT.
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> SUNNY BUT IT'S GOING TO BE
REALLY COLD.
WE KNEW IT WAS COMING.
IT'S STILL ON TARGET TO TURN
MUCH, MUCH COLDER BY TOMORROW
MORNING.
LOOK AT STORM TRACKER RADAR.
RAIN IS LONG GONE AS WE
CONTINUE TO CLEAR OUT FROM
WHAT WAS A PRETTY SOGGY START
TO YOUR THUR THURSDAY.
WE KNEW WE WOULD HAVE SHOWERS.
THERE'S THE FRONTAL BOUNDARY
STRUNG UP ALONG THE EAST
COAST.
DRY AIR IS PUSHING IN AS HIGH
PRESSURE STARTS TO SETTLE OVER
US.
STILL SEE A LOT OF CLOUDS
OUTSIDE.
A LIVE LOOK AT NORMAL WEST
D.C.
MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES REPORTED
AT THE AIRPORT.
56 DEGREES.
WINDS ARE OUT OF THE WEST.
THEY'LL SHIFT MORE
NORTHWESTERLY MOMENTARILY
PROBABLY WITHIN THE NEXT
COUPLE OF HOURS AS COLDER AIR
WILL SLOWLY WORK ITS WAY
THROUGH.
FOR THE REST OF THE EVENING IT
WILL BE DRIVE.
WINDS WILL PICK UP AND
TEMPERATURES WILL BE FALLING
PRETTY SWIFTLY SO IT'S IN THE
MID-50'S NOW.
WE SHOULD BE AT 49 BY
7 O'CLOCK, 46 BY 9 P.M., 44 BY
11:00 P.M. AND TEMPERATURES
WILL BE PLUMMETING SO THAT
WE'RE RIGHT AROUND THE
FREEZING MARK HERE IN THE
METRO TOMORROW MORNING.
20'S NORTH AND WEST.
THE WINDS WILL ALSO START TO
GUST OVER 20 MILES AN HOUR SO
BY TOMORROW MORNING, NICE TO
HAVE THE SUNSHINE BACK BUT
WE'RE EXPECTING SOME PRETTY
LOW WIND CHILLS AND SOME
PRETTY COLD CONDITIONS THAT WE
HAVEN'T REALLY DONE MUCH OF
THIS WINTER.
SO IT IS A SHOCK TO THE
SYSTEM.
BY SATURDAY MORNING, THE AIR
TEMPERATURES, THEY WILL BE THE
COLDEST WE'VE SEEN SINCE
DECEMBER.
WATCH YOUR FUTURE WIND CHILLS.
BY 10:30 TONIGHT FEELS LIKE
THE 30'S, 20'S NORTH AND WEST.
TOMORROW YOU STEP OUTSIDE IT
FEELS LIKE THE TEENS
WIDESPREAD.
NOT MUCH OF A REPRIEVE THROUGH
THE DAY.
ALL AFTERNOON WE'LL HAVE WIND
CHILLS IN THE 20'S.
IT STAYS BLUSTERY AS YOU HEAD
OUT WITH YOUR SWEETHEART ON
FRIDAY NIGHT.
MIGHT WANT TO STAY IN
ACTUALLY.
WIND CHILLS IN THE TEENS
AREN'T TOO FRIENDLY BUT IT
LOOKS VERY COLD TO START OUR
WEEKEND.
CHANGES BY THE WEEK BLAKE.
>> CHINA IS REPORTING A HUGE
SPIKE IN THE NUMBER OF
INFECTED PATIENTS AND DEATHS.
LATEST NUMBERS IN CHINA SHOW
MORE THAN 60,000 CONFIRMED
CASES THAT NUMBER ON THE TOP
LEFT OF YOUR SCREEN.
LOOK AT THE DEATHS ON THE
RIGHT.
MORE THAN 1300 DEATHS.
THE CDC ALSO CONFIRMING A 15TH
CASE IN THE UNITED STATES, A
PATIENT WHO WAS RECENTLY
EVACUATED FROM CHINA
THANKFULLY THEY WERE ALREADY
UNDER QUARANTINE AT A MILITARY
BASE IN TEXAS.
>>> WE ARE LEARNING SOME
CORONAVIRUS TEST KITS SHIPPED
TO LABS ACROSS THE COUNTRY ARE
NOT WORKING AS THEY SHOULD.
AS A RESULT THE CDC IS
REMAKING PARTS OF THE TEST
KITS AFTER SOME PRODUCED
INCONCLUSIVE RESULTS.
THOSE TEST KITS WERE SENT TO
STATES TO SPEED UP THE TESTING
PROCESS.
THEN THEY DISCOVERED THE FLAW.
>> NEW DETAILS ON THE FIRE IN
ALEXANDRIA OVER THE WEEKEND.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE NOW
DETERMINED WHAT CAUSED THAT
ACCIDENT.
A CIGARETTE OR A CIGAR IN A
TRASH CHUTE IGNITED THAT FIRE.
WE KNOW IN IT WAS ENORMOUS.
WE KNOW THAT IT ALSO COST A
LOT OF MONEY, MORE THAN
$48 MILLION IN DAMAGE WE'RE
TOLD.
THE FIRE TOUR THROUGH A
CONSTRUCTION SITE BUT ALSO DID
DAMAGE TO MORE THAN A DOZEN
TOWNHOMES.
FOUR HOMES AND SEVERAL CARS.
>> WOW.
HOW MANY -- WHAT WAS THE
DAMAGE.
>> 48 MILLION DOLLARS.
>> ALL FROM AN IMPROPERLY
DISCARDED CIGARETTE.
>>> NO EXPIRATION DATE ON
EQUALITY THOSE ARE THE WORDS
OF FEMALE LAWMAKERS TRYING TO
REMOVE THE 1982 DEADLINE FOR
RATIFYING THE EQUAL RIGHTS
AMENDMENT FOR WOMEN.
HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES VOTED
TO REVERSE LEGISLATION PASSED
BY CONGRESS IN 1973 THAT GAVE
STATES A DEADLINE TO PASS THE
ERA.
ALL HOUSE DEMOCRATS SUPPORTIS
THERE IT ALONG WITH FIVE
REPUBLICANS.
VIRGINIA BECAME THE 38TH STATE
TO RATIFY THE AMENDMENT IT
SOLIDIFIED INTO LAW THE ERA
WOULD ADD PROTECTIONS FOR
WOMEN WHO STRUGGLE AGAINST
DOMESTIC AND SEXUAL
HARASSMENT.
DO YOU THINK THE EQUAL RIGHTS
AMENDMENT IS STILL NECESSARY?
ALL THESE YEARS LATER IN 2020.
VOTE NOW ON FOX5DC.COM OR THE
FOX5 NEWS APP JUST LOOK UNDER
THE BROWSE SECTIONS.
>> AN APOLOGY FROM PLAYERS ON
THE HOUSTON ASTROS.
THAT IS THE TEAM THAT LOST TO
THE NATIONALS IN THE WORLD
SERIES BACK IN OCTOBER.
THEY WERE PUNISHED FOR USING A
TELEVISION CAMERA TO STEAL
SIGNS FROM OTHER TEENS BACK IN
2017.
ALEX BREGMAN AND JOSÉ ALTUVE
SAY THEY'RE SORRY.
NO PLAYERS WERE PUNISHED.
THE TEAM'S OWNER SAYS THEY
CANNOT TAKE BACK WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> AS LONG AS THEY'RE SORRY,
OKAY.
ASTRONAUT CHRISTINA KOCH IS
SPEAKING OUT ABOUT HER SPACE
EXPERIENCE.
KOCH SPENT 328 DAYS OH ALMOST
A YEAR ABOARD THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION
BREAKING THE RECORD FOR
LONGEST CONTINUOUS SPACE
FLIGHT BY A WOMAN.
SHE RETURNED TO WORK LAST
WEEK.
HER MAIN GOAL WAS TO HELP
RESEARCHERS UNDERSTAND HOW
LONG TERM WEIGHTLESSNESS AND
SPACE RADIATION AFFECT WOMEN.
>> I'M FEELING GREAT.
I JUST THINK ALL OF THE NEW
THINGS THAT I'M EXPERIENCING
SORT OF YOU SEE YOUR MIND WAKE
UP TO THE SENSORY EXPERIENCES
THAT DEFINE EARTH AND THE
THINGS THAT ARE HERE.
HELPED ME TO SEE ALL HUMANS
ARE INHERENTLY THE SAME WE
HAVE MORE THAT UNITES US.
>> KOCH CARRIED OUT ROUGHLY
200 EXPERIMENTS FOR NASA
ORBITING THE EARTH MORE THAN
5,000 TIMES.
>> SO COOL, SO COOL.
>>> NOW WE WANT TO TAKE YOU TO
SOME TOP CAUGHT ON CAMERA
MOMENTS.
LOOK AT THIS DRAMATIC RESCUE.
THIS IS ON A FLORIDA HIGHWAY.
A GOOD SAMARITAN JUMPS INTO
ACTION TO HELP SEAY A DRIVER
STUCK INSIDE OF THAT BURNING
TRUCK.
>> WOW.
>> YOU CAN SEE ANOTHER MAN AT
ONE POINT STEPS IN TO HELP
OUT.
THE GOOD SAMARITAN THEY'RE
ABLE TO PULL THE DRIVER OUT
TOGETHER.
FORTUNATELY THE DRIVER DID
MAKE IT OUT SAFELY BUT
SUFFERED BURNS ON HIS BODY.
>> WASHINGTON STATE PATROL GOT
A SURPRISE WHEN HE PULLED OVER
A DRIVER FOR SPEEDING.
A STUFFED DINOSAUR IN THE
FRONT SEAT.
AT LEAST GET A DUMMY THAT
LOOKS LIKE A PERSON.
HE WAS HOPING TO USE THE HOV
LANES.
IN A TWEET THE AGENCY REMINDED
DRIVERS EVEN IF YOU HAVE A
FAVORITE STUFFED ANIMAL IT
DOES NOT COUNT AS A PASSENGER.
>> GOODNESS.
THIS CAUGHT ON CAMERA STORY.
IT'S A GOOD REMINDER TO ALL
THE HUSBANDS TO ALWAYS LISTEN
TO THE WIFE.
A MAN TRIED TO PROVE TO HIS
INSISTENT WIFE THAT THERE WAS
NO SQUIRREL INSIDE OF THEIR
BATHROOM.
LOOK AT WHAT HAPPENED.
>> IT IS LITERALLY IMPOSSIBLE.
> THERE IS A SQUIRREL IN
THERE.
I HEAR IT.
>> NO, I'M TELLING YOU.
>> DON'T OPEN THAT DOOR.
>> I GOT A STICK.
>> NO.
>> WATCH, WATCH, WATCH.
>> STOP.
>> WATCH, WATCH.
>> AHHH.
>> WHAT DID I JUST TELL YOU.
THERE LITERALLY  IS NOTHING IN
HERE, LITERALLY NOTHING.
NOTHING.
NOTHING, I'M LOOKING
EVERYWHERE.
>> I KNOW --
>> AHHH.
[LAUGHTER]
>> OH, MY -- I'M SORRY, THIS
IS THE FIRST TIME THAT --
LITERALLY THIS IS -- OH, MY
GOSH IS THAT REAL.
DO YOU THINK THIS IS REAL.
>> THAT'S SO FUNNY.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
SEEN THAT VIDEO.
SORRY.
DO IT AGAIN.
OKAY, THAT IS CRAZY.
>> SO FUNNY THAT.
>> THAT'S A FLYING SQUIRREL,
RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> THE SECOND SCREAM
DEFINITELY WAS THE HUSBAND
TOO.
I THINK THAT SAYS ENOUGH
KNOCKED ME OUT OF MY CHAIR.
DID YOU SEE THAT MOMENT
ALREADY?  YOU KNEW IT WAS
COMING OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
STILL TO COME HERE AT 4:00
CITATION CHALLENGE.
METRO TRANSIT POLICE TURN THE
ACT OF WRITING TICKETS INTO A
GAME.
IT HAS SINCE BEEN SHUT DOWN
BUT WE GOT A COPY OF THE
RULES.
>> SPOTIFY REVEALING THE MOST
POPULAR LOVE SONGS OUT THERE.
FIND OUT WHO TOOK THE NUMBER
ONE SPOT BUT WE ITS WANT YOU
TO TELL US WHAT YOU THINK
SHOULD BE THE NUMBER ONE LOVE
SONG.
YOU CAN TWEET US.
>> AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
AT TRAFFIC AROUND THE DMV AS
RUSH HOUR RAMPS UP.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Uh oh!
What?
I think I forgot
to lock my Buick.
Got it.
I bet you lunch
you can't make it in there.
I'm thinkin' sushi.
Alexa, ask Buick
to start my SUV.
You can do that?
Yeah, with a Buick.
What?
At the heart of every
Buick SUV...is you.
Find out why Buick
is number one
in dealer sales
and service satisfaction.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick SUV models
plus current eligible
GM owners
get 7-50 purchase
allowance.
>> ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, CONTEST ON METRO
BUT APPARENTLY NOT THE KIND
THAT BENEFITED RIDERS.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A CONTEST
BETWEEN METRO TRANSIT POLICE.
>> OFFICERS AT THE FORT TOTTEN
STATION WERE A WARDED POINTS
FOR MAKING ARRESTS, WRITING
TICKETS AND ALSO HANDING OUT
CITATIONS.
FOX5's PAUL WAGNER IS LIVE
AT THE FORT TOTTEN STATION
RIGHT NOW WITH MORE ON THIS
STORY.
HI, PAUL.
>> Reporter: HEY, ANGIE AND
BLAKE.
WE REALLY DUG INTO THIS TODAY.
WE LEARNED A LOT MORE ABOUT
IT.
I TALKED WITH THE POLICE
CHIEF, RON PAVLIK DOWNTOWN AT
METRO HEADQUARTERS.
HE TOLD ME TODAY THAT HE
ACTUALLY FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS
LAST AUGUST WHEN AN OFFICER
BROUGHT IT TO HIS ATTENTION.
HE SAYS HE IMMEDIATELY SHUT IT
DOWN AND ORDERED AN INTERNAL
INVESTIGATION.
HE SAYS THE OFFICER WHO WAS
TRYING TO MOTIVATE HER
OFFICERS HERE AT FORT TOTTEN
WAS ACTUALLY BEHIND IT.
AND ACTUALLY CAME UP WAY FLIER
THAT WAS GIVEN TO THE OFFICERS
AND BASICALLY LAID OUT HOW THE
COMPETITION WOULD RUN.
WE WANT TO SHOW THAT TO YOU
NOW.
WE HAVE A COPY.
THE FLIER BEGINS WITH WHAT THE
RULES SAY WOULD BE A FRIENDLY
COMPETITION AND MAY THE ODDS
BE FOREVER IN YOUR FAVOR.
IT GOES ON TO SAY THE WEEKLY
WINNERS WOULD BE GIVEN A
CHOICE OF GAS CARDS, LUNCH
CARDS AMAZON CARDS OR A CHOICE
OF THEIR BEATS OR MOBILE
PREFERENCES.
THE POINTS WERE THEN BROKEN
DOWN LIKE THIS.
EACH ARREST WAS WORTH 20
POINTS.
ONE POINT WAS GIVEN FOR EVERY
10 PARKING TICKETS.
FOUR POINTS FOR EACH CITATION
AND MOVING VIOLATION AND A
VARIETY OF POINTS FOR OTHER
ROUTINE JOBS PERFORMED BY THE
POLICE AT THE STATION.
NOW, CHIEF PAVLIK SAYS DURING
THE MONTH OF THE COMPETITION
THERE WAS NO SPIKE IN REPORTS,
TICKETS OR CITATIONS AT THE
STATION.
AND HE DOES NOT THINK THE
CHALLENGE SIGNIFICANTLY
ALTERED THE WAY POLICING WAS
DONE THERE.
PAVLIK ALSO SAYS THE
LIEUTENANT WHO CAME UP WITH
THE IDEA WAS TRYING TO EMPOWER
HER OFFICERS TO DO WORK.
HE SAYS THAT WAS WRONG.
BUT NOBODY WAS TARGETED AND
THE NUMBERS DO NOT SHOW A
SPIKE AT THE FORT TOTTEN
STATION.
NOW, WE DO KNOW THAT ONE
OFFICER ACTUALLY WAS ONE OF
THE WEEKLY WINNERS AND DID
RECEIVE A PRIZE.
HE GOT A $20 GAS CARD THAT THE
LIEUTENANT ACTUALLY PAID FOR
AND THEN GAVE IT TO HIM AND
THAT WAS BEFORE THE
COMPETITION WAS COMPLETELY
SHUT DOWN.
BLAKE AND ANGIE.
>> PAUL, I'M CURIOUS IF NO
SPECIFIC GROUP W WAS TARGETED
WAS THIS AGAINST THE LAW OR IS
THIS JUST IN POOR TASTE?
>> Reporter: IT'S -- WELL,
IT'S IN POOR TASTE BUT IT'S
ALSO JUST NOT THE RIGHT WAY TO
DO POLICING ACCORDING TO THE
CHIEF AND THE CITY COUNCIL AS
WELL AS MEMBERS OF THE METRO
BOARD WHO WE TALKED TO TODAY.
THEY SAW IT RIGHT AWAY AS JUST
BEING ABSOLUTELY WRONG, THAT
YOU'RE TARGETING PEOPLE FOR AN
ARREST FOR PROFIT BASICALLY.
THAT WAS WRONG.
AND AS FAR AS THE DISCIPLINE
IS CONCERNED FOR THIS OFFICER
WE ASKED ABOUT THAT.
THE CHIEF SAID CORRECTIVE
ACTION WAS TAKEN BUT HE WOULD
NOT COMMENT SPECIFICALLY ON
WHETHER OR NOT SHE WAS
DISCIPLINED.
>> ALL RIGHT, PAUL WAGNER LIVE
FOR US AT THE FORT TOTTEN
STATION.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
>>> LET'S TURN OUR ATTENTION
TO THE WEATHER BECAUSE.
>> BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE ON
VALENTINE'S DAY, WE'RE WAKING
UP TO SOME SERIOUS SNUGGLE
WEATHER.
>> YES, WE ARE.
THE TRADE-OFF IT'S GOING TO BE
MUCH COLDER IS BRIGHT
SUNSHINE.
ALWAYS A GIVE AND TAKE.
>> LIKE RELATIONSHIPS, RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THIS IS A GOOD ANALOGY.
YES, I WOULD LIKE A
RELATIONSHIP ANALOGY TO YOUR
ENTIRE WEATHER CAST, PLEASE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M JUST
GOING TO TIE IN LOVE AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE.
YES, WE ARE COMPROMISING ONE
THING FOR ANOTHER HERE.
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AT THE
CAPITOL BUILDING.
CLOUDS ARE STARTING TO CLEAR
USHERING IN SOME ARCTIC AIR
WHICH WILL BE ARRIVING ON
FRIDAY.
THAT'S TOMORROW.
THAT'S VALENTINE'S DAY.
HEAR ME AGAIN, GENTLEMEN,
THAT'S VALENTINE'S DAY
TOMORROW.
[LAUGHTER]
>>> SO, CVS IS STILL OPENED,
THE LIQUOR STORE IS STILL
OPENED BLOOMINGDALE'S IS STILL
OPENED.
YOU'VE GOT TIME.
BUT ARCTIC AIR ALONG WITH
VALENTINE'S ARRIVING TOMORROW.
AND THOSE WINDS OUT THERE ARE
ALREADY STARTING TO SHOW THAT
CHANGE ESPECIALLY NORTH AND
WEST.
15 TO 20 MILES AN HOUR WINDS
THERE AND THAT IS SIGNALING
SOME OF THE COLDER AIR.
CUMBERLAND HAS ALREADY FALLEN
INTO THE LOW 40'S, UPPER 40'S
ACROSS THE MOUNTAINS, 56 IN
D.C.
SO, CERTAINLY STILL THAT MILD
FEELING IN THE AIR.
60 IN FREDERICKSBURG.
57 IN LEONARDTOWN.
SO, WE ARE STILL QUITE MILD.
WE'LL SEE THOSE TEMPERATURES
TUMBLE THROUGH THE REST OF THE
EVENING BECAUSE LOOK WHAT TO
THE WEST, 35 IN PITTSBURGH, 23
IN DETROIT.
ALREADY IN THE TEENS IN
CHICAGO.
PLACES IN THE NORTHERN PLAINS
THIS MORNING WOKE UP WITH MANY
TEMPERATURES BELOW ZERO SO
COLD AIR MASS THAT WILL MODIFY
SLIGHTLY BY THE TIME IT
REACHES US IS PUSHING
EASTWARD.
AND THERE'S THE SHOWERS FROM
EARLIER STRUNG UP ALONG THE
EASTERN SEABOARD BUT THEY'RE
GONE AND THE CLOUDS WILL
SLOWLY CLEAR OUT THROUGH THE
REST OF TONIGHT.
SO, MOSTLY CLOUDY PROBABLY NOT
TOO MUCH CLEARING OVERNIGHT,
34 IS THAT LOW TEMPERATURE IN
THE DISTRICT.
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY WE'LL SEE
20'S.
WINDS WILL GUST AT 20 MILES AN
HOUR AT TIMES THAT WILL KEEP
WIND CHILLS TOMORROW MORNING
IN THE TEENS AND 20'S.
BY THE AFTERNOON, SUNSHINE, 38 .
DEFINITELY FEELS MORE LIKE
WINTER.
THAT'S PROBABLY AN EARLY
38 DEGREES.
BY THE TIME YOUR FRIDAY NIGHT
STARTS WE'RE AROUND THE
FREEZING MARK AND FALLING.
BY THE TIME WE HIT THE WEEK,
SATURDAY MORNING YOU WAKE UP
TO SOME VERY COLD CONDITIONS,
A LOT OF SUNSHINE ONCE AGAIN.
SUNDAY THOUGH EVEN THOUGH IT'S
COLD IT'S SUCH A BRIEF, BRIEF
SNAP BECAUSE BY SUNDAY IT WILL
BE MUCH MILDER IN THE
AFTERNOON LOOKING AT
TEMPERATURES IN THE 50'S SO 38
IS IT FOR SATURDAY AND WITH
THAT HIGH TEMPERATURE OF 51 ON
SUNDAY TAKING THE EDGE OFF
THAT COLD AND WE'RE BACK TO
SPRINGLIKE TEMPERATURES WE'VE
BASICALLY HAD ALL MONTH LONG.
BLAKE AND ANGIE BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT YOU WERE GIVING
SOME GREAT SUGGESTIONS OUT
THERE CAITLIN BY BUYING FOR
THAT SPECIAL SOMEONE.
DO YOU NEED GIFT IDEAS.
DON'T WORRY YOU'RE IN LUCK
BECAUSE WE ARE PREVIEWING THE
NEW EPISODE OF THE OH MY GOFF
SHOW INCLUDING YOU NEED GIFTS
FOR SOMEONE SPECIAL ON
VALENTINE'S DAY OR ANY DAY AT
THAT.
LIFE CASTING THIS IS A THING.
>> REALLY BELIEVE THAT HANDS
SPEAK SO MUCH ABOUT PEOPLE.
>> SO, THIS IS PAULA WITH
PULSE LIVE CASTING DIPPING
HANDS IN A BUCKET OF
SOMETHING.
ABOUT A MONTH OR SO THEY'RE
GOING HAVE A SCULPTURE.
LIFE CASTING IS SOMETHING THEY
CAN DO, OBVIOUSLY YOU'VE SEEN
IT WITH BABY HANDS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE MY LOVE
BOX.
>> I GOT TO SEE THIS.
>> DESPITE WHAT IT SOUNDS LIKE
THIS IS SUPER COOL.
THIS IS WHAT YOU CAN CONSIDER
A MODERN DAY LOVE MESSENGER
WHEN YOU SEND IT THROUGH APP
THAT HEART START SPINNING
RAPIDLY AND THEN YOU OPEN UP
THE BOX AND THAT'S WHERE YOU
GET YOUR MESSAGE, IT DISPLAYS.
WHEN ALL THIS FAILS LIKE IN MY
BRO' IN LAW'S CASE, CHRIS.
>> ALEXA, SEXY TIME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> THAT'S MY SISTER.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I'M
ALLOWED TO SHOW THAT ON TV BUT
I AM BECAUSE IT'S HILARIOUS.
SHE SENT IT IN A GROUP CHAT.
HE SET THE MOOD SEXY TIME --
YOU CAN SET SEXY TIME ON ALEXA
AND SET IT TO DIM THE LIGHTS
TO NICE SULTRY PURPLE.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WORKED.
>> YOU HAVE TWO SISTERS.
IS THIS THE ONE THAT GETS
ANNOYED BY YOU SHARING TOO
MUCH.
>> YES.
>> GREAT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> STILL TO COME MANY WILL BE
CELEBRATING VALENTINE'S DAY
TOMORROW BUT ONE MAN IS STILL
TRYING TO FIND A PARTNER AND
HE'S WILLING TO SHELL OUT A
HEFTY AMOUNT OF MONEY TO DO
IT.
>> I JUST HAVE TO ADD WE ARE
OVERSHARING MORE ON THE
PODCAST WHEN IT DOES COME OUT
TOMORROW.
>> THE OH MY GOFF SHOW LOOK
WHEREVER YOU FIND PODCASTS OR
WATCH IT ON YOUTUBE.
>> FACEBOOK.
>> YUP.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Lo necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month,
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Plus, you can get up to $200 in
Visa Prepaid Cards.
Mix and match your perfect
Fios plan.
Only on Verizon.
>> A LOOK AT WHAT'S TRENDING
WITH MARINA MARRACO.
>> AT LEAST ONE OF US IS READY
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
IT'S NOT US.
>> SHE'S OFF TOMORROW.
SHE'S DECIDED TODAY IS
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> WANT EVERYBODY TO KNOW
SHE'S READY FOR SOME LOVING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WELL, TALK ABOUT
MATCHMAKERS THIS MAN IN KANSAS
WILLING TO PAY SOMEBODY
$25,000 TO FIND HIM A
GIRLFRIEND.
HE'S 47 AND SAYS HE IS SICK OF
DATING AND DATING APPS.
MATCHMAKERS SUBMIT A WOMAN
THEY THINK WOULD BE PERFECT
FOR THIS FINE GENTLEMAN OR
SINGLE LADIES THEY CAN
COMPLETE A PERSONALITY
MATCHING SURVEY ON HIS SITE
DATE JEFF G.
>> WILL YOU TELL EXECUTIVE
PRODUCER JEFF THAT YOU CANNOT
IN THIS DAY AND AGE PUT FAKE
PHOTOS OF YOURSELF UP WHEN YOU
PUT THESE ADS OUT.
>> MATCHMAKER ONLY GETS CASH
IF THEY VOTE FOR A YEAR.
HE'LL DONATE $25,000 TO A NO
KILL DOG SHELTER OR A CHARITY.
HE'S SERIOUS.
>> THEY NEED THEIR OWN DATE.
WOW .
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> I THINK THAT MAYBE HE'S
GOING TO HAVE SOME LUCK.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M THINKING.
>> THE FACT HE'S WILLING TO
>> YEAH.
DONATE $25,000 TO CHARITY
>> THE FACT HE'S WILLING TO
SHOWS HE'S A GOOD GUY, TOO.
DONATE $25,000 TO CHARITY
>> OR HE'S TRYING TO GET A
SHOWS HE'S A GOOD GUY, TOO.
DATING SHOW.
>> OR HE'S TRYING TO GET A
>> WE'RE STILL FIXATED ON
DATING SHOW.
THE --
>> WE'RE STILL FIXATED ON
>> YOU THINK HE WANTS TO BE
THE --
THE NEXT BACHELOR AND THIS IS
>> YOU THINK HE WANTS TO BE
HIS WAY TO DO IT.
THE NEXT BACHELOR AND THIS IS
>> MAYBE.
HIS WAY TO DO IT.
IF YOU HAVE NOTHING TO PLAY
>> MAYBE.
MAYBE FOR YOUR SISTER FOR THIS
IF YOU HAVE NOTHING TO PLAY
ALEXA, SOME TOP SONGS FOR THE
MAYBE FOR YOUR SISTER FOR THIS
V-DAY PLAYLIST AND HERE ARE
ALEXA, SOME TOP SONGS FOR THE
THE TOP FIVE SONGS.
V-DAY PLAYLIST AND HERE ARE
THIS IS NUMBER ONE BUT LET'S
THE TOP FIVE SONGS.
START WITH NUMBER FIVE WHICH
THIS IS NUMBER ONE BUT LET'S
IS ELVIS CAN'T HELP FALLING IN
START WITH NUMBER FIVE WHICH
LOVE.
IS ELVIS CAN'T HELP FALLING IN
NUMBER FOUR, WHITNEY HOUSTON'S
LOVE.
I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
NUMBER FOUR, WHITNEY HOUSTON'S
NUMBER THREE JUST THE WAY YOU
I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
ARE BRUNO MARS.
NUMBER THREE JUST THE WAY YOU
NUMBER TWO, THINKING OUT LOUD
ARE BRUNO MARS.
ED SHEERAN NOT CLEAR WHY HE'S
NUMBER TWO, THINKING OUT LOUD
ON THE LIST AND YEAH NUMBER
ED SHEERAN NOT CLEAR WHY HE'S
ONE RIGHT NOW JOHN LEGEND, ALL
ON THE LIST AND YEAH NUMBER
OF ME.
ONE RIGHT NOW JOHN LEGEND, ALL
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAINST ED
OF ME.
SHEERAN.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAINST ED
>> I MEAN, LOVE SONGS OF ALL
SHEERAN.
TIME, ED SHEERAN WAS BORN
>> I MEAN, LOVE SONGS OF ALL
YESTERDAY.
TIME, ED SHEERAN WAS BORN
>> WHAT ABOUT AS TIME GOES BY
YESTERDAY.
FROM CASABLANCA OR HOW ABOUT
>> WHAT ABOUT AS TIME GOES BY
LATELY BY JODECI.
FROM CASABLANCA OR HOW ABOUT
>> WHO.
LATELY BY JODECI.
>> SOMEONE REMOVE HER FROM THE
>> WHO.
SET RIGHT NOW.
>> SOMEONE REMOVE HER FROM THE
PLEASE.
SET RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M ALL WHITNEY.
PLEASE.
PLAY THE BODYGUARD SOUNDTRACK
>> I'M ALL WHITNEY.
AND WE'RE GOOD.
PLAY THE BODYGUARD SOUNDTRACK
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED.
AND WE'RE GOOD.
>> DOLLY PARTON SANG THAT SONG
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED.
FIRST.
>> DOLLY PARTON SANG THAT SONG
>> A MARYLAND MAN FACING
FIRST.
DECADES IN PRISON FOR SKIMMING
>> A MARYLAND MAN FACING
CREDIT CARDS.
DECADES IN PRISON FOR SKIMMING
HE ST TARGETED HIGH PROFILE
CREDIT CARDS.
PLAYS.
HE ST TARGETED HIGH PROFILE
WE'LL EXPLAIN HOW HE WAS
PLAYS.
CAUGHT.
WE'LL EXPLAIN HOW HE WAS
>> ♪
CAUGHT.
>> THAT'S A GOOD SONG.
>> ♪
[ fast-paced drumming ]
MIKE: Anyone hear the slogan,
'Mike Will Get It Done?'
OK, let me tell
you what the 'it' is.
As Mayor,
I expanded healthcare coverage.
As President,
I'll build on Obamacare
because healthcare is a right.
I created nearly
500,000 jobs in New York City.
As President,
I'll build an economy
that delivers good jobs
with higher wages.
I'll take on the gun lobby
and save lives.
And I will stop Trump's assault
on women's reproductive rights.
I've got a record
of doing things.
I've got the resources
to take on this fight.
As mayor,
I held myself
accountable for results.
As President,
I'll offer common sense plans
and I will get it done.
So let's stay on the offensive,
and let's win.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> WELCOME BACK.
HERE'S A LOOK NOW AT SOME OF
THE TOP STORIES WE CONTINUE TO
FOLLOW AT 4:30 INCLUDING THIS
WILD CARJACKING THAT ENDED IN
THIS APARTMENT COMMUNITY
PARKING LOT.
THIS HAPPENED IN ANNAPOLIS
EARLY THIS MORNING.
POLICE SAYING THAT THE
17-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT USED A
SLEDGEHAMMER AND THREATENED TO
SHOOT AND KILL THE YOUNG MAN
THAT HE ALLEGEDLY STOLE THIS
CAR FROM.
THE TEENAGED HIGHJACKER LED
POLICE ON A BRIEF PURSUIT THEN
CRASHED THE STOLEN CAR INTO A
THREE -- INTO THREE PARKED
CARS INCLUDING ONE THAT YOU
SAW ON YOUR SCREEN AT BAYSHORE
LANDING.
OFFICERS CAUGHT THE TEEN SOON
AFTER HE BAILED OUT OF THAT
CRASHED CAR.
THEY SAY THAT HE'S GOING TO BE
CHARGED AS AN ADULT.
>> A GIANT INFERNO EARLY THIS
MORNING IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY.
FIRE INVESTIGATOR SAY NO ONE
WAS HOME AT THE TIME BECAUSE
THE HOME ON SPRINGDALE COURT
IN ACCOKEEK WAS UNDER
RENOVATION.
FIRE INVESTIGATORS ARE STILL
LOOKING INTO WHAT HAPPENED.
NEIGHBORS SHARED THIS VIDEO
WITH FOX5.
>> IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY,
POLICE IN RIVERDALE PARK ARE
LOOKING FOR TWO THIEVES
ACCUSED OF STEALING AN ATM.
THESE ARE THE PHOTOS OF THE
THIEVES IN ACTION.
YUP, IT HAPPENED AT A GAS
STATION ON BALTIMORE AVENUE
THIS MORNING.
POLICE ARE HOPING THAT
SOMEBODY'S ABLE TO LOOK AT
THESE PICTURES AND RECOGNIZE
THE TRUCK THAT THEY USED OR
THE MEN INVOLVED IN THESE
PHOTOS RIGHT HERE.
>> FOX5 HAS BEEN STAYING AHEAD
OF ATM AND CREDIT CARD FRAUD
AROUND THE REGION AND TONIGHT
WE'VE LEARNED OF A MONTGOMERY
COUNTY MAN WHO FACES 60 YEARS
IN PRISON FOR ALLEGEDLY
SKIMMING CREDIT CARDS FROM A
LOCAL HOTEL.
FOX5's IKE EJIOCHI IS LIVE
IN SILVER SPRING.
IKE, I UNDERSTAND THIS GUY WAS
WORKING THE FRONT DESK OF THE
HOTEL.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
BLAKE.
ACCORDING TO CHARGING
DOCUMENTS FROM MONTGOMERY
COUNTY POLICE, A LOT OF THOSE
CREDIT CARDS CAME FROM RIGHT
HERE IN THIS BUILDING.
IT'S THE SILVER SPRING
MARRIOTT THAT APPARENTLY HE
USED TO WORK AT AND POLICE SAY
THAT THIS ALL HAPPENED FROM A
TRAFFIC STOP.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS VIDEO
RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS THE 25-YEAR-OLD AND
JUST AS YOU SAID HE FACES OVER
60 YEARS IN PRISON FOR THESE
CRIMES.
IT ALL STARTD FROM A TRAFFIC
STOP.
POLICE WERE WATCHING HIM IN
HIS BLACK MUSTANG WHEN THEY
THOUGHT THEY SAW HIM ENGAGE IN
A DRUG DEAL.
THEY PULLED HIM OVER SEARCHED
HIS CAR AND FOUND A BLACK BAG
ON THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
IN THAT BAG WERE SEVERAL
CREDIT CARDS, SOME TO HIS
NAME, A LOT OF THEM NOT TO HIS
NAME.
AFTER FURTHER SEARCH OF THE
CAR, THEY FOUND ANOTHER BAG IN
THE BACK SEAT THAT CONTAINED
CREDIT CARD SKIMMING DEVICE.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE DEVICES THAT
CAN BE USED TO TRACK YOUR
CREDIT CARD INFORMATION AND
IMPLANT THAT INFORMATION ON
ANOTHER CARD.
NOW, THEY ASKED HIM IF THAT
WAS HIS BAG, WHERE DID THE
CARDS COME FROM AND HE'S TOLD
POLICE AT THAT TIME THAT, YOU
KNOW WHAT, I FOUND THOSE CARDS
AT THE JOB AT MY HOTEL.
I WAS GOING TO RETURN THEM.
I JUST NEVER HAD A CHANCE TO
DO THAT YET.
WELL, POLICE WENT BACK, THEY
INTERVIEWED HIS OLD BOSS AND
FOUND OUT THAT HE WAS IN FACT
FIRED TWO MONTHS PRIOR TO THAT
TRAFFIC STOP.
>> WOW, IKE, STORIES LIKE THIS
MAKE ME SO MAD BECAUSE WHEN
YOU TRAVEL LIKE TO EUROPE FOR
EXAMPLE, THEY'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO TAKE YOUR CARD ANYWHERE.
THEY BRING THE CARD MACHINES
TO YOUR TABLE, THEY DO
EVERYTHING RIGHT IN FRONT OF
YOU BUT THESE GUYS IF THEY
HAVE A SKIMMER BEHIND THE
COUNTER IT'S SO EASY FOR THEM
TO SWIPE THIS.
WHAT CAN ALL OF US DO TO
PROTECT OURSELVES.
>> Reporter: BLAKE, THAT'S
THE THING.
IT'S SO TOUGH.
WE SPOKE TO FORENSIC
DETECTIVES TODAY AND THEY SAY
THESE ARE SOME OF THE HARDEST
CRIMES TO PROTECT YOURSELF
AGAINST.
THERE'S A COUPLE THINGS YOU
CAN DO.
ONE THING TRY TO UPGRADE YOUR
DEBIT CARD OR CREDIT CARD WITH
A CHIP.
DETECTIVES SAY IT'S SO MUCH
HARDER TO SKIM THOSE CARDS
THAT HAVE A CHIP.
ANOTHER THING USE A CREDIT
CARD WHEN YOU CAN AS OPPOSED
TO A DEBIT CARD.
IT'S A LOT BETTER IF PEOPLE
STEAL SOMEONE ELSE'S MONEY
OTHER THAN YOUR OWN.
>> GOOD ADVICE IKE EJIOCHI
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I HAVE BEEN TELLING ANGIE
THIS.
SHE STILL USES HER ATM CARD.
>> FOR EVERYTHING.
>> ANGIE YOU GOT TO USE THE
CREDIT CARD BECAUSE IF THERE'S
FRAUD YOU CAN CALL THE CREDIT
CARD COMPANY AND THEY CAN PUT
A STOP TO IT.
IF YOU USE AN ATM CARD IT'S A
LOT HARDER TO REVERSE THAT.
>> OKAY, THANKS DAD.
THANKS COACH.
>>> STILL TO COME, SOME
INSPIRATION ON THE ICE.
AN OLYMPIC HOCKEY PLAYER IS IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA RIGHT NOW
HELPING TO INSPIRE OTHER WOMEN
TO TRY OUT THE SPORT.
>> LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
ALONG 395 IN ALEXANDRIA.
THIS IS NEAR DUKE STREET.
YOU CAN SEE IT'S A LITTLE SLOW
GOING BUT IT'S MOVING.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ♪
>> BIG NAMES ON THE ICE ARE
INSPIRING WOMEN TO PLAY HOCKEY
AND THEY'RE DOING IT AT A FREE
CLINIC TODAY.
>> OUR GWEN TOLBERT IS LIE IN
ARLINGTON WITH ALL OF THE
DETAILS.
HEY, GWEN I HOPE THAT YOU
BROUGHT YOUR SKATES.
>> Reporter: OH, I'M TELLING
YOU, I THOUGHT I SHOULD LEAVE
THEM AT HOME.
I DON'T WANT TO SHOW EVERYBODY
UP.
I'M FROM CANADA.
ME AND ICE.
I HAVE TWO VERY SPECIAL WOMEN
HERE WHO ARE GOING TO TALK TO
US TODAY ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON
AND WE COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
TWO BETTER ROLE MODELS AT ALL
IN TERMS OF WOMEN'S HOCKEY
BECAUSE THESE TWO HAVE A MEDAL
TO PROVE THEIR ABILITY.
SO, TELL US YOUR NAMES AND
TELL US WHY THAT MEDAL --
WHERE THAT MEDAL CAME FROM.
>> I'M HALEY AND WE'RE BOTH ON
THE 2018 U.S. WOMEN'S OLYMPIC
TEAM AND I'M FROM ROCKVILLE,
MARYLAND AND I'M NOW A HOCKEY
AMBASSADOR FOR THE WASHINGTON
CAPITALS.
>> Reporter: HOW DO YOU LIKE
THOSE CREDENTIALS.
>> I'M AMANDA PELKE FROM
VERMONT.
WE WON GOLD TWO YEARS AGO.
>> Reporter: WE PLAYED A
LITTLE SMACK TALK.
THE LAST COUNTRY THEY PLAYED
AGAINST TO WIN THAT MEDAL WAS
MY COUNTRY CANADA.
YOU ARE FANTASTIC ROLE MODELS.
WHY IS IT SO IMPORTANT TO TALK
TO TRAIN AND TO WORK WITH
YOUNG WOMEN.
>> THAT'S OUR BIGGEST GOAL IS
TO GIVE BACK AFTER WINNING THE
GOLD.
IT WAS TO PROMOTE THE GAME IN
THIS AREA AND BEYOND SO THAT'S
KIND OF WHAT WE DO DAY TO DAY
AND WE'RE SUPER EXCITED ABOUT
IT.
>> Reporter: NOW, THIS IS
THE FIRST OF ITS KIND.
>> IT IS.
WE'VE BEEN HERE I THINK -- HOW
LONG HAS THE TOURNAMENT BEEN
GOING ON FOR.
>> FOR AWHILE.
>> AWHILE NOW.
IT'S ONE OF THE BIGGEST
TOURNAMENTS IN THE AREA AND
REALLY FOR ALL TEAMS FOR
SEASONS FOR COLLEGE COACHES
COMING AND THE GIRLS REALLY
GET EXCITED ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: SO, WE'VE GOT
ALL AGES THEN TODAY COMING IN
FOR THIS CLINIC.
YOUNG WOMEN WHO ARE GOING TO
GET OUT HERE, GET ON THE ICE,
HOLD THOSE HOCKEY STICKS AND
GO FOR THOSE GOALS AND LEARN
THE CRAFT THAT YOU DO SO VERY
WELL.
WHAT IS SOME OF THE ADVICE
THAT YOU GIVE TO SOME OF THE
YOUNG GIRLS.
>> MY BIGGEST THING IS JUST TO
HAVE FUN, ENJOY IT AND THE
REST WILL COME.
ENJOY THOSE EARLY MORNINGS,
THE COLD RINKS, THE HARD
PRACTICES BECAUSE YOU'LL LOOK
BACK AND THOSE ARE THE THINGS
YOU'LL REMEMBER WITH YOUR
TEAMMATES NOT IF YOU WON OR
LOSE A SPECIFIC GAME.
>> Reporter: AND THERE'S A
BIG GAME TONIGHT.
TELL US ABOUT THAT.
>> THERE IS A BIG GAME.
IT'S THE -- IT'S AN ALL-STAR
GAME AND HALEY'S COACHING THE
OPPOSING TEAM WHILE I'M ON THE
OTHER BENCH SO IT'S A BIG
TILTON NIGHT.
A LOT ON THE LINE.
GIRLS WILL HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
IT'S A GREAT OPPORTUNITY FOR
THEM TO MEET NEW PEOPLE AND
MEET THEIR OPPONENTS THAT
THEY'VE BEEN PLAYING ALL YEAR.
IT'S A FUN ENVIRONMENT FOR
THEM AS WELL.
>> Reporter: I'M REALLY
HAPPY YOU'RE BOTH HERE.
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOU'RE DOING
FOR YOUNG GIRLS AND YOUNG
WOMEN TO INSPIRE THEM.
I'M WITH TWO CHAMPIONS AND
LOVING IT.
BACK TO YOU.
>> THAT IS AWESOME.
I KNOW WE'RE LIKE GEARING UP
FOR THE WINTER -- THE SUMMER
OLYMPICS BUT BEFORE WE KNOW IT
IT'S GOING TO BE TIME TO BE
CHEERING ON TEAM U.S.A. AGAIN
SO GOOD TO SEE THEM HERE.
>> STILL TO COME HERE AT 4:00
A FEEL GOOD STORY THAT
HAPPENED 30,000 FEET IN THE
AIR.
NORMALLY WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
BAD THINGS THAT HAPPEN IN
AIRPLANES.
THIS ONE IS REALLY GOOD.
A MAN AND HIS WIFE WERE
HEADING HOME WITH A NEWLY
ADOPTED BABY AND EVERYONE ON
BOARD GOT TOGETHER FOR A
SURPRISE FOR THEM.
>> PLUS, A SPECIAL VALENTINE'S
PERFORMANCE ON "THE MASKED
SINGER" BUT THERE WAS NO LOVE
FOR ONE OF THE CONTESTANTS.
WE ARE GOING TO REVEAL WHO WAS
BEHIND THE MASK.
CAITLIN.
>> ANGIE, READY FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY?
>> I THINK SO.
>> I BET YOU ARE.
YOU LOOK THE PART.
THAT'S HALF THE BATTLE.
WE HAVE THE HOLIDAY RAPIDLY
APPROACHING TOMORROW AND THE
WEATHER WILL BE CHANGING
COMPLETELY.
WE'RE GOING TO SAY GOODBYE TO
THE GLOOMY SKIES AND THE WET
WEATHER.
HELLO TO SOME REAL ARCTIC AIR.
READY OR NOT IT'S GOING THE
FEEL LIKE WINTER.
THAT FULL HOUR-BY-HOUR
FORECAST COMING UP WHEN FOX5
RETURNS.
>> ♪
RNS.
>> ♪♪
(upbeat whistling music)
(couple sighs)
- Ah!
- All buckled up,
let's go!
- Tuition Monster,
how are you here already?
She's only two days old!
- And that means
there's only
6,720 days until she's
off to college.
But it is a bit snug
back here,
so next time I'll be
calling shotgun.
(baby giggles)
Vroom vroom!
- [Narrator] Tame the
Tuition Monster
with a Virginia529
savings account.
Learn how at
virginia529.com
>> BACK WITH BREAKING NEWS.
2306 CONFIRMS THERE HAS BEEN
AN ARREST IN THE MURDERS OF A
LOCAL COUPLE FOUND DEAD LAST
WEEKEND IN SOUTHWEST VIRGINIA.
STATE POLICE TELLING US AN
18-YEAR-OLD FROM ALEXANDRIA IS
CHARGED WITH KILLING AYANNA
MURTONS AND JOEL FIANDA.
THEY HAD BEEN LIVING IN
ALEXANDRIA.
THEY WERE FOUND EARLY SATURDAY
MORNING OUTSIDE BIAN D.A.'S
CAR ALONG A HIGHWAY NEAR
ROANOKE.
AGAIN AN ARREST HAS BEEN MADE.
>>> WILD NEW VIDEO OF AN
OFFICER UNDER ATTACK.
>> SARAH SIMMONS IS IN THE
NEWSROOM WITH THAT.
>> THE SHOCKING ENCOUNTER
CAUGHT ON DASH CAMERA VIDEO
HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT
LED TO THIS HEATED ALTERCATION
BETWEEN A COLLEGE FOOTBALL
PLAYER AND A COP.
AND AT McDONALD'S YOU KNOW
THEY ARE NOTORIOUS FOR HAVING
BROKEN ICE CREAM MACHINES BUT
ONE COMPANY THINKS THEY HAVE A
SOLUTION FOR IT.
WHAT THEY ARE DOING TO FIX THE
ISSUE BEFORE SHAMROCK SHAKE
SEASON, GUYS.
>> APPARENTLY HAVE YOU NOT RUN
INTO THIS PROBLEM.
>> NO, BECAUSE I DON'T GO TO
McDONALD'S FOR A SHAKE.
>> A McFLURRY IS LIFE.
>> YES,.
>> LIFE CHANGING.
>> ONE TIME I WENT TO THREE
DIFFERENT McDONALD'S AND
THEY WERE ALL BROKEN 'CAUSE IT
WAS AFTER 7:00 P.M.
I TWEET IT OUT AND I FOUND A
MAP ONLINE WHERE PEOPLE
DOCUMENT WHERE ALL THE ICE
CREAM MACHINES ARE BROKEN.
>> APPARENTLY SARAH IS TOO
BOUGIE TO GO TO McDONALD'S
FOR ICE CREAM.
>> THEY'RE GETTING TO THE
BOTTOM OF IT.
>> WE'RE GLAD.
>> THANK YOU.
>> UH-HUH.
>> WELL, EXPECT A TOUCHING
TRIBUTE AT THE NBA ALL-STAR
GAME ON SUNDAY.
GRAMMY AWARD WINNING SINGER
JENNIFER HUDSON WILL BE
PERFORMING A SPECIAL TRIBUTE
TO THE LATE KOBE BRYANT AND
HIS DAUGHTER GIANNI BRYANT.
HIS DAUGHTER AND SEVEN OTHERS
DIED IN A HELICOPTER CRASH
LAST MONTH.
THE ALL-STAR GAME WILL TAKE
PLACE AT THE UNITED CENTER.
>> THIS STORY WILL WARM YOUR
HEART.
A PLANE FULL OF STRANGERS
CONGRATULATING A CALIFORNIA
COUPLE THAT WAS BRINGING THEIR
BABY GIRL HOME FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
THIS IS A PICTURE OF THE BOOK,
OF KIND MESSAGES THEY
RECEIVED.
THE COUPLE DUSTIN AND KAREN
STRUGGLED TO GET PREGNANT FOR
NINE YEARS.
THEY FINALLY GOT THE
OPPORTUNITY TO ADOPT A
NEWBORN.
A PAIR OF OBSERVANT FLIGHT
ATTENDANTS NOTICED YOU THE NEW
BUNDLE OF JOY AND EVERYONE
WROTE KIND AND ENCOURAGING
MESSAGES ON NAPKINS FOR THE
NEW PARENTS AND THEY WERE NEWT
A BOOKLET LIKE THIS.
HOW SPECIAL IS THAT.
>> SO SWEET.
>> ♪
>> ALL RIGHT.
"THE MASKED SINGER" GOT
ROMANTIC LAST NIGHT
CELEBRATING LOVE WITH A
SPECIAL VALENTINE'S DAY SHOW.
ALL OF THEM SANG A KISS SONG
TOGETHER ROCK AND ROLL ALL
NIGHT YOU HEARD IT THROUGHOUT
BUT IN THE END THERE WAS NO
LOVE MORE MISS MONSTER AND HER
MASK WAS TAKEN OFF.
>> ♪
>> TAKE IT OFF!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
CHAKA KHAN.
SUPERSTAR GRAMMY AWARD WINNER.
>> ♪
>> MISS MONSTER WAS THE
LEGENDARY SINGER CHAKA KHAN,
CHAKA KHAN.
THE 10 TIME GRAMMY WINNER
ELIMINATION CAME AS A SURPRISE
TO FANS WHO TOOK TO SOCIAL
MEDIA TO BLAST HER GETTING THE
BOOT.
THE QUEEN OF FUNK SAID SHE WAS
FLATTERED BY SOME OF THE
JUDGE'S GUESSES WHICH INCLUDED
DOLLY PARTON AND QUEEN
LATIFAH.
THE SHOW IS GETTING BECAUSEFUL-
THEY'RE GETTING NAMES.
>> IF YOU CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF
THE MacDONOF"THE MASKED SINGER.
THE SHOW IS GOING ON TOUR.
THEY'RE HITTING THE ROAD.
YOUR FAVORITE CHARACTERS PLUS
SPECIAL CELEBRITY GUESTS WILL
BE LIVE AT WARNER THEATER IN
WASHINGTON IN D.C. ON
JUNE 11TH.
TICKETS ARE NOW ON SALE AND
THEY START AT $60.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
ON THIS RAINY THURSDAY
AFTERNOON.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE WE ARE
LOOKING OUT ALONG WASHINGTON,
D.C. AND CAITLIN, IS THAT
CLEARING IN THE CLOUDS I SEE.
>> SURE IS, YEAH.
LOOK AT THAT, A LITTLE BIT OF
SUNSHINE TO END THE DAY, GUYS.
AMAZING.
THAT IS THE SIGN OF CHANGE
THAT WE'RE LOOKING FORWARD TO
TOMORROW.
THERE WILL BE MANY IT THINGS
CHANGING BETWEEN NOW AND
TOMORROW MORNING AS KATY PERRY
SO ELOQUENTLY SAYS YOU'RE HOT
AND THEN YOU'RE COLD.
SUMS IT UPPER IF HE CAN'TLY.
I MEAN, I WOULDN'T CALL TODAY
HOT BUT FOR FEBRUARY WE WERE
IN THE UPPER 50'S TO AROUND 60 .
THAT'S CHANGING OVERNIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO FEEL THOSE
NORTHWESTERLY WINDS START
BLOWING A LITTLE BIT LATER ON
AND THAT WILL USHER IN SOME
ARCTIC AIR.
WE HAVE NOT DONE A LOT OF
ARCTIC AIR THIS WINTER BUT WE
ARE GOING HAVE A BRIEF LITTLE
SNAP HERE TOMORROW AND
SATURDAY OF SOME BELOW NORMAL
TEMPERATURES.
WE'RE CALLING THAT BUNDLE UP,
SNUGGLE WEATHER ON YOUR
VALENTINE'S DAY.
IT'S VERY APPROPRIATE.
AND THOSE TEMPERATURES ARE
REBOUNDING BY SUNDAY.
SO IF YOU GET CABIN FEVER OVER
THE NEXT TWO DAYS YOU CAN BE
OUT AND ABOUT AGAIN ON SUNDAY
AFTERNOON.
IT'S GOING TO FEEL MUCH
MILDER.
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE.
YES, WE ARE SEEING JUST A FEW
HINTS OF SOME SUN BREAKING
THROUGH THAT CLOUD COVER HERE
AS WE'RE STILL ABOUT AN HOUR
AWAY FROM SUNSET.
THOSE DAYS DEFINITELY GETTING
LONGER.
SUN SETTING NOW AFTER 5:30.
56 DEGREES, MOSTLY CLOUDY
SKIES.
IT'S STILL ON THE MILD SIDE.
THAT WARM AIR JUST HUGGING THE
COAST HERE.
56 D.C.,  WE'RE ALREADY IN THE
TEENS IN THE MIDWEST.
IT'S 14 IN CHICAGO RIGHT NOW,
15 IN SAINT LOUIS, 15 IN
LINCOLN.
ONE IN THE TWIN CITIES, THREE
BELOW IN FARGO SO THAT COLD
AIR IS SPILLING SOUTHWARD,
THOSE PINKS AND PURPLES TAKING
OVER THE BLUES AND EVENTUALLY
WILL BE TAKING OVER THE GREENS
WHERE WE ARE.
PRETTY SOON THAT COLD AIR WILL
BE OVERHEAD OF US.
ARCTIC AIR DELIVERS THE
TEMPERATURES.
DOESN'T DELIVER MUCH ELSE.
CLEAR SKIES ACROSS MUCH OF THE
COUNTRY.
WE'LL PUSH LINGERING SHOWERS
OFF SHORE.
WE GOT RID OF RAIN EARLIER
TODAY.
WE'LL HAVE PART TO MOSTLY
CLOUDY SKIES TONIGHT.
JET FREEZING MARK TAKING A BIG
DIP TO THE SOUTH AND THAT WILL
BE NOTICEABLE.
WE HAVE NOT DONE MUCH WINTER
COLD OVER THE PAST FEW MONTHS.
IN FACT YOU HAVE TO GO BACK TO
DECEMBER 2019 TO SEE THE
TEMPERATURES THAT WE'RE GOING
TO FEEL OVER THE NEXT COUPLE
OF DAYS.
A LOT OF SUNSHINE BUT ALSO
KIND OF BREEZY AND COLD.
WATCH YOUR FUTURE WIND CHILLS.
BY 10 O'CLOCK TONIGHT IT FEELS
LIKE 14 BELOW IN MINNEAPOLIS,
16 BELOW IN SAINT CLOUD.
THAT AIR MASS OVERHEAD SO THAT
BY 8:00 A.M. TOMORROW MORNING
IT FEELS LIKE 19 IN
WASHINGTON, SIX IN PITTSBURGH
AND THOSE MOST BITTER WIND
CHILLS OVER THE GREAT LAKES.
THE COLDEST OF THE AIR WILL
PROBABLY BE FRIDAY AFTERNOON
WHERE IT FEELS LIKE IT'S IN
THE TEENS NORTH AND WEST, 20'S
HERE IN WASHINGTON.
BY SATURDAY MORNING, THE WIND
IS NOT AS BAD.
THAT AIR MASS HAS KIND OF
RETREATED BUT THE OVERALL AIR
TEMPERATURES WILL STILL ONLY
BE IN THE 20'S.
SO YOUR TWO DAY OUTLOOK A LOT
OF SUNSHINE BOTH DAYS WE THINK
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE HIGH
TEMPERATURES SOMEWHERE IN THE
30'S.
TOMORROW IT WILL BE A VERY
EARLY HIGH TEMPERATURE AS
WE'LL FALL LATER IN THE
AFTERNOON.
DON'T FORGET THOSE WIND CHILLS
IN THE 20'S AND TEENS.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN-DAY.
BY PRESIDENT'S DAY, THIS IS A
BONUS WEEKEND.
MONDAY ALSO LOOKS GREAT.
50'S PARTLY CLOUDY SKIES, SO
ANY SERVICES OR MEMORIALS OR
ANYTHING AROUND TOWN, YOU'VE
GOT GREAT WEATHER.
AND WE'RE RIGHT BACK INTO THAT
MILD PATTERN.
SHOWERS ARE POSSIBLE TUESDAY
INTO WEDNESDAY BUT ANOTHER
COLD SNAP IS LURKING.
LOOK AT NEXT THURSDAY.
TEMPERATURES BACK IN THE 30'S.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN-DAY GUYS.
ANGIE BACK TO YOU.
>> CAITLIN THANK YOU.
>>> WE WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT
FOX5's "LIKE IT OR NOT."
LAST NIGHT WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT A MIDAIR DEBATE OVARY
KLIOVERRECLINING THOSE SEATS A N
REPEATEDLY JUST PUNCHED THE
BACK OF HER SEAT.
SHE CLAIMS THAT WHEN SHE FIRST
RECLINED HER SEAT THE MAN
ASKED HER TO PUT IT BACK UP
WHILE HE ATE HIS MEAL.
SHE SUPPLIED.
WHEN HE FINISHED SHE RECLINED
AGAIN AND THAT'S WHEN THE
PUNCHING BEGAN.
WHEN SHE EXPLAINED TO A FLIGHT
ATTENDANT HE WAS OFFERED A
FREE DRINK.
>> I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
CALLED CONSIDERATION.
IF YOU SEE A GUY SITTING
BEHIND YOU 6-FOOT FIVE SITTING
ON THE LAST ROW YOU SAY MAYBE
I'M NOT GOING TO RECLINE BUT
AGAIN THAT IS YOUR SEAT YOU
PAID FOR IT.
>> I REALLY THINK IT'S FLYER
DISCRETION IS ADVISED AND
THERE ARE SOME UNWRITTEN RULES
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT.
WHEN YOU DO HAVE TALLER PEOPLE
BEHIND YOU THEN I MOST LIKELY
NOT TO RECLINE.
>> IF I HAD KIDS BEHIND ME
THEY'RE SHORTER THEY GOT SHORT
LEGS YOU CAN DO IT.
TONIGHT COMING UP AT 7:00
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT BABIES,
SPEAKING OF LITTLE KIDS MORE
SPECIFICALLY THE NAMES PARENTS
ACTUALLY GIVE THEM BECAUSE
ACCORDING TO A RECENT BRITISH
SURVEY, 7 PERCENT OF PARENTS
SAY THAT THEY GIVE THEIR BABY
AN OUTLANDISH NAME SOMETHING
BIZARRE JUST FOR THE POTENTIAL
OF A SOCIAL MEDIA FOLLOWING.
THEY WANT THEM TO BE ABLE TO
BREAK OUT OF THE NOISE AND
65 PERCENT SAID THAT THEY'RE
CONSIDERING IT.
SOME OF THOSE NEWS NAMES
INCLUDE JASPEN, RENLO AND
MAVERY.
I PUT THIS OUT ON TWITTER, THE
NAME GAME.
I SAID WE'RE GOING TO BE
DISCUSSING IT.
PEOPLE ARE FIRED UP.
THEY SAY THIS IS THE MOST
LUDICROUS RIDICULOUS THING
I'VE EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE BUT
OTHER PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO
THINK AHEAD.
THEY'RE LIKE I NEED MY CHILD
TO CARVE THEIR PLACE OUT OF
THE --
>> IF THAT'S THE REASON IT'S
FOR SOCIAL MEDIA IT'S ABSURD
BUT I KIND OF LIKE THE NAME
JASPE IN.
>> I HAVE A WREN.
>> SHE COULD HAVE HAD A FULL
NAME.
SHE COULD HAVE BEEN WREN LOWE.
>> NASA WILL BE ACCEPTING
APPLICATIONS FOR ITS NEXT
CLASS OF CANDIDATES AND WE
HAVE THE LIST OF REQUIREMENTS
IF YOU WANT TO BE AN ASTRONAUT
IN 2020.
>> ♪
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
>> ♪
>> MEET RONNIE BACKENSTOE.
SHE MIGHT BE 98 YEARS OLD BUT
SHE DOESN'T LETTING AGE STOP
HER FROM SELLING GIRL SCOUT
COOKIES.
RONNIE JOINED THE GIRL SCOUTS
WHEN SHE WAS 10 YEARS OLD.
BACK THEN GIRL SCOUT COOKIES
SOLD FOR 15 CENTS A BOX.
>> WOW.
>> NOW RONNIE SELLS THE
COOKIES AT HER RETIREMENT HOME
IN PENNSYLVANIA ALONG WITH THE
LOCAL SCOUTS.
>> ONCE A SCOUT, ALWAYS A
SCOUT, RIGHT.
>> GOT A CAPTIVE AUDIENCE AT
THE RETIREMENT HOME.
GOOD FOR YOU RONNIE.
ENTREPRENEURSHIP RIGHT THERE.
>> AND IF YOU'VE EVER DREAMED
OF BECOMING A NASA ASTRONAUT
LISTEN UP.
NOW IS YOUR CHANCE.
FROM MARCH 2ND TO THE 31ST
ANYONE INTERESTED CAN APPLY.
THE PROCESS IS HIGHLY
COMPETITIVE.
ONLY 12 ASTRONAUTS WERE CHOSEN
THE LAST TIME AROUND FROM
18,000 QUALIFIED APPLICANTS.
>> WOW.
NOT 18,000 APPLICANTS, 18,000
APPLICANTS WHO WERE QUALIFIED
AND THEY CLOSE 12.
>> UH-HUH.
>> TO QUALIFY APPLICANTS NEED
TO HAVE A STEM RELATED
MASTER'S DEGREE AND TWO YEARS
EXPERIENCE IN A RELATED FIELD
LIKE BEING A PILOT.
>> SO WE'RE OUT.
>> WE'RE OUT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I WAS TALKING TO JONES.
>> HE DROPS THE SOCK YOU SEE.
TALKS TO THE DOG.
PIWATCH.
THE DOG PICKS UP THE SOCK,
BRINGS IT UP THE STAIRS.
THE OWNER IS LIKE SHOCKED.
YOU CAN TELL THEY DID NOT PLAN
THIS.
THIS DOES NOT HAPPEN REGULARLY
>> [LAUGHTER]
>> ISN'T THAT CUTE.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> I KNOW.
>> HOW DO YOU TRAIN HIM TO DO
THAT.
MINE JUST EATS THE SOCKS.
>> I'M CONVINCED DOGS ALWAYS
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYING THEY
JUST SELECTIVELY CHOOSE WHEN
TO LISTEN.
>> THEY ARE SMART.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON THIS
THURSDAY.
>> YOUR NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> ♪
>> RIGHT NOW AT 5:00 A MAN
JUMPS THROUGH A GLASS WINDOW
AT A LOCAL PREGNANCY CENTER
AND PUTS A FOUR-YEAR-OLD GIRL
IN A CHOKEHOLD.
YOU'LL HEAR FROM WITNESSES WHO
HELPED SAVE HER.
>>> PLUS, DASHCAM VIDEO
CAPTURE A COLLEGE FOOTBALL
PLAYER BODY SLAMMING A COP.
SO WHAT LED UP TO THE
ENCOUNTER.
>>> AND A MARYLAND MAN IS
FACING DECADES IN PRISON AFTER
TARGETING A HOTEL IN A CREDIT
CARD SCAM.
YOUR NEWS STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> ♪
>> RIGHT OFF THE TOP AT 5:00
BREAKING NEWS.
AN ARREST IN THE MURDER OF A
LOCAL COUPLE FOUND DEAD LAST
WEEKEND IN SOUTHWEST VIRGINIA.
>> FOX5's MARINA