Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
ATTENTION BICYCLISTS DID YOU
KNOW IN ONE LOCAL COUNTRY
YOU'RE REQUIRED TO REGISTER
YOUR BIKE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ONE CYCLIST
THAT GOT CAUGHT BREAKING LAW.
>> SPECIAL DELIVERY APP EARLY
CHRISTMAS STOP TROOPS
STATIONED OVERSEAS THE HOLIDAY
EXPRESS MAKING A SPECIAL DROP
TOP U.S. BASES IN SYRIA.
"FOX5" MORNING AT 7 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>>  GOOD MORNING GREAT TO BE
WITH YOU ON THIS TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY, LET'S SEE TUESDAY
MORNING.
>>  TUESDAY MORNING.
>>  CHRISTMAS EVE HE.
>> IT'S A WEIRD WEEK.
>>  IT IS.
>>  ALLISON ALLISON SEYMOUR.
>> AND I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>>  IF YOU'RE WAKING UP ON
THIS TUESDAY MORNING HERE'S A
LIVE VIEW.
>>  BEAUTIFUL.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>>  DOES NOT FEEL LIKE WE'RE
IN WINTER TIME BUT WE ARE.
>>  LOOKS GORGEOUS.
>>  QUICK LOOK AT WARM AND
TRAFFIC NOT TO WORRY MUCH
ABOUT WEATHER DEPARTMENT AND
WEATHER TOO.
>>  BEAUTIFUL FOR ALL THINGS
OUTDOOR RELATED.
IT'S CHILLY THIS MORNING.
OVERNIGHT LOWs BACK NEAR
FREEZING, TAKE A JACKET
GORGEOUS CHRISTMAS EVE AND
GORGEOUS CHRISTMAS DAY.
DETAILS IN A IPT M. GOOD
MORNING.
>>  7:01 CRASH PROBLEMS RIGHT
SHOULDER AND LEFT LANE.
WE'LL LOOK AT DELAYS AND REST
OF TRAVEL AROUND THE DMV NEXT.
>>> TWO PAST THE HOUR NOW ARE
YOU HEADED HOME FOR HOLIDAYS
AND IF SO YOU MAY HAVE DODGED
LONG LINES AND JAMMED ROADS.
TODAY IS EXPECTED TO BE THE
BEST DAY TO TRAVEL ESPECIALLY
IF YOU FLY.
>> ANGIE GOFF JOINS US LIVE
FROM DULLES INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT WITH MORE ON THE
HUSTLE AND BUSTLE OF CHRISTMAS
EVE AND GOOD FEELING FIRSTEN
FOREMOST.
PEOPLE ARE GOING HOME, ANGIE.
>>  YES, THEY ARE.
YOU CAN TELL WHICH ONE IT ME?
>> THERE ARE YOU.
>> DO I FIT N TRYING TO FWLEND
HERE AT DULLES INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT WITH MY FELLOW NUT
CRACKERS YES WE HAVE CHRISTMAS
IN THE AREAS TONS OF PEOPLE
TRAVELING MOST OF THEM BY
GROUND.
TRAVELING ON THE ROADWAY.
BUT THERE ARE 7 MILLION PEOPLE
GOING TO BE DOING JUST WHAT
THESE PEOPLE ARE DOING.
CAR WRITING SUITCASES AND
TRYING TO CHECK N TRYING TO
HOP A LIGHT TO GET TO LOVED
ONES ALL OVER THE NATION.
AND SOME PEOPLE WE TALKED TO
ACTUALLY GOING TO PUERTO RICO
AND JAMAICA.
I'M HERE WITH MY FRIEND WENDY
OPT PHONE RIGHTS NOW.
HI, WENDY.
WHERE ARE YOU GUYS HEADED.
>>  WELL, WE ACTUALLY ARE
GOING TO LOOK AND FROM THERE
WE'RE DRIVING TO GRAND CANYON.
>>  ARIZONA ONE OF THE TOP
PLACES PEOPLE ARE GOING THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
LOTS OF PEOPLE WANT TO GO
SOMEWHERE WARM.
LOS ANGELES NOW THERE'S BEEN
DICEY WEATHER OUT.
THERE HAS THAT CONCERNED YOU
AT ALL.
>>  NOT REALLY.
>>  WAS IT TOUGH GETTING UP
EARLY IN THE MORNING.
>>  YEAH.
>> BUT UBL EXCITED ONCE YOU
GET THERE, RIGHT.
>>  YES.
>>  AND WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO
TRAVEL CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> MY HUSBAND HE LOVES TO
TRAVEL.
YEAH BEFORE CHRISTMAS WE
ALWAYS TRAVEL.
>>  ALL RIGHT 'TIS THE SEASON
FOR TRADITION.
SAFE TRAVELS.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
I SAW SOMEBODY HERE WHERE ARE
THE COOKIES, WHERE ARE THE
COOKIES, SO PEOPLE FOR THE
MOST PART THEY'RE ALL BUNDLED
UP AND WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE.
>>  WE HAVE SOME HOLIDAY
COOKIES FOR AIRPORT WORKERS
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO WORK ON
HOLIDAY.
>>  THAT'S SWEET ARE YOU
FLYING OUT TODAY.
>>  YEAH GOING TO ULTIMATELY
WHERE TELLU RI DE BUT STOPPING
IN CHICAGO.
>>  WHY THE 2 IT 4th OF
DECEMBER.
>>  OH, WELL I MEAN WE'RE
JEWISH SO WE CELEBRATE
HANUKKAH SO CHRISTMAS IS NOT
RIGHT NOW FOR US BUT WE WANT
TO BE ON THE SLOPES TOMORROW
IT WILL BE LEAST CROWDED DAY
OF WEEK ON THE MOUNTAIN.
>>  HAPPY HANUKKAH TO YOU AND
SAVE ME ONE OF THOSE COOKIE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO TAKE LOOK HERE.
THE LINES HAVE BEEN BUILDING.
OVER THE HOUR AAA SAYING GET
HERE A COUPLE HOURS BEFORE THE
FLIGHT TAKES OFF AND ALSO
ADVISING YOU TO HAVE YOUR
BOARDING PASS PRINTED OUT.
YOU GUYS ARE READY TO GO AND
HERE EARLY NOT GOING TO MISS
YOUR FLIGHT NO MAD DASH TO THE
SECURITY LINE.
>> THAT'S TRUE, THAT'S TRUE.
>>  WHO ARE YOU GOING TO SEE
AND WHERE ARE YOU GOING.
>>  WE'RE GOING TO MIAMI.
>>  THESE PEOPLE.
>>  IT'S A NICE VACATION CAN I
GO WITH YOU.
>>  ALL RIGHT I'LL SEE YOU
GUYS LATER.
>>  YOU CAN COME WITH US.
>>  YEAH WE'RE ALL GOING I
HAVE A NEW FAMILY "FOX5"
YOU'VE BEEN GREAT BACK TO YOU.
>>  SHE'S ON HER WAY TO MIAMI.
>> NOT A BAD PLACE TO BE.
>>  SHE'S NEGOTIATING ON THE
TRIP.
>> THANKS.
>> CRUNCH TIME TO BUY LAST
MINUTE GIFTS AND THAT BRINGS
US TO "FOX5" INSTAPOLL.
EVERYBODY SEEMS TO BE DOING
WELL AT LEAST THOSE TAKING
MART IN INSTAPOLL.
DO YOU HAVE LAST MINUTE
CHRISTMAS SHOPPING MOST SAY NO
THEY'RE G YOU CAN VOTE ON
FOX5DC APRIL FIND BROWSE
SECTION AND WEIGH IN ON "FOX5"
D. CRK.com.
AGAIN 7 0% SAY I'M GOOD AND
DONE AND 70% SAYING I'M GOING
TO PICK UP A FEW MORE GIFTS AT
SOME POINT TODAY.
>>  ALL RIGHTY.
>>  TIME FOR WEATHER TEAM.
>>  I CAN GIVE ADVICE ABOUT
THIS.
I'M LAST MINUTE SHOPPER.
>> YOU WANT LAST MINUTE, LAST
MINUTE SHOPPING IF YOU WAIT TO
END OF DAY PEOPLE ARE GETTING
UP LIKE I HAVE TO LAST MINUTE
SHOP EVERYBODY FWHAITS LINE
TOGETHER IF YOU WAIT UNTIL THE
END GUESS WHAT YOU'RE IN.
>>  I FORGET SOME CLOSE.
>>  A LOT CLOSE AT 6.
>>  I FORGOT TO PLAN FOR THAT
ONE.
>>  CON VEEPS STORES DON'T
FORGET THEM.
>>  THEY HAVE GIFT CARDS.
>>  THEY'RE OPEN LATEST AS YOU
NEED THEM TO BE AND GREAT
STUFF IN THERE.
>>  ONE YEAR HE SPRUPING FOR
JUMBO SIZE CHOCOLATE BAR FOR
ME.
>>  HE DID.
>>  IT'S THE HOLIDAY.
>>  HE'S A TURKEY JERKY GUY I
MAKE HIM HAPPY EVERY YEAR.
>>  NO ISSUES FOR SANTA
TONIGHT.
THAT'S MOST IMPORTANT.
SANTA DELIVERIES HERE ON TIME
AS WE HAVE QUIET WEATHER FOR
THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS
INCLUDING ALL THIS AFTERNOON
TONIGHT LOOKS GREAT TOMORROW
LOOKS GOOD TOO AND DAYTIME
EYES 50 BOTH DAYS.
CHILLY THIS MORNING.
LOTS OF SUN OUT.
THERE BUT 35 DEGREES REAGAN
NAG AT 30 DULLES AND 322 TO
START MORNING IN BALTIMORE.
BWI MARSHALL QUIET FOR US
COULD NOT BE QUIETER PATTERN.
TRAVELING DULLES AIRPORT AIR
TRAVEL SHOULD NOT BE ANY
PROBLEM AT ALL ACROSS THE MID
ATLANTIC TO NEW ENGLAND.
MOST OF COUNTRY IS QUIET HERE.
NOT EXPECTING A LOT OF TRAVEL
DAYS TODAY AND WE'RE LOOKING
FANTASTIC AGAIN WITH DAYTIME
HIGHs WHICH WILL BE ABOUT 50
AND 32 TONIGHT.
WE'RE EXPECTING SANTA WILL NOT
HAVE ANY ISSUES AS IT WILL BE
PARTLY CLOUDY SKIES AND QUICK
LOOK AT FORECAST FOR THIS
AFTERNOON.
50.
PLENTY OF SUNSHINE.
AND LITTLE COOL OUT THERE AND
NICE DAY.
WINDS NORTH 5 TO 10.
7 DAY COMING UP LOOK AT REST
OF WEEK AND SNEAK PEEK AT THE
WEEKEND.
>>  HI.
>> I HAD TO GET MY CLICKER.
7:07 NOW SKY FOX OVER BW
PARKWAY 19 NORTHBOUND LANES
IMPACTED BY CRASH TAKING OUT
LEFT SHOULDER LEFT LANE
TRAFFIC MERMINGING TO RIGHT
LANE.
WE ARE SEEING A DELAY HEAD
BACK TO 32.
YOU CAN ALWAYS TAKE 95
NORTHBOUND TO SQUEEZE AROUND
THAT ONE AND AVOID BACKUPS.
AGAIN YOU CAN SEE THE RED ON
MAP 99 THE 55 BETTER BET.
OUTER LOOP CRASH AFTER 1 IS 93
BLOCKING SHOULDER VOLUME LIGHT
AND NO MAJOR SLOW DOWNS PAST
THAT POINT.
STERLING BELIEVE A PERSON HIT
BY CAR AT 7 UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
WATCH FOR SLOW DOWNS AND LANES
BLOCKED.
BAY BRIDGE WIDE OPEN AND REST
OF AREA BRIDGES LOOKING GOOD.
NO SLOW DOWNS THROUGH
FREDERICKSBURG SOUTH OF THAT
POINT IN SPOTSYLVANIA OR NORTH
OF THAT POINT TO DALE CITY.
66 AT SPEED.
METRO RAIL LINE ON TIME DALE
CITY TRAFFIC LOOKS GREAT AND
SECONDARYS IN THE DISTRICT
PLEASANT TO UNION STATION AND
NO SLOW DOWNS ON WAY TO REAGAN
NATIONAL.
BWI OR DULLES HOW ABOUT THAT.
LET'S TAKE IT CHRISTMAS EVE
BACK TO YOU.
>>  THIS MORNING 7:08 MARYLAND
STATE POLICE INVESTIGATING A
DEADLY CRASH ON FREDERICK NEAR
HARMONY ROAD 2 A.M. THE CAR
WENT OFF THE ROAD CRASHED
CAUGHT FIRE APP THE DRIVER
PRONOUNCED DEAD ON THE SCENE.
POLICE ARE TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
>> STEVE.
>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT IN THE
DISTRICT BOTH DIRECTIONS ON 11
STREET BRIDGE BACK OPEN AFTER
A CRASH INVESTIGATION THERE
AFTER MIDNIGHT.
PRINCE GEORGE COUNTY POLICE
TELL US IT STARTED WHEN THEY
RESPONDED ROBBY LIVINGSTON
ROAD GAS STATION THAT VICTIM
DESCRIBED A DESCRIPTION FOR
POLICE.
HE WAS TRANSPORTED TO THE
HOSPITAL AND LATER DIED.
>>  DEVELOPING THIS MORNING
THE WHITE HOUSE KEEPING CLOSE
EYE ON NORTH KOREA.
A COMPLETION OF NEW TRUCK T
TOUR.
THEY THREATND A SO-CALLED
CHRISTMAS GIFT DEPENDING ON
WASHINGTON ACTION NEWS ONGOING
NUCLEAR NEGOTIATIONS ONE
SATELLITE IMAGE DECEMBER 19
CAPTURES NEW STRUCTURE IN A
FACTORY NEAR PUNG YANG U.S.
OFFICIALS ALLOW YOU TO BIG
ALERT.
>>  LET'S TALK ABOUT BETH
BETHLEHEM.
PEOPLE FROM AROUND THE WORLD
WILL GATHER AROUND A LARGE
TREE IN MAINKER SQUARE TODAY.
IT'S THE SITE WHERE JESUS IS
BELIEVED TO HAVE ABOUT BORN.
>>  ALSO NEW THIS MORNING
BRITAIN PRINCE PHILIP OUT
HOSPITAL FOLLOWING FOUR DAY
STAIVRM THE 98-YEAR-OLD WAS
DISCHARGED EARLY THIS MORNING
HE WAS HOSPITALIZED FOR
"OBSERVATION AND TREATMENT IN
RELATION TO A PREEXISTING
CONDITION.
THE PRINCE RETIRED FROM PUBLIC
DUTYS IN 2017.
>>  STAYING OVERSEAS NOW
CHRISTMAS SHOPPING CELEBRATION
TURNED INTO SDAINGTSNER
AUSTRALIA AND THE CROWD
GATHERED FOR A PROMOTIONAL
EVENT IN A MALL NEAR SYDNEY
WHERE BALLOONS FILLED WITH
GIFTS WERE DROPPED FROM SC
SCEELING AND AS THEY FELL THE
CROWD PUSHDZ AND SHOVED EACH
OTHER SENDING FIVE PEOPLE TO
THE HOSPITAL.
>>  COULD HOUSE LAWMAKERS BE
CONSIDERING IMPEACHING
PRESIDENT AGAIN NEW COURT
FILINGS SAY IT'S POSSIBLE AAND
DEPENDS ON WHAT THEY LEARN
FROM FORMER WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIAL.
>>  YAYs 230.
>>  LESS THAN A WEEK AFTER
APPROVING ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT HOUSE JUDICIARY
LAWYERS ARE SAYING IT COULD
HAPPEN AGAIN.
THEY STILL WANT TO HEAR FROM
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DONE McGAN
WRITE IF McGAN TESTIMONY HAS
NEW EVIDENCE SUPPORTING HE
COMMITTED IMPEACHMENT OFFENSES
NOT COVERED BY ARTICLES
APPROVED BY HOUSE THE COMMIT
TY TEE WILL PROCEED
ACCODINGLY.
THE FIGHT OVER WHAT HAPPENS TO
IMPEEVEMENT ARTICLES REMAINS
STALLED.
>>  IT'S AA SPEEDY APE FAIR
TRIAL THAT'S WHAT WE WANT.
>> DEMOCRATS PRESSURING SENATE
MAJORITY LEADER MITCH
McCONNELL TO ALLOW WITNESSES
AND DOCUMENTS TO BE INTRODUCED
IN THE SENATE TRIAL.
>>  IF THE PRIDZ WANTS A BIG
TRIAL AND FAIR TRIAL WHY ARE
THEY WORKING SO HARD TO
PREVENT KEY WITNESSES FROM
TESTIFY IN THE SENATE TRIAL.
>>  BUT McCONNELL SAYS IT WAS
UP TO THE HOUSE TO THE
INVESTIGATE NOT THE SENATE AND
HIS HAPPENED REMAINED TIED
UNTIL HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY WITH
PELOSI SENDS CASE TO SENATE.
>>  IT SEEMS OB SUBURB AFTER
YOU IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT YOU
WON'T SEND PAPERS OVER TO
SENATE FOR IMPEACHMENT TRIAL
MANDATED BY CONSTITUTION.
>>> MCCONNELL TELLS FOX NEWS
HE'S NOT RULING OUT ALLOWING
WITNESS TOSS TESTIFY AND
NEGOTIATIONS OVER HOW A TRIAL
WILL WORK REMAIN ONGOING.
>>  STILL TO COME AN UPDATE
FROM WEST VIRGINIA ABOUT
EVACUATION OF A NUMBER OF
HOMES YESTERDAY NEAR A SEWAGE
PLANT.
>>  PLUS THE GREAT SWING
DEBATE.
SO HAVE YOU SEEP THE VIDEO?
INTERNET IS GETTING HEATED
OVER WHICH DIRECTION THE
PERSON IS FACING IT'S TRENDING
AND PRETTY OBVIOUS TO ME.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT IT NEXT.
T.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE GETS
A TUX THAT BIG TO BE HONEST.
TAILS HE'S WEARING, THAT'S NBA
TUCKO FALLS HE'S A ROOKIE
CENTER FOR CELTICS AND 7 FOOT
5.
>>  THAT MAKES HIM TALLEST
PLAYER IN NBA AND TALLEST
CONDUCTOR IN HISTORY.
>>> ONE OF THEM.
WE DON'T HAVE PROOF TO STAT
SHEET OF ALL OTHER CONDUCTORS
OUT THERE.
>>  IF YOU'RE CURIOUS ABOUT
THE OUTFIT IT'S 48 DOUBLE
EXTRA LONG TUX.
SLEIGH RIDING LOOKS LIKE HE
WAS HAVING A GOOD TIME TOO.
>>  FULL DISCLOSURE OUR SHARED
FATHER IS A CONDUCTOR.
>>  MY FATHER, YES.
>> OUR FATHER.
>>  DID NOT WEAR THE 48 DIBL
SONG.  NO HE DID NOT.
>>  NOWHERE CLOSE TO 7' 5 JOY
IN THESE ARE THE WONDERFUL
THINGS ABOUT STEVE.
I SHARE HIS DAD RIGHT.
>> THAT WAS AAMAZING STEVE
THAT'S COOL.
>>  I THINK TUCKER MAYBE MY
TACKO MAY BE MY FAVORITE NBA
PLAYER I ENJOYED WATCHING HIM
IN COLLEGE.
>>  COLD START TO THE DAY.
34 LEONARDTOWN ANNAPOLIS 35,
20s, WINCHESTER AND 2 IT 4
MARTINSBURG.
SCHOOL TEMPS TO START DAY.
HOW ABOUT THIS AFTERNOON 50.
WE CAN DO IT NIRKS MILD OU
AFTERNOON AND PLENTY OF
SUNSHINE TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
TRAVEL COG NOT ASK FOR BETTER
DAY OF TRAVELING ACROSS THE
COUNTRY HERE.
STILL SHOWERS ALONG THE
SOUTHEAST COASTLINE THERE.
ALTHOUGH THAT'S STORM IS
WINDING DOWN AND THESE WILL
JUST LOCALIZED -- THIS IS NOT
-- THIS IS A WEAK STORM THAT'S
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY OUT TO
WEST.
WILL CAUSE A LOT OF TRAVEL
DELAYS AND MOST OF THE
COMMUNITY QUIET.
LOOK GOING.
LOCALLY COULDN'T ASK FOR
NERUOSCIENCE WEATHER THIS TIME
OF YEAR.
AFTER A CHILLY START OF 50
THIS AFTERNOON AND JUST A FEW
CLOUDS TO START THE DAY AND
WE'LL KEEP IT DRY.
AS YOU RUN OUT AND ABOUT
RUNNING LAST MINUTE SHOOPING
GIFT AND IDEAS AND YOU'RE
OUTRUN AROUND YOU SHOULD BE
FINE.
SUNNY SKIES, 50.
GREAT CONDITIONS WITH SANTA
DELIVERYES, PERFECT TOMORROW
MUCH OF THE DAY FOR CHRISTMAS
DAY.
ABOUT 50 AND THEN DPRAD YOU'LL
WARM-UP WE MAY GET CLOSE TO 60
BY SATURDAY AFTERNOON AHEAD OF
NEXT ROUND OF RAIN SHOWERS
GETTING IN HERE SURPRISED AND
MONDAY.
BUT AGAIN NICE WEATHER AND
SUNNY SKIES AND 50 THIS
AFTERNOON.
AIRPORT GOOD MORNING.
>>  TUCK, 7:18 KEEPING EYES ON
ROADS THIS MORNING SKY FOX
OVER BW PARKWAY OUTSIDE THE
TOPSIDE OF BELTWAY MADE THEIR
WAY TO 198 WITH NORTHBOUND
CRASH AND IT LOOKS LIKE RIGHT
NOW TRAFFIC IS GETTING BY AS
THEY ZOOM THINGS OUT
PREVIOUSLY LEFT LANE, LEFT
SHOULDER BLOCKED WATCH
RESIDUAL DELAYS LOOKS LIKE
TRAFFIC PATERNS ARE STARTING
TO GET BACK TO NORMAL.
LET'S GO AHEAD AND FORWARD
ALONG AND SEE YOU WHAT ELSE
YOU'RE UP AGAINST IN THE DMV.
ASIDE FROM CRASH IN MEDIAN
AREA A CRASH IN VISH VISH AS
WELL.
STERLING BOULEVARD PERSON
STRUCK BY VEHICLE VIRGINIA 7
WATCH TORE SLOW DOWNS AT THAT
LOCATION.
BAY BRIDGE LOOKS GOOD AND IN
FACT AREA BRIDGES ARE WIDE
OPEN.
2 IT 70 NORTH AND SOUTHBOUND
LOOKS GREAT AND 95 FRED
FREDERICKSBURG AND STAFFORD
QUIET SPEEDS AS THEY SHOULD
BE.
DOESN'T FEEL LIKE MORNING
COMMUTE TYPICAL WEEKDAY.
IF YOU WORK THIS CHRISTMAS EVE
HOLIDAY LIKE A LOT OF US ARE
TRAFFIC AT LEAST WON'T BE A
PROBLEM.
YOU CAN SEE OVER LEGION BRIDGE
955.
LOOKING GOOD.
METRO RAIL LINE ON TIME.
THAT'S WHAT WE GOT BACK TO Y
YOU.
>>  7:19 EVACUATION ORDER IN
WEST VIRGINIA HAS NOW ABOUT
LIFTED FOR DOZENS IN MAR
MARTINSBURG AREA THEY WERE
FORCED FROM HOMES AFTER TOXIC
GAS STARTED SPREADING AT
NEARBY PLANT.
TWO OF THE CHEMICALS MIXED AND
THAT CREATED A STRONG CHLORINE
LIKE GAS.
FIRE AND POLICE OFFICERS WILL
BE STATIONED IN SEVERAL
NEIGHBORHOODS HELPING PEOPLE
OUT AS THEY RETURN HOME.
>>  TAKE A LOOK NOW TO WHAT IS
HOT ON THE WEB THIS MORNING.
>>  JOINS US WITH THAT.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>>  AND IT'S NICE BE HERE WITH
YOU GUYS.
HAPPY CHRISTMAS EVE.
>>  HAPPY CHRISTMAS EVE.
>>  YOU HAVE NOT FINISHED YOUR
SHOPPING HU?
>>  NO.
>> I'M GOOD.
>>  GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
>>  YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FIRST ONE WHAT'S HOT.
MAIM INUNLOCKING DOORS ON A
CAR WITH ONE WAVE OF A
HAPPENED THAT'S WHAT ONE UTAH
MAN THANKS TO TECH UNDER HIS
SKIN.
HE'S ONE OF FEW PEOPLE IN THE
WORLD TURNING TO CYBER NETIC
IMPLANTS WITH FOUR CHIPS HE
HAS IN HIS HANDS.
HE CAN UP LOCK HIS TES LARKS
DOORS AT WORK, LOG ON AND OFF
OF HIS COMPUTER AND EVEN SHARE
CONTACT INFORMATION USING SAME
TECHNOLOGY USED FOR THINGS
LIKE APPLE PAY AND GOOGLE PAY.
YOU MAY BE WONDER WHAT WOULD
INSPIRE HIM TO DO A THING.
>>  MONEY.
>>  LOTS OF MONEY.
>>  PROBABLY PART OF IT HE
SAYS JUST EXPERIENTATION AND
CURIOSITY.
I MEAN I DON'T WANT TO
EXPERIMENT WITH SOMETHING LIKE
THAT PERSONALLY.
>>  NO.
>> RISKY ONE.
>> NOT THAT HARD FOR ME TO
PUSH A BUTTON TO OPEN BY CAR
DOOR AS OPPOSED TO WAVE AT IT.
>>  I HAVE THE TECHNICAL WITH
MY CAR WHERE I CAN WAVE MY LEG
UNDER KIND OF THE BACK BUT IT
IT NEVER EVEN WORKS RIGHT.
>>  MOVING ON TO NEXT STORY.
VIDEO OF A MAN RIDING A SWING
HAS INTERNET FEROCIOUSLY
DIVIDED AND NEWSROOM AS WELL.
MANY COMPARING THIS TO THE
DRESS OF 2015 DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT OR THE LAUREL YANNI
DEBATE OF 201.
SO TAKE A LOOK AT THIS NEW O
ONE.
IT'S SHOWING THE MAN ALONE ON
SNOW COVERED PLAYGROUND RIDING
A SWING.
SIMPLE ENOUGH.
BUT VIEWERS CANNOT AGREE ON
WHETHER OR NOT THIS MAN IS
FACING THE CAMERA OR FACE AGO
WAY FROM IT.
EACH SIDE STEADFASTLY HE
DEFEND WHAT THEY SEE I DON'T
THINK IT'S EVEN A QUESTION.
>>  TOWARD THE CAMERA.
>>  RIGHT.
>>  I TRIED TO LOOK AT THIS
FLEW THE PERSPECTIVE OF THE
OTHER WAY AND I CAN'T.
>>  I KNOW, ME, TOO.
HOWEVER I BROUGHT THIS UP IN
THE NEWSROOM THINKING NO
DEBATE EVERYBODY AGREES HE'S
FASHION CAMERA NO.
A COUPLE PEOPLE IN THE
NEWSROOM SAID HE'S FACE AGO
WAY FROM IT.
>> I NEED A FOOTBALL SHEET
WHERE YOU DRAW IT OUT.
>>  PEOPLE LITERALLY DONE THIS
ONLINE.
>>  BUT FOR THE PEOPLE WHO
AGREE WITH US.
>>  LIKE MINDED PEOPLE.
>> THAT THINK DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU HAVE THAT MOVE FACING
OTHER DIRECTION.
>>  PERHAPS HE'S MOST LIMBER
PERSON IN THE WORLD THAT'S FUN
THANKS ANNE.
>>  COMING UP STAR NFL
QUARTERBACK THAT STOPS BY
TYSON CORN TO DO SHOPPING.
>>  LITTLE WOMEN HEAD BACK TO
BIG SCREEN IN TIME FOR
CHRISTMAS.
SUPPOSED TO BE G NEW LOOK AT
TIMELESS CLASSIC AND CAST
COMING UP LATER THIS HOUR.
(VO)
The moth,
struggles in the spider's web.
Unaware that an exhilarating
escape is just within reach.
Defy the laws of human nature.
At the
Season of Audi Sales Event.
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
S
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
>> SPECIAL VISITORS AT
CHILDREN'S NATIONAL THAT IS
WASHINGTON NATIONAL'S PAPA G
MANAGER DAVID MAR TEEN
ANESTHESIA AND KATIE LEDECKY
AND THE TWO HANDED OUT
PRESENTS AND SIGNED AUTO DPRAV
AND GRATE DAY FOR A COUPLE OF
CHAMPIONS TO BE VISITING AND
DOING GREAT THINGS ON THE
HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> YEAH.
>> GOOD STUFF.
>> WE HAVE MOPTORS RIGHT HERE
SOMETIMES WE LIKE TO GET UP
CLOSE ON A VERY GOOD STORY.
>>  GOOD VIEW.
>>  TUCK, GOOD MORNING.
>>  GOOD MORNINGS GUYS LOOK AT
SUNRISE BEHIND ME.
THERE BEAUTIFUL.
35 TO START THE MORNING.
COOL TO COLD ACROSS THE REGION
HERE.
MUCH OF THE AREA IN THE 20s
EARLY.
DO NOT DISPAIR WE'LL TURN INTO
BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON FOR YOU.
I MEAN 50.
CAN'T COMPLAIN THIS TIME OF
YEAR LOTS OF SUNSHINE TO LOOK
FORWARD TO.  JUST A FEW CLOUDS
LOCALLY LATER TODAY AND WE'LL
KEEP IT DRY THIS AFTERNOON AND
THIS EVENING FOR SANTA
DELIVERYES FOR CHRISTMAS EVE
HERE.
WE CAN LOOK -- COULDN'T LOOK
ANY BET THEY ARE IS NICE QUIET
WEATHER PATTERN THIS TIME YEAR
TO LOOK AT NICE STREAK.
50 TODAY, 50 TOMORROW FOR
CHRISTMAS DAY AND WE'LL HAVE A
FEW MORE CLOUDS TOMORROW.
CAN'T WAKE UP WITH FOG.
TOMORROW MORNING CHILLY 32.
NOTICE NICE WARM-UP BY END OF
WEEK.
THURSDAY, FRIDAY, SATURDAY ALL
NICE AND QUIET DAYTIME HIGHs
IN UPPER 50s AND MAYBE MAKE A
RUN ON SATURDAY BEFORE SHOWERS
ARRIVE ON SUNDAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK.
>> TIME TO JAM NET CAM.
>>  TAKE A LOOK.
>> EARLIER CRASH BW PARKWAY
NORTHBOUND CLEARED 1198.
>>  ROADS ARE PLEASANT.
IF ARE YOU OUT AND ABOUT EARLY
THIS CHRISTMAS EVE.
RUNNING LAST MINTER ERRANDS
YOU'RE IN GREAT SHAPE ON THE
LOCAL ROADS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> STILL AHEAD JUST A COUPLE
MINUTES 7:30 A UPS DRIVER IN
THE DISTRICTS ROBBED AT GUN
POINT AND HAPPENED A COUPLE
TIMES VIDEO POLICE WANT TO YOU
SEE TO TRACK DOWN THE SUSPECT.
>>  PLUS HEADS UP FOR
BICYCLIST IN ONE MARYLAND
COUNTRY.
WHERE IT IS THE LAW TO
REGISTER YOUR BIKES AND CHANGE
THAT COULD SOON BE COMING
WE'LL HAVE IT NEXT.
People aren't talking
about Giant's
sustainable shrimp
wrapped in prosciutto.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's the little things
that make entertaining easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you,
during the holidays.
People aren't talking
about Giant's delicious
spiral ham glazed
with real honey.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you,
during the holidays.
♪
>>> THAT'S PRETTY LOOKING AT THE
CAPITOL WHEEL THIS MORNING
SOMEBODY FLYING SOMEWHERE.
THE AIRPLANE IN THE SHOT RIGHT
OVER THE CAPITOL WHEEL AT
NATIONAL HARBOR PERHAPS JUST
TAKE OFF FROM REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT.
FLYING OVER THE WILSON BRIDGE.
HOPE YOU HAVE A SAFE TRAVELS
WHEREVER YOU GO.
>>> THANKS FOR BEING WITH US ON
THIS TUESDAY MORNING.
IT IS 7:30 RIGHT NOW.
UNFORTUNATELY WE START WITH SAD
NEWS FROM THE ROADWAYS AS WE
FOLLOW OUR TOP STORIES.
MARYLAND STATE POLICE
INVESTIGATING WHAT TURNED INTO A
DEADLY CRASH ON I70 IN FRED
FREDERICK.&
>> THIS HAPPENED NEAR HARMONY
ROAD AROUND 2:00 A.M.
SKYFOX OVER THE SCENE AND POLICE
SAY THE CAR WENT OFF THE ROAD
AND CRASHED AND THEN CAUGHT
FIRE.
THAT DRIVER NOT ABLE TO MAKE IT
OUT ALIVE.
PRONOUNCED DEAD AT THE SCENE.
POLICE ARE WORKING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT HAPPENED.
>>> ALSO KNEW THIS MORNING D.C.
POLICE SEARCHING FOR TWO PEOPLE
WHO ROBBED UPS WORKER AND THEN
STOLE THEIR DELIVERY TRUCK.
THIS WAS ON THE MORNING OF
DECEMBER 6th IN THE 300 BLOCK
OF 63rd STREET NORTHEAST.
POLICE SAY THE SUSPECTS ATTACKED
THE UPS EMPLOYEE AND THEN DROVE
OFF IN THE TRUCK.
IF YOU RECOGNIZE EITHER OF THESE
PEOPLE, PLEASE GIVE D.C. POLICE
A CALL.
>>> NEW THIS MORNING IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA, FAUQUIER'S BOARD OF
SUPERVISE UNANIMOUSLY APPROVED A
RESOLUTION IN SUPPORT OF THE
SECOND AMENDMENT.
AROUND 90 OTHER COUNTIES AND THE
COMMONWEALTH HAVE ADOPTED
SIMILAR RESOLUTIONS.
>> SURPRISE FOR SOME FOOTBALL
FANS SHOPPING AT TYSONS LAST
NIGHT.
YES, IN FACT THAT IS RAVENS
QUARTERBACK LA JAR JACKSON AT
TYSONS CORNERS.
FANS SNAPPED VIDEOS OF JACKSON
AS DID HE HIS CHRISTMAS SHO
SHOPPING.
HE MADE A STOP AT GAME STOP
BUYING SOME THINGS FOR TEAMMATES
TO DOMINATE THE FOOTBALL VIDEO
FIELD MUCH LIKE DID HE THE REAL
FIELD THIS YEAR.
WE SHALL SEE.
>> GO FROM TYSONS TO MONTGOMERY
MONTGOMERY COUNTY, MARYLAND.
HEADS IF YOU YOUR BICYCLE OR IF
BICYCLE IS ON CHRISTMAS LIST
THIS YEAR.
DID YOU KNOW YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T
YOU HAVE TO ACTUALLY REGISTER
YOUR BIKE IN THE COUNTY.
>> ONE CYCLIST FOUND OUT THE
HARD WAY.
FOX5'S JOSH ROSENTHAL HAS VIDEO
OF A STOP AND THE LAW MANY
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
♪
>> Reporter: ON THE MEAN
STREETS OF MONTGOMERY COUNTY,
HUNDREDS IF NOT THOUSANDS OF
LAWS AND ORDINANCES ARE ON THE
BOOKS.
SOME YOU KNOW, AND OTHERS, WELL,
MAYBE NOT.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN YOU
FOUND OUT ABOUT THE SECOND
CITATION?
>> I DUMB FOUNDED BY THAT.
>> Reporter: HERE'S THE STORY.
BACK IN JUNE, STEVE SILVERMAN
STOPPED TO TALKED TO A TEEN
APPROACHED BY TWO POLICE OFF
OFFICERS.
SILVERMAN IS AN ACTIVIST AND
THIS IS SOMETHING HE DOES.
>> I TEACH PEOPLE HOW TO TALK TO
COMPS.
>> Reporter: SHORTLY AFTER
YARDS AFTER SILVERMAN HOPPED
BACK ON HIS BOX THE OFFICERS
STOPPED HIM.
>> YORKS YOU GOT TO STOP.
I'M PULLING YOU OVER.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE YOU RAN THE STOP SIGN
BACK THERE.
>> SILVERMAN OBTAINED THIS BODY
CAMERA FOOTAGE FROM POLICE.
AT ONE POINT HE BEGINS RECORDING
AND THEN THIS.
[ INAUDIBLE ]
>> CAN YOU CHECK.
>> DO YOU HAVE A REGISTRATION
STICKER, COUNTY REGISTRATION
STICKER FOR YOUR BICYCLE.
>> A REGISTRATION STICKER FOR MY
BICYCLE.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: YOU HEARD THAT
RIGHT.
RARELY ENFORCED LAW IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY THAT MANDATES
BICYCLE REGISTRATION AND
SILVERMAN WAS CITED FOR THAT,
TOO.
>> I HAD NEVER HEARD OF SUCH A
THING BEFORE.
>> HE WASN'T ALONE AFTER
SILVERMAN POSTED HIS VIDEO ON
HIS NON-PROFIT WEBSITE A
MARYLAND DELEGATE SPOKE OUT
CALLING A STUPID LAW.
BETHESDA BEAT WROTE AN ARTICLE
ABOUT IT GARNERING MORE
ATTENTION AND NOW POLICE ARE
RESPONDING.
TELLING FOX5 SILVERMAN WAS
PULLED OVER BECAUSE HE RAN A
STOP SIGN WHICH IS A SAFETY
HAZARD AND ADDING THAT THEY ARE
LOOKING INTO HOW FREQUENTLY
OFFICERS CHARGE PEOPLE FOR
UNREGISTERED BIKES.
>> HAVE YOU GOTTEN YOUR BIKE
REGISTERED?
>> I HAVE.
>> SO YOU ARE NO LONGER BREAK
THE LAW?  I AM NO LONGER A SCOFF
LAW.
>> JOSH ROSENTHAL REPORT BECAUSE
OF THIS CASE MONTGOMERY COUNTY
COUNCIL MEMBERS TELL US THEY
PLAN TO INTRODUCE LEGISLATION
THAT WOULD MAKE REGISTERING YOUR
BIKE VOLUNTARY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
7:34 RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GET OVER TO TUCKER WITH A
CHECK OF THE FORECAST.
MAN, THINGS ARE LOOKING GREAT
FOR THIS CHRISTMAS EVE, TUCK.
>> THEY'RING LOOING FANTASTIC.
I MEAN WEATHER WISE WE COULDN'T
ASK FOR NICER WEATHER, QUIETER
WEATHER.
YEAH, IT'S COOL OR COLD THIS
MORNING.
THAT'S YOUR SUNRISE ACTUAL
SUNRISE BEHIND YOU THERE.
YOU CAN SEE WE'RE GETTING OFF
BEAUTIFUL START.
35 THIS MORNING.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH AT SEVEN.
WHAT CAN WE EXPECT TODAY?  LOTS
OF SUNSHINE, QUIET CONDITIONS,
DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT 50.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT'S PRETTY GOOD FOR THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
WE SHOULD TYPICALLY BE IN THE
MID 40.
>> ERIN TRYING TO DECIDE WHETHER
OR NOT SHE THINKS 50 GOOD.
>> WHAT?  HOW DARE YOU?
>> NICE AND QUIET.
LISTEN, TRAVELING WE'LL DOT
TRAVEL MAP COMING UP BUT
TRAVELING MOST OF THE COUNTRY
FAIRLY QUIET, AND THERE'S A
QUICK LOOK AT THE SEVEN DAY.
YOU CAN JUST SEE, YEAH, IN THE
WEATHER DEPARTMENT IT'S A NICE
QUIET TIME OF YEAR.
LOOK AT THAT.
50 TODAY.
50 TOMORROW.
ALL THINGS GO HERE FOR DELIVERY
TONIGHT.
AND MAYBE WE'LL GET TO NEAR
60 DEGREES BY SATURDAY BEFORE
SOME RAIN RETURNS ON SUNDAY.
ERIN.
>> THANK YOU TUCKER BARNES.
RIGHT NOW 7:35.
KEEPING A LOOK AT THE ROADS
AROUND THE DMV, AND IT'S QUIET
IN ALL OF THOSE CAMERAS.
EARLIER CRASH BW PARKWAY
NORTHBOUND BEFORE 198 JUST A
SLIGHT RESIDUAL DELAY.
95 LOOKS GREAT JUST HOSPITAL OP
ON THAT IF YOU'RE HEADING TOWARD
BWI.
TRAFFIC QUIET ON THE WAY TO
REAGAN NATIONAL.
PEDESTRIAN STRUCK AT SEVEN.
CAUTION THERE.
BAY BRIDGE RIGHT WIDE.
OPEN AREA BRIDGES ARE LOOKING
PLEASANT RIGHT NOW.
270 NORTH TOWARD PITTSBURGH
LOOKS GREAT.
95 SOUTH TOWARDS VIRGINIA BEACH
STAFFORD ALSO IN GOOD SHAPE ALL
OF YOUR METRO RAIL LINES ON
TIME.
NOW, I WANT TO TOSS OUT TO
SOMEONE WHO IS THE QUEEN OF
CHRISTMAS ANGIE CLAUSE IS AT
DULLES AND SHE'S BRINGING THE
CHRISTMAS SPIRIT.
ANGIE?
>> Reporter: HEY, HEY, HEY,
HO, HO, HO GUESS WHAT?  ANGIE
CLAUSE STILL DELIVERING BECAUSE
IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THE BOARD
BEHIND ME, IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE
STILL MINIMAL DELAYS ONLY TWO.
IN FACT, ANNE MENTIONED EARLIER
THAT, UM, THE LAST COUPLE OF
DAYS THEY NOTICED THAT THE
ARRIVALS PLANES WERE LANDING
EARLIER THAN THEY WERE
SCHEDULED.
I CHECKED DOWNSTAIRS ON THE
BOARD.
THAT SEEMS TO BE THE CASE FOR
MANY OF THE FLIGHTS COMING IN.
WANT TO SAY HELLO TO SOME OF MY
FRIENDS FELLOW TRAVELERS THEY'RE
JUST A FEW OF THE 7 MILLION
TAKING TO THE SKIES.
WHERE YOU GOING?  WHY DID YOU
WAIT TILL CHRISTMAS EVE TO FLY
OUT?
>> WE JUST WANTING TO AWAY, YOU
KNOW, FOR A LITTLE BIT WITNESS
KIDS FROM THE WEATHER, UM, AND
TRYING TO HAVE FUN.
>> WHERE YOU FROM?
>> I'M FROM EL SALVADOR.
>> IS THAT WHERE YOU'RE GOING
BACK.
>> THAT'S WHERE WE GOING.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR
CHRISTMAS?  I GOT TO FIND OUT.
>> A DIRT BIKE.
ALL RIGHT.
MAKE SURE YOU WEAR THAT HELMET.
HAVE A SAFE FLIGHT, EVERYBODY.
AND RIGHT NOW, WHAT WE'RE SEEING
IS THAT THERE ARE STILL A RUSH
OF PEOPLE CHECKING IN.
OVER ALL HUSTLE AND BUSTLE NOT
TOO BAD.
LOOKS LIKE EVERYBODY TAKING THE
ADVICE SHOWING UP EARLY.
NOT REALLY SEEING A LOT OF
STRESSED OUT PEOPLE WHICH IS A
GOOD SIGN.
IN FACT EARLIER I SAW SOMEONE
WHO BROUGHT COOKIES FOR ALL THE
AIRPORT WORKERS HERE.
BECAUSE THEY WERE HERE EARLY AS
WE WERE, TOO.
WORKING HARD AND TRYING TO BE AS
HELPFUL AS WE CAN TO KEEP THESE
LINES MOVING AS FAST AS
POSSIBLE.
BUT, UM, YEAH, WE'RE LOOKING AT
A RECORD BREAKING NUMBER OF
TRAVELERS NOT ONLY IN THE SKIES
BUT ALSO ON THE GROUND.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE NUMBERS,
105 MILLION PEOPLE TALKING TO
THE ROADS.
OKAY.
AND 7 MILLION I MENTIONED SKIES
AND 4 MILLION GETTING WHERE THEY
NEED TO GO BY SOME OTHER MEANS.
BUT THAT'S PRETTY INCREDIBLE.
THE DAY YOU'LL WANT TO AVOID IF
YOU ARE TRAVELING TO AND FROM OR
IF YOU HAVE FAMILY THAT'S COMING
BACK TO THE AREA TELL THEM HOLD
OFF ON DECEMBER 26th.
BETWEEN 4:00 AND 6:00 P.M.
THEY'RE SAYING IT COULD BE THREE
TIMES THE CONGESTION TO GET BACK
HOME.
IT WILL BE TOUGH.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> REMEMBER THE REASON FOR THE
SEASON.
RIGHT?
>> ANGIE, YOU SHOULD BE OKAY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YES.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU A LITTLE BIT
LATER.
>>> ROYAL REVEAL.
NEXT, PRINCE HARRY AND DUCHESS
MEGAN SHARE THEIR CHRISTMAS
CARD.
SO CUTE.
>> WHERE IS SANTA AS WE'RE
TRACKING THE BIG GUY ON THIS
CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> ♪
>> STILL OVER THE ISLANDS RIGHT
NOW BUT OVER HALF A BILLION
GIFTS DELIVERED ALREADY.
BUSY COUPLE OF HOURS.
>> BRUTE ISLANDS.
♪
E ISLANDS.
♪♪
[ dramatic music ]
This holiday...
Ahhhhh!!!
-Ahhhhh!!!
A distant friend returns...
Elliott.
You came back!
And while lots of
things have changed...
Wooooah!
-Woah!
It's called the Internet.
Some things haven't.
Get ready for a reunion
3 million light
years in the making.
Woohoo!
-Yeah!
TWEETED THE CARD.
SWEETEST CHRISTMAS CARD FROM THE
DUKE AND DUCHESS OF SUSSEX VERY
MERRY CHRISTMAS, EVERYONE.
THAT'S CUTE.
>>> THAT IS SO PRECIOUS.
ALL RIGHT.
MORE ROYAL NEWS.
WHY NOT?  OKAY.
SNEAK PEEK OF QUEEN ELIZABETH'S
ANNUAL CHRISTMAS SPEECH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THE 93-YEAR-OLD RECORDED HER
MESSAGE AT WINDSOR CASTLE
YESTERDAY.
SHARING A LITTLE PREVIEW ABOUT
THIS PAST YEAR WHICH SHE
DESCRIBES AS HAVING FELT QUOTE
QUIET BUMPY.
BUT ADDING THAT SMALL STEPS CAN
MAKE A WORLD OF DIFFERENCE.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S IT.
I'M DONE.
YOUR TURN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL IN PARIS
CANCELED CHRISTMAS MASS FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN 200 YEARS.
THEY HAD THAT BIG FIRE, OF
COURSE AND CREWS ARE STILL
TRYING TO RESTORE THE BUILDING.
FOLLOWING THAT MASSIVE FIRE IN
APRIL.
FRENCH PRESIDENT MACRON EXPECTS
THE RESTORATION TO BE FINISHED
BY 2024.
A FEW YEARS AWAY.
ALSO JUST IN TIME FOR THE PARIS
SUMMER OLYMPICS.
>>> COMING UP, THE LATEST NIKE
SHOE TO SELL OUT.
ALSO COMING WITH A BIT OF
CONTROVERSY.
>> PLUS HOLIDAYS ALWAYS BIG AT
THE BOX OFFICE.
LITTLE WOMEN MAKING ITS DEBUT.
KEVIN'S SIT DOWN WITH THE CAST
IS COMING UP AFTER THE BREAK.
LITTLE WOMEN AGAIN.
♪
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
♪
>> THIS IS THE CUTEST THING.
THAT IS MAXWELL, MY MAN RIGHT
THERE.
ALL RIGHTY.
THIS IS WHOLE BUNCH OF CELE
CELEBRITIES GETTING IN ON MARIAH
CAREY' JUST RELEASED BRAND NEW
MUSICAL VIDEO FOR HER HOLIDAY
CLASSIC ALL I WANT FOR CHRI
CHRISTMAS.
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
HER CELEB FRIENDS SINGING ALONG
TO THE FAMOUS TUNE.
THAT VIDEO INCLUDES HOME VIDEOS
FROM OF COURSE THE KARDASHIANS.
HEY, THAT'S, UM, JOE JOE, YEAH.
OKAY.
ARIANA GRANDE, CHANCE THE
RAPPER, KATIE PER WREAK SNOOP
DOGG, MAXWELL JUST TO NAME A F
FEW.
THAT'S DEBBIE ALLEN DID WE SAY
THAT?  OKAY.
THIS IS GREAT.
>> FROM STRANGER THINGS. THINGS.
PEOPLE IN THIS.
TRACY ELLIS ROSS.
I THINK WATCH THIS ALL DAY.
I THINK THAT WAS LAVERNE COX.
>> FUN.
>> WAS THAT YOUR MAN --
>> WE GOING TO WANT WHOLE VIDEO.
EVERYBODY GOT ASKED TO BE IN IT
EXCEPT US.
>> I THINK I SAW YOU IN IT,
STEVE, BEHIND THE CHRISTMAS T
TREE.
>> WHAT'S BETTER TO SHOW ON
CHRISTMAS EVE IF WE'RE REALLY
BEING HONEST.
WE SHOULD SHOW ON THAT A LOOP
TOMORROW MORNING ACTUALLY.
>> WELL, LISTEN WE GOT HOURS
TOMORROW.
>> CHANCE OF THAT.
A LOT OF TIME TO FILL.
>> YOU MIGHT GET YOUR CHRISTMAS
WISH, ALLISON.
>> PUT ME IN A GOOD MOOD.
HIGHS YESTERDAY 53.
55 WAS WINNING NUMBER AT DULLES
AND BWI MARSHALL.
NORMAL HIGH 45.
WE'LL TREND ABOVE THIS NUMBER
EACH AND OF DAY FOR THE NEXT
WEEK OR SO.
SO AGAIN, VERY QUITE MILD
PATTERN EXPECTED FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS INCLUDING THIS
AFTERNOON.
NOW THE MORNINGS OF COURSE WITH
CLEAR SKIES OVERNIGHT WE'VE HAD
A CHANCE TO COOL IT DOWN.
22 THE COOL SPOT RIGHT NOW IN
MAN NASS.
DULLES 30 DEGREES.
32 IN GAITHERSBURG.
LEONARDTOWN GOOD MORNING
36 DEGREES FOR YOU.
35 IN ANNAPOLIS.
SO AGAIN CHILLY TEMPERATURES.
TRAVELING TODAY, I MEAN IT'S
NOT -- BASICALLY WHAT'S HAPPENED
IS THE VERY COLD WINTER AIR IS
BOLTED UP NORTH.
ALASKA TEMPERATURES OVER THE
NEXT WEEK 20, 30, IN SOME CASES
40 DEGREES BELOW NORMAL.
SANTA, NIGHT.
THERE IT IS BUT FOR THE REST OF
THE COUNTRY JUST A NICE QUIET
PATTERN HERE.
IF YOU'RE TRAVELING TODAY, YOU
REALLY CAN'T COMPLAIN ABOUT THAT
AS MOST OF THE COUNTRY WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF THE ROCKY MOUNTAIN
STATES PRETTY QUIET AND THOSE
SHOWERS ACROSS THE SOUTHEAST
SHOULD BE OUT OF HERE IN THE
NEXT 12 HOURS OR SO.
SO CONDITIONS IMPROVING IN
FLORIDA IF YOU'RE HEADED DOWN TO
MIAMI OF COURSE THEY HAD HEAVY
RAIN TOWARDS FT. LAUDERDALE.
FOR US JUST A FEW CLOUDS OUT
THERE.
YOU CAN SEE THEM.
OTHERWISE, A NICE AFTERNOON.
DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT 50, AND A
NICE QUIET WEATHER PATTERN HERE
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
WE'RE FINE TONIGHT FOR SANTA'S
DELIVERIES AND WE LOOK GREAT FOR
CHRISTMAS DAY, TOO.
DON'T WORRY.
SANTA WILL BE ON TIME WITH THOSE
GIFTS.
THERE'S OUR RAIN SHOWER ACTIVITY
ACROSS SOUTHEAST COAST.
WE'LL GET THAT STORM TO SCOOT
OUT TO SEA, AND WE'RE LOOKING AT
A NICE QUIET PATTERN UP AND DOWN
THE EASTERN SEABOARD INCLUDING
RIGHT HERE THE NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS.
50 THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS.
WARM IT UP MAKE A RUN TO
60 DEGREES BY SATURDAY AFTE
AFTERNOON.
STEVE THAT BIG WHEEL YOU GOT FOR
CHRISTMAS LAST YEAR YOU CAN TAKE
IT OUT FOR A SPIN OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
>> AWESOME.
BEEP BEEP.
>> HI.
>> STEVE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
HE WAS LIKE WHATEVER, TUCKER.
>> METRO HOLIDAY SCHEDULE FOR
CHRISTMAS EVE RAIL LINES AND
BUSES ON NORMAL SCHEDULE.
THEY'RE ON TIME RIGHT NOW.
METRO ACCESS SUBSCRIPTION SHIPS
CANCELED TODAY.
AS FOR CHRISTMAS DAY KEEP IN
MIND METRO BUS OPERATING ON A
SUNDAY SCHEDULE.
METRO RAIL OPENS 8:00 A.M.
TOMORROW WITH SERVICE LASTING
THROUGH 11:00 P.M.
ALL PEAK FAIRS IN EFFECT AND
PARKING FREE AT ALL METRO
FACILITIES.
METRO ACCESS CANCELED TOMORROW
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT
THAT.
AS WE TAKE LOOK AT OUR SIX PACK
JUST FOR TUCKER I CAN TELL YOU
TRAFFIC MOVING ON ALL OF OUR
MAJORS.
NO PROBLEMS THERE OVER THE
LEGION BRIDGE.
I LIKE THAT WE CAN MAKE KEVIN
MCCARTHY LAUGH.
SUN LOOKS BEAUTIFUL OVER 395.
HARDLY ANY TRAFFIC.
EARLIER CRASH CLEARED OUT BY 198
IN THE MEDIAN BW PARKWAY
NORTHBOUND.
95 WIDE OPEN QUIET ON THE WAY TO
BWI REAGAN NATIONAL AND DULLES.
270 DELAYS IN BOTH DIRECTIONS.
WHOOP WHOOP, BACK TO YOU.
>> COLIN KAEPERNICK RELEASED
NICKY SHOE SOLD OUT WITHIN
MINUTES.
BLACK AIR FORCE ONE CALLED TRUE
TO SEVEN WHICH IS THE NUMBER
THAT CAP WORE WHEN HE PLAYED FOR
THE 49ERS.
IMAGE ON THE HEEL OF THE SHOE IS
AS WELL AND THE NUMBERS 814 AND
16 PRINTED OUT SOUL THE DATE HE
STARTED KNEELING DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM TO PROTEST
POLICE BRUTALITY.
SHOE RETAILED FOR $110 IF YOU
COULD FIND IT BUT AGAIN SOLD OUT
RIGHT AWAY NOW ON THE SECONDARY
PARK FOR MUCH MORE.
>>> 7:49.
AND EARLY CHRISTMAS SURPRISE FOR
TROOPS OVERSEAS THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
MILITARY OPERATIVES EMBARKING ON
WHAT THEY CALL THE HOLIDAY
EXPRESS.
TRAVELING BY HELICOPTER ACROSS
PARTS OF SYRIA HANDING OUT GIFTS
TO THE MEN HARD-WORKING MEN AND
WOMEN IN UNIFORM THAT ARE
STATIONED THERE.
AND THE GIFT GIVING WAS DONE TO
FESTIVE TUNES PLAYED BY THE
MILITARY BAND.
ACCOMPANYING OFFICIALS ON THEIR
TRIP.
AWESOME.
>> ♪
>>> 7:49 RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GIVE YOU LOOK AT THE GOOD
DAY LIST.
THE GUEST LIST.
IT'S ON AND POPPING AS IT ALWAYS
IS.
LIVE IN THE LOFT THIS MORNING,
ACTOR SINGER SONG WRITER CHARLES
HE IS TON YOU KNOW HIM FROM THE
HIT SHOW NASHVILLE MUCH HE'S
GOING TO PERFORM FOR US LIVE IN
THE LOFT.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE AREA
CHARLES.
GONE DAY WE'LL HELP YOU KEEP UP
YORK WORK OUTS HANGING OUT WITH
YOUR MANY IF ALLY ON THE
HOLIDAYS.
FIT LESS TRAINER WILL JOIN US
LIVE WITH TIPS TO KEEP YOU
MOVING.
>> IF YOU NEED RECOMMENDATIONS
FOR YOUR TV BINGING OVER THE
HOLIDAYS, KEVIN HAS GOT YOU
COVERED.
HE'LL OFF UP A LIST OF THE MOST
BINGE WORTHY SHOWS ON NETFLIX TO
KEEP YOU ENTERTAINED.
IT'S ONE WORD, WITCHED.
>> THE WITCHER.
>> I MEAN ALL THE RAGE, RIGHT?
SO THERE YOU GO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT NOW.
>> KEV IS WITH US RIGHT NOW IN
THE MEANTIME.
WHAT YOU GOT.
>> GO TO SEE YOU THIS MORNING.
>> YOU TOO.
>> WE'LL DO 8:50 AND 10AM HOUR
IF YOU'RE TUNING IN.
>> THIS WEEKEND LITTLE WOMEN
HITTING THEATERS TECHNICALLY
TOMORROW CHRISTMAS DAY AND FOR
PEOPLE WHO AREN'T AWARE THIS IS
A CLASSIC STORY AND I WILL SAY
THIS.
IN FULL DISCLOSURE I HAD NEVER
READ LITTLE WOMEN THE BOOK AND I
HAD NEVER SEEN THE '90'S FILM
WITH WINONA RIDER THIS IS MY
FIRST EXPERIENCE WITH LITTLE
WOMEN.
I THOUGHT IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE
FILM GRETA GERWIG PUT TOGETHER
ONE OF THEMES OF LITTLE WOMEN
THIS IDEA OF YOUR CHILDHOOD
SLIPPING AWAY AND THE MOMENT YOU
BECOME AN ADULT, RIGHT?  SO WHEN
I SPOKE TO THE CAST INCLUDING
LAUREN COHN, FLORENCE PEW AND
SASHA RONAN I WANTED TO FIND OUT
IF THEY REMEMBERED THE MOMENT IN
THEIR LIVES WHEN THE CHILDHOOD
MOMENT SLIPPED AWAY AND THEY
BECAME ADULTS.
WATCH THIS.
>> DO YOU KNOW THAT MOMENT IN
YOUR LIFE OR VAGUELY KNOW THAT
MOMENT IN YOUR LIFE YOU REALLY
KIND OF THOUGHT YOUR CHILDHOOD
SLIPPING AWAY AND BECOMING AN
ADULT?
>> UM-HMM.
>> YEAH.
>> FOR ME IT WAS WHEN I WAS 19
AND I MOVED TO LONDON AND I
REMEMBER MY MOM HAD COME OVER TO
HELP ME GET SETTLED IN AND SHE
LEFT AND WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT THIS HOW LOVELY IT IS TO
HAVE THEM THERE AND LIKE MADE
DINNER FOR YOU AND THE PLACE IS
CLEAN AND ALL THAT SORT OF STUFF
AND SHE LEFT AND I REMEMBER THE
DAY AFTER SHE LEFT I WAS LIKE,
I'M REALLY HUNGRY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WENT TO THE KITCHEN.
I DON'T HAVE ANY FOOD.
I THOUGHT, OH, I HAVE TO GO GET
FOOD.
THEN I SHOULD GO COOK IT AND
THEN I HAVE TO GO AND GET MORE
FOOD IT KEEPS GOING ON AND ON
AND ON AND I HAD THIS
REALIZATION THAT LIKE AS SOON AS
YOU LEAVE HOME BASICALLY AND
ESPECIALLY THEN WHEN YOU RETURN
HOME AFTER YOU'VE LEFT, IT'S
NEVER THE SAME AGAIN.
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT I WAS
INDEPENDENT AND THEN, UM, I WENT
TO AMERICA WHEN I WAS 19.
THE FIRST TIME I HAD EVER BEEN
TO AMERICA.
FIRST TIME I --
>> 19.
>> YEAH.
>> DONE A LONG HAUL FLIGHT I
REMEMBER MY MOM I WAS OFFERED IF
I WANTED A CAR TO GO TO THE
AIRPORT AND I -- GOING UP TO MY
MOM, MOM THEY'VE OFFERED A CAR
TO TAKE ME TO THE AIRPORT AND
SHE GOES, OH, DO YOU WANT IT?  I
WAS LIKE, WELL I MEAN IF IT'S
TOO TRICKY FOR YOU TO TAKE ME.
>> SHE WAS LIKE NO, NO, NO, I'LL
TAKE YOU.
THE WHOLE JOURNEY AND I SAT IN
THE CAR IN SILENCE AND WE WERE
JUST LIKE -- I THINK I ALWAYS
SUSPECTED I WAS VERY ADULT UNTIL
THE MOMENT I ALSO MOVED OUT AND
I THINK MY MOTHER'S FEELING WAS,
YOU'RE 17 BUT YOU'VE ALREADY
DONE A NUMBER OF MOVIES WHERE
YOU'RE WITHOUT ME SO YOU'RE
READY FOR THIS.
AND MY MEMORY WAS THE FIRST TIME
I WAS IN AN APARTMENT NOT LIVING
WITH MY MOM THAT I GOT SICK.
>> AND THERE WAS NOBODY THERE,
AND CALLING MY MOM AND SAYING
I'M SICK.
WAITING FOR HER TO SAY I'M
DRIVING OVER RIGHT NOW.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SHE WAS WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
FOR YOURSELF?
>> IT WAS JUST DEVASTATING.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO LITTLE WOMEN OPENS UP TONIGHT
TECHNICALLY THAT THEATERS
TOMORROW IS THE OFFICIAL RELEASE
DATE IN THE WASHINGTON, D.C.
AREA.
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR AND SEE IT
GRETA GERWIG IS SOME A GREAT
DIRECTOR.
SHE'LL BE ON THE SHOW LATER THIS
WEEK.
WE'LL BE BACK LATER ON.
>> GUYS, APPRECIATE IT.
>> SANTA IS ON HIS WAY.
>> IS HE?
>> WE'RE TRACKING HIM RIGHT.
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> HE'S OUT THERE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT RIGHT NOW --
>> BRINGING STAR WARS GIFTS.
>> POSSIBLY.
STAR WARS WOULD LIKE HE BRINGS A
FEW MORE VIEWERS TO THE THE
THEATERS.
>> $175 MILLION NOTHING TO BE
SHAMED OF.
EVEN THOUGH IT IS LOW FOR STAR
WARS.
>> MOST PEOPLE WON'T COMPLAIN
ABOUT THAT YOU CAN TRACK HIM IN
THE NORAD SANTA TRACKER AS HE
GOES FROM CITY TO CITY AND CHECK
OUT A FEW THEATERS IN SCREENINGS
FOR 64 YEARS U IS THE AND
CANADIAN DEFENSE COMMAND
PARTNERED UP TO KEEP A CLOSE
WATCH ON SANTA'S JOURNEY.
♪
>> TUCKER, HOW IS HIS WEATHER
GOING TO BE.
>> KEV I HAVE A QUICK
ENTERTAINMENT QUESTION FOR YOU.
IS BABY YODA IS OUR YODA OR
ANOTHER CHARACTER THAT LOOKS
LIKE BABY YODA.
>> TECHNICALLY SPEAKING BECAUSE
YOU DID ASK --
>> OKAY.
>> THE YODA THAT YOU'RE
SEEING --
>> KEVIN, DO NOT ANSWER HIM.
HE'S BEING A WISE GUY?
>> NO, I'M ASKING A SERIOUS
QUESTION.
>> HE'S BEING A WISE ANKLE.
>> I DO KNOW THE ANSWER.
>> HE KNOWS THE ANSWER TOO.
>> I'M NOT DOING THE WEATHER
UNTIL HE TELLS ME THE ANSWER.
I HAVE TO KNOW THE ANSWER, KE
KEVIN.
>> EMPTY MA DORIAN THAT TAKES
PLACE FIVE YEARS AFTER RETURN OF
THE JEDI THAT DARK BABY YODA IS
NOT THE SAME YODA YOU SAW IN THE
ORIGINAL TRILOGY THE ORIGINAL
YODA DIED.
THIS IS A 50-YEAR-OLD CHARACTER
NAMED WE DON'T KNOW WHO IT'S
CALLED THE CHILD WHAT THEY'RE
CALLING.
>> IS IT POSSIBLE IT'S YODA'S
>> COULD BE.
>> OOH.
>> WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE WHO IT
IS.
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT YODA.
WE CALL HIM BABY YODA.
>> THE SEARCH FOR THE FAMILY
CONNECTION WILL BE THE NEXT SPIN
OFF.
>> YOU DO REALIZE WE'RE THE ONES
WHO CALL HIM THAT.
>> I'VE NOT SEEN IT.
>> I WAS ASKING A SERIOUS
QUESTION.
>> SAME SPECIES.
>> IT'S POSSIBLE IT'S YODA'S S
SON.
>> 35 IN WASHINGTON.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH NORTHEAST
AT SEVEN.
OKAY.
WEATHER COULDN'T BE EASIER NICE
AND QUIET.
SUNSHINE JUST A FEW FARE WEATHER
CLOUDS OUT THERE.
HIGH CLOUDS EXPECTED TODAY.
ABOUT 50 THIS AFTERNOON AND
WE'RE LOOKING AT VERY QUIET
CONDITIONS LOCALLY.
HEY, SOUTH EAT COAST.
THAT RAINSTORM THAT BROUGHT VERY
HEAVY RAINS TO PLACES LIKE FT.
LAUDERDALE AND MIAMI YESTERDAY
FINALLY GETTING OUT OF HERE SO
THE BEACH WEATHER WILL IMPROVE
DOWN HERE.
MIAMI 75 AND THEY'RE EXPECTING
SUNSHINE THIS AFTERNOON WHICH IS
GREAT.
ALL THINGS CHRISTMAS RELATE WE
LOOK GREAT CHRISTMAS RELATED AS
WELL LATER TONIGHT PERFECT FOR
DELIVERY.
OH, MY POCKET IS STUCK.
>> I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU.
>> I WASN'T SURE WHAT YOU WERE
POINTING AT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WAS TRYING TO HELP YOU WITH
SCHARR RAIDS AND YOU WERE JUST
NOT PICKING UP WHAT I WAS DOING.
>> 270 DELAY FREE HEADING TO OR
FROM DEEP CREEK RIGHT NOW.
95 NORTHBOUND FREDERICKSBURG
THROUGH STAFFORD IT'S A DREAM.
YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT ELSE IS
NICE?  DALE CITY TRAFFIC, HEY,
LORTON TRAFFIC LOOKS GOOD.
NO PROBLEMS ON THE INNER LOOP
THROUGH ANNANDALE.
THINGS ARE GOOD IN SOUTHERN
MARYLAND.
NO PROBLEMS IN FORT WASHINGTON.
UPPER MARLBORO TRAFFIC LOOKS
GOOD.
SUITLAND PARKWAY ACTUALLY WIDE
OPEN.
GUESS WHAT IF YOU'RE WORKING ON
THIS CHRISTMAS EVE THE WAY WE
ARE, ENJOY THE QUIET COMMUTE.
METRO IS ON TIME, TOO.
TAKE THAT.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> AND KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO
FOX5 MORNING.
SO MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR 8AM
HOUR INCLUDING A WARNING FROM
THE PENTAGON ABOUT USING THOSE
DNA KITS YOU BUY ONLINE.
>> PLUS FESTIVE FEEL LINES ONE
LOCAL CAT CAFE TRANSFORMED INTO
A WINTER WONDERLAND FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
WE WILL TAKE A LOOK COMING UP
NEXT HOUR.
7:57.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT 8:00.
♪
♪♪
I'm Jimmy Dean and thank you
very much for lettin'
us become just a little
part of your holiday.
And we sincerely hope
that Jimmy Dean sausage
might make your holiday just
a little bit brighter.
Happy Holiday to ya.
♪
>>> ALMOST 8:00 A.M. ON THIS
CHRISTMAS EVE MORNING 2019.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS LOOK TO START
YOUR DAY WITH SOME CHRISTMAS
CHEER.
WE'RE TAKING LIVE LOOK AT D.C.'S
CITY CENTER IN NORTHWEST.
>> ABSOLUTELY GORGEOUS.
WE'RE ACTUALLY ENJOYING SOME
CHRISTMAS CHEER HERE AT FOX5 AS
WELL AS WE SAY GOOD TUESDAY
MORNING IN FRONT OF OUR FOX5
CHRISTMAS TREE.
>> IF YOU WERE HOPING FOR WHITE
CHRISTMAS, GOT BAD NEWS IN THAT
DEPARTMENT.
LET'S GET TO TUCK CONCERN ERIN
FOR A FIRST WEATHER AND TRAFFIC
LOOK.
GOOD MORNING, GUYS.
HAPPY CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> THANK YOU ALLISON.
GOOD MORNING.
ABSOLUTELY PERFECT WEATHER,
YEAH, I MEAN AS FAR AS A WHITE
CHRISTMAS IT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN THIS YEAR FOR US WE GOT
MILD TEMPERATURES ON THE WAGE
ALL THE DETAILS ON THAT FORECAST
COMING RIGHT UP.
>> ERIN, GOOD MORNING.
66 WESTBOUND DISABLE VEHICLE
BLOCKS THE RIGHT LANE BY 123.
EASTBOUND VOLUME IS LIGHT.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT THE RAILS
AND REST OF YOUR COMMUTE AROUND
THE DMV NEXT.
>>> FROM THE ROADS TO THE SKIES,
TODAY IS ANTICIPATED TO BE THE
BEST DAY TO HEAD OUT OF TOWN IF
YOU'RE FLYING.
>> IT'S STILL PRETTY BUSY BUT
THE BULK OF PRE CHRISTMAS FLYING
IS NOW BEHIND US.
AIRPORTS NOT EXACTLY EMPTY AS
ANGIE GOFF FOUND OUT SHE'S AT
DULLES THIS MORNING WITH MORE.
ANGIE, AS WE GET CLOSER, YOU
KNOW, INTO THE MORNING OR DIVE A
LITTLE DEEPER INTO THE MORNING
ARE WE GETTING MORE PEOPLE OR
LESS IT LOOKS KIND OF CROWDED
THERE NOW.
>> Reporter: MORE PEOPLE.
TAKE A LOOK BEHIND ME.
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE NIGHT TO EL
SALVADOR AND IT IS FILLING UP.
AND THAT'S TYPICALLY WHAT WE'RE
FINDING IS THAT YOU HAVE A CRUSH
OF PEOPLE AND THEN THERE'S A
LITTLE BIT OF A LULL AND THEN
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE BUT THEY SAY
IT'S GOING TO HOLD STEADY ALL
DAY THEY'RE EXPECTING IT TO BE
VERY, VERY BUSY.
I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND DUCK
UNDERNEATH HERE.
WHOOP, WATCH THE SANTA HAT.
AND I WANTED TO RUN OVER HERE
AND FIND OUT, UM, YOU'RE HEADED
TO EL SALVADOR FOR CHRISTMAS,
RIGHT?  I ASSUME.
>> UM-HMM AND MY GRANDMOTHER'S
BIRTHDAY AS WELL.
>> REPORT THAT'S A BIG
CELEBRATION AND YOUR FLIGHT IS
NOT FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
SO IT SEEMS LIKE YOU TOOK GOOD
ADVICE AND GOT HERE EARLY.
>> YES.
HAD TO.
WE'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE AND IT
GETS VERY CROWDED HERE.
>> Reporter: WHY DID YOU
DECIDE TO FLY OUT TODAY?
>> UM, PROBABLY THE BEST VALUE
IN TERM OF PRICE.
THEY DO SAY TODAY AND STEVE I
KNOW YOU MENTIONED EARLY THAT
TODAY IS THE BEST TIME THEY SAY
TO BUY YOUR TICKETS FOR, UM, IF
YOU'RE GOING TO FLY OUT.
THE MOST EXPENSIVE TIME TO FLY
THEY'RE SAYING IS ON THURSDAY.
THE DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS.
SO YOU MIGHT WANT TO HOLD OFF ON
THAT.
IF YOU HAVEN'T BOUGHT YOUR
TICKET YET.
WHEN WE LOOK AT THE NUMBERS, I
MEAN IT'S PRETTY INCREDIBLE
THEY'RE SAYING 4 MILLION MORE
AMERICANS ARE GOING TO ACTUALLY
TRAVEL THIS HOLIDAY SEASON
BETWEEN NOW THROUGH JAN
JANUARY 2nd.
SO THIS IS GOING TO GO ON FOR
LIKE A WEEK TALKING ABOUT THE
ROADWAYS, 105 MILLION PEOPLE.
7 MILLION IN THE AIR NEAR
4 MILLION, UM, TAKING TRAINS AND
BUSES AND WHATNOT.
NOW, THE ONE THING TO REMEMBER,
IF YOU ARE COMING TO THE AIRPORT
THERE'S A COUPLE OPTIONS AS YOU
CAN SEE OUT HERE LET'S MAKE OUR
WAY.
THE LINES ARE BUILDING UP.
YOU CAN SEE OUTSIDE CARS ARE
ALREADY LINING UP AND WHAT WE'RE
FINDING YOU WANT ME TO GO OUT
HERE.
LET'S DO IT.
THAT'S DO NOT ENTER.
I CAN READ.
THERE WE GO.
IT'S NOT SO BAD BUT WHAT YOU
MIGHT WANT TO CONSIDER AS THE
DAY GOES ON THEY SAY TO SHAVE
MINUTES OFF IS JUST DOING YOUR
CURB SIDE CHECK IN.
THERE'S SOMEONE STANDING BY
RIGHT THERE, AND THAT WILL SHAVE
OFF SOME MINUTES IF YOU ARE
RUNNING LINED BECAUSE THE
REALITY IS THEY'RE SAYING TWO
EXTRA HOURS AHEAD OF TIME
BECAUSE OF THE LONG SECURITY
LINES, AND THE LINES AT THE
CHECK OUT COUNTER, UM, BUT OVER
ALL THINGS ARE LOOKING GOOD OVER
HERE AND EVERYBODY IS SEEMS TO
BE IN A GOOD HOLIDAY SPIRIT.
SO THAT MAKES ME HAPPY.
I'M READY TO FLY IN A COUPLE OF
HOURS.
I'M ALREADY HERE.
SO IT'S GREAT.
NOT GOING TO MISS MY FLIGHT.
BACK TO YOU.
>> DEFINITELY THERE A FEW HOURS
EARLY.
>> PERFECT ASSIGNMENT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> IF YOU STILL HAVE SOME LAST
MINUTE SHOPPING TO DO, NO NEED
TO WORRY JUST YET BECAUSE AMAZON
IS STILL IN THE GAME.
THEY HAVE SAME DAY CHRISTMAS EVE
DELIVERY.
ORDERS HAVE TO BE MADE THOUGH BY
9:30 THIS MORNING.
SO MAKE YOUR CHOICES.
STORES LIKE KOHL'S, BEST BUY,
DICK'S SPORTING GOODS, HOME
GOODS, WALMART ALL OPEN UNTIL AT
LEAST 6:00 P.M.
TARGET IS OPEN UNTIL 10:00 P.M.
AS FOR SOME LOCAL MALLS TYSONS
CLOSES AT 6:00 AND WESTFIELD,
MONTGOMERY MALL IS OPEN UNTIL
7:00.
>>> THAT BRINGS US TO THIS
MORNING'S FOX STAIN POLL.
DO YOU HAVE LAST MINUTE SHOPPING
TO DO FOR CHRISTMAS MORNING?
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE RESULTS
SO FAR.
>> HASN'T MOVED, HAS IT.
>> 70% SAY THEY'RE ALL DONE.
WE'RE DONE, THANKS.
30% STILL NEED TO GET OUT THERE
AND GRAB SOMETHING.
YOU CAN STILL VOTE ON OUR FOX5
D.C. APP.
FIND THE BROWSE SECTION ALSO WAY
IN ON OUR WEBSITE FOXDC.COM.
>> NEW THIS MORNING BRITAIN'S
PRINCE PHILIP OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL AFTER FOUR-DAY STAY.
HE'S 98 YEARS OLD AND THAT'S HIM
WALKING TO THE CAR DISCHARGED
THIS MORNING HOSPITALIZED FOR
QUOTE OBSERVATION AND TREATMENT
IN RELATION TO A PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION.
THE PRINCE RETIRED FROM PUBLIC
LIFE IN 2017 SAYING THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, CHEERS AND I'LL BE ON
MY WAY.
>> FULL SUIT.
>> FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
LOOKING SHARP.
NINE AT YEARS OLD.
>>> WHITE HOUSE KEEPING A VERY
CLOSE EYE ON NORTH KOREA THIS
WEEK AS NEW SATELLITE IMAGES OF
A FACTORY WHERE NORTH KOREA
MAKES MILITARY EQUIPMENT SHOWS
THE COMPLETION OF A NEW
STRUCTURE ON THE GROUNDS.
NORTH KOREA HAS THREATENED A
SO-CALLED CHRISTMAS GIFT
DEPENDING ON WASHINGTON'S
ACTIONS ON GOING NUCLEAR TALKS.
ONE OF THOSE SATELLITE IMAGES
TAKEN JUST A WEEK AGO CAPTURES A
NEW STRUCTURE AND A FACTORY.
US OFFICIALS ARE STILL ON HIGH
ALERT.
>>> NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL IN
PARIS WILL NOT HAVE CHRISTMAS
MASS FOR THE FIRST TIME IN SOME
200 YEARS.
BECAUSE STILL TRYING TO REBUILD
AFTER THAT MASSIVE FIRE IN
APRIL.
FRENCH READ MACRON SAID IT LAB
FEW YEARS BEFORE THE FULL
RESTORATION IS COMPLETE.
THAT SHOULD BE DONE BY 2024 JUST
IN TIME FOR THE PARIS SUMMIT
SUMMER OLYMPICS.
>>> I'M TRYING TO CHALLENGE
MYSELF TO FIGURE OUT WHY I LIKE
TO WAIT TILL THE LAST MINUTE.
I COULD GET IT DONE EARLIER.
>> THE CHALLENGE THAT YOU LIKE.
>> I LIKE IT.
I LIKE BEING OUT THERE MIXING IT
UP WITH THE FOLKS.
>> THERE ARE AMAZING DEALS.
>> NOT EVEN THE DEALS.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK THE DEALS ARE GOING
TO BE LIKE ON THURSDAY.
>> YEAH ABSOLUTELY.
>> RIGHT.
OKAY.
I LIKE IT.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO LIE PEOPLE
IN MY LIFE THAT THEY GET THE
GIFTS A FEW DAYS LATER WHEN THE
DEALS START COOKING.
>> THAT'S JUST BEING FISCALLY
RESPONSIBLE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON TODAY?  YOU
GIVING US A GREAT DAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY FINE.
LOOKING AT SUNSHINE, COLD
TEMPERATURES EARLY THIS MORNING
BUT, YORKS WANT TO CALL IT A
MILD AFTERNOON BUT COMFORTABLE
AFTERNOON BUTT ABOUT 50 LATER
TODAY.
MOST IMPORTANTLY DO NOT DID HE
SAY PRAYER.
SANTA WILL MAKE ON TIME
DELIVERIES.
>> DESPAIR NOT.
>> WEATHER WILL BE ABSOLUTELY
QUIET AROUND HERE.
35 THIS MORNING IN WASHINGTON AT
REAGAN NATIONAL.
34 DULLES.
33 THIS MORNING BWI MARSHALL.
OKAY.
THAT'S AS QUIET AS IT GETS THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
JUST A FEW FARE WEATHER CLOUDS
TO START YOUR MORNING.
SOME HIGH CIRRUS CLOUDS IF YOU
WANT TO IMPRESS YOUR FRIENDS.
OTHERWISE A NICE QUIET AFTERNOON
AND A STORM FREE COUPLE OF DAYS
TO LOOK FORWARD TO.
SO TODAY, TONIGHT, TOMORROW ALL
LOOK GOOD.
HEADED TO FLORIDA?  THAT STORM
WAS A BIG PROBLEM YESTERDAY THAT
BROUGHTED FLOODING TOWARDS FT.
LAUDERDALE.
GARAGELY WHATLY PUSHING EAST AND
GETTING OUT OF THERE.
SO BEACH WEATHER WILL RETURN TO
THE PLACES LIKE MIAMI LATER
TODAY WHICH IS GREAT NEWS.
>> 50 FOR US AND MORE ON TRAVEL
FORECAST COMING RIGHT UP.
WE LOOK GREAT LOCALLY FOR THE
NEXT SEVERAL DAYS.
>> ISN'T THAT NICE LITTLE GIFT
FOR EVERYBODY.
>> RIGHT?
>> THANK YOU, TUCKER.
>> YOU'RE THE BEST.
GOOD MORNING, ERIN.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS NICE
GIFT I SHARED A PICTURE ON
TWITTER OF MY CAT WEARING HIS
SANTA OUTFIT.
>> HE LET YOU PUT HIM ON HIM.
>> THAT'S NOT WHERE I WAS GOING
TO GO.
>> A LOT OF TREATS AND MAYBE TWO
MINUTES HE KEPT IT ON.
>> THAT'S ENOUGH FOR THE
PICTURES.
LITTLE MISS IS IN HER CHRISTMAS
DRESS ERIN FOX5 D.C.
I WANT TO SEE YOUR PET PICTURES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DRESS THEM UP
I GOT SHAME.
>> 66 WESTBOUND DISABLE VEHICLE
BLOCKS THE RIGHT LANE BY 123
MANY VOLUME SUPER LIGHT IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS WE DON'T HAVE ANY
MAJOR SLOW DOWNS ON 66.
28 IN THE DULLES TOLL ROAD
LOOKING GOOD ON THE WAY TO THE
AIRPORT.
QUIET ON THE WAY TO BWI AND
REAGAN NATIONAL.
95BW PARKWAY QUIET.
EARLIER BW PARKWAY NORTHBOUND
CRASH BY 198.
THAT CLEARED.
METRO RAIL LINES ON TIME FOR THE
HOLIDAY SCHEDULE TODAY FOR
CHRISTMAS EVE.
THERE'S JUST NO METRO ACCESS
SUBSCRIPTION THOSE TRIPS
CANCELED.
METRO RAIL AND BUS REGULAR
SCHEDULE.
TAKE A LOOK AT CHRISTMAS DAY
NEXT.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> 8:08 RIGHT NOW.
DOZENS MUCH PEOPLE EVACUATED
FROM THEIR HOMES IN MARTINSBURG,
WEST VIRGINIA ARE ABLE TO RETURN
TODAY.
THEY LIVE NEAR A SEWAGE
TREATMENT PLANT AND THEY WERE
FORCED OUT YESTERDAY MORNING
AFTER A TOXIC GAS STARTED TO
SPREAD THROUGH THE AREA.
YOU CAN SEE IT RIGHT THERE IN
THIS AERIAL PICTURE.
OFFICIALS SAY A TANKER WAS OFF
LOADING CHEMICALS USED TO CLEAN
THE WATER AT THE PLANT WHEN TWO
CHEMICALS ACCIDENTALLY MIXED
CREATING A STRONG CHLORINE LIKE
GAS.
IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA, FAUQUIER
COUNTY BOARD OF SUPERVISE
UNANIMOUSLY APPROVED A
RESOLUTION IN SUPPORT OF THE
SECOND AMENDMENT.
SECOND AMENDMENT SANCTUARY PART
OF THE REGULAR LUCIEN RECOMMENDS
VIRGINIA LAWMAKERS APPROVE GUN
SAFETY MEASURES INCLUDING MORE
FUNDING FOR MENTAL HEALTH
SERVICE AROUND 90 OTHER COUNTIES
IN THE COMMONWEALTH HAVE ADOPTED
SIMILAR RESOLUTIONS.
>>> DEVELOPING OVERNIGHT A
ARREST WARRANTS ISSUED FOR THE
MAN ACCUSED OF KILLING THE
YOUNGER BROTHER OF SAN FRANCISCO
49ERS QUARTERBACK CJ AND ANOTHER
MAN.
23-YEAR-OLD MICHAEL MOSLEY
ACCUSED OF STABBING 22-YEAR-OLD
CLAYTON AND 21-YEAR-OLD PAUL
DURING A FIGHT OUTSIDE OF A BA
ARE IN NASHVILLE.
THE GRANDSON OF FORMER REDSKINS
GENERAL MANAGER BOBBY BETH
THIRD.
MOSLEY MADE UNWANTED ADVANCES
TOWARD A FEMALE FRIEND OF THE
VICTIM'S.
VERBAL ALTERCATION INSIDE THE
BAR LEADING TO PHYSICAL FIGHT
AND THE STABBINGS OUTSIDE THE
BAR.
A THIRD MAN WAS ALSO STABBED BUT
SURVIVED.
>>> A FORMER RED SOX PITCHER
FINDING HIMSELF IN LEGAL TROUBLE
AT THE FOOTBALL STADIUM.
RICH HILL AND HIS WIFE CAITLIN
ARRESTED OUTSIDE GILLETTE
STADIUM IN MASSACHUSETTS PRIOR
TO THE START OF NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS GAME AGAINST THE BILLS.
HE PITCHED FOR THE DODGERS AS
WELL WHICH IS THE VIDEO YOU'RE
SEEING HERE.
POLICE SAY CAITLIN HILL
ATTEMPTED TO ENTER THE STADIUM
WITH AN OVERSIZED BAG THEN
REFUSED TO LEAVE THE AREA.
WHEN ORDERED TO DO SO BY POLICE.
RICH HILL HER HUSBAND WAS
ARRESTED WHEN HE TRIED TO STOP
POLICE FROM PUTTING HIS WIFE
INTO A PRISONER TRANSPORT
VEHICLE.
THEY WERE BOTH INITIALLY CHARGED
WITH DISORDERLY CONDUCT BUT IN
COURT YESTERDAY THE CHARGES
REDUCED TO CIVIL INFRACTIONS AND
ORDERED TO PAY FINES.
♪
>>> BIZARRE STORY, STEVE.
OKAY.
8:10 RIGHT NOW.
STILL AHEAD, THE POPULAR DATING
APP THAT'S ACCUSED OF LEAKING
SOME PERSONAL INFORMATION OF ITS
USERS IN ORDER TO BENEFIT OTHER
USERS.
PLUS, HOME FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
THE MOMENT A PAIR OF LOST DOGS
WANDERED ON TO A BUS AND HOW THE
DRIVER HELPED THEM REUNITE WITH
THEIR FAMILY.
AND 2019 WINDS DOWN, WHAT'S YOUR
NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION?  TURNS
OUT THERE'S A CERTAIN TIME OF
THE YEAR THAT MAY ENSURE THE
GREATEST SUCCESS WITH YOUR
RESOLUTION AND NO, IT'S N
>>VEOOK OUTSIDE AS WE TAKE
YOU TO THE BREAK.
♪
>> Reporter: NOT ONLY ARE WE
TRACKING YOUR CHRISTMAS EVE AND
YOUR CHRISTMAS DAY FORECASTS.
WE'RE ALSO KEEPING AN EYE ON
SANTA'S JOURNEY.
SO THAT'S THAT BIG BOX YOU'RE
LOOKING AT COURTESY OF NORAD.
HE'S NEAR JAPAN RIGHT NOW
ENTERING THAT AREA.
SO DROPPING OFF SOME GIFTS FOR
ALL THE GOOD GIRLS AND BOYS OF
JAPAN.
STAY WITH US.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
♪♪
People aren't talking
about Giant's
sustainable shrimp
wrapped in prosciutto.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's the little things
that make entertaining easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you,
during the holidays.
People aren't talking
about Giant's delicious
spiral ham glazed
with real honey.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you,
during the holidays.
♪
>>> ♪ I DON'T WANT A LOT FOR
CHRISTMAS, THERE'S JUST ONE
THING I NEED ♪
>> THAT'S WASHINGTON CAPITALS
WISHING EVERYBODY A VERY MERRY
CHRISTMAS.
LOOK RIGHT IN THE CENTER NOT
MOVING THAT'S OUR FRIEND CAPTAIN
JUST HERE IN OUR STUDIOS A
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
>> WHAT'S UP CAPTAIN.
>> TEAM RELEASED THIS VIDEO OF
THE PLAYERS SINGING ALONG TO ALL
I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS YOU AND
CAPTAIN TAKING LEAD VOCALS WITH
EVERYBODY ELSE INCLUDING ALEX
OVECHKIN.
>> HE'S A SUPER GOOD BOY.
>> RIGHT.
HE'S THE BEST.
SERVICE DOG IN TRAINING.
>> BUT HE'S STANDING SO STILL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> SO CUTE.
>> DOING A GREAT JOB.
AS CAPTAIN.
>>> THIS TIME OF YEAR SOME
PEOPLE LIKE TO GET LITTLE
CREATIVE WITH GIFT WRAPPING THIS
MORNING ONE CELEBRITY'S WRAPPING
IS TURNING SOME HEADS.
WE'RE TALKING KIM KARDASHIAN
POSTERIOR THIS INDIVIDUAL I
DON'T KNOW SHOWING GIFTS GRABBED
IN CREAM COLORED FABRIC
CAPTIONED IT, EVERY YEAR EVERY
FAMILY PICKS COLOR AND VIBE.
WE KNOW WHO THE GIFTS FOR.
THIS YEAR WE CHOSE CREAMY VELVET
AND WHILE SOME PEOPLE PRAISE
KK'S ECO FRIENDLY WRAPPING
OTHERS POKED FUN ON IT.
ON LAST NIGHT'S LIKE IT OR NOT
THE CREW WAIVED.
>> YOU THINK ABOUT ALL THE
PRIVATE JETS AND THE LIFE THE
KARDASHIANS LIVE BUT THEY'LL
SAVE THE WORLD BY WRAPPING
THINGS IN CLOTH.
BY THE WAY THAT LOCKS SO
DEPRESSING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> CAN WE GET SOMETHING COL
COLORFUL.
>> THEY DON'T BELIEVE IN COLORS.
ALL NEUTRAL AND MUTED.
NO FURNITURE.
THEY'RE SO COOL THEY DON'T NEED
FURNITURE.
>> YOU CAN CATCH FOX5 LIKE IT OR
NOT WEEKDAYS AT 7:00 P.M.
>> THAT'S KANYESS COLOR FOR A
LOT OF HIS FASHIONINGS, RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> KIND OF MATCHE THE FASHION
SHOWS THE RUNWAYS.
>> YEAH.
BUT SOME PEOPLE TRYING TO DO IT
THEMSELVES.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THEY CAN WRAP
HOWEVER THEY LIKE.
I WOULD TAKE A GIFT FROM THE
KARDASHIANS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW IT'S A GOOD GIFT.
>>> HELLO.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU.
>> I'M WELL, THANKS.
ARE YOU HAVING A GOOD CHRISTMAS
EVE WITH JUS.
>> I'M HAVING A WONDERFUL
MORNING, YEAH.
>> OKAY.
WEATHER IS COOPERATING THIS NICE
AND EASY IT WILL BE NICE AND
EASY GOING FORWARD.
I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE DOING
LAST MINUTE SHOPPING AND RUNNING
AROUND AND YOU GOT FAMILY TIME.
YOU DON'T QUITE NO WHAT TO DO
EVERYBODY HAS TO GO OUT FOR A
WALK MUCH THAT'S WHAT WE DID IN
OUR FAMILY SO THE WEATHER WILL
COOPERATE FOR THAT.
>> RIGHT.
THAT'S AWESOME.
PERFECT.
35 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
REAL QUICK, HAPPY BIRTHDAY EARL.
EARL HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY EARL.
>> HE'S WATCHING THIS MORNING.
>> BIG BIRTHDAY.
CHRISTMAS EVE BIRTHDAY.
>> OKAY.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT A
CHRISTMAS EVE OR CHRISTMAS DAY
BIRTHDAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD ONE.
IF YOU HAVE ONE LET US KNOW.
>> I HAVE UNCLE BORN ON
CHRISTMAS DAY AND HE HAS MIXED
EMOTIONS ABOUT IT.
>> DO YOU GET LIKE CHRISTMAS AND
BIRTHDAY GIFTS.
>> DOUBLE IT UP.
>> DO YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> CHRISTMAS EVE, HEY, LISTEN
TRAVEL FORECAST COULDN'T BE
QUIETER.
THAT SOUTHEAST STORM IS FINALLY
GETTING OUT OF HERE LEFTOVER
SHOWERS ALONG THE SOUTHEAST
COAST, AND A FEW SNOW MOUNTAIN
SNOW SHOWERS OUT IN THE ROCKY
MOUNTAIN STATES BUT THIS IS
REALLY WIDELY SCATTERED NOT
ENOUGH TO DELAY AIR TRAVEL IF
YOU'RE FLYING LATER TODAY.
MOST OF THE COUNTRY COULDN'T BE
QUIETER THERE'S THE LAST OF YOUR
RAIN SHOWERS THAT BROUGHT THE
HEAVY RAINS TO FLORIDA THAT'S
GETTING OUT OF HERE.
BEACH WEATHER RETURNS.
75 WITH SUNSHINE MIAMI LATER
TODAY AND LOOK AT OUR FORECAST.
COULDN'T BE QUIETER.
50 TODAY AND TOMORROW.
IT WILL BE CHILLY TOMORROW
MORNING GETTING UP EARLY.
AND THEN THURSDAY, FRIDAY AND
SATURDAY WARMING TREND WE MIGHT
DO 60 ON SATURDAY BEFORE SOME
RAIN SHOWERS GET HERE SUNDAY AT
LEAST UPPER 50S.
A LOT TO LOOK FORWARD TO WEATHER
WISE.
ERIN BACK TO TRAFFIC?
>> YES.
BACK TO TRAFFIC.
8:17.
UNFORTUNATELY, IN VIRGINIA, WE
DO HAVE A PROBLEM.
BIG CRASH ON THE NORTHBOUND SIDE
BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE COMING
UP THROUGH QUANTICO.
WE HAVE THE FIRE DEPARTMENT,
POLICE OUT THERE TAKING OUT THAT
RIGHT LANE.
THIS IS CAUSING AN ATYPICAL SLOW
DOWN FOR THIS CHRISTMAS EVE
COMMUTE.
YOU CAN ALWAYS BAIL OUT TAKE
ROUTE 1 OTHERWISE FACTOR IN
ABOUT 10 EXTRA MINUTES.
VOLUME IS LIGHT ENOUGH IT'S NOT
MAJOR IMPACT.
NORTH AT THAT POINT YOU'RE QUIET
THROUGH DALE CITY TO THE
BELTWAY.
BELTWAY INNER AND OUTER LOOP
QUIET THROUGH VIRGINIA AND
MARYLAND.
66 WESTBOUND ADDITION ABLED
VEHICLE CLEARED IT WAS BLOCKING
THE RIGHT LANE AT 123.
EASTBOUND SIDE VERY PLEASANT
THROUGH FAR FAKE GETTING INSIDE
THE BELTWAY THROUGH FALLS CH
CHURCH.
THINGS IN GEORGETOWN LOOKING
GOOD.
NO PROBLEM ON THE DULLES TOLL
ROAD IF YOU'RE HEADED TO DELL US
WILL AIRPORT, BWI REAGAN
NATIONAL YOU'RE IN THE CLEAR.
IF YOU'RE HEADING OUT SHOPPING
THINGS LOOKING GOOD ON THE WAY
TO TYSONS.
NO PROBLEMS FOR LAST MINUTE
GIFTS TRYING TO GET TO WORK,
WE'RE IN VERY GOOD SHAPE ON MOST
OF OUR MAJORS.
ALLISON?
>> 8:17 THIS STORY TWO LOST DOGS
WILL BE ABLE TO SPEND CHRISTMAS
AT HOME WITH THEIR FAMILY.
THANKS TO BUS DRIVER WHO WENT
ABOVE AND BEYOND THE DRIVE HAD
JUST FINISHED HER ROUTE IN
MILWAUKEE SHE SPOTTER THE DOGS
RUNNING IN OUT OF THE STREET SHE
PULLED OVER LET THE DOGS ON THE
BUS.
>> AW.
>> CALLED POLICE AND OFFICERS
TOOK THEM TO ANIMAL CONTROL AND
YESTERDAY THE DOGS WERE REUNITED
WITH THEIR FAMILY NO DOUBT THEY
WERE JUST WORRIED SICK.
TURNS OUT THE DOGS ESCAPED FROM
THE YARD ABOUT 2 MILES.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> AWAY.
>> TOOK A LONG JOURNEY.
>> THERE'S NOTHING LIKE THAT.
WHEN YOU HAVE A DOG AND I
SUPPOSE CATS JUST SEEM LIKE
THEY'RE MORE, YOU KNOW, I KNOW
THEY'RE HOUSE CATS THAT MAYBE
GET OUT, TOO.
BUT WITH THE DOGS WHEN THEY'RE
LOST AND, YOU KNOW,.
THIS SOUNDS STUPID BUT THEY
CAN'T TALK.
THEY CAN'T SAY, HEY, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?  SO I'M SO GLAD
THEY'RE REUNITED.
>> HAPPY REUNION.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
AS 2019 WINDS DOWN, HAVE YOU
MADE YOUR MEOWS RESOLUTION YET?
WELL, IF YOU WANT TO STICK TO IT
WAIT UNTIL SPRING.
>> EXPERTS SAY SPRING IS REALLY
THE TIME OF NEW BEGINNINGS AND
IT CAN BE EASIER TO CHANGE UP
BEHAVIORS THEN ONE PSYCHOLOGIST
EVEN DUBBING THAT TIME MUCH YEAR
SPRING RENEWAL SAYS THE COLD
WEATHER AND SHORTER DAYS MAKE IT
A LITTLE TOUGHER TO STICK TO ANY
GOALS YOU MIGHT SET NOW.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT
TUCK CONCERN ERIN DID YOU MAKE
ANY RESOLUTIONS?  ARE YOU
RESOLUTION PEOPLE?
>> THAT EXPLAINS EVERYTHING.
LET'S THINK.
AM I A RESOLUTION PERSON?  UM,
OKAY.
SURE.
WHY NOT?  I AM A RESOLUTION
PERSON, STEVE.
>> GOOD.
>> YOU ARE NOT A RESOLUTION
PERSON.
>> HAVE YOU MADE ONE, TUCKER?
>> NO, I HAVE NOT MADE ONE.
IT'S NOT --
>> WHAT WAS LAST YEAR.
>> WHAT MAKES YOU THINK YOU'RE A
RESOLUTION PERSON.
>> GOING FROM ONE DECADE TO THE
NEXT I THINK IT THIS MIGHT BE A
TIME FOR ME TO LOOK BACK AT SOME
THINGS I WANT TO IMPROVE UPON
AND GOING FORWARD THIS IS A GOOD
TIME FOR ME TO MAKE RESOLUTIONS.
>> THIS IS A SPECIAL OCCASION
RSOLUTION.
>> NEW RESOLUTION.
>> SPECIAL OCCASION RESOLUTION
ABSOLUTELY, STEVE.
>> ERIN, WHAT ABOUT YOU.
>> MY RESOLUTION JUST TO RUN
MORE BECAUSE I USED TO DO A
RUNNING GROUP IN NASHVILLE AND
DO HALF MARATHONS AND I HAVEN'T
DONE IN TWO YEARS.
I RAN TWO AND A HALF MILES
YESTERDAY AND MY GOAL TO GET UP
TO RUNNING 10 MILES REGULARLY ON
LIKE A SATURDAY MORNING.
>> I THINK THAT'S FANTASTIC.
>> I HAD THIS CONVERSATION LAST
NIGHT AND I SAID I FEEL LIKE THE
RESOLUTIONS OF I'M GOING EAT
BETTER, GET IN BETTER SHAPE, BE
A BETTER PERSON THAT'S KIND OF
LIKE WHEN YOU WATCH WHEEL OF
FORTUNE S-T-E-N AND E SHOULD BE
THE GIVENS.
RESOLUTION SHOULD BE ABOVE AND
BEYOND THAT.
>> CONCRETE GOALS.
>> I'M NOT A BIG RESOLUTION
PERSON.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHERE YOU CAN
SEE THE RESOLUTIONS BEING
REALIZED.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> THE LOCAL GYMS LIKE THE FIRST
TWO WEEKS OF JANUARY ARE PACKED.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THAT.
>> THEY DISS APP AFTER THE
14th OF JANUARY.
>> PEOPLE TRY.
YOU HAVE GOOD INTENTIONS AND I
THINK THAT'S IT I LIKE THIS IDEA
ABOUT KICKING IT OFF IN THE
SPRING, YOU KNOW.
BUT IT FEELS LIKE A NICE FRESH
START AT THE BEGINNING OF THE
YEAR AND THEN ALSO TUCKER I'M
WITH YOU I'M NOT GOING TO GIVE
YOU HARD TIME THE YEAR 2020 JUST
FEELS LIKE A RENEWAL PERIOD.
>> LIKE A REBOOT.
RIGHT.
>> TOTAL REBOOT.
I'M A RESOLUTION PERSON BUT I'M
DEFINITELY A RESOLUTION PERSON
IN THE 82 WENT 20.
>> GET A CLEAN START.
BREAK THOSE BAD HABITS.
>> DON'T PUT THE PRESSURE I
DON'T KNOW SELF EITHER.
IF YOU DON'T MAKE IT TO THE GYM
PAST JANUARY THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH THAT YOU GAVE EIGHT
SHOT.
>> BEING KINDER TO YOURSELF IS A
RESOLUTION, TOO.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> AND SMILE MORE, TUCK.
>> IS TUCKER DOING HIS CUTE
FACE.
>> SO SWEET.
>> LETTER THAN PUPPIES OR
KISSES.
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> STILL AHEAD THE PENTAGON --
THANKS GUYS.
PENTAGON LAS A WARNING FOR
MILITARY PERSONNEL BOY A POPULAR
HOLIDAY GIFT.
WHY OFFICIALS ARE TELLING
SERVICE MEMBERS TO STAY AWAY
FROM THOSE AT HOME DNA KITS.
>> IMAGINE DRIVING HOME AND ALL
OF A SUDDEN A FISH FALLS FROM
THE SKY.OM
THE SKY.
>> SMASHING YOUR WINDSHIELD.
BASED ON THAT PARTICULAR FISH, I
HAVE AN IDEA WHERE IT CAME FROM.
I'LL PUT MY DETECTIVE SKILLS TO
WORK AND WE'LL FIND OUT WHAT
HAPPENED IN NORTH CAROLINA.
>> IS THAT A CATFISH?  ♪
♪♪
Did you know Comcast Business
goes beyond fast with
a Gig-speed network,
complete Internet reliability,
cloud-based security.
That's huge.
Advanced voice solutions,
WiFi to keep everyone connected,
video monitoring.
Wow.
Business TV,
cloud apps and support.
I need that.
It's everything a small
business owner needs.
Save over $200 a month
on Internet and Voice
with our new business packages
starting at $99.99.
Call 1-800-501-6000.
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
♪
>>> 8:24.
SANTA IS OFFICIALLY ON HIS WAY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT IT HAS BEEN
VERY BUSY NIGHT ALREADY IN NEW
GUINEA.
>> HE'S IN PAO, PAO NEW GUINEA.
SO FAR.MILONIFTS DELIVER
TRKER
64 YEARS NOW THE U.S. AND
CANADIAN AIR DEFENSE COMMAND
KEPT A CLOSE WATCH ON SANTA'S
JOURNEY.
>> GUESS WHERE HE IS.
>> PAO, PAO.
HE'SEADED TWO MINUTES AY
GO TE.S A STRAHLE Y MAKING REAL
HI, GUYS.
>> WHAT A SWEET TIME OF YEAR.
T'S HARD TO BELIEVE --
OBVIOUSLY IT IS THAT'S ALREADY,
YOU KNOW, DARK AND THEY'RE
ALREADY WELL INTO CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> SCHUYLER.E MIDDLE ONE'S NAME?
>> SCHUYLER.
SCHUYLER HAD A BREAK D LAST
NIGHT.
>> WHY?
>> SHE DIDN'T REALIZE THATAY
CHRTM EVE, ANDHE'SIME OFF AND G
SISTER IS HOME, AND YOU KNOW
WHAT MEAN.
E'S LIKE WHAT?  I TUGHTHAT
WAS THUDAY LAST WEEK.
NO.
>> CHRISTMAS EVE.
>>T COME REALLY QUICK THIS
YEAR.
YE IT REALLY DID SNEAK UP THANKS
>>IG
>> NEXTWEE LHROW A LITTLE BIT.
UP.
'S CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> TUCK, IT'S TOUGH WHEN THE THE
24th ON THE CALENDAR EVERY
YEAR.
SNEAKS UP ON YOU SOMETIMES.
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON.
>> IT'S A BUSY TIME OF YEAR.
PEOPLE FORGET.
>> YOUR UNCLE STEVE, SCHUYLER IS
A WISE ALE.
>> JUST GIVING AL A HARD TIME.
>> IT HOTHING TO DOITHLER.
[ LAHTER ]
BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON F US.
TH STORM SYSTEM TT BROUGHT
US THE ACROSS THE SOUTHEAST
IT'S GRADUALLYTING OUTF
HE AND TT MEANSUNSHINE
RETUSO FLORIDA AND THE
BEACHES AND FOR A QUIET
PATTERN CONTINUES
50 TODAY.
COMFORTABLE THT FORAN
DELIVERIES.
NICE TOMORW,0 DEGREES AND
BYATUR U TO UPPER 50S MAYBE 60
>> NEXT CHANCE OFAI ON
LOOK AT THIS 9 NTHUND CRASH
BLOCKS THE RIGHT LAN.
ME ATY DELAYS ITEELS
LIKE AHAN A
WEEKDAYEING THAT  I
CHSTMA EVE.
SOF Y'RERYIN TO TO
WORKVERALL TRAFFICS LHT
LOOKGTTY GOOD ON THE WAY
TO THE AIRPORTS.
TRO I GOO NEWS.
>> IS IT POSSIBLE THAT'S THE
LIGHT TESTRA EVER IN THE
HISTORY OF I-95 NORTHBOUND?
>> PERHAPS, YES, TUCKER.
>> THERE'S LIKE FOUR CARS.
>> YOU'RE A TRAFFIC EXPERT.
>> THANK YOU TRYING TO TAKE MY
JOB FOR THE NEW YEAR, GUYS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD EIGHT COT 30
THE PENTAGON WARNING MILITARY
PERSONNEL ABOUT POPULAR DNA
TESTS THAT YOU CAN BUY.
IT'S A POPULAR GIFT THIS TIME OF
YEAR.
WHY THEY DON'T WANT YOU
SQUABBING YOUR CHEEK.
>> IF YOU HAVE NOT YET REACHED
YOUR HOLIDAY DESTINATION YOU ARE
NOT THE ONLY ONE.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE HEADING OUT
AND WE'LL SHOW YOU WHAT IT'S
LIKE AT THE AIRPORT.
PRETTY GOOD IF YOU'RE TRAVELING
TO DULLES RIGHT NOW.
ABOUT AS EMPTY AS YOU'LL EVER
SEE IT.
8:27.
♪
♪♪
8:30 AS WE TAKE LOOK AT
GAITHERSBURG AND THE CHRISTMAS
TREE THAT WE'VE BEEN KEEPING AN
EYE ON FOR THE LAST COUPLE OF
WEEKS.
REAL NICE OUT THERE.
CITY CENTER OUT THERE AS WELL
LOOKING GOOD.
ALL FESTIVE FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE UP EARLY GETTING
READY TO HEAD HOME.
MIGHT BE LAST MINUTE FOR SOME
BUT STILL GETTING OUT THERE.
>> TODAY IS ANTICIPATED TO BE
THE BEST DAY TO HEAD HOME IF
YOU'RE FLYING AS FAR AS PRICES
GO, RIGHT?  FOX5 ANGIE GOFF
JOINS US LIVE FROM DULLES
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT WITH MORE
ON THE HUSTLE AND THE BUSTLE.
WHAT TIME ARE YOU HEADED OUT,
LADY?
>> Reporter: HEY, GUYS.
LIKE IN A COUPLE MUCH HOURS.
I'M ACTUALLY HERE BECAUSE I'M
WRAPPING UP AROUND 9:00 WITH THE
JOB AND ALL.
SO I'M ACTUALLY HERE EARLY JUST
IN TIME SO I KNOW I'LL BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT THROUGH SECURITY.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE BOARD BEHIND
ME.
WHY DID YOU STOP THAT MUSIC?  I
LOVE THAT FLOW.
TAKE A LOOK IT'S LIGHTING UP IT
LOOKS LIKE WE DO HAVE ONE
CONFIRMED DELAY AND GUESS WHERE
IT IS?  ORLANDO AND THAT IS
WHERE WE WERE SEEING THAT TRICKY
WEATHER ALL THAT FLOODING THAT
THEY WERE DEALING WITH DOWN
THERE.
TALKED TO A LOT OF PEOPLE OUT OF
THE 7 MILLION BY THE WAY THE
RECORD TECH MILLION PEOPLE
THAT -- THANK YOU.
YES.
THIS ACTUALLY -- HEY, THIS FITS
THE MOOD OF THE AIRPORT RIGHT
NOW.
THIS IS THE VIBE, OKAY, BECAUSE
WE'VE HAD LIKE CRAZY, CRAZINESS
AND THEN WE'VE HAD THIS.
WHERE IT'S KIND OF JUST, YOU
KNOW, DESOLATE AND THERE'S NO
REAL BIG LINES.
BUT LOOK WHO I FOUND HERE.
I FOUND SOMEONE WHO KNOWS HOW TO
TRAVEL.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?  HOW LONG
ARE YOU GOING AWAY FOR HOLIDAY?
>> A WEEK.
>> A WEEK?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE IN HERE?
>> UM, MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> AND YOU SAY THIS IS WHY YOU
DON'T TRAVEL FOR MORE THAN A
WEEK, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I STRUGGLE TO KEEP IT SIMPLE AND
MINIMAL.
>> OKAY.
AND YOU CAME ALL WEIGHT DOWN
FROM BALTIMORE.
YOU GOT HERE EARLY.
DO YOU TRAVEL A LOT?  DO YOU
HAVE ANY TIPS FOR THOSE WHO ARE
TRYING TO STAY STRESS FREE THIS
HOLIDAY?
>> TRY TO BE ON TIME SEW TO THE
AIRPORT.
DON'T PACK AS MUCH AS I DID.
AND JUST HAVE FUN WHEN YOU GET
TO YOUR DESTINATION.
>> Reporter: I KNOW.
I KNOW YOU'RE FLYING
INTERNATIONALLY SAVE TRAVELS TO
YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
ALL RIGHT.
>> WE GOT TO GET HER ANOTHER
CART.
SO, UM, IT'S NOT ONLY PEOPLE
FLYING IN THE AIR THAT, UM, THAT
ARE BREAKING THE RECORDS.
105 MILLION PEOPLE ARE DRIVING
TO THEIR HOLIDAY DESTINATION.
THIS IS GOING TO GO ON THROUGH
JANUARY 2nd, AND BY THE WAY,
IF YOU'RE DRIVING OR YOU KNOW
SOMEBODY WHO IS, GIVE THEM A
HEADS UP.
THAT THE DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS THE
26th FOUR TO 6:00 P.M. IS
GOING TO BE HORRENDOUS.
GOING TO BE HORRIBLE.
THREE TIMES THE CONGESTION THEY
SAY.
SO I'LL LEAVE YOU ON THAT NOTE
BUT THANK YOU FOR THAT MUSIC.
IT'S REALLY PUT ME IN THE
HOLIDAY MOOD.
>> ANGIE, YOU FOUND THE BADDEST
CHICK EVER AT THE AIRPORT.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
>> Reporter: YOU THINK SO.
>> RIGHT.
SHE WAS DOING CIRCLES.
LOOK I KNOW YOU MIGHT MISS YOUR
NIGHT, BUT YOU HAVE TO BE IN MY
LIVE SHOT.
>> SHE LOOKED AMAZING.
>> SEASON OF GIVING.
SHE DELIVERED.
>> YES.
>> AND SO SHE'S FINE.
SHE ACTUALLY GOT HERE A COUPLE
HOURS EARLY.
>> OKAY GOOD.
I DON'T WANT HER TO MISS HER
FLIGHT.
>> CUTE RECOGNIZES CUTE.
I'M NOT SURPRISED SHE WAS IN
YOUR LIVE SHOT.
SHE WAS MAZING.
>> I SAW SOMEBODY GET ON THE
METRO TRAIN GOING TO THE AIRPORT
H3 ROLLER BAGS.
VICK 21 IN EACH HAND.
THEY HAD THREE THEY WERE TRYING
TO NEGOTIATE.
>> DID YOU SEE HER OUTFIT SURELY
SHE NEEDS WARDROBE CHANGES.
MY GOSH WHAT IS GOING ON.
GONE FOR A WEEK INTERNATIONALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS SO MUCH, ANGIE.
>> Reporter: YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> TAKE HOME DNA KITS POPULAR
THIS TIME OF YEAR FOR THE
HOLIDAYS THEY CAN HELP IDENTIFY
FAMILY MEMBERS, MEDICAL RISKS
AND MORE BUT THE PENTAGON IS
SAYING MILITARY MEMBERS SHOULD
AVOID USING THEM AND ANNE CUTLER
HAS MORE FOR US THIS MORNING.
ANNE.
>> Reporter: I DON'T KNOW IF I
CAN LIVE UP TO THAT LAST STORY
BUT I'LL TRY.
THE PENTAGON SAYS EXPOSING
SENSITIVE INFORMATION POSES
PERSONAL AND OPERATIONAL RISKS.
DNA KITS LIKE 23 AND ME AND
ANCESTRY HAVE BECOME WILDLY
POPULAR IN DETERMINING
INFORMATION ON ANCESTRY MEDICAL
RISKS AND THOSE UNKNOWN FAMILY
MEMBERS
BUT THEY'VE ALSO RAISED SOME
LEGAL AND ETHICAL CONCERNS.
THAT'S BECAUSE SOME COMPANIES
SHARE THE DATA WITH LAW
ENFORCEMENT OR SELL IT TO THIRD
PARTIES.
MEMO CO SIGNED BY THE DEPARTMENT
OF DEFENSE'S TOP INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIAL SAYS SOME DNA KIT
COMPANIES HAVE ACTUALLY BEEN
TARGETING MILITARY PERSONNEL
WITH DISCOUNTS.
IT ALSO SAYS THOSE TESTS ARE
LARGELY UNREGULATED.
SO WHAT TYPES OF SPECIFIC
PROBLEMS DO THEY POSE?
ACCORDING TO REPORTS NAVY'S TOP
OFFICER WARNED DNA FROM CONSUMER
TESTING KITS MIGHT ONE DAY BE
USED FOR MAKING BIOLOGICAL
WEAPONS.
IMAGINE THAT.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> ANNE, THANKS VERY MUCH 8:34
RIGHT NOW.
>>> THE NAVY THINKS THE POPULAR
APP TICK TOCK IS A THREAT TO
NATIONAL CYBER SECURITY.
IT SENT OUT AN ALERT URGING
MILITARY PERSONNEL AND STAFF TO
DELETE TIKTOK IF THEY'VE
DOWNLOADED IT ON GOVERNMENT
ISSUED DEVICES.
OFFICIALS SAY THE DECISION WAS
MADE BASED ON CYBER SECURITY
THREAT ASSESSMENTS.
MILITARY PERSONNEL CAN STILL
USING SOCIAL NETWORKING APPS ON
THEIR PERSONAL DEVICES AS
LAWMAKERS ARE WORRIED ABOUT THE
KLEIN NIECE RUN APPS POPULARITY
HERE IN THE STATES.
TIKTOK HAS MORE THAN 110 MILLION
DOWN LOADS IN THE US.
>> MAKES SENSE YOU DON'T WANT TO
PUT THOSE ON YOUR GOVERNMENT
PHONES.
I WAS 35:00.
TUCK IT LOOKS NICE OUT THERE.
>> GOING TO BE BEAUTIFUL DAY FOR
DECEMBER THE 24th, DAYTIME
HIGHS ABOUT 50 DEGREES AND
PLENTY OF SUNSHINE TO LOOK
FORWARD TO.
NICE QUIET AFTERNOON ALL THINGS
RELATED TO HITTING THE ROADWAYS
AND GOING FOR A NICE WALK IN THE
WOODS.
SHOULD BE BEAUTIFUL DAY FOR IT.
35 TO START YOUR MORNING HERE IN
WASHINGTON.
IT'S CHILLY OUT THERE.
LOTS OF 20S EARLY THIS MORNING.
AS THE SUN WAS GETTING UP, BUT A
BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF A CLOUD DECK
WORKING THROUGH FROM THE NORTH
AND WEST, AND DON'T WORRY THAT
WILL PASS THROUGH AND WE'LL BE
MOSTLY SUNNY FOR A GOOD PART OF
THE DAY HERE AND NICE AND QUIET.
TRAVELING TODAY, BOSTON, NEW
YORK, D.C., EVEN DOWN TOWARDS AT
LAND WHERE IT RAINED YESTERDAY,
CHICAGO ALL LOOKING GREAT.
HERE'S YOUR CHRISTMAS FORECAST.
YOU KNOW WHAT BEAUTIFUL NIGHT TO
GO OUT CHRISTMAS CAROLING
50 DEGREES.
>> FA, LA, LA, LA.
>> 50 DEGREES TOMORROW AND
TOMORROW MIX OF CLOUDS AND SUN
BOTH DAYS.
HERE'S THE OTHER GOOD NEWS.
SANTA SHOULD HAVE ON TIME
DELIVERY.
>> WHAT'S YOUR GO TO CAROLING
SONG.
>> WISH I WAS MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> WOULD YOU SING ME INTO
TRAFFIC?
>> MAYBE IN A FEW MINUTES.
>> OH, THAT'S YOUR WAY OF SAYING
NO.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
8:00 THICK RIGHT NOW.
>>> 95 NORTHBOUND RIGHT SHOULDER
BLOCKED BY A CRASH AT QUANTICO.
EARLIER DELAYS QUICKLY DISS
DISSIPATED BECAUSE TUCKER
MENTIONED EARLIER VERY LIGHT
VOLUME ON 95.
CHRISTMAS EVE FEELS MORE LIKE A
SATURDAY MORNING DELAY FREE ON
66 EARLIER DISABLED VEHICLE ON
THE WE BELIEVED SIDE CLEARED BY
123.
WE'RE QUIET ON THE WAY TO THE
DULLES AIRPORT.
REAGAN NATIONAL AND BWI LOOKING
GOOD ON THE WAY TO UNION STATION
TRAIN IS YOUR SELECT WAY OF
TRAVEL, AND WE'RE SEEING NICE
CONDITIONS ON METRO.
METRO CURRENTLY ON TIME.
LOOKING GOOD TO AND FROM THE
BALTIMORE BELTWAY QUIET BY
TYSONS RIGHT NOW I ANTICIPATE
LITTLE BIT LATER THIS AFTERNOON
CROWDED PARKING LOTS AT ALL THE
AREA MALLS.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> STILL AHEAD DATA BREACH HAS
SOME ONLINE USERS WORRIED ABOUT
THEIR INFORMATION.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHICH DATING APP
WAS IMPACTED.
>> AND AS WE TAKE YOU TO THE
BREAK ANOTHER CHECK ON THE MAN
OF THE HOUR.
>> WHERE IS SANTA NOW, AL.
>> HE'S OVER AUSTRALIA RIGHT
NOW, STEVE.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO KEEP AN EYE ON
THE BIG GUY IN RED AS HE
DELIVERS AROUND THE GLOBE.
♪
GLOBE.
♪♪
♪
>>> BACK NOW 8:40.
HEADS UP IF YOU USE THE DATING
APP PLENTY OF FISH.
THE COMPANY SAYS SENSITIVE
INFORMATION INCLUDING USER NAMES
AND ZIP CODES OF SOME OF THE
USER'S PROFILES WERE VISIBLE
EVEN WHEN THE SETTINGS WERE SET
TO PRIVATE.
THE DATING COMPANY SAYS ONLY
REALLY TECH SAVVY PEOPLE WOULD
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO SEE THE DATA
BUT IT STILL COULD HAVE BEEN
THERE.
THE INCIDENT HAPPENED IN
OCTOBER.
THEY SAY IT IS NOW FIXED.
>>> FROM POTENTIAL ONLINE
CATFISH TO REAL LIVE ONES CHECK
THIS OUT.
A REAL LIVE ONES I SHOULD SAY
THEY'RE NOT ALIVE AFTER THIS.
NORTH CAROLINA WOMAN HIT A
CATFISH WITH HER CAR.
SHE WAS DRIVING HOME WEDNESDAY
NIGHT WHEN SHE SAW A BIRD
CARRYING THAT MASSIVE FISH
PERHAPS SHE STARTLED THE BIRD
BECAUSE HE DROPPED THE FEBRUARY
RIGHT ON HER WINDSHIELD.
>> OH.
>> THAT BIG OLD CATFISH
SHATTERED THE GLASS.
HER COUSIN AND HER COUSIN'S
HUSBAND SAW HER AS THEY WERE
DRIVING AND PULLED OVER TO HELP
AND IT'S NOT OF DAY THAT HAPPENS
SO YOU KNOW SHE HAS A STORY FOR
LIFE NOW ABOUT THE DAY THAT SHE
HIT A FISH WITH HER CAR.
>> I WOULD SAY THE FISH HIT THE
CAR.
>> IT IS BUT BETTER STORY
PERHAPS.
>> RIGHT.
>> I HIT A FISH WITH MY CAR.
>> BETTER FISH STORY.
>> SORRY CAN'T COME IN TO WORK
JUST HIT A FISH WITH THE CAR.
>> THAT WINDOW IS DONE.
>>> COMING UP IF YOU'RE LOOKING
SOMETHING TO BINGE WATCH THIS
HOLIDAY WEEK KEVIN MCCARTHY HAS
OPTIONS FOR YOU, AND MAYBE THE
PERFECT GIFT FOR YOU ONE WITH
FUR AND FOUR LEGS.
THOSE THEY WOULD SAY DON'T DO
THIS, BUT MAYBE AFTER THE
HOLIDAYS, RIGHT?  YOU CAN START
THE PROCESS NOW.
STILL AHEAD HOW YOU CAN MAKE THE
HOLIDAY A LITTLE BRIGHTER FOR
SOME FURRY FRIENDS WHO NEED
THEIR FOREVER HOMES.
BUT FIRST, YOUR CHRISTMAS EVE
FORECAST AND A LOOK AT THE
ROADS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
♪♪
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
♪
>>> 8:44.
WE'RE BACK NOW WITH WHAT IS TO
COME ON GOOD DAY D.C. ON THIS
CHRISTMAS EVE MORNING.
LIVE IN THE LOFT THIS MORNING,
ACTOR, SINGER, SONG WRITER
CHARLES HE IS 10 YOU KNOW HIM
FROM THE HIT SHOW NASHVILLE
HE'LL WORM FOR US LIVE IN THE
LOFT.
>> ALSO, ON GOOD DAY WE'LL HELP
YOU KEEP UP YOUR WORKOUTS WHILE
HANGING OUT WITH THE FAMILY ON
CHRISTMAS.
FITNESS TRAINER IS GOING TO JOIN
US THIS MORNING WITH SOME TIPS
TO KEEP YOU MOVING.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>>> LET'S MOVE ON OVER TO TUCKER
KNOWLEDGE GET IT BECAUSE YOU
SAID MOVING.
>> STEVE, I THINK I'M INVOLVED
IN THAT SEGMENT WITH YOU.
>> I THINK YOU'RE DOING THAT
SEGMENT.
>> I AM.
LEARN NEW THINGS EVERY HOUR.
YESTERDAY COMFORTABLE DAY, 55
WAS THE WINNING NUMBER AT DULLES
AND BWI MARSHALL.
NORMAL HIGH 45.
GUESS WHAT, WE'LL KEEP IT
TEMPERATURE WISE AT OR ABOVE
NORMAL IN FACT ABOVE NORMAL HERE
THE NEXT FIVE TO SEVEN DAYS.
INCLUDING THIS AFTERNOON.
IT'S STILL COLD THIS MORNING OR
CHILLY THIS MORNING.
WE'RE STARTING TO WARM IT UP NOW
THAT THE SUN IS OUT.
35 IN WASHINGTON.
LEONARDTOWN YOU JUMPED TO
43 DEGREES NOW.
25 IN MANASSAS.
34 DULLES.
SO MUCH OF THE AREA STILL
HANGING AROUND THAT FREEZING
MARK BUT WITH PLENTY OF SUNSHINE
IT WILL BE BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON
FOR US, AND TRAVELING WE HAVE
ANGIE OUT AT THE AIRPORT BUT
TRAVELING COULD NOT BE A QUIETER
DAY FOR CHRISTMAS EVE.
STILL SOME SHOWERS ALONG THE
SOUTHEAST COAST GETTING OUT OF
HERE AND VERY WEAK STORM SYSTEM
FOR PARTS OF THE ROCKY MOUNTAIN
STATES AND DOWN TOWARDS ARIZONA.
PHOENIX GETTING LIGHT RAIN
SHOWERS BUT THIS IS REALLY NOT A
BIG EVENT AND IF YOU'RE
TRAVELING I THINK YOU'LL BE IN
PRETTY GOOD SHAPE HERE AS FAR AS
AIR TRAVEL AT LEAST WEATHER W
WISE.
CAN'T GUARANTEE YOU'LL BE ON
TIME WEATHER WISE NO BIG ISSUES.
OKAY.
THERE'S YOUR STORM SYSTEM OFF
THE SOUTHEAST COAST STILL KIND
OF JUST MEANDERING.
IT WILL SCOOT OUT TO SEA.
IMPROVING CONDITIONS EXPECTED
FOR FLORIDA OVER THE NEXT 24
HOURS.
THAT'S GREAT.
AND WE COULDN'T BE QUIETER.
SO LATER THIS AFTERNOON ABOUT
50.
MENTEE OF SUNSHINE AND WE'LL
KEEP IT QUITE TONIGHT.
SANTA SHOULD ARRIVE WITHOUT ANY
PROBLEMS.
RUDOLPH WILL NOT NEED THE RED
NOSE AS WE'RE LOOKING AT CLEAR
SKIES.
MAYBE A LITTLE FOG EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING THEN 50
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
THURSDAY, FRIDAY, SATURDAY IN
THE 50'S AND OUR NEXT CHANCE FOR
RAIN SHOWER ACTIVITY SUNDAY
AFTERNOON WITH DAYTIME HIGHS
ABOUT 60 DEGREES.
BUT THOSE TEMPERATURES REMEMBER
I JUST SHOWED YOU 45 THE NORMAL
HIGH ABOVE NORMAL FOR THE NEXT
SEVEN DAYS.
REALLY FANTASTIC FORECAST FOR
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
STEVE, I WILL TOSS IT BACK TO
YOU.
>>> 8:46.
I'M A LITTLE DISTRACTED GREAT
SEGMENT COMING UP AFTER TRAFFIC
IN THE LOFT.
CHRISTMAS EVE COMMUTE LOOKS GOOD
RIGHT NOW.
ALL OF OUR MAJORS ALL GREEN ALL
GOOD PROBLEM FREE TOWARD THE BAY
BRIDGE.
ALL OF OUR AREA BRIDGES LOOKING
GOOD.
270 PROBLEM FREE.
95 IN VIRGINIA ALSO QUITE INSIDE
THE DISTRICT SECONDARIES LOOKING
GOOD ON THE WAY TO UNION
STATION.
PROBLEM FREE IF YOU HAVE A TRAIN
TO CATCH.
WE'RE ALSO SEEING NICE
CONDITIONS THE ENTIRE STRETCH OF
270.
WE'RE NOT SEEING ANY ISSUES
RIGHT NOW.
SO IF YOU'RE HEADING OUT
SHOPPING JUST WATCH FOR CROWDED
PARKING LOTS LATER AS MORE
PEOPLE HIT THE ROAD TO RUN SOME
LAST MINUTE ERRANDS MY GUESS IS
GROCERY STORES AND MALLS ARE
GOING TO BE CROWD LATER IN TERMS
OF PARKING.
AS OF RIGHT NOW TRAFFIC ON THE
WAY TO BWI REAGAN NATIONAL
DULLES LOOKING GOOD.
SO FAR SO GOOD IF YOU'RE WORKING
THIS CHRISTMAS EVE.
I'LL START MAKING MY WAY OVER
OUT OF THIS SHOT FROM YOUR
CHRISTMAS EVE COMMUTE OVER TO
SOME VERY CUTE BABIES ALONGSIDE
ALLISON SEYMOUR.
ALLISON HAS BEEN THINKING ABOUT
GETTING A KITTY FOR QUITE A LONG
TIME.
I'M GOING TO WALK OVER THIS WAY.
THIS BABY TRYING TO MAKE A
MISTAKE.
WHAT'S HIS NAME.
>> JAMES.
>> JAMES IS SO CUTE.
>> SORRY, ALLISON.
>> JUMPING RIGHT IN.
GO AHEAD.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A SCRIPT
HERE SO WE'LL JUST SAY THAT WE
ARE JOINED THIS MORNING BY
ELIZABETH REBA OF CRUMBS AND
WHISKERS THAT REALLY POPULAR CAT
AND KITTY CAFE.
THE PEOPLE COME IN AND THEY CAN
CUDDLE AND FALL IN LOVE WITH
CATS AND HOPEFULLY TAKE ONE
HOME.
>> EXACTLY.
THAT'S THE WHOLE DEAL.
AND FOR THE HOLIDAYS WE'RE SUPER
DECKED OUT.
IT'S A WINTER WONDERLAND.
THESE LITTLE BABIES ARE
USUALLY -- OOH.
>> I WAS MADE A FRIEND.
THAT'S BAT GIRL SHE USUALLY
WEARS A HOLIDAY SWEATER FOR THE
EVENT.
WE'RE HERE FOR HOLIDAY SEASON
THROUGH HANUKKAH AND CHRISTMAS
INTO THE NEW YEAR.
WINTER WONDERLAND FOR KIDS TO
COME WITH THEIR PARENTS AND HANG
OUT WITH KITTENS.
>> THE HOPE IS THAT YOU
ULTIMATELY FALL IN LOVE WITH
SOMEONE AND GET A CAT OR KITTEN
A GREAT HOME.
BUT NOT NECESSARILY FOR LIKE
UNDER THE TREE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> THIS IS NOT AN IMPULSE MUCH
THIS IS LIVE.
>> WE MAKE SURE THESE CATS HERE
FOR THE LONG HALL.
THIS IS LYNN FORSYTHE SHE'S
VOLUNTEER AN ADOPTION
COORDINATOR AND FOSTER MOM WITH
LUCKY DOG.
>> LUCKY DOG.
DON'T BE FOOLED BY THE NAME
LUCKY DOG RESCUES.
CATS, DOGS AND OTHER BEAUTIFUL
ANIMALS, RIGHT?
>> TELL US ABOUT THE NEED THIS
TIME OF YEAR FOR GOOD FAMILIES
FOR ALL OF OUR FRIENDS.
>> OH BABY.
>> AROUND THIS TIME OF YEAR THE
SHELTERS ARE HAVE OVERCROWDED.
SO WE ARE VERY HAPPY IF PEOPLE
ADOPT AROUND THIS TIME FOR SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT OF COURSE AS ELIZABETH
SAID BEFORE WE WANT TO MAKE SURE
PEOPLE REALIZE --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THE COMMITMENT.
>> SO FUN.
NEED TO BE SOMETHING REALLY WELL
CONSIDERED.
>> RIGHT.
ERIN, ERIN IS OUR RESIDENT CAT
LOVER.
BUT I REALLY HAVE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT, UM, ADOPTING A KITTEN OR
A CAT.
YOU SAID YOU WOULD HELP ME.
>> ALLISON, THE THING CATS PICK
YOU.
CATS CHOOSE YOU WAY DIFFERENT
THAN DOGS PERSONALITY WISE.
YOU SEE THEY THEY HAVE DIFFERENT
UNIQUE PERSONALITIES.
SOME ARE MORE CHILL CHILL.
SOME ARE MORE ACTIVE AND
PLAYFUL.
GO TO CRUMBS AND WHISKERS SIT
DOWN AND SEE WHAT CAT GRAVITATES
TOWARDS YOU AND GO FROM THERE
AND FIND YOURSELF A LITTLE LO
LOVER.
HOW OLD IS THIS LITTLE GIRL
TOFFEE.
>> TOFFEE IS ABOUT FOUR MONTHS.
>> PLAYFUL KITTEN.
GOOD AND CULLED.
SHE LOVES TO SNUGGLE AND EAT
PEOPLE'S DRINKS.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS BEAUTIFUL
BLACK CAT.
WE DON'T WANT TO FORGET BLACK
CATS.
THEY SOMETIMES GET OVERLOOKED.
>> HER NAME IS A BAT GIRL AND
SUPER ACTIVE AN PURR MACHINE.
JUST NUZZLES AND PURSE AND
CUDDLES.
>> ALLISON, I REALLY WILL MAKE
AN APPOINTMENT AND GO WITH YOU.
>> I'M GOING TO NEED SOME HELP
BECAUSE AS A DOG PERSON LIKE
IT'S INTIMIDATING.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> IT IS.
WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN RIGHT
NOW.
THEY ARE JUST MAGIC TIS
BEAUTIFUL ANIMALS.
SO YEAH.
ALSO YOU'VE GOT A WHOLE --
>> WE BROUGHT YOU SOME THINGS.
WEE BROUGHT YOU T-SHIRTS AND
RELATIONSHIP BAGS AND HATS AS
WELL.
JUST SORT OF SHOWCASE SOME OF
OUR NEW LINE WHICH IS GOING TO
BE ALL ONLINE EVERYTHING FOR CAT
LOVERS FROM MUGS TO T-SHIRTS TO
IPHONE CASES.
WHOLE NEW REVAMP ALL COOL ON ALL
OUR WEBSITE CRUMBS AND
WHISKERS.COM.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU LOVE CATS.
>> WAY TOO MUCH.
I HAVE THREE AND I ALWAYS WANT
TO TAKE ANOTHER ONE HOME.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
>> ALLISON, GRAB THIS ONE.
>> I'M NERVOUS.
>> DON'T BE NERVOUS.
>> OKAY.
SO TELL US BEFORE WE LET YOU GO
HERE JUST ONE MORE THING FROM
LYNN.
WHAT CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT THE
ADOPTION PROCESS IF IF YOU THINK
THAT YOU'RE READY TO HAVE A
FOREVER BABY IN YOUR HOME?
>> WHERE DO I HOLD HER.
>> GO TO OUR WEBSITE WWW.LUCKY
DOG ANIMAL RESCUE.ORG.
AND YOU CAN FILL OUT AN
APPLICATION ONLINE AND WIN 24
HOURS ONE OF OUR ADOPTION
COORDINATORS EACH ALSO AN
ADOPTION COORDINATORS FOR THE
CATS WILL GET IN TOUCH WITH YOU
AND WE'LL START LIKE A LITTLE
SCREENING PROCESS.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> TO MAKE SURE IF YOU'RE
RENTING YOUR PET POLICY ALLOWS
YOU TO HAVE CATS.
>> IMPORTANT QUESTIONS TO ASK.
>> EXACTLY.
EXACTLY.
>> RIGHT.
>> IF YOU HAVE ROOMMATES LIKE
EVERYONE IS ON BOARD BECAUSE
LIKE I SAID IT IS A VERY BIG
COMMITMENT.
WE WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
EVERYTHING IS THE WAY IT SHOULD
BE AND THAT THE ANIMAL WILL GET
A SAVE HOME.
>> YES.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> GREAT ADDITION FOR THE
HOLIDAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR JOINING
US.
BLESSING US WITH THESE BEAUTIFUL
BABIES.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> I'LL STAY HERE AND PLAY WITH
YOU.
>> STEVE, BACK TO YOU.
>> I'M SIDE TRACKED.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE THE CATS.
WE'LL MOVE FROM CATS TO DOGS
THOUGH.
YOU MIGHT HAVE HEARD OF PORCH
PAIR RATES HOW ABOUT A POOCH
PIRATE.
MAX SPOTTED ON CAM STEALING A
PACKAGE FROM A FRONT PORCH IN
CALIFORNIA.
THAT IS NOT A GOOD BOY.
BUT CAN YOU BLAME HIM?  BECAUSE
THE PACKAGE CONTAINED A BOX OF
JERKY AND OTHER FOOD ITEMS ZOMAX
GOT A LITTLE HUNGRY.
HIS OWNERS OFFED TO PATE
RECIPIENT BACK FOR THE STOLEN
GOODS.
THE RECIPIENT SAID WE'RE GOOD.
IF YOU PLAN ON STAYING HOPE THIS
HOLIDAY WEEK AND YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING TO BINGE WATCH WE
GOT YOU COVERED.
KEVIN HAS A LIFT OF WHAT YOUR
FAMILY CAN ENJOY TOGETHER COMING
UP A LITTLE BIT LATER.
♪
Sometimes, the pressures of
today's world can make it tough
to take care
of yourself.
But Nature's Bounty
has innovative ways
to help you
maintain balance
and help keep you
active and well-rested.
Because hey,
tomorrow's
coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty.
Because you're
better off healthy.
♪
>> TIME FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA
MCCARTHY WITH THIS GUY, KEVIN
MCCARTHY.
>> GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
WE'LL GO THROUGH SOME -- GOOD
MORNING, ALLISON.
SHOWS TO BINGE OVER THE
CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> AND AGAIN, NOT A LOT OF THESE
WILL BE FAMILY FRIENDLY
UNFORTUNATELY.
A LOT OF SHOWS THAT ARE OUT
THERE ARE --
>> NOT ALL THE HOLIDAYS ARE
FAMILY FRIENDLY.
>> A LOT OF SHOWS AREN'T FAMILY
FRIENDLY MUCH HERE'S WHAT WE'LL
DO.
WE'LL GO THROUGH A LIST OF FIVE
OF THEM.
>> BINGING.
>> WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS I'M
GOING TO GIVE YOU RECOMMENDATION
FROM OUR PRODUCERS AS WELCH THIS
ACTUALLY HAD COME FROM THE ME.
MANDALORIAN TUCKER HAS BEEN
TALKING A LOT ABOUT IT THIS
MORNING BABY YODA.
BABY YODA, BABY YODA, BABY YODA.
>> FINAL EPISODE OF THIS SEASON
IS ACTUALLY GOING TO BE PREMIER
THIS FRIDAY THE 27th.
SO IF YOU'RE BINGING THE
MANDALORIAN CREATED BY JOHN BE
IN BEFORE HE STAR WARS SERIES,.
>>ET CT UP AND WATCH IT.
>> THE FINAL EPISODE OF SEASON
ONE WILL PREMIER THIS FRIDAY ON
DISNEY PLUS.
>> IAVE A FEELING SEASON TOO
IS NOT FAR BEHIND.
>> IT WILL BE HUGE.
THE SHOW WILL CONTINUE GOING.
>> NUMBER TWO.
>> I ONLY BRING THIS ONE UP ONLY
BECAUSE.
>> EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT
IT?
>> EVERYBODY IS DISCUSSING IT.
ALSO, EVERYONE LOVES HENRY
CAVEL.
BASED AROUND THE IDEA OF A
MONSTER HUNTER OF HUNTER.
I HAVE NOT SEEN THE COMPLETED
SERIES.
WE HAD HENRY CAVEL ON THE SHOW
IF YOU MIFF THE INTERVIEW GO
FOXDC.COM.
BUT APPARENTLY THIS IS A
MASSIVELY TALKED ABOUT SHOW AND
RIGHT NOW THERE'S A HUGE TALK
ABOUT SEASON TWO WHICH WAS
CONFIRMED IN NOVEMBER BEFORE THE
SHOW WAS EVEN RELEASED FOR
SEASON ONE.
SEASON ONE IS STREAMING NOW ON
NETFLIX.
BUT MARK HAMILL IS POSSIBLY
BEING RUMORED.
>> REALLY.
>> IT'S NOT BEING OFFICIALLY
TALKED ABOUT.
THERE'S BEEN ONLINE FAN DOM KIM
UP SAYING THAT MARK HAMILL
SHOULD BE IN THE SEASON TWO
PLAYING A CERTAIN CHARACTER.
SO I'M INTEREST TO DO CITY THAT
HAPPENS.
>> INTEREST.
>> WHAT IS THIS.
>> WATCHMAN.
WATCHMAN IS GOING TO BE -- THIS
IS A PICK FROM IN A KIA SIMON
ONE MUCH OUR PRODUCERS HERE AT
FOX5.
WE HAD AN E-MAIL CHAIN GOING
AROUND OF DIFFERENT PRODUCERS
SAYING WHAT SHOWS PEOPLE SHOULD
BINGE.
I HAVE NOT SEEN WATCHMAN YET.
I SEE ABOUT 150 FILMS A YEAR.
I DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME TO
WATCH A TON OF TELEVISION.
BUT THIS SHOW I CANNOT WAIT TO
WATCH.
I LOVE DAMON LINDH LAUGH WHO
CREATOR THE SHOW AND THE SHOW
LOST.
THIS IS RHEE REGINA KING AMAZING
ACTOR.
I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE THIS.
IT LOOKS AMAZING THE FINAL
EPISODE JUST PREMIERED A COUPLE
WEEKS BACK.
>> PRODUCER NIKIA APPROVED.
>> AND ALSO YOU THE ANOTHER ONE
A MICK FROM SCHENN NEL OLIVER.
THIS IS THE SEASON TWO OF THIS
SHOW IS ACTUALLY GOING PREMIER
ON DECEMBER 26th WHICH IS THE
DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS.
SEASON ONE WE ALL KNOW PREMIERED
ORIGINALLY WITH LIFETIME WENT TO
NETFLIX BECAME A VERY VERY
MASSIVE HIT.
FOR PEOPLE WHO AREN'T AWARE THE
SHOW IT'S A BOOKSTORE MANAGER
AND KIND OF DEALING WITH CERTAIN
CRAZY ASPENS OF LOVE WHICH I
WON'T GO INTO SPECIFICALLY
BECAUSE I KNOW SOME OF IT CAN BE
VERY R RATED THAT'S GOING TO BE
SEAN NEL'S PICK IS YOU SEASON
ONE STREAMING NOW ON NETFLIX.
SEASON TWO ON NETFLIX DECE
DECEMBER 26th FINALLY WE'LL GO
WITH MORNING SHOW WITH JEFF
GEUGAS THE EXECUTIVE PRODUCER OF
GOOD DAY D.C.
JENNIFER ANISTON, REECE
WITHERSPOON AND STEVE CARELL
MUCH THIS IS A PICK FROM OUR
PRODUCER I'VE NOT SEEN THIS FULL
SEASON EITHER BUT JEFF WHO
PRODUCES THE MORNING SHOW
ABSOLUTELY LOVES THE MORNING
SHOW.
SO THAT COMES FROM HIM AS A
RECOMMENDATION BUT AS YOU CAN
SEE LIKE A LOT OF THESE
RECOMMENDATIONS THEY'RE PEOPLE
WHO GET TO WATCH A LOT OF TV
SHOWS.
PEOPLE DON'T GET TO WATCH TV
SHOWS BUT THANK YOU SEAN NEL AND
NIKIA AND JEFF FOR GIVING THEIR
RECOMMENDATIONS.
MANDALORIAN IS MY NUMBER ONE
SHOW TO STREAM OVER THE HOLIDAYS
PERSONALLY I HAVE NOT SEEN THE
LAST EPISODE.
NO SPOILERS PLEASE.
>> TWO WORDS, BOBBY YODA MAYBE
THAT TIME YOU TOOK MY CARDBOARD
CUT OUT AND STORM OUT OF THE
STATION WITH IT.
>> I WAS SO MAD.
>> LIKE DI CAP PIO PUNCHING HIS
CARDBOARD CUT OUT AT THE END OF
ONCE UPON A TIME IN HOLLYWOOD.
>> THAT TOO.
>> I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN STEVE
AND I FIGHT.
>> NOT FOR CHRISTMAS HEAVE.
>> NO.
WE'RE A FAMILY.
THAT'S NEW YEAR'S BUSINESS.
>> EXACTLY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>>> WEATHER WISE WE COULD NOT
ASK FOR A NICER AT NOON.
IT WILL BE A LITTLE ON THE COOL
SIDE.
TAKE A JACKET.
50 DEGREES WITH PLENTY OF
SUNSHINE.
GREAT TONIGHT FOR SANTA'S
DELIVERIES AND TOMORROW LOOKS
GREAT, CHRISTMAS DAY 50 DEGREES.
MAYBE SHOWERS BY SUNDAY.
>> THE NEWS IS NON-STOP.
GOOD DAY DC AT 9:00 A.M. STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
♪
>> STEVE?
>> COME ON.
>> STEVE, YOU'RE LATE.
>> STEVE, GO.
♪
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD THE CHRISTMAS
COUNTDOWN.
THE HOLIDAY NOW LESS THAN 24
HOURS AWAY.
WHICH MEANS THE LAST MINUTE RUSH
HOME AND FOR GIFTS IS OFFICIALLY
UNDERWAY.
COMING UP WE'LL HAVE UPDATES
FROM THE AIRPORTS, THE ROADS AND
THE SHOPPING MALLS.
>>> AND TRAVELING OVER THE
HOLIDAYS?  WILL THE FORECAST BE
NAUGHTY OR NICE?  I'LL HAVE ALL
THE DETAILS ON THAT WEATHER
FORECAST COMING UP.
>>> A BUMPY YEAR.
THE QUEEN OF ENGLAND OPENING UP
ABOUT THE ROYAL FAMILY DRAMA IN
HER A