NELSON STREET SOUTHEAST.
TAKE A LOOK AGAIN.
IF YOU'VE SEEN HIM PLEASE CALL
POLICE.
WE'VE ALSO PUT HIS PICTURE ON OT
ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
>>> ANSWERS ABOUT A DISTURBING
INCIDENT AT A MONTGOMERY
COUNTY SCHOOL.
SEVERAL CLARKSBURG HIGH SCHOOL
STUDENTS ARE UNDER ARREST
AFTER ONE OF THEM ADMITTED
BRINGING A GUN TO SCHOOL ON
MONDAY.
>> IKE EJIOCHI IS LIVE IN
CLARKSBURG.
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE THE
CHARGING DOCUMENTS WHICH MEANS
WE HAVE A LOT MORE DETAILS
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED AT THIS
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
BLAKE.
FOX5 VIEWERS HAVE BEEN CALLING
US TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
HAPPENED BEHIND ME AT
CLARKSBURG HIGH SCHOOL.
WE'VE CONTACTED MONTGOMERY
COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS ON
MULTIPLE OCCASIONS.
WE'VE CONTACTED MONTGOMERY
COUNTY POLICE DEPARTMENT
YESTERDAY ON THREE SEPARATE
OCCASIONS AND THEY GAVE US
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
IT WASN'T UNTIL WE FINALLY GOT
A PRESS RELEASE PLUS THOSE
CHARGING DOCUMENTS TODAY 48
HOURS AFTER THE FACT WE
FINALLY HAVE SOME INFORMATION
WE CAN REPORT TO YOU.
LET ME TELL YOU EXACTLY WHAT
HAPPENED.
THIS INCIDENT HAPPENED ON
FEBRUARY 10TH, MONDAY FEBRUARY .
CHARGING DOCUMENT SAY
18-YEAR-OLD JUSTIN FERGUSON
WAS ONE OF THE FOUR
INDIVIDUALS INSIDE HERE THAT
WAS CHARGED WITH ROBBERY AND
CERTAIN OTHER THINGS.
HERE'S EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
A 15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE WAS
REPORTED SAYING THAT HE FELT
AFRAID OF 18-YEAR-OLD JUSTIN
FERGUSON SO HE WENT AND HE
TOOK HIS STEPFATHER'S BLACK
AND SILVER GLOCK AND BROUGHT
IT TO SCHOOL ON FEBRUARY 10TH.
CHARGING DOCUMENTS SAID THAT
THAT 15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE AS
WELL AS FOUR OTHER INDIVIDUALS
MET AT A BATHROM TO QUOTE BUY
OR SELL MARIJUANA.
THAT 15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE TOOK
OUT THE GUN AND SHOWED THE
OTHER INDIVIDUALS JUST TO KIND
OF SHOW THEM WHAT HE HAD.
THE OTHER INDIVIDUALS THEY ALL
PASSED THE GUN AROUND AND IT
WAS REPORTED THAT ONE OF THEM
ACTUALLY LEFT.
NOW, THAT 15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE
FOLLOWED THAT INDIVIDUAL OUT
OF THE BATHROOM.
THEY WERE IN A GROUP.
MANAGED TO COME OUT OF THE
SCHOOL AND THEY WENT TO A
BASEBALL FIELD RIGHT HERE
BEHIND CLARKSBURG HIGH SCHOOL.
NOW IT WAS AT THAT BASEBALL
FIELD THAT THE FOUR
INDIVIDUALS HELD DOWN THAT
15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE, THEY
TOOK HIS GLOCK, THEY TOOK $150
WORTH OF CASH, THEY TOOK HIS
WALLET AND THEY TOOK HIS
SCHOOL I.D.
THAT 15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE WENT
BACK INTO THE SCHOOL ALONG
WITH ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL WHILE
THE OTHER STUDENTS LEFT.
NOW, HERE'S EXACTLY HOW THE
SCHOOL FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS.
SOMEONE TOLD A SCHOOL RESOURCE
OFFICER WHAT HAD HAPPENED.
THAT SCHOOL RESOURCE OFFICER
WENT TO GO LOOK FOR THAT
15-YEAR-OLD JUVENILE FOUND HIM
WENT THROUGH THAT JUVENILE'S
BACKPACK AND FOUND A FULLY
LOADED HANDGUN MAGAZINE.
NOW HE DID THAT AND THE POLICE
WERE CALLED.
HE WAS ARRESTED AS WELL AS THE
OTHER INDIVIDUALS AND
EVERYBODY INVOLVED WAS
CHARGED.
HOWEVER THE ACTUAL HANDGUN HAS
STILL NOT BEEN FOUND AT THE
MOMENT.
>> A LOT OF PARENTS HAVE BEEN
REALLY WONDERING WHAT'S GOING
ON OUT THERE.
GLAD THEY'RE GETTING SOME
ANSWERS TODAY.
IKE EJIOCHI LIVE FOR US.
THANK YOU.
>> ♪
>> LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK NOW
DOWNTOWN BETHESDA ON THIS
WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON.
WE ARE EXPECTING SOME RAIN TO
START MOVING INTO THE AREA.
>> YES, SO IF YOU ARE HEADED
OUT, IT'S A GOOD IDEA, BRING
THAT UMBRELLA WITH YOU.
MAYBE A PONCHO.
CAITLIN IS STANDING BY --
>> PONCHO.
A LITTLE DRAMATIC.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I STILL HAVE A PONCHO.
>> DO YOU SOMETIMES USE THAT.
>> YES.
>> IN LIEU OF AN UMBRELLA.
>> THEY'RE EASY TO WRAP UP IN.
BUT THAT PICTURE WE JUST
LOOKED AT, THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE OUTSIDE.
>> YEAH, IT'S DREARY I KNOW.
WE'RE SEEING SHOWERS START TO
FILL INTO OUR WEST GUYS.
THIS EVENING WHILE IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE IT WILL BE A SOAKING
RAIN IT DOES LOOK LIKE WE'LL
HAVE A FEW SHOWERS AROUND.
LIGHT RAIN TO OUR WEST MAINLY
WEST ON 66 UP ALONG 81 TOWARDS
HAGERSTOWN.
NOTICE THE TINY PURPLE AND
PINK MIXING IN.
THAT COULD BE A FEW SLEET
PELLETS MAYBE A FEW WET
SNOWFLAKES.
SLEET REPORTED IN CHANTILLY.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT AS YOU
CHECK IN ON FAIRFAX COUNTY AND
OTHER VIRGINIA COUNTIES BUT I
WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF YOU
SEE SOMETHING FROZEN MIXING IN
WITH THOSE RAIN SHOWERS
ESPECIALLY BACK TOWARDS FRONT
ROYAL WINCHESTER AND UP
TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN.
THIS IS THE LEADING EDGE OF A
STORM SYSTEM WHICH IS QUITE
SPRAWLING, THE WARM FRONT OVER
US BACK THROUGH THE OHIO
VALLEY.
THERE'S THE LOW PRESSURE
ITSELF AND THE COLD FRONT FROM
SAINT LOUIS DOWN INTO THE
SOUTHEASTERN STATES.
WE'VE GOT A WAYS TO GO WITH
THIS LOW PRESSURE SYSTEM
THAT'S GOING TO ROLL UP ON US,
BRING US NOTHING BUT RAIN
SHOWERS BUT I THINK THE
STEADIEST WILL BE TOMORROW
MORNING DURING THE COMMUTE.
49 DEGREES OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW.
IT'S BEEN MOSTLY CLOUDY.
IT'S BEEN CHILLY.
WE DID HAVE SOME SUNSHINE
EARLIER WHICH WAS SO LOVELY.
BUT BLINK AND YOU MISS IT.
WE'RE BACK TO THE GRAY SKIES
RIGHT NOW.
SHOWERS WILL CONTINUE TO FILL
IN THIS EVENING.
AGAIN, PRETTY LIGHT AND WIDELY
SCATTERED.
AREAS SOUTH AND EAST OF US
MIGHT NOT SEE MUCH UNTIL
OVERNIGHT.
AT 11 O'CLOCK JUST DRIZZLE AND
LIGHT RAIN SHOWERS.
BY 6:00 A.M. TOMORROW MORNING,
HERE'S THE COMMUTE GETTING
STARTED.
WE'VE GOT STEADY TO POSSIBLY
EVEN HEAVY RAIN OVERHEAD SO
THIS IS GOING TO BE OUR THIRD
OUT OF FOUR MORNINGS IN A ROW
WHERE WE'RE DEALING WITH RAIN.
SHOWERS WILL CONTINUE THROUGH
THE MORNING HOURS AND THEN BY
ABOUT MIDAFTERNOON I THINK
WE'RE DONE.
WE'LL CLEAR OUT AND AS WE
CLEAR OUT, THOSE WINDS WILL
REALLY PICK UP.
THAT WILL HELP DRY US AND
USHER IN THIS NEW AIR MASS BUT
IT WILL BE MILD TOMORROW.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO SEE THAT
COLD AIR UNTIL FRIDAY.
UMBRELLAS NEEDED FOR THE
COMMUTE, 48 DEGREES.
55 AS WE CLEAR OUT BY NOON.
60 ON A NICE MILD THURSDAY
AFTERNOON BUT THAT COLD AIR IS
DEFINITELY COMING.
MUCH MORE ON THAT BIG CHANGE
FOR FRIDAY STILL AHEAD.
BLAKE.
>> THANK YOU INDICATE LYNCH
CAITLIN.THE CITY OF CHICAGO IS
PURSUING A CIVIL LAWSUIT
AGAINST JUSSIE SMOLLETT EVEN
THOUGH NO CRIMINAL CHANCE HAVE
BEEN FILED.
CHICAGO WANTS TO RECOVER THE
COST OF ITS INVESTIGATION INTO
THE ALLEGED RACIST AND
HOMOPHOBIC ATTACK AGAINST HIM.
HE WAS INDICTED ON NEW
CRIMINAL CHARGES BY A GRAND
JURY YESTERDAY.
TMZ WILL JOIN US LIVE LATER IN
THE FORECAST.
>> RESULTS FROM THE NEW
HAMPSHIRE PRIMARY AND SENATOR
BERNIE SANDERS IS THE BIG
WINNER HE EDGED OUT PETE
BUTTIGIEG FOR THE FIRST CLEAR
VICTORY.
AMY KLOBUCHAR CAME IN THIRD.
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN CAME
IN FOURTH WHILE FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN DROPPED TO
FIFTH.
>>> SINCE THE RESULTS CAME OUT
SEVERAL DEMOCRATS ARE DROPPED
OUT.
DUVAL PATRICK ENDED HIS LONG
SHOT WHITE HOUSE BID TODAY.
HIS DEPARTURE MEANS THERE ARE
NO AFRICAN-AMERICANS LEFT IN
THE RACE.
ANDREW YANG AND MICHAEL
BENNETT ALSO ENDED THEIR
CAMPAIGNS.
>> A POSSIBLE SIGN THE
CORONAVIRUS COULD BE SLOWING
DOWN.
THE WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION
SAID TODAY THE NUMBER OF NEW
CASES IN CHINA DROPPED FOR A
SECOND STRAIGHT DAY.
STILL, 2015 NEW CASES WERE
COUNCOUNTED IN YESTERDAY DOWN FM
3900 CASES LAST WEEK.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT IS
STEPPING UP EFFORTS TO CONTAIN
AND STOP THE SPREAD.
HEALTH DEPARTMENTS ACROSS THE
NATION ARE NOW RECEIVING TEST
KITS TO HELP THEM QUICKLY
IDENTIFY NEW CORONAVIRUS
CASES.
SO FAR THERE HAVE BEEN JUST 13
CASES IN THE U.S.
>> AIR TRAVEL CONNECTS THE
WORLD BUT CAN ALSO BRING
UNWANTED ITEMS AND DISEASES
BACK WITH THE PASSENGERS.
>> TODAY U.S. CUSTOMS AND
BORDER PATROL SHARING SOME OF
THE ITEMS THEY'VE RECENTLY
SEIZED AT DULLES AIRPORT WITH
A WARNING FOR ALL OF US,
FOX5's MARINA MARRACO HAS
MORE.
>> THESE ARE INTERESTING ITEMS
AND SOME OF THEM QUESTIONABLE.
WE'RE SEEING THEM AT DULLES
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT.
THEY COULD BE HARMLESS BUT WE
DON'T KNOW AND THERE COULD BE
HIDDEN THREATS IN FORMS OF
SPECIES THAT PEOPLE DON'T
REALIZE.
SOME GET CREATIVE WITH HOW
THEY TRY TO GET THOSE ITEMS
INTO THE COUNTRY.
IN JANUARY AT DULLES
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT CUSTOMS
AND BORDER PATROL STOPPING A
PASSENGER FROM VIETNAM HEADING
TO MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
HE DECLARED THAT HE HAD 25
NOODLE CUPS BUT WHEN AGENTS
TOOK A CLOSER LOOK, THEY FOUND
THAT EACH CUP WAS OPEN AND HAD
LITTLE PORK SAUSAGES INSIDE OF
THEM.
YOU CAN SEE HOW THEY WERE
WRAPPED THERE.
THEN THERE WAS A TRAVELER WHO
ARRIVED FROM TUNISIA.
BEASLEY THE DETECTOR DOG
SNIFFING OUT A POUND OF
PROTECTED RICE.
YOU CAN SEE IT COMES IN THAT
SEALED TIN CAN.
THE TRAVELER TRYING TO TAKE
THAT PRODUCT THOSE ITEMS TO
FAIRFAX COUNTY.
AND OF COURSE WE HAVE TO
MENTION PROBABLY THE MOST
BIZARRE OF THOSE DISCOVERIES.
A TRAVELER ARRIVING FROM A
FLIGHT FROM BEIJING.
THOSE ARE TINY DEAD BIRDS
INSIDE OF A PACKAGE.
THE PACKAGE HAD PICTURES OF A
CAT AND A DOG ON IT THE
PASSENGER TELLING AGENTS IT
WAS LIKELY CAT FOOD.
THE PACKAGE INCINERATED
BECAUSE IT CARRIES THE THREAT
OF POTENTIALLY AVIAN
INFLUENZA.
DURING A TIP DAY AGENTS SEIZE
MORE THAN 4500 PROHIBITED
ITEMS AT AIRPORTS NATIONWIDE.
OF COURSE WITH THE CORONAVIRUS
OUTBREAK IT'S UNCLEAR IF ANY
OF THESE PRODUCTS COULD
POTENTIALLY BRING IN NEW
DISEASES, NEW FLUS INTO OUR
REGION AND OF COURSE WITH THIS
OUTBREAK IT'S NOT SOMETHING WE
WANT.
>> CORONAVIRUS IS TOP OF MIND
BUT AS YOU MENTIONED WITH THE
BIRD IT COULD BE BIRD FLEW,
INVASIVE BUGS.
>> ANYTHING.
>> BUT TO ME WHAT'S SO
FASCINATING IS YOU LOOK AT A
PACKAGE LIKE THAT AND YOU
MIGHT THINK IT'S A SNACK.
WHEN I GO NOT LITTLE ASIAN
STORE AND I GET MY SNACKS I
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
THE FACT THEY WERE ABLE TO
SNIFF IT OUT THAT'S AMAZING.
>> THE TASK U.S. BORDER HAS
IDENTIFYING THIS STUFF.
>> YOU WOULDN'T KNOW UNTIL YOU
OPEN IT.
>> THANKS MARINA.
>> OKAY.
WE GOT SOME TOP CAUGHT ON
CAMERA MOMENTS TO SHARE WITH
YOU RIGHT NOW.
CHECK OUT THIS SURVEILLANCE
FOOTAGE FROM A SHOPPING CENTER
IN A PARKING LOT IN GEORGIA.
THINGS GOT OUT OF HAND REAL
QUICK.
A SHOPPER SHOVE HIS CART
TRIPPING THAT MAN AS OFFICERS
CATCH HIM.
LATER VIDEO SHOW THE SHOPPERS
HELPING HIM PICK UP HIS ITEMS.
IT ALSO SHOWS A PAT ON THE
BACK FROM POLICE.
OFFICERS SAY THEY APPRECIATE
HIS HELP.
>> CRIME FIGHTING ANYTHING
COULD BE A WEAPON WHATEVER
YOU'VE GOT.
>>> VIDEO SHOWS A MASSIVE WAVE
KNOCKING A MAN OFF HIS BOARD
IN CHOPPY WATERS.
FIRST OF ALL LOOK AT HOW BIG
THESE WAVES R THIS IS IN
PORTUGAL.
WE KNOW THEY HAVE BEEN DEALING
WITH STORM CIARA.
ON THEIR WAY BACK TO SHORE
ANOTHER WAVE HIT THE JET SKI
KNOCKED THE PAIR INTO THE
SURF.
LUCKILY THEY WERE BOTH ABLE TO
MAKE IT BACK AND TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
THEY'RE EXPECTED TO BE OKAY.
THE SIZE OF THOSE WAVES.
>> THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>>> THIS PHOTO TAKE A LOOK IT
WON ONE OF THE WORLD'S TOP
AWARDS FOR WILDLIFE
PHOTOGRAPHY.
IT WAS TAKEN IN A LONDON
SUBWAY AND IT SHOWS TWO MICE
IF YOU TAKE A CLOSER LOOK,
THEY ARE FIGHTING, THEY'RE
SQUABBLING.
THE NATURAL HISTORY MUSEUM OF
LONDON HOLDS THE COMPETITION.
THE PHOTOGRAPHER NAMED IT
SUBWAY SQUABBLE.
>> NATURE CAN BE FOUND EVEN IN
THE SUBWAYS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THE METRO SYSTEM ALWAYS
BEING CRITICIZED.
SO, WHY WOULD ANYBODY
PURPOSELY SPEND ALL DAY RIDING
THE RAILS JUST FOR KICKS?
IT'S BEING CALLED THE METRO
CHALLENGE.
THE GOAL IS TO VISIT ALL 91
METRO STATIONS WITHOUT EVER
LEAVING THE SYSTEM.
IT TOOK REILLY DASH8 HOURS TO
ACCOMPLISH THIS FEAT LAST
JANUARY.
FOX5 DID A MINI METRO
CHALLENGE VISITING 40 STATIONS
IN THREE AND A HALF HOURS ALL
OF IT LIVE ON OUR MORNING
SHOW.
>> I'M A MATH NERDS.
I TOOK IT AS A CHALLENGE.
WANTED TO SEE HOW FAST I COULD
DO IT.
TOOK ABOUT EIGHT HOURS.
THE ROUTE I TOOK YOU DO THE
WHOLE RED LINE THEN THE WHOLE
GREEN LINE THEN BACKTRACK AND
DO THE WHOLE YELLOW LINE OR
REMAINING PORTION, THE WHOLE
BLUE LINE AND THEN YOU TAKE
THE ORANGE LINE AND THEN
FINISH ON THE SILVER.
>> I'VE LOOKED AT THAT MAP SO
MUCH TAKING THE METRO I DIDN'T
REALIZE THERE WERE 91 STOPS.
THAT'S A LOT.
IF YOU THING THAT CHALLENGE IS
TAXING PEOPLE HAVE COMPLETED
THE CHALLENGE IN NEW YORK CITY
VISITING ALL 472 SUBWAY
STATIONS IN AS LITTLE AS 25
HOURS.
>> MORE THAN A DAY.
>> THEIR SYSTEM IS 24 HOURS SO
YOU CAN DO IT THERE.
OURS YOU HAVE TO DO IT BEFORE
THEY KICK YOU OUT AT 4:00 P.M.
WHENEVER IT CLOSES.
>> I'VE DRIVEN THE WHOLE
BELTWAY JUST TO SEE THE INNER
LOOP AND THE OUTER LOOP.
>> LIKE FOR FUN?
>> YEAH BACK IN THE DAY WHEN I
FIRST MOVED BACK AND I WAS
TRYING TO GET REACCLIMATED TO
THE AREA.
>> SHE DIDN'T KNOW ANYBODY.
>> BEFORE THE KIDS, YOU KNOW,
JUST KILLING TIME.
HERE'S A SURE SIGN OF SPRING
AROUND THE CORNER GUYS.
READY TO PLAY BALL?  TODAY THE
WASHINGTON NATIONALS BEGAN
THEIR QUEST TO DEFEND THEIR
WORLD SERIES CHAMPIONSHIP
TITLE.
NATS PITCHERS AND CATCHERS
REPORTED TO THEIR FACILITY IN
WEST PALM BEACH FLORIDA FOR
SPRING TRAINING.
THE FULL TEAM REPORTS MONDAY.
NATS OPEN UP SPRING TRAINING
SCHEDULE WITH A REMATCH OF
LAST YEAR'S WORLD SERIES WHEN
THEY FACE OFF AGAINST THE
HOUSTON ASTROS ON
FEBRUARY 22ND AND THEY
ACTUALLY SHARE A TRAINING
FACILITY TOGETHER WHICH IS SO
FUNNY.
YEAH.
>> STILL TO COME MAYBE
VIRGINIA IS NOT FOR LOVERS.
A NEW BILL COULD FINALLY MAKE
IT LEGAL FOR UNMARRIED PEOPLE
TO HAVE SEX IN VIRGINIA.
DID YOU KNOW THAT'S STILL A
CRIME IN VIRGINIA?  LEADS TO
THE QUESTION WHY HAS IT TAKEN
SO LONG.
>> PLUS WE MAY BE ASLEEP AT
NIGHT BUT OUR BRAINS ARE STILL
HARD AT WORK.
WE'LL REVEAL THE MOST COMMON
NIGHTMARES THAT WE'RE HAVING.
>> AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
AT TRAFFIC AROUND THE DMV ON
THIS WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON.
WOW, I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE ON
66.
>> NO.
>> BACKING UP EARLY.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Y
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
OBAMA: He's been a leader
throughout the country for the
past twelve years,
Mr. Michael Bloomberg is here.
VO: Leadership in action.
Mayor Bloomberg and
President Obama worked together
in the fight for gun safety
laws,
to improve education, and to
develop innovative ways to help
teens gain the skills needed to
find good jobs.
OBAMA: At a time
when Washington is divided in
old ideological battles he shows
us what can be achieved when
we bring people together
to seek pragmatic solutions.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> ♪
>> VIRGINIA IT'S FOR LOVERS
BUT DID YOU KNOW IT'S ILLEGAL
IN VIRGINIA FOR UNMARRIED
PEOPLE TO HAVE CONSENSUAL SEX?
>> YEAH, IT'S NOT A LAW THAT
IS ENFORCED AND IT'S BEEN
RULED UNCONSTITUTIONAL BUT
TONIGHT A LOCAL LAWMAKER IS
CLOSER THAN EVER TO GETTING
RID OF VIRGINIA'S FORNICATION
LAW.
TOM FITZGERALD IS IN ARLI
ARLINGTON.
FITZ WHAT'S THIS ALL ABOUT.
>> Reporter: ARE WE GOING TO
TALK ABOUT THIS?  WE ARE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S THE DEAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WEREN'T AWARE
OF IT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT IT.
BUT FOR A LONG TIME AND WE'RE
TALKING POSSIBLY HUNDREDS OF
YEARS, THE VIRGINIA CODE HAD A
FORNICATION LAW AND WHAT THAT
MEANT WAS THAT CONSENTING
ADULTS, IF THEY WERE UNMARRIED
IN VIRGINIA WERE BREAKING THE
LAW.
SO, YOU NOT ONLY COULD HAVE
BEEN IN VIOLATION OF THE
VIRGINIA CODE ANGIE, YOU KOCH
FINED -- NOT YOU BUT ANY OF
US, $250 FOR FORNICATION IN
THE COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA.
NOW, FINALLY, APPARENTLY THE
HOUSE OF DELEGATES IS MAKING
THE FIRST MOVE TOWARDS GETTING
RID OF ALL OF THIS.
MARK LEVINE, HE'S A DELEGATE
FROM ALEXANDRIA HE'S BEEN
TRYING FOR THE LAST COUPLE OF
YEARS TO GET THIS OVERTURNED,
HAVE IT KICKED OFF THE BOOKS.
IT WAS RULED UNCONSTITUTIONAL
A COUPLE YEARS AGO.
FINALLY AND JUST RECENTLY THE
HOUSE OF DELEGATES VOTED TO
GET RID OF THIS SO THEY MIGHT
FINALLY BE ABLE TO EXTRACT
THIS OUTDATED LAW OFF OF THE
BOOKS IN VIRGINIA ONCE AND FOR
ALL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO, WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
NEXT?  I MEAN, HAS THIS COME
UP BEFORE DO WE KNOW?  THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME I'VE EVER HEARD
ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: FIRST TIME I
EVER HEARD ABOUT IT JUST TO
PUT ALL OUR CARDS ON THE TABLE
HERE.
NO, ACTUALLY THE EFFORTS
STARTED RIGHT AFTER THE
VIRGINIA SUPREME COURT RULED
THIS UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
YOU KNOW, LET'S BE CLEAR.
IT'S HARDLY EVER BEEN CHARGED
BUT WHEN IT HAS BEEN CHARGED,
WELL, DELEGATE LEVINE TOLD US
IT'S LIKE ONE OF THOSE ODD-ON
LAWS THAT THEY WOULD TACK ON
TO ANOTHER SENTENCE AND THE
PERSON WOULD HAVE TO PLEAD
THAT OUT.
BUT NOT ONLY IS IT
UNCONSTITUTIONAL ACCORDING TO
VIRGINIA CONSTITUTION NOW IT'S
NEVER BEEN USED SO IT'S BEEN
ONE OF THESE THINGS LAYING
AROUND THE VIRGINIA CODE
THAT'S OUTLIVED ITS USEFULNESS
NOT THAT IT EVER HAD A
USEFULNESS.
BUT IT WAS OUT THERE AND
SOMEBODY COULD HAVE BEEN
CHARGED WITH IT AND IF THE
STATE SENATE NOW GOES ALONG
WITH THIS ACTION THAT THE
HOUSE OF DELEGATES TOOK OVER,
WELL, YOU KNOW, THIS SIGN,
VIRGINIA IS FOR LOVERS IT
MIGHT ACTUALLY MEAN WHAT IT'S
SUPPOSED TO MEAN FROM NOW ON.
>> ALL RIGHT, FITZ THANKS SO
MUCH FOR BREAKING IT ALL DOWN.
>> ♪
>> CAITLIN ROTH GOOD THING
WE'RE D.C. AND MARYLAND
PEOPLE.
>> RIGHT.
DON'T WANT THOSE SORT OF
PROBLEMS IN MY LIFE.
I GOT ENOUGH TRYING TO KEEP UP
WITH THE WEATHER.
>> ANGIE LET US KNOW HOW IT
GOES.
>> VIRGINIA IS FOR LOVERS CAN
I SAY -- NEVER MIND I'M NOT
GOING TO SAY IT.
VIRGINIA IS FOR VIRGINS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAW ON THE
TWITTER MANY PEOPLE WERE LIKE
THAT'S WHAT IT SHOULD BE BUT
LIKE FITZ SAID WE MIGHT BE
ABLE TO KEEP THE SLOGAN.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH, I'M LIKE -- BLAKE AND
I ARE LIKE NOT OUR PROBLEM BUT
WE WILL DEFINITELY GET UPDATES
FROM YOU ANGIE.
>> I'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
>> ALL RIGHT CAITLIN, THIS
RAIN YOU SAY IT'S MOVING IN.
WHEN ARE WE EXPECTING IT.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY SEEING
SHOWERS IN OUR WESTERN SUBURBS
RIGHT NOW GUYS.
IT'S JUST A GLOOMY DAY BEHIND
ME AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
ANY SUNSHINE WE HAD I'M AFRAID
EARLIER TODAY WHICH WAS LOVELY
IS LONG GONE.
SHOWERS WILL FILL IN TONIGHT.
THEY WILL BE STEADIEST
TOMORROW MORNING.
FOLLOWING THE SHOWERS WHICH
SHOULD CLEAR OUT IN THE
AFTERNOON, THE WINDS WILL PICK
UP AND THEN FOLLOWING THE WIND
WHICH WILL USHER US INTO
FRIDAY MORNING WE'LL GET THE
COLD.
A TRUE ARCTIC BLAST HEADED OUR
WAY TO END THE WORK WEEK.
ONE THING WE HAVE NOT DONE A
LOT OF THIS WINTER.
IT'S 49 IN D.C., 44 IN BOSTON,
34 IN BUFFALO, 60 IN
WILMINGTON.
LOOK ATLANTA 72 DEGREES.
LOOK AT THIS COLD SPILLING
SOUTHWARD FROM THE CENTRAL
CANADIAN PRAIRIES.
13 BELOW IN FARGO NORTH DAKOTA
WHERE THAT PINK SHADING IS.
THAT'S THE COLDEST OF THE
AREA.
39 LINCOLN, 34 IN CHICAGO.
THAT WHOLE AIR MASS WHILE IT
WILL MODIFY A LITTLE BIT BY
THE TIME IT REACHES US, WILL
BE HEADED IN OUR DIRECTION.
OUT AHEAD OF IT THOUGH WE HAVE
THIS LOW PRESSURE SYSTEM
THAT'S BRINGING SNOW TO SOME
OF THE NORTHERN OHIO VALLEY
STATES AND MANLY RAIN ALONG
THAT WARM FRONT WEST VIRGINIA
INTO OUR AREA, COLD FRONT
STRETCHES BACK TOWARDS MEMPHIS
AND THE SOUTHEAST.
NOW, THAT COLD FRONT WILL MOVE
THROUGH TOMORROW MORNING.
SO, WE'VE GOT THE SHOWERS
OVERHEAD ASSOCIATED WITH A
WARM FRONT RIGHT NOW.
BY THE TIME THE COLD FRONT
REACHES US, THAT WILL BE YOUR
COMMUTE TOMORROW.
SO, WITH THAT GUSTY RAIN
SHOWERS WILL QUICKLY CLEAR OUT
WINDS PICK UP HIGH PRESSURE
BUILDS IN.
THE COLD HAIR WILL BE MOVING
IN TOMORROW -- AIR WILL BE
MOVING IN TOMORROW NIGHT.
IT WILL BE DRAMATICALLY COLDER
WITH PRETTY BITTER WIND CHILLS
BY FRIDAY MORNING AND THEN
SATURDAY MORNING, WHEN HIGH
PRESSURE RIGH IS RIGHT OVER US
PROBABLY THE COLDEST MORNING
SINCE DECEMBER.
WE FALL TO 4 O'CLOCK TOMORROW
NIGHT AND THEN WE'RE AT THE
FREEZING MARK BY EARLY FRIDAY.
ANY WARMUP WE GET WE'RE RIGHT
BACK DOWN TO THAT FREEZING
MARK AS WE END YOUR FRIDAY.
HERE'S A LOOK AT EARLY
SATURDAY MORNING, TEMPERATURES
IN THE 20'S, MAYBE EVEN SOME
TEENS NORTH AND WEST.
WE'LL HAVE A LOOK AT THAT
WEEKEND FORECAST STILL COMING
UP IN MY SEVEN-DAY.
BLAKE AND ANGIE.
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>>> YOU CAN TELL IT'S
VALENTINE'S WEEK BECAUSE
EVERYTHING IS LOVE RELATED
THIS WEEK.
>> DO YOU LIKE MY EARRINGS.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> LITTLE HEARTS.
>> STILL TO COME LITTLE
ROMANCE IN THE OFFICE IS NOT
UNCOMMON.
IN FACT, A NEW STUDY REVEALS
JUST HOW MANY ADMIT TO A
WORKPLACE CRUSH AND HOW MANY
HAVE ACTED ON THOSE FEELINGS.
GET YOUR PHONES OUT.
THIS IS OUR FOX5 INSTAPOLL.
EXPERIENCE IN THE OFFICE WHEN
WE RETURN.
Can my side be firm?
And my side super soft?
Yes. With the Sleep Number 360
smart bed, on sale now,
you can both adjust your comfort
with your sleep number setting.
Can it help me
fall asleep faster?
Yes, by gently
warming your feet.
But can it help
keep me asleep?
Absolutely, it intelligently
senses your movements and
automatically adjusts to
keep you both comfortable.
So, you can really
promise better sleep?
Not promise. Prove.
And now, during the Ultimate
Sleep Number Event,
save 50% on the
Sleep Number 360 Limited
Edition smart bed.
Plus 0% interest for 24
months on all smart beds.
Only for a limited time.
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
>> MARINA MARRACO WITH A LOOK
AT WHAT'S TRENDING TODAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO START THIS
VALENTINE'S DAY WEEK TALKING
ABOUT NIGHTMARES.
HERE ARE WHAT AMERICANS ARE
DREAMING ABOUT AND THESE ARE
THE MOST COMMON ONES.
YOU'RE FALLING IS THE NUMBER
ONE ON THE LIST.
>> YOU'RE FALLING.
>> YOU CAN'T WALK STRAIGHT
YOU'RE TIPPING OVER.
>> SIGN YOU'RE PROBABLY LOSING
CONTROL, YOU DON'T FEEL IN
CONTROL OF THINGS.
>> PSYCHO ANALYST BLAKE
McCOY.
KEEP THEM COMING.
WHAT ABOUT BEING CHASED IN
DEATH, THAT'S NUMBER TWO.
>> OKAY.
>> BLAKE.
>> YOU ASKING ME WHAT THAT
MEANS.
>> YOU'RE PSYCHO ANALYZING SO
PLEASE DR. McCOY LET US KNOW
MOST PEOPLE DREAM ABOUT BEING
LATE.
JOURNALISTS ARE MORE LIKE TO
HAVE DREAMS ABOUT MISSING
DEADLINES.
I THINK IT SPEAKS TO THE
PRESSURES YOU'RE UNDER.
I HAVE THIS RECURRING BAD
DREAM THAT MY TEETH ARE
FALLING OUT.
>> SAME HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT
MEANS.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN
DR. McCOY.
>> YOUR HUSBAND IS A DENTIST
MUCH THAT'S A WEIRD DREAM TO
HAVE WITH A DENTIST HUSBAND.
>> I DON'T KNOW, HE --
>> MAYBE YOU WANT MORE
ATTENTION FROM HIM.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT HIM
WORKING.
>> PSYCHOANALYSIS.
>> DEFINITELY, THE TEETH ONE.
>> AND FAILING MATH CLASS.
>> BUT I ALSO GRIND MY TEETH
TOO SO I WONDER IF THAT HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> MAYBE.
COULD BE.
>> YOUR FEAR IS THAT YOU'RE
GRINDING YOUR TEETH TOO MUCH.
ANYWAY, GO AHEAD.
>> VALENTINE'S DAY IS FRIDAY
AS YOU KNOW.
AND YEAH, A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
WONDERING IS IT APPROPRIATE TO
CRUSH ON SOMEONE AT WORK
BECAUSE APPARENTLY YOU'RE NOT
ALONE.
SURVEY FOUND 54 PERCENT OF
AMERICAN WORKERS ADMITTED
THEY'VE HAD A CRUSH ON A
CO-WORKER.
THE SURVEY FOUND 41 PERCENT
HAD BEEN ASKED OUT BY A
CO-WORKER AND 27 PERCENT TOOK
THEM UP ON THAT DATE OFFER.
I GUESS IT BEGS THE QUESTION
IS IT APPROPRIATE TO HAVE A
WORKPLACE ROMANCE.
>> I THINK A WORKPLACE CRUSH
IS OKAY.
I THINK THAT KEEPS WORK
INTERESTING YOU TALK TO YOUR
CO-WORKER.
>> IT GIVES YOU MOTIVATION TO
SHOW UP.
[LAUGHTER]
>> BUT YOU SHOULDN'T ACT ON
IT.
THAT IS A RECIPE FOR DISASTER
I THINK.
>> YEAH, BUT I HAVE SEEN IT
WHERE IT HAS WORKED OUT
BETWEEN COUPLES, TOO.
SO IT COULD GO EITHER WAY.
IT'S UP TO THE INDIVIDUAL BUT
IT CAN GET MESSY AND I'M NOT
SHOCKED BY THIS BECAUSE WHEN
YOU ARE RESTRICTED TO ONE
PLACE -- PEOPLE START --
>> SPENDING 10 HOURS A DAY
WITH THE SAME PERSON.
>> THEY START LOOKING GOOD.
>> YOU AND I SIT ACROSS FROM
EACH OTHER ALL DAY.
>> I KNOW AND I LOVE YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> ALL RIGHT, WOW.
THIS IS A 4:00 P.M. NEWSCAST.
[LAUGHTER]
>> NOT 11:00 P.M.
SAVE IT FOR LATER.
>> WHAT DO THE PEOPLE THINK.
>> MARINA DOESN'T LIVE IN
VIRGINIA.
>> OUR INSTAPOLL TODAY, IS IT
OKAY TO HAVE A WORKPLACE
ROMANCE.
[LAUGHTER]
>>> LET US KNOW WHAT YOU
THINK.
VOTE ON FOX5DC.COM OR THE FOX5
D.C. APP AND IT LOOKS LIKE
RIGHT NOW MOST OF OUR VIEWERS
ARE SPLIT ON THIS ISSUE.
>> SEE.
>> KEEP THOSE VOTES COMING.
THEY'LL REVISIT THIS QUESTION.
>> THEY DON'T LIKE BILL 69,
EITHER.
>> IT IS -- STILL TO COME HERE
AT 4:00 HOW DOES THIS HAPPEN?
A FAMILY SERVICES WORKER TOOK
THE WRONG STUDENT FROM A D.C.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
WE'RE TALKING TO THE CHILD'S
MOTHER ABOUT HOW THAT MIXUP
HAPPENED.
>> ♪
>> LOOK AT SOME OF THE TOP
STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING.
FIRST UP A MONTGOMERY COUNTY
WOMAN KNOWN FOR USING A FIRE
BATON DURING PERFORMANCES WAS
CRITICALLY INJURED WHEN HER
CLOTHING CAUGHT FIRE.
THE WOMAN WENT UP IN FLAMES
YESTERDAY AFTERNOON ON SUMMIT
AVENUE IN KENSINGTON.
ANOTHER MAN WAS TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL WITH BURNS.
OFFICIAL SAY THE FIRE CAUSED
ABOUT $10,000 IN DAMAGE.
>> IN THE DISTRICT, POLICE
WANT YOU TO TAKE A LOOK AT TWO
MEN SUSPECTED OF HOLDING UP A
GAS STATION.
IT HAPPENED LAST WEEK ON
KENILWORTH AVENUE IN
NORTHEAST.
BOTH SUSPECTS DREW HANDGUNS
AND DEMANDED MONEY FROM THE
CASHIER.
IF YOU RECOGNIZE THESE MEN
FROM THESE PHOTOS YOU COULD
EARN A REWARD FOR INFORMATION
THAT LEADS TO A CONVICTION.
>> WE'RE LEARNING MONTGOMERY
COUNTY POLICE DETECTIVES WERE
INVOLVED IN A DEADLY SHOOTING
OF A FUGITIVE IN VIRGINIA
BEACH.
IT WAS PART OF A U.S. MARSHALS
OPERATION TO GET A WANTED
FUGITIVE EARLY THIS MORNING.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE SAY
THOSE DETECTIVES WERE WORKING
ON A COLD CASE BUT NO FURTHER
DETAILS HAVE BEEN GIVEN.
WE ARE ALSO AWAITING MORE
DETAILS ABOUT THE SHOOTING
FROM VIRGINIA BEACH POLICE.
>> DEVELOPING IN THE DISTRICT,
ANOTHER INVESTIGATION INTO AN
AUTHORIZED PERSON TAKING A
CHILD OUT OF A D.C. SCHOOL.
BUT THIS TIME WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT AN EIGHT-YEAR-OLD SECOND
GRADER.
THE ADULT WAS A CHILD FAMILY
SERVICES WORKER WHO PICKED UP
THE WRONG KID.
FOX5's STEPHANIE RAMIREZ
JOINS US LIVE FROM HARRIET
TUBMAN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
NORTHWEST D.C.
THIS IS THE SCHOOL WHERE IT
HAPPENED.
STEPHANIE, FIRST OFF, HOW IS
THE CHILD DOING?  IS THE KID
OKAY?
>> Reporter: YEAH, THE
PARENTS TELL ME THEIR
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD SON HE DOES NOT
WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL, HE IS
THAT TRAUMATIZED AND SCARED BY
WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
THE INCIDENT ABOUT TWO WEEKS
AGO IS WHEN THIS HAPPENED.
AND THAT'S HOW SCARED THIS KID
IS.
SO, JANUARY 31ST IS THE DAY
THAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THIS IS WHEN D.C.P.S. AREN'T AND
POLICE SAY THE MIXUP OCCURRED.
WE'RE TOLD A D.C. CHILD AND
FAMILY SERVICES WORKER WENT TO
HARRIET TUBMAN ELEMENTARY TO
PICK UP A KID SCHEDULED FOR A
VISITATION MEETING WITH A
PARENT.
CSFA SAYS THE SCHOOL HANDED
OVER A CHILD WITH THE SAME
FIRST NAME BUT NOT THE SAME
LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS THE WRONG KID.
CHILD AND FAMILY SERVICES
AGENCY TOLD FOX5 IN PART OF A
WRITTEN RESPONSE THAT THE
CHILD WAS NEVER IN ANY DANGER
THE ENTIRE INCIDENT TOOK PLACE
OVER AN HOUR OR LESS.
THE MISTAKE WAS REALIZED.
THE CHILD WAS RETURNED AND NO
CHILDREN WERE IN DANGER.
NOW, I CAN TELL YOU WHEN I
TALKED TO THE EIGHT-YEAR-OLD'S
MOTHER SHE EXPERIENCED
SOMETHING VERY DIFFERENT.
SHE WAS VERY UPSET TELLING US
THAT SHE ALMOST HAD A PANIC
ATTACK.
WE HAVE SOME OF HER SOUND.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I WAS SO SCARED.
I WAS PANICKED.
I WAS CRYING.
I ALMOST HAD A AS MARKS,
ASTHMA, ALMOSTHAD A ASTHMA ATTA.
IT WAS SCARY.
LIKE THAT'S MY SON.
>> Reporter: AND I CAN TELL
YOU WE ASKED HER HOW SHE FEELS
ABOUT THE SCHOOL HANDLING THIS
SITUATION.
SHE TELLS US THAT SHE DOES
FEEL THEY HANDLED IT
APPROPRIATELY.
THEY DID SEND OUT A LETTER
SAYING THEY'RE GOING THE
REINFORCE A LOT OF SECURITY
POLICIES INCLUDING WHEN YOU
SIGN CHILDREN OUT BUT SHE'S
UPSET AT HOW THE CHILD SERVICE
AGENCY IS HANDLING THIS AND
SHE WANTS SOMETHING TO CHANGE.
GUYS BACK TO YOU.
>> I WANT TO GO BACK TO THE
SCHOOL THOUGH BECAUSE I WOULD
LIKE TO KNOW HOW THEY ARE
RESPONDING.
WHAT HAVE THEY SAID AT THIS
POINT?
>> Reporter: WELL, THEY SAID
A WHOLE BULLET LIST OF THINGS
THEY WANT TO DO BUT AT THE END
OF THE DAY THEY DID HAND OVER
THE WRONG CHILD.
WE ALSO ASKED THE CHILD AGENCY
ABOUT THIS, IF THEY WERE GOING
TO CHANGE ANY POLICIES AND
INTERESTINGLY I WAS TOLD THEIR
WORKER FOLLOWED THEIR POLICY
AND I GOT A LITTLE BIT MORE
ABOUT THAT.
THIS INCLUDES GIVING A PAPER
THAT HAS THE CORRECT CHILD'S
FIRST AND LAST NAME IN IT.
WHETHER IT WAS CHECKED AGAIN
WHEN THE CHILD WAS HANDED
OVER.
GUYS.
>> AALL RIGHT, STEPHANIE
RAMIREZ FOR US.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ♪
>> STILL TO COME, OLYMPIAN
SIMONE BILES SAYS SHE IS DONE
COMPETING AGAINST IMPOSSIBLE
BEAUTY STANDARDS.
THE GYMNAST SHARES A POWERFUL
MESSAGE OF SELF ACCEPTANCE
COMING UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT HOW
THE ROADS ARE SHAPING UP
AROUND THE DMV RIGHT NOW.
A LIVE LOOK AT THE ROADWAYS
RIGHT HERE.
WHAT DO WE GOT?  LET'S SEE
HERE.
IS THAT 395.
YUP, 395 TRAFFIC FREE FLOWING
BUT VOLUME BUILDING.
WE'RE BACK AFTER THIS.
>> ♪
OBAMA: He's been a leader
throughout the country for the
past twelve years,
Mr. Michael Bloomberg is here.
VO: Leadership in action.
Mayor Bloomberg and
President Obama worked together
in the fight for gun safety
laws,
to improve education, and to
develop innovative ways to help
teens gain the skills needed to
find good jobs.
OBAMA: At a time
when Washington is divided in
old ideological battles he shows
us what can be achieved when
we bring people together
to seek pragmatic solutions.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
>> ♪
>> VALENTINE'S DAY JUST TWO
DAYS AWAY.
LOVE IS IN THE AIR.
ANGIE IS WEARING HOT PINK.
>> THIS IS MY WEDDING SONG.
>> WAS IT REALLY?
>> UH-HUH INGRID MICHAELSON,
UH-HUH, YES.
>> SPEAKING OF YOUR WEDDING
SONG YOUR LOVE OF YOUR LIFE
JOINED YOU ON GOOD DAY THIS
MORNING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY WERE DOING THE GREATEST
LOVE SEGMENT.
AND MY HUSBAND ORIGINALLY SAID
NO BUT I FORCED HIM TO COME
ON.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I SAID THIS IS ROBERT AND
HE IS A DAUGHTER MAGNET AS YOU
CAN TELL AND HE'S VERY
ROMANTIC AS YOU CAN TELL,
VERY, VERY GENITAL.
GENTLE.
HE WORKS IN SOUTH CAROLINA.
WE TALKED WITH ALLISON SEYMOUR
ABOUT HOW THE JOURNEY TO
HAPPILY EVER AFTER HAS BEEN
QUITE THE BALANCING ACT TRYING
TO DO FROM IT TWO DIFFERENT
STATES.
>> THIS IS THE GREATEST STORY,
GREATEST LOVE STORY OF ALL
TIME.
>> PLEASE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SHOW THE LOVE.
I ALWAYS TELL PEOPLE THERE'S A
BOOK TO WRITE IT'S CALLED GET
MARRIED, LIVE APART.
>> YES.
>> IT'S A WINNING RECIPE.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE DID.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> YOU WOULD AGREE.
>> NO, IT DID WORK, IT DID
WORK.
WHEN WE GOT ENGAGED AND SHE
GOT A JOB IN D.C. I THOUGHT IT
WAS A LITTLE ODD TO START OUT
A MARRIAGE IN A LONG DISTANCE
RELATIONSHIP BUT 12 YEARS
LATER, THREE KIDS LATER.
>> YOU GUYS MET UP AT SOME
POINT.
>> OH, YEAH WE DID.
>> THOSE THREE BEAUTIFUL KIDS.
>> THOSE WERE PENCILED IN.
THE FIRST ONE WASN'T.
THE FIRST ONE WAS A SURPRISE.
>> ANGIE IS SO VISIBLE AND
HIGH ENERGY.
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE DIFFERENT,
LIKE YOU'RE A PRIVATE PERSON
AND A PUBLIC PERSON BUT HOW DO
YOU DEAL WITH THAT?  I MEAN,
CAN YOU GO ANYWHERE WITH THIS
LADY.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE VERY
PATIENT.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S GREAT, SHE'S GREAT.
>> SOUNDS LIKE WHAT MY WORK
HUSBAND WOULD SAY, TOO.
VERY PATIENT.
>> YEAH YEAH.
>> NO, THE ONE THING WE DID
TALK ABOUT IS HOW AND IT'S A
QUESTION WE GET ASKED A LOT
HOW DO YOU MAKE IT WORK FOR
YEARS LIVING APART AND I THINK
IT'S WITH ANY RELATIONSHIP IS
JUST NOT DEPENDING ON THE
OTHER PERSON FOR YOUR
HAPPINESS.
AND THINKING THEY'RE GOING TO
CHANGE YOUR PERSONAL HAPPINESS
FOREVER.
IT REALLY -- YOU HAVE TO HAVE
THAT WITHIN YOURSELF AND I
THINK THAT'S BEEN THE SECRET
RECIPE FOR US LASTING THIS
LONG, 12 YEARS.
>> WE'LL HAVE MY LOVE STORY
COMING UP IN 2025 SO STAY
TUNED FOR THAT.
>> I'M THE GATEKEEPER THOUGH.
GOT TO GET THROUGH ME FIRST.
>> LOOKS LIKE ACTOR JUSSIE
SMOLLETT IS WRAPPED UP IN TWO
LEGAL BATTLES NOW STEMMING
FROM HIS ALLEGED ATTACK IN
CHICAGO LAST YEAR.
WE'RE TALKING TO TMZ ABOUT
THAT.
>> PLUS, OKAY, THE SUPER BOWL
WE KNOW THAT IT'S OVER BUT
PEOPLE CAN'T LET IT GO.
THEY'RE STILL TALKING ABOUT
THE HALFTIME SHOW.
NOW Y L J-LO IS RESPONDING TO TE
CRITICS WHO CALLED IT TOO
SEXY.
>> THERE WERE A LOT OF
CRITICS.
>> WHY DID IT TAKE SO LONG.
>> WE'VE MOVED ON.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT PEOPLE
THINK ANY MORE.
WE HAD AWARDS SHOWS AND SO
MANY OTHER THINGS HAPPEN IN
THE NEWS SINCE THEN.
BLAKE I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
YOUR WHERE ARE THEY NOW LOVE
STORIES 2025.
>> I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
THAT, TOO.
IT COULD GO MANY DIFFERENT
DIRECTIONS CAITLIN.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, IT'S ALL UP
TO YOU BLAKE.
IT'S HOWEVER YOU WANT IT TO
LOOK, THAT'S THE GREATEST
PART.
>>> ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE LOTS TO
TALK ABOUT HERE.
SHOWERS MOVING IN RIGHT NOW.
THAT WILL BE A WET START TO
YOUR THURSDAY FOLLOWED BY SOME
WIND AND THEN FOLLOWED BY SOME
COLD SO BREAK IT ALL DOWN FOR
YOU IN YOUR FULL SEVEN-DAY
FORECAST WHEN FOX5 RETURNS.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
>> LOCAL MAN ABOUT TO
EXPERIENCE FREEDOM FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN ALMOST 25 YEARS.
>> SARAH SIMMONS HAS MORE ON
THAT.
>> NEW AT 5:00 THIS IS A CRAZY
STORY.
A D.C. MAN CONVICTED IN 1994
DOUBLE MURDER IS ABOUT TO GET
OUT OF PRISON AFTER
INVESTIGATORS FOUND A HIDDEN
NOTE ABOUT ANOTHER SUSPECT.
AND THEY ARE MEANT TO KEEP
STUDENTS SAFE BUT ARE ACTIVE
SHOOTER DRILLS REALLY DOING
MORE HARM THAN GOOD?  WHY SOME
TEACHERS WANT THEM TO BE A
THING OF THE PAST.
PLUS, A DANGEROUS DEFECT
PROMPTS A POPULAR AUTOMAKER TO
RECALL ONE OF ITS BEST SELLING
CARS.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW BEFORE
GETTING BEHIND THE WHEEL.
THAT'S ALL NEXT AT 5:00.
>> NOT THE HONDA ODYSSEY.
>> MY PARENTS JUST GOT A NEW
ONE A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
>> MY PARENTS HAVE A HONDA
ODYSSEY.
MY DAD HE'S HAD IT FOR 12
YEARS.
NEVER HAD TO TAKE IT TO THE
SHOP FOR ANYTHING.
IT'S HIS PRIDE AND JOY.
OH LOVES THE HONDA ODYSSEY.
>> SOME EVEN HAVE A VACUUM IN
THE BACK.
>> HE'S GOING TO PASS IT DOWN.
THAT'S GOING TO BE YOUR NEXT
CAR.
>> A 20-YEAR-OLD HONDA
ODYSSEY.
>> YUP.
>> THANK YOU SARAH.
>>> SIMONE BILES IS ABOUT A
GOOD COMPETITION ALL ABOUT A
GOOD COMPETITION BUT THERE'S
ONE SHE SAYS SHE'S TIRED OF
BEING THROWN INTO.
THE 22-YEAR-OLD OLYMPIC
MEDALIST SLAMMED TROLLS AND
THOSE WHO CONSTANTLY JUDGE HER
BEAUTY SOMETIMES OVER HER
ATHLETICISM.
SHE TOOK TO INSTAGRAM TO
ADDRESS WHAT SHE CALLED TOXIC
BEAUTY STANDARDS.
SHE SAYS SHE OFTEN LET'S IT
SLIDE BUT SOMETIMES SHE GETS
IT DOWN.
SHE SAYS SHE'S DONE COMPETING
AGAINST BEAUTY STANDARDS AND
ENCOURAGES OTHERS TO DO THE
SAME.
>> ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, SO IT'S BEEN
MORE THAN A WEEK SINCE SUPER
BOWL LIV BUT PEOPLE ARE STILL
TALKING ABOUT THE HALFTIME
SHOW AND NOW J-LO SHE HAD
SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT IT,
SHE'S RESPONDING.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH VARIETY
SHE CALLED THE CRITICISM OF
HER SHOW WITH SHAKIRA
"SILLINESS."
SOME PEOPLE DEEMED IT TOO
RACY.
J-LO SAYS SHE AND SHAKIRA ARE
RESPECTFUL PERFORMERS WHO ARE
MOMS AND CONSCIOUS OF WHAT
THEY DO.
>> EVERYONE HAS GOT AN
OPINION.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST DO YOUR THING.
>> SHE DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO
RESPOND.
>> WE TALKED ABOUT IT EARLIER
AND NOW TMZ IS WEIGHING IN.
JUSSIE SMOLLETT NOW FIGHTING
TWO LEGAL BATTLES.
YESTERDAY TWO CHARGES CRIMINAL
CHARGES FILED AGAINST THE
ACTOR AND NOW THE CITY OF
CHICAGO SAYS IT'S STILL DOING
ITS OWN CIVIL LAWSUIT TO GET
MONEY FROM HIM.
LAURA LAROSA IS JOINING US
LIVE FROM THEIR NEWSROOM IN
LOS ANGELES.
HE'S NOW FACING TWO
CRIMINAL -- TWO LEGAL
CHALLENGES IN CHICAGO.
>> YES, YES.
SO, ON THE CIVIL SIDE, THIS
LAWSUIT BROUGHT BY THE CITY OF
CHICAGO IS BASICALLY TO FIND
HIM AT FAULT FOR THE MONEY
THEY SPENT WHILE TRYING TO
INVESTIGATE THIS WHOLE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT INCIDENT IN THE FIRST
PLACE.
JUSSIE WILL BE USING HIS RIGHT
TO NOT TAKE THE STAND AND
INCRIMINATE HIMSELF DURING THE
CIVIL LAWSUIT.
NOW, IN ILLINOIS, THIS IS THE
THING, IF A DEFENDANT PLEADS
THE FIFTH, THE JUDGE CAN TELL
THE JURY TO CONCLUDE THAT A
DEFENDANT IS HIDING SOMETHING.
NOW, WE ALSO KNOW THAT THE --
RIGHT.
THE BROTHERS WILL BE
TESTIFYING.
THEY WILL BE TESTIFYING THAT
THIS WHOLE THING WAS A SETUP
AND IT WAS ALL SET UP BY
JUSSIE SMOLLETT SO VERY
INTERESTING TO SEE HOW THIS
WILL PLAY OUT FOR JUSSIE.
>> DO WE KNOW HOW MUCH THE
CITY OF CHICAGO IS TRYING TO
GET FROM JUSSIE IN THECIVIL
LAWSUIT?
>> I'M NOT FOR SURE OF THE
NUMBER BUT WE HAVE REPORTED
IT.
IT'S NOT ANYTHING SMALL AS YOU
CAN IMAGINE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IN THE -- THE CRAZY
THING ABOUT THIS IS THAT THE
CITY OF CHICAGO COULD HAVE
CHOSEN TO NOT PURSUE THIS
CIVIL LAWSUIT ANYMORE BECAUSE,
OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, IT WOULD
HAVE SAVED THEM MONEY ON END
TO NOT PURSUE IT BUT THEY
CHOSE TO MOVE FORWARD.
>> THE CIVIL LAWSUIT HAS BEEN
IN THE WORKS FOR SOME TIME.
SO THAT'S GOING TO BE GOING TO
TRIAL SOONER THAN THE
CRIMINAL.
THAT'S GOING TO TRIAL SOON.
>> Y-I'M ASSUMING SO.
THE NEW INDICTMENT JUST CAME
YESTERDAY WITH THE NEW SIX
COUNTS.
I'M ASSUMING THIS CIVIL
LAWSUIT WILL COME UP FIRST
WHICH IS WHY JUSSIE FEELS LIKE
HE DOESN'T WANT TO GET ON THE
STAND AND SAY ANYTHING BECAUSE
ANYTHING HE SAYS ESPECIALLY
UNDER OATH CAN BE USED MOVING
FORWARD IN THAT SECOND TRIAL.
SO --
>> AALL RIGHT, LAUREN LAROSA.
I THOUGHT WE WERE DONE WITH
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
BUT I GUESS IT'S ALL COMING
BACK.
IT'S ALL RESTARTING HERE IN
2020.
>> YEAH, JUSSIE -- I MEAN, HE
HAS TO GO TO THESE COURT CASES
SO WE'LL BE TALKING ABOUT HIM
FOR A LITTLE WHILE COMING UP
AS WELL, TOO, SO GET
COMFORTABLE.
>> WE'RE RELYING ON YOU TO
FOLLOW ALL THE DETAILS FOR US.
LAUREN LAROSA THANK YOU.
TMZ AIRS AT 7:30 ON FOX5 RIGHT
AFTER "LIKE IT OR NOT."
>> THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO, NOW A TIME TO CHECK ON OUR
WEATHER ON THIS WEDNESDAY.
AS WE TAKE A LIVE LOOK OUT AT
GAITHERSBURG AND TRAFFIC JUST
INCHING ALONG THERE.
CAITLIN YOU SAID IT WAS COMING
AND NOW WE'RE ALREADY SEEING
SOME SHOWERS, HM?
>> YEAH, A LITTLE BIT ANGIE.
NOTHING TOO HEAVY JUST QUITE
YET BUT A SLOW GO THERE ON 270
AS THE EVENING COMMUTE BEGINS.
AND YES, WE'LL HAVE SHOWERS
FILLING IN TONIGHT ALTHOUGH
EVERYTHING TONIGHT LOOKS VERY
LIGHT.
I DON'T THINK WE SEE MUCH
STEADY RAIN UNTIL THE COMMUTE
TOMORROW MORNING.
BUT IT WILL BE IMPACTING THE
THURSDAY MORNING COMMUTE.
SO, SHOWERS ARE MOVING IN
RIGHT NOW.
THE STEADIEST OF THE RAIN WILL
PROBABLY BE BETWEEN ABOUT 6:00
A.M. AND NOON TOMORROW AS A
COLD FRONT WORKS ITS WAY
THROUGH.
BEHIND THAT FRONT WE WILL
ACTUALLY BE MILD TOMORROW
AFTERNOON BUT WINDS WILL BE
PICKING UP AND THEN WE'LL BE
MUCH COLDER BY TOMORROW NIGHT.
SO, WE'LL KIND OF SPIKE AND
THEN WE'RE QUICKLY GOING TO
FALL WHEN IT COMES TO OUR
TEMPERATURES.
OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW, IT'S BEEN A
PRETTY CHILLY DAY.
CLOUDS BEING REPORTED AT ALL
THREE AIRPORTS, EVEN A LITTLE
BIT OF LIGHT RAIN AT DULLES
AND LAST HOUR DULLES EVEN
REPORTED SOME SLEET.
THAT DESPITE THE FACT THAT
IT'S 44 DEGREES THERE.
IT'S 49 IN REAGAN, 46 AT BWI
SO A LITTLE BIT OF MIXING FAR
NORTH AND WEST.
AND STORM TRACKER RADAR SHOWS
A TINY BIT OF PURPLE AND PINK
MOSTLY MIXING IN ALONG THE
MASON-DIXON LINE AS WE
TRANSITION OVER TO ALL RAIN
BUT AT LEAST AT THE ONSET WE
HAD IN BOTH LOUDOUN COUNTY AND
FAIRFAX COUNTY SOME REPORTS OF
SLEET.
YOU COULD SEE THESE SHOWERS
OVERHEAD.
VERY WIDELY SCATTERED AND VERY
LIGHT SO IT SHOULDN'T BE
ANYTHING THAT SLOWS YOU DOWN
TOO MUCH THIS EVENING AND I'LL
INCLUDE EVEN AREAS BACK OFF
TOWARDS OUR NORTH AND WEST,
HAGERSTOWN AND CUMBERLAND IN
THAT.
EVERYTHING LOOKS PRETTY LIGHT
EVEN THOUGH YOU MAY SEE WET
SNOWFLAKES AND SLEET MIXING IN
UP THERE.
FOR THE REST OF THE EVENING
TEMPERATURES WILL BE MAINLY IN
THE MID 40'S.
YES, SHOWERS WILL FILL IN MORE
LATER TONIGHT, SO YOU KNOW,
EVENING PLANNER JUST CLOUDY
SKIES, 45 WITH A FEW SPRINKLES
AT 7 O'CLOCK.
44 WITH LIGHT RAIN.
HERE'S FUTURECST.
OVER THE NEXT FEW HOURS VERY
LIGHT SCATTERED SHOWERS THIS
EVENING.
THAT CONTINUES THROUGH THE
11 O'CLOCK MIDNIGHT HOUR.
NOTICE BY 6:00 A.M. IT LOOKS A
LITTLE STEADIER OVERHEAD AND
YOU HAVE POCKETS OF HEAVY RAIN
BACK WEST OF THE MOUNTAINS.
THAT'S THE COLD FRONT
APPROACHING AND MOVING
THROUGH.
SO RAIN AND MAYBE EVEN SOME
GUSTY WINDS AT TIMES
ESPECIALLY THE SECOND HALF OF
THE COMMUTE, 8, 9 O'CLOCK AS
THE STEADIEST PART IS PUSHING
THROUGH.
NOT EXACTLY CALLING FOR
TORNADOES LIKE LAST FRIDAY
MORNING WHEN A FRONTAL SYSTEM
MOVED THROUGH BUT IT COULD BE
RATHER GUSTY AT TIMES AND RAIN
COULD BE STEADY.
ONCE THE SHOWERS WORK THROUGH
IN THE AFTERNOON LOOK AT
TEMPERATURES SPIKING.
60 IN D.C. TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
WIND WILL BE GUSTING OUT OF
THE SOUTH UNTIL WE TRANSITION
OVER TO NORTHWESTERN WINDS.
BUT A WIDE VARIETY OF
TEMPERATURES.
I MEAN YOU'RE ONLY SEEING LOW
50'S WHERE THAT COLD AIR HAS
WORKED ITS WAY IN.
FREDERICKSBURG CULPEPER
MANASSAS WELL INTO THE 60'S
BUT THIS WILL BE VERY
CHANGEABLE AS COLD AIR WHICH
WE'RE ALREADY SEEING IN THE
NORTHERN PLAINS RIGHT NOW TRUE
ARCTIC AIR MASS COMES JUST
BLOWING IN LATE TOMORROW NIGHT
AND THROUGH THE DAY ON FRIDAY.
SO, IT WILL FEEL, IF YOU'RE
OUT LATE THURSDAY NIGHT, VERY
DIFFERENT BY ABOUT 11 O'CLOCK.
YOU KNOW, WINDS ARE GUSTING
AND TEMPERATURES ARE FALLING
INTO THE 40'S.
THEY'LL BE IN THE 30'S BY
FRIDAY MORNING AND HERE'S A
LOOK AT THOSE FORECASTED WIND
CHILLS.
20'S HERE IN D.C.
THE REAL CRUX OF THIS COLD AIR
WELL BACK ACROSS THE UPPER
MIDWEST BUT THIS IS SOMETHING
WE HAVEN'T SEEN MUCH OF THIS
WINTER.
AMAZING.
VERY COLD WIND CHILLS FOR THE
GREAT LAKES.
GREEN BAY OVER TOWARDS THE
TWIN CITIES ON THE ORDER OF 10
TO 20 TO 30 DEGREES BELOW
ZERO, THAT'S WHAT IT WILL FEEL
LIKE.
WE'LL HAVE THE COLDEST WIND
CHILLS PROBABLY BY SOMETIME
FRIDAY NIGHT INTO SATURDAY
MORNING.
SATURDAY LOOKS VERY COLD.
WEEKEND OUTLOOK, WE'LL START
THE DAY IN THE 20'S, HIT JUST
38 FOR A HIGH TEMPERATURE.
BUT THIS IS A VERY SHORT LIVED
BLAST BECAUSE BY SUNDAY
AFTERNOON, WE ARE ALREADY BACK
IN THE 50'S.
IT'S JUST HARD TO HAVE WINTER
WEATHER AROUND HERE.
WE HAVEN'T HAD MUCH SNOW, WE
REALLY HAVEN'T HAD MUCH COLD
AND YOUR SEVEN-DAY SHOWS ANY
LITTLE SIGNS OF WINTER WE GET
QUICKLY ERASED AS 50'S ARE
BACK SUNDAY WE LOOK VERY MILD
AS WE HEAD INTO NEXT WEEK WITH
MORE CHANCE OF SHOWERS THERE
BY TUESDAY.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN-DAY, BLAKE
AND ANGIE.
BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> STILL TO COME SHE WAS
CROWNED THE WORLD'S TOP DOG.
BUT APPARENTLY SIBA THE POODLE
IS A BIT OF A PICKY EATER.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR WHAT SHE
CHOWED DOWN ON BEFORE WINNING
BEST IN SHOW.
>> LOOK AT THAT COAT.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
MIKE: Anyone hear the slogan,
'Mike Will Get It Done?'
OK, let me tell
you what the 'it' is.
As Mayor,
I expanded healthcare coverage.
As President,
I'll build on Obamacare
because healthcare is a right.
I created nearly
500,000 jobs in New York City.
As President,
I'll build an economy
that delivers good jobs
with higher wages.
I'll take on the gun lobby
and save lives.
And I will stop Trump's assault
on women's reproductive rights.
I've got a record
of doing things.
I've got the resources
to take on this fight.
As mayor,
I held myself
accountable for results.
As President,
I'll offer common sense plans
and I will get it done.
So let's stay on the offensive,
and let's win.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> ♪
>> OKAY, A WOMAN'S WEDDING
RING, IT ENDED UP IN HER DOG'S
BELLY.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THEY HAD AN X-RAY TO PROVE
THIS.
STEPHANIE LAMB WALKED AWAY
AFTER SETTING HER WEDDING AND
ENGAGEMENT RINGS ON COFFEE
TABLE.
WHEN SHE RETURNED THE RINGS
WERE GONE MUCH SHE HAD A
SNEAKING SUSPICION HER DOG WAS
TO BLAME.
SHE TOOK HIM TO THE VET AND
SURE ENOUGH VOILA X-RAYS SHOW
THE RINGS IN THE BELLY.
THE RINGS HAD TO BE SURGICALLY
REMOVED AND THE DOG IS DOING
JUST FINE SO LAST TIME SHE
PROBABLY LEAVE THOSE LAYING
AROUND.
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S NOTHING
WORSE THAN HAVING TO COMPETE
ON AN EMPTY STOMACH BUT THAT'S
THE EXACT SITUATION THE
WINNING DOG OF THE WESTMINSTER
KENNEL CLUB SHOW FOUND HERSELF
IN.
THERE WAS NOT ANY AVAILABLE AT
THE EVENT SO HER OWNER POPPED
OVER TO A MCDONALD'S AFTER C
CHOKING DOWN ON CHICKEN
NUGGETS SHE WENT ON TO WIN THE
NON SPORINGT GROUP AND BEST IN
SHOW.
BEST IN SHOW, ON A STOMACH
FULL OF CHICKEN NUGGETS,
MCDONALD'S CHICKEN SNUG JETS
IN YOU KNOW HE'LL BE THE
SPOKESPERSON NOW FOR
MCDONALD'S.
>>  SIBA.
>>  YES.
>> NOW IF THAT DOESN'T MAKE
YOU SMILE [ BABY GIGGLING ]
[ LAUGHTER ].
>>  OH, MY GOSH THAT IS SO
CUTE.
YEAH, IT REMIND ME OF THE
PERSON WHO TORE PAIN AIRPORT
BABY COULD NOT STOP LAUGHING.
SO MOMMY THERE TRYING TO
PRETEND TO SNEEZING DURING
BENTON HE CANNOT HANDLE IT.
HE'S LIKE IN STITCHES ABOUT TO
ROLL OUT OF HIS HIGHCHAIR
CRACKING UP EVERY TIME.
THE VIDEO GARNERED MILLIONS OF
VIEWS YOU CAN SEE WHY.
THAT'S INSTANT HAPPINESS AND
MOOD BOOST SEEING THAT.
SOMETHING SO SIMPLE.
>> THANKS, EVERYBODY FOR
JOINING US HERE AT 4 P.M.
>>  YOUR NEWS AT 5 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 5:00, "FOX5"
GETTING ANSWERS AFTER I GUN AN
AMMUNITION TURN UP AT A
MARYLAND HIGH SCHOOL.
>>  AN A FAMILY SERVICES
WORKER PICKS UP THE WRONG
STUDENT FROM A LOCAL
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND NOW THE
CHILD'S MOTHER IS SPEAKING TO
"FOX5".
>> I WAS SO SQUARED.
I WAS PANICKED.
>>  AND VIRGINIA MAY BE FOR
MARRIED LOVERS AND THERE'S A
FOUSH MAKE IT LEGAL FOR
UNMARRIED PEOPLE IN THE
COMMONWEALTH TO HAVE SEX.
WHY HAS IT TAKEN SO LONG.
YOUR NEWS STARTS RIGHTS NOW.
OFF THE TOP A DEVELOPING RIGHT
NOW "FOX5" TIMELY GETTING
ANSWERS AFTER I STUDENT
BROUGHT A GUN TO A MONTGOMERY
COUNTY SCHOOL.
>>  AND NOW THAT STUDENTS AND
FOUR OTHERS CLARKSBURG HIGH
ARE UNDER ARREST.
"FOX5" IKE EJIOCKH IS IN
CLARKSBURG TONIGHT WITH THE
LATEST.
IKE EJIOCKH.
>>  "FOX5" VIEWERS HAVE ABOUT
COST US NON STOP SINCE
YESTERDAY MORNING TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT HAPPENED HERE
AT CLARKSBURG HIGH SCHOOL.
NOW