OF THE FIVE COUNTS.
THE MOST DAMAGING CONVICTION
FOR THE ASSAULT OF PRODUCTION
ASSISTANT HALEY CARRIES UP TO
25 YEARS BEHIND BARS, THE RAPE
CHARGE CARRIES SENTENCE OF TO
UP FOUR YEARS, THE VERDICT
FOLLOWS WEEKS OF HARROWING
TESTIMONY FROM A STRING OF
ACCUSERS WHO TOLD THE RAPES
FORCED ORAL SEX AND GROPING.
>> VICIOUS SERIAL SEXUAL
PREDITOR WHO USED HIS POWER TO
THREATEN, RAPE, ASSAULT,
TRICK, HUMILIATE, AND SILENCE
HIS VICTIMS.
>> HE'LL BE --
>> IT WILL BE FILED.
>> APPEAL WILL BE FILED.
>> WHILE WEINSTEIN DID NOT
TESTIFY HIS LAWYERS CONTENDED
ANY SEXUAL CONTACT WAS
CONCENTUAL AND HIS ACCUSERS
WENT TO BED TO ADVANCE THEIR
CARREERS, SENTENCING EXCEPT
FOR MARCH 1; CAN GET TO UP 25
YEARS, WE'LL SEE WHAT HE ENDS
UP GETTING ANGIE, BUT ASIDE
FROM BILL COSBY I CAN'T THINK
AFTER BIGGER NAME.
>> YES.
>> TO ACTUALLY BE CONVICTED IN
A.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW, BIG
DEVELOPMENT IN THE STORY THAT
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING SO
CLOSELY, AND OBVIOUSLY MORE TO
COME.
MEANWHILE, ANOTHER STORY THAT
AFFECTS US ALL HERE IS WHAT'S
GOING ON OUTSIDE.
SO, LET'S OPEN UP THAT DOOR,
SHOW YOU A LIVE PICTURE OF
NATIONAL HARBOR.
NOT A BAD WAY TO START THE
WORK WEEK.
>> CAITLIN, AT WHAT POINT CAN
WE SAY GOOD-BYE WINTER HELLO
FLING BECAUSE IT FEELS LIKE IT
OUTSIDE.
>> I THINK WE HAVE ONE MORE
ROUND OF COLD WEATHER HEADED
OUR WAY LATER, AT THE END OF
THE WEEK, AND THEN, BUT BY
THEN, NEXT WEEK, IT IS MARCH.
I THINK THOSE COLD SNAPS WILL
EXIT A WEEK, GIVE IT A WEEK.
>> KEEP THE JACKET HANDY UNTIL
THEN, PLAY ALONG WITH
WINTER'S.
>> I AM RIVAL WE'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT OF THIS BUT EVENTUALLY
IT WILL LEVEL OFF AND WINTER
WHICH HAS BEEN VERY
SPRING-LIKE WILL ROLL MORE
INTO THE SPRING, WE WON'T GET
THOSE COLD SNAPS ANY MORE.
THIS WEEKENDED, UNBELIEVABLE
FOR THE SECOND HALF OF
FEBRUARY.
TODAY, ABSOLUTELY GORGEOUS.
AND YOUR ZERO SIX AGREES HERE
IN THE DISTRICT EVEN LITTLE
SUNSHINE ZERO DESPITE
INCREASING CLOUD COVER TODAY.
FIFTY-NINE OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN SEE IT IS 58 IN
FREDERICKS BERG, 61 IN
FREDERICK, 63 WESTMINSTER, SO
ODDLY TODAY THE NORTHERN TOWNS
THERE, COMING IN WITH THE
WARMEST NUMBERS, LITTLE COOLER
BY THE WATER 51 ANNAPOLIS, 54
IN LEONARDTOWN.
SATELLITE AND RADAR SHOWING
THERE ARE SOME SHOWERS DOWN TO
THE SOUTH.
BACK TO OUR WEST.
THIS IS ALL PART OF SYSTEM
THAT WILL SPREAD SOME RAIN
INTO THE AREA LATER TONIGHT.
IN THE MEANTIME IT IS GREAT
AFTERNOON, BEAUTIFUL EVENING,
NO PROBLEMS FOR THE COMMUTE.
SHOWERS DON'T LOOK TO ARRIVE
UNTIL AFTER MIDNIGHT FOR THE
METRO, BY 11:00 MOVING UP 95,
AND EASTBOUND ON 66.
SO YOU CAN SHE GREEN,
INFRINGING UPON THE METRO.
AFTER MIDNIGT SHOWERS
INCREASE TOMORROW MORNING'S
COMMUTE LOOKS TO BE WET, JUST
RAIN SHOWERS, THOUGH.
AND THEY'LL START TO TAPER OFF
THROUGH THE LATE MORNING,
EARLY AFTERNOON HOURS, BUT I
THINK WE WILL BE STUCK IN THE
CLOUDS, FOG, KIND OF DREARY
TOMORROW.
SO, WHILE WE KEEP KIND OF THE
MILDER TEMPERATURES FOR
TOMORROW, IT IS GOING TO
DEFINITELY AND LITTLE WEATHER
STARTING OFF WITH RAIN
SHOWERS, TEMPERATURES IN THE
40'S, FOG WILL PREVENT THE
TELL FROST JUMPING TOO HIGH
AROUND 50 DEGREES LATER IN THE
AFTERNOON.
COLD BLAST STILL HEADED OUR
WAY TOWARD THE END OF THE
WEEK.
I'LL HAVE A LOOK AT THAT STILL
AHEAD.
>> POLICE IN CHURCH TON
MARYLAND JUST RELEASING VIDEO
OF BIZARRE ASSAULT AT GROCERY
STORE, NOW WE DO WANT TO GAVE
YOU A HEADS UP.
THAT THE VIDEO WE ARE ABOUT TO
SHARE IS DISTURBING.
>> SURVEILLANCE VIDEO HERE
SHOWING THE SUSPECT AT ONE
POINT POKING A WOMAN WITH WHAT
IS BELIEVED, SAW THAT, SAW
THAT REACTION RIGHT THERE.
>> FLINCH.
WHAT JUST SNAPPED.
>> YA, SO,  THIS IS THE DEAL.
THEY THINK THAT HE USED A SIR
INNING TO POKE HER.
SHE IS PUT THAT SHOPPING CART
BACK.
YOU CAN SEE IT REPLAY RIGHT
HERE.
THE SUSPECT AND VICTIM, THEY
HAD THAT BRIEF INTERACTION.
POLICE ARE NOW LOOKING FOR
THIS MAN THAT YOU SEE RIGHT
HERE ON YOUR SCREEN.
WHAT APPEARS TO BE LIKE A BLUE
PULL-OVER.
ANYONE WITH INFORMATION,
YOU'RE ASKED TO CONTACT
POLICE.
>> WHAT A BIZARRE ASSAULT.
>> FREAKY.
>> WE ALSO HAVE MORE ON
ANOTHER CARJACKING.
>> THIS ONE IN ARLINGTON HAS
POLICE RAMP UP PATROLS AT
PENTAGON SEPTEMBER I AND
PENTAGON ROAM TWO SCARY
ENCOUNTERS HAPPEN FRIDAY NIGHT
INSIDE A PARKING GARAGE THERE.
>> AND THEY ARE JUST THE
LATEST IN A STRING OF
INCIDENTS, FOX5 TISHA LEWIS
JOINS US LIVE FROM ARLINGTON,
TEEN, A I REMEMBER IT WAS JUST
A MONTH OR TWO AGO WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT CARJACKING IN
THE SAME PLACE?
>> WELL, BLAKE, ANGIE, HERE WE
GO AGAIN.
AND ATTEMPTED CARJACKING, HERE
AT FASHION CENTER AT PENTAGON
CITY ANOTHER ONE HERE AT
PENTAGON ROW, ACTUAL
CARJACKING, THERE BOTH
HAPPENING FRIDAY HOURS APART.
NOW LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
SUSPECT, POLICE GIVING US
DESCRIPTIONS, SAYING THAT HE
IS A MAN IN HIS 20'S, THIN
BUILD, WEARING DARK CLOTHING
AT THE TIME.
NOW, WE ALSO KNOW THAT THERE
MAY BE SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OF
THIS SUSPECT, BEFORE OR AFTER
THE ENCOUNTER, BUS HERE IS
SOME NEW INFORMATION.
ARLINGTON POLICE NOW TURNING
TO THE PUBLIC ASKING RESIDENTS
IF THEY HAVE PRIVATE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO, THAT MAY
HAVE CAPTURED SOMETHING TO
MAKE SURE THAT THEY COME
FORWARD.
NOW, WE ARE TOLD THAT THESE
LAST TWO INCIDENTS ARE PART OF
A SERIES OF CARJACKINGS, ALL
UNDER INVESTIGATION, ARLINGTON
COUNTY POLICE DEPARTMENT, IN
FACT, THE SAME DETECTIVE IS
INVESTIGATING AT ALL.
SO, DETECTIVES ARE BUSY AT
WORK TRYING TO PIECE TOGETHER
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
AND WHO IS RESPONSIBLE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS FIRST
INCIDENT, THOUGH, THAT
HAPPENED HERE ON FRIDAY NIGHT,
AROUND 10:30, ABOUT AN HOUR
AFTER THE MALL CLOSES.
THE VICTIM WAS REPORTEDLY
SITTING IN HIS CAR AND CELL
PHONE WHEN THE ATTACKER KNOCK
ON THE WINDOW, APPARENTLY
SHOWING GUN.
AND DEMANDING THE VICTIM GET
OUT.
ONCE OUT, HE WAS ATTACKED BY
THE SUSPECT.
POLICE SAY THE VICTIM BEGAN TO
SCREAM AND THE SUSPECT TOOK
OFF.
WHILE POLICE WERE
INVESTIGATING, THAT INCIDENT,
THEY WERE CALLED TO AN ACTUAL
CARJACKING, NEARBY, ON THE 900
BLOCK OF ARMY-NAVY DRIVE.
BLAKE, ANKLEY?
>> WOW, THESE ARE ARMED
CARJACKING, TEEN, A WHAT'S
AMAZING HOW BRAZE THEN IS,
BECAUSE A MALL PRESUMABLY HAS
SECURITY CAMERAS EVERYWHERE.
DO WE KNOW IF THEY CAPTURED
ANYTHING?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
INTERESTING?
IS THAT, YES, THERE ARE
SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS, BUT
APPARENTLY WHERE THESE
ENCOUNTERS ARE TAKING PLACE,
THEY WERE NOT CAUGHT ON
CAMERA. WE DO KNOW THAT THERE
IS VIDEO SHOWING THE SUSPECT,
IN SOME WAY, SHAPE OR FORM,
EITHER GOING IN, COMING OUT.
BUT POLICE ARE HAVING
CHALLENGES PINPOINTING EXACTLY
WHO IS RESPONSIBLE BECAUSE THE
SUSPECT DESCRIPTION IS VAGUE.
AND IN THE ACTUAL CARJACKING
THAT TOOK PLACE AT PENTAGON
ROW, BLAKE, THE SUSPECT WAS
ABLE TO GET AWAY.
HERE IS PROBABLY WHY.
THERE IS PENTAGON ROW F WE GO
LITTLE MORE TO THE RIGHT, YOU
CAN SEE THAT THE INTERSTATE IS
THERE.
SO HE LITERALLY GOT AWAY IN
THIS STOLEN BLACK HONDA
CIVIC -- CIVIC, PLANS LATE U
M.D.-4813 ON THE RUN, AT
LARGE, FREEMAN, BUT DETECTIVES
ARE HOPING THAT SOMEBODY
RECOGNIZES OR THIS JARS A
MEMORY MAYBE SOMEBODY SAW THIS
CAR, OR SAW SOMETHING
SUSPICIOUS IN THE
SECOND INCIDENT THAT HAPPENED
AT PENTAGON ROW, THE VICTIM
ACTUALLY SAW THE SUSPECT AND
SAW SOMETHING SUSPICIOUS, BUT
CONTINUED ON HIS BUSINESS.
CAME BACK TO HIS CAR AND
THAT'S WHEN HE WAS CONFRONTED.
>> GOOD REMINDER FOR ALL OF
US, BE AWARE OF THE
SURROUNDINGS, LOOK BEHIND YOU,
IF YOU THINK SOMETHING IS
FISHY, IT IS OKAY TO TURN
AROUND AND GO BACK INSIDE AND
WAIT.
TISHA LEWIS, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> FRIENDS, FAMILY AND FANS
WERE ALTOGETHER UNDER ONE ROOF
TODAY 20,000 PEOPLE PACKED THE
STAPLES CENTER IN DOWNTOWN LOS
ANGELES TO REMEMBER KOBE
BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER
GIANNA.
BRYANT PLAYED HIS ENTIRE 20
YEAR CAREER WITH THE RANGERS.
SEVENTEEN OF THOSE SEASON WERE
AT THE STAPLES CENTER.
EVEN TODAY'S DATE IS SPECIAL.
BRYANT WORE THE NUMBER 24 IN
THE LATER HALF OF HIS CAREER.
AND GIANNA WORE NUMBER TWO.
SO YOU'RE GOING HAVE MUCH MORE
ON THE IS HER MOAN WHEN "TMZ"
JOINS US LATER THIS HOUR.
>> STAR STUDDED CEREMONY I'M
SURE THE LIST EVEN LONGER FOR
PEOPLE WHO WANTED TO.
>> INCREDIBLY EMOTIONAL.
>> LATEST ON THE CASINO
OUTBREAK, NEARLY 08,000 CASES
RECORDED 30 COUNTRIES AND TWO
COUNTRIES IN PARTICULAR, HAVE
SEEN A RECENT SPIKE IN CASES.
THOSE ARE ITALY, AND SOUTH
KOREA AUTHORITIES IN BOTH
COUNTRIES ARE ARE TAKING STEPS
TO STOP THE DISEASE FROM
SPREADING, HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES WE'VE SEEN SLIGHT
INCREASE, 53 PEOPLE HERE NOW
INFECTED.
THERE ARE REPORTS JAPAN IS
ROUNDED UP NEARLY TWO DOZEN
PASSENGERS MISTAKENLY RELEASED
FROM THE DIAMOND PRINCESS
CRUISE SHIP.
THE COUNTRY'S HEALTH MINISTER
SAID THE PASSENGER LEFT THE
SHIP WITHOUT UNDERGOING A
SECOND BATTERY OF TESTS, TO
DETERMINE WHETHER THEY HAD THE
CASINO.
THE PASSENGERS HAD TESTED
NEGATIVE ON INITIAL TESTS, AND
WERE QUARANTINED FOR TWO WEEKS
BUT LEFT THE SHIP BEFORE
UNDERGOING SECOND TEST.
NEARLY 700 PASSENGERS AND CREW
MEMBERS FROM THE SHIP ARE
CONTRACTED THE VIRUS INCLUDING
AT LEAST 18 AMERICANS.
>> AND, WE KNOW THIS.
THE STOCK MARKET TOOK NOSE
DIVE TODAY ON FEARS OF A
GLOBAL ECONOMIC DOWN TURN,
BECAUSE OF THE CORONAVIRUS.
THE DOW JONES INDUSTRIAL
AVERAGE FELL MORE THAN 1,000
POINTS.
THE NASDAQ AND S&P 500 ALSO
LOSING ABOUT 3% OF ITS WORTH
IN TRADING DAY.
>> SOME CAUGHT ON CAMERA
MOMENTS, SNOWMOBILER SURVIVING
AN AVALANCH.
VIDEO FROM EARLY FEBRUARY, SEE
CLOSELY THERE, SEE TWO SNOW
MOBILE ERS, CHARGING UP A
MOUNTAIN IN COLORADO.
ONE TRIGGERS AVALANCH.
>> OKAY?
> AND SNOW QUICKLY COVERS THE
SECOND RIDER.
FORTUNATELY, THAT RIDER WAS
ABLE TO KEEP HIS HEAD ABOVE
THE SNOW AND WAS RESCUED.
>> WOW.
>> I IMAGINE IF YOU'RE DOING
THIS YOU PROBABLY HAVE SOME
TRAINING IN WHAT TO DO IF THIS
HAPPENS.
>> WOW.
OKAY, WELL, HERE IS ANOTHER
VIDEO TO SHOW YOU, POLICE AND
FIRE FIGHTERS OHIO WORKING
TOGETHER TO RESCUE THIS DOG
THAT WAS TRAPPED IN THE MIDDLE
OF A ICY POND.
DOG HAD GONE TOO FAR OUT AND
HE FELL THROUGH OBVIOUSLY, OBVI,
RIGHT THERE, VIDEO SHOWING THE
MAN CRAWLING OUT ON THE ICE TO
PULL THE PUP TO SAFETY.
DOG ROUNDS HIS OWNER, LITTLE
COLD, BUT THEY'RE SAYING
OTHERWISE HE WAS DOING JUST
FINE, BUT HOW BRAVE OF THAT
MAN TO GO OUT THERE AND DO
THAT.
>> DOG'S FIRST RETURN TO THE
LAKE IN THE SUMMER.
LITTLE HESITANT TO GO IN.
>> I BET.
>> HE'S GOT A SACK TODAY AND
HE FOUND THE GIRL WITH THE
THIN MINTS, HE TRADE ADD
FOOTBALL FOR AN ENTIRE BOX.
>> SUPPLY AND DEMAND, BABY.
ONLY ONE BOX OF THIN MINTS
THERE.
THIN MINTS IN HIGH DEMAND
DURING XFL GAME SATURDAY.
DEFENSIVE LINEMAN CASEY SALES
TRADE ADD FOOTBALL FOR A BOX
OF GIRL SCOUT COOKIES, THE
GIRL WAS HOLDING A SIGN
ADVERTISING THAT OFFER AND HE
SAID HEY, SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> CRASHES AND WE KNOW FOX
IS -- BOX ALIKE FIVE BUCKS.
THAT WILL FOOTBALL IS A LOT
MORE.
>> I BET THE ONLY UNOPENED BOX
EVERY GIRL SCOUT KOOKINESS
THEN TIRE PLACE, COULD HAVE
TRADED WHATEVER SHE WANT.
>> BUT HE DUG INTO THEM REAL
FAST.
DC STUDENTS GOT THE FIRST LOOK
AT THE NEW NATIONAL CHILDREN'S
MUSEUM TODAY, A LOT OF
ANTICIPATION BUILDING TO UP
THIS MOMENT.
DOORS, NOW OPEN DAILY PARENTS,
FROM 9:30 TO 4:30, THE MUSEUM
COMBINATION CHILDREN'S CENTER
AND SCIENCE CENTER TO GIVE
KIDS LOT TO EXPLORE AND
INTERACT W SOME OF THE AREAS
FOCUS ON TECHNOLOGY,
ENGINEERING AS WELL AS MATH
LOCATED ON 13TH AND
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
TICKETS $11 TO GET IN.
>> TERRIBLE.
YOU GUYS READY?
>> ♪ ♪
>> OKAY, SO IS THAT DRUM OR
THE WHITE TIGER FROM THE MASK
SINGER?
HE WOULDN'T SAY.
BUT WHAT I DO KNOW IS THAT A
LONG WITH TENNIS GREAT JOHN
MCENROE, I BELIEVE WE HAVE
SOME PICTURES HERE, THEY
BROUGHT THE HOUSE DOWN AT
CHANCE FOR LIFE AT THE MGM
NATIONAL HARBOR, GRAMMY AWARD
WINNING SINGER DAYA WAS A
SURPRISE ACT AT THE EVENT, AS
WOMEN.
THEY RAISED $2.7 MILLION.
>> IN ONE NIGHT.
>> IN ONE NIGHT, STILL
COUNTING, FOR PEDIATRIC CANCER
RESEARCH.
DOLLARS THAT ARE GOING TO GO
DIRECTLY TO CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL AND OTHER GROUPS TO
FUND LIFE SAVING RESEARCH AND
NEW CLINICAL TRIALS.
>> AND YOU EMCEE THE EVENT.
>> YES, IF THERE ARE TWO
PARTS, HUGE POKER TOURNAMENT
AND THEN THEY HAVE THE BIG
TASTE EVENT, AND THERE IS
ALWAYS AN ELEMENT OF SURPRISE.
SO THEY BROUGHT OUT THE SINGER
DAYA, SO FUN, THAN WAS THE FUN
AFTER PARTY, YES.
THAT IS NIGHT.
STILL RECOVERING.
BUT ALL FOR A GRADE CAUSE.
>> AWESOME.
STILL TO COME:  ELDERLY COUPLE
VANISHED INTO THE WOODS ON
VALENTINE DAY MORE THAN A WEEK
LATER THEY WERE FOUND ALIVE.
HOW THEY MADE IT TO SURVIVE
THAT WHOLE TIME.
>> PLUS, WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
DIFFERENT KIND OF MIRACLE, ON
ICE, INTRODUCE YOU TO THE 42
YEAR OLD ZAMBONI DRIVER WHO
TRAPPED HIMSELF AT THE NET OF
THE TOLL COOKER DURINGTHE
HOCKEY GAME THIS WEEKEND.
>> LET'S TAKE LIVE LOOK AT
TRAFFIC AROUND THE DMV AS RUSH
HOUR RAMPS UP.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
BACK.
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
>> CUP THEM THEIR 70S WERE
LOST, AROUND IN THE WOODS FOR
EIGHT DAYS, AROUND VALENTINE
DAY.
BUT, THEY WERE ABLE TO GET THE
THUMBS-UP AFTER THEIR AMAZING
RESCUE, THE COUPLE BOTH IN
THEIR 70S, THEY WENT FOR A
HIKE, AND THIS WAS IN NORTHERN
CALIFORNIA, THEY SAID THEY
JUST GOT LOST.
THEY WERE WEARING ONLY LIGHT
WEIGHT CLOTHING, THEY DIDN'T
HAVE ANY FOOD WITH THEM.
THE COUPLE SAYS THAT THEY
SURVIVED BY EATING PLANTS AND
DRINKING WATER FROM A PUDDLE
THEY FOUND.
SATURDAY TWO VOLUNTEERS FOUND
THEM ALIVE DOCTORS TREATED
THEM FOR HYPOTHERMIA.
BOTH EXPECTED TO MAKE A FULL
RECOVERY.
>> WOW.
>> IMPRESSIVE.
>> I'VE THAT HAPPEN, THOUGH.
YOU'RE ON A HIKE.
>> OH, YOU'VE BEEN LOST?
YOU.
>> THINK YOU'LL TAKE SHORT
CUT.
I WASN'T LOST FOR EIGHT DAYS,
LOST FOR EIGHT MINUTES WHICH
TO ME FELT LIKE EIGHT DAYS.
THERE WERE BUGS I HAD NEVER
SEEN BEFORE.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> AND YA, YOU THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO RECONNECT
WITH THE TRAIL IT JUST DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S SCARY.
YOU DIDN'T A COMPASS OR
ANYTHING WITH YOU?
>> , NO I HAD A FRIENDS WHO
WAS MORE USELESS THAN ME.
>> OH, REMIND ME NOT TO GO ON
ANY HIKING TRIPS.
>> THE INAUGURAL HISTORICALLY
BETTER GALA KICKS OFF TONIGHT
AT THE HOWARD THEATER, AND
HONORS TRAILBLAZERS IN THE
BLACK COMMUNITY, WE GOT THE
SCOOP ABOUT THE GALA.
>> WE ARE HONORING AL MCCALLA
JUNIOR FOR PEPSI, ONE OF BEING
ONE OF THE BLACK INTERNS BACK
IN THE 1940'S, SO HE WAS A
TRAILBLAZER.
AND YOU KNOW I DON'T KNOW IF
PEOPLE LIKE MYSELF WOULD EVEN
BE AROUND TODAY IN THE WORLD
I'M IN IT WASN'T FOR -- WE
WILL ' CELEBRATE HIS LEGACY
AND ALL THE PEOPLE THAT COME
BEHIND HIM.
>> THIS EVENT WILL BE AMAZING,
WEAVER SOME SPECIAL SURPRISE
GUESTS, I PICK UP THE PHONE,
MADE SOME PHONECALLS, SO I'M
BRINGING SOME HEAVY HITTERS.
>> TONIGHT'S EVENT BEGINS
AT THREE AND ALSO HOSTING
AFTER-PARTY AT THE PARK AT
14TH.
>>> VERY COOL.
WHAT'S THE WEATHER GOING TO BE
LIKE?
WELL, LET'S GET MAYBE SMALL
SAMPLE BY TAKING LIVE LOOK AT
THE CAPITOL BUILDING RIGHT
BEHIND CAITLIN.
>> HIGH THERE, GUYS.
DID YOU GET OUTSIDE THIS
WEEKEND?
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>> YES, IT WAS NICE.
I THOUGHT TODAY WAS BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT WAS, YES, I KNOW, JUST
CARRIED IT RIGHT ON OVER TO
THE WORK WEEK.
SHOWERS THOUGH.
FILLING IN TONIGHT.
SO WE WILL DO THAT MIDDLE OF
THE WEEK THING WE RAWLS SEEM
TO DO WITH THE RAIN COMING ON
IN.
BUT, YA, I KNOW, I CAN'T GET
OVER BOTH DAYS THIS WEEKENDED,
SO BEAUTIFUL TODAY, NEARLY
60 DEGREES, OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW,
AND IF YOU WANT TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE.
NICE MILD WEATHER PROBABLY GOT
A WINDOW OF FEW HOURS THROUGH
THE EVENING, WHERE COULD YOU
STILL SIT OUTSIDE AND EAT IT
IS THAT COMFORTABLE FOR THIS
MOVES IN.
BUT THIS IS A LOT OF THE
SATELLITE AND RADAR SHOWING
SPRAWLING AREA OF RAIN
SHOWERS, FROM CHICAGO, ALL THE
WAY DOWN TO ATLANTA ONCE
AGAIN, TOO WARM FOR ANYTHING,
EXCEPT RAIN SHOWERS, EVEN ALL
THE WAY UP IN CHICAGO.
LOCALLY WE'VE SEEN INCREASE IN
CLOUD COVER.
BUT ENOUGH SUNSHINE TO KEEP
THINGS VERY MILD TODAY.
AND JUST BEAUTIFUL,
59 DEGREES, OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW,
MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES, WINDS ARE
OUT OF THE SOUTHWEST LITTLE
BREEZY, POMMING IN THE WARM
AIR OUT AHEAD OF THE NEXT
SYSTEM 14 MILES PER HOUR
THERE.
FOR THIS EVENING, I THINK
THEY'RE ABOUT 9:00, NOT GOING
TO SEE ANY SHOWERS ANY WAR,
BETWEEN 10:00 AND MIDNIGHT
THEY FILL IF FROM SOUTHWEST TO
NORTHEAST, SO UNLESS IT IS A
REAL LATE MONDAY NIGHT FOR YOU
PROBABLY GOING TO MISS THIS,
BUT YOU WILL SEE THE RAIN
SHOWERS, WHEN DRIVING IN TO
WORK TOMORROW MORNING.
SO, LOW PRESSURE, OUT ACROSS
THE OHIO VALLEY, FIRST LIFTS
THE WARMFRONT THROUGH, THAT
MEANS TEMPERATURES PRETTY MILD
OVERNIGHT.
SHOWERS WILL BE MOVING IN AND
BY THE TIME WE HIT THE DRIVE THE
RAIN.
RAIN WILL TENDS TO END AS WE
GO INTO THE AFTERNOON HOURS,
BUT WHAT WILL LINGER WILL BE
THE CLOUDS, THE FOG, PROBABLY
EVEN POCKETS OF SOME DRIZZLE,
TEMPERATURES WILL STRUGGLE,
THIS TIME OF YEAR GETTING
WARMFRONT ALL THE WAY THROUGH
AND GET THAT WARM AIR BEHIND
IT IS VERY DIFFICULT.
I THINK PROBABLY SITTING
BETWEEN THE MID 40'S AND THE
LOW 50'S AREA WIDE.
SO HIGH TEMPERATURES FOR
TOMORROW, 52 DEGREES IN D.C.
NOTICE, YOU GET THE VARIETY,
COULD BE ONLY 45 IN ANNAPOLIS
BUT 55 IN WINCHESTER, SO
DEPENDS ON WHERE THAT FRONT
LAYS UP.
SHOWERS, MOSTLY IN THE
MORNING, COULD HAVE SPOTTY
SHOWERS INTO THE AFTERNOON.
SEE TEMPERATURES PEAK THIS
WEEK WEDNESDAY.
58 DEGREES.
WE'RE UP AND ABOVE NORMAL.
BUT THEN RIGHT BACK DOWN AS
COLDER AIR STARTS TO FILTER
THROUGH, BY THURSDAY,
TEMPERATURES BACK TO NORMAL,
HIGH OF JUST 47, 45 FRIDAY,
GOING TO KEEP FALLING, AS WE
HEAD INTO THE WEEKENDS, AND
ANOTHER ROUND EVERY COLD AIR
TO ROUND OUT THE MONTH OF
FEBRUARY.
I'LL HAVE ALL OF THAT STILL
AHEAD IN MY SEVEN DAY
FORECAST.
BLAKE?
>> AND THEN, CAITLIN PROMISES
A WARM AND RAIN-FREE MARCH.
>> OH, PROMISE.
>> MARCH.
>> FROM ZAMBONI DRIVER TO HERO
GOALIE ON SATURDAY, 42 YEAR
OLD DAVID AIRS GOT THE
OPPORTUNITY AFTER LIFETIME.
LISTEN TO.
>> THIS CAROLINA HURRICANES
LOST BOTH OF THEIR GOALIES TO
INJURY DURING THE GAME AGAINST
THE MAPLELEAFS.
SO IN STEPPED AIRS, THE
HURRICANE'S DESIGNATED
EMERGENCY GOALIE.
HE ACTUALLY DRIVES THE ZAMBONI
FOR THE MAPLELEAFS AHL
AFFILIATE, THEIR PRACTICE GOAL
TENDER.
THE FIRST TWO SHOTS HE FACED
GOT BY HIM.
BUT HE SAVED THE NEXT EIGHT
SHOTS THAT CAME HIS WAY, AND
ENDED UP GETTING CREDIT FOR
THE CAROLINE'S SIX-THREE
VICTORY.
TALK ABOUT LYING TO THE
OCCASION.
>> WOW.
>> HERE TO MISS IT.
CAN'T DO THIS AT HOME SO EAST.
>> I OF COURSE YOU CAN, BUT
WHAT'S BETTER THAN ROSE GOLD,
MY LADY.
>> OH, THE OH, MY GOFF SHOW
GOES TO THE MARDI GRAS THIS
WEEK WITH A FRIENDLY HURRICANE
COCKTAIL COMPETITION LED BY
MARDI GRAS, MIXOLOGIES, GINA.
>> IT IS GENERALLY EQUAL PARTS
OF THE BOOZE TO THE JUICE.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> SO THIS IS BRITTANY.
VALUE HER ON CAMERA?
IT IS GOOD.
>> A LOT OF DRAMA.
>> ♪ ♪
>> DELICIOUS.
>> IT IS GOOD.
I GOT SAY YOU WIN.
IT IS GOOD.
>> SO MY GUEST CO-HOST MY
FRIENDS JENNIFER WON THE
COCKTAIL COMPETITION.
THERE IS GOING TO BE ACTUALLY
REAL ONE GOING ON BY THE WAY
THE MARDI GRAS EXTRAVAGANT ARE
SIX TO 10:00 P.M., BANDS,
BEADS, FOOD AND MORE BY THE
WAY GET RECIPES FOR MARDI GRAS
DRINKS AND HEAR FROM TAR OWE
READER JUST WATCH THE REST OF
OUR PARTYGR A ON OH, MY GOFF
ON THE SHOW WHICH YOU CAN
SUBSCRIBE TO ON YOUTUBE OR
APPLE POD CAST.
>> WE HAD CHEF HERE AHEAD OF
THE SUPER BOWL.
AND ONE OF HIS BEST TIPS I
THOUGHT WAS IF YOU'RE DOING A
PUNCH DRINK AT ANY PARTY, YOU
CAN HAVE THE LIQUOR SEPARATE,
BECAUSE IT IS SO EASY TO ADD
AFTER.
AND THEN THE KIDS CAN ENJOY
THE PUNCH TOO.
SO MAKE THE PUNCH LIQUOR FREE
HAVE LITTLE LIQUOR STATION,
YOU KNOW, HIGHER UP AWAY FROM
THE KIDS, AFTER THEY CAN GO
ADD WHATEVER AMOUNT OF BOOZE
THEY WANT.
>> OH, YOU LET THE GUESTS ADD
THEIR OWN BOOZE.
>> THAT WAY THE KIDS CAN ENJOY
IN THE PUNCH TOO.
>> KIND OF SMART TOO.
I PREFER JUST A PARTY WITH NO
KIDS.
>> SAYS THE ONE WITH KIDS.
>> EXACTLY.
>> CAN YOU REMEMBER THE KIND
OF MUSIC YOU WERE LISTENING TO
WERE YOU A TEENAGER?
>> YES.
>> AND NEW STUDY SAYS WHEN YOU
FAWN YOUR FAVORITE BAND OR
ARTIST AND WE'RE GOING TO
REVEAL THE BIGGEST INFLUENCES
ON A PERSON'S MUSIC TASTE.
>> ♪ ♪
VO: A problem solver
for president.
That's Mike Bloomberg.
A middle class kid who built a
global company from scratch.
Mayor of New York,
rebuilding the city after the
9-11 terrorist attack, creating
450,000 jobs.
Running for president
- and on a roll.
Workable plans to deliver on
better health care.
Affordable college.
Job creation.
Common sense plans to beat
Trump, fix the chaos
in Washington,
and get things done.
MIKE: I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> FIRST, DO YOU REMEMBER THE
FIRST TIME YOU HEARD YOUR
FAVORITE MUSICIAN?
>> GOSH, I DON'T KNOW, HAVEN'T
THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
>> YOU HAVE 20 SECONDS.
>> SURVEY FROM THE SECRETARY
TIGHT ASKED A THOUSAND PEOPLE
ABOUT THEIR MUSIC EXPERIENCE
IT, FOUND THAT MOST PEOPLE
DISCOVERED THEIR FAVORITE
ARTIST, AT 13 YEARS OLD
BIGGEST INFLUENCES, FRIENDS,
TV, ALREADY ENDS.
>> I WOULDN'T SAY MY FAVORITE
WAS FOUND AT 13 YEARS OLD.
>> DOLLY PARTON, MORE AFTER
CELEBRITY.
>> RIGHT?
OVER TIME, THE ARTISTS MEAN
MORE TO YOU, BUT I THINK THAT
BACK TO WHAT I HEAR IN THAT
TIME PERIOD, IT IS TO JUST
TAKES ME BACK, AND I THINK
WHERE IT IS CAME FROM.
>> THIRTEEN IS PROBABLY GOOD
AGE FOR.
THAT WILL OR HIGH SCHOOL.
>> STARTING TO FORM A LOT
OFFER OPINIONS WHAT ABOUT YOU
WHAT LIKE, BUT THEN ARTIST
CHANGE SO QUICKLY.
>> INTERESTING, AGE WHERE YOU
FORM A LOT OF OPINIONS.
>> I THINK THOSE SONGS THAT
GET YOU SUPER EXCITED THOUGH
WHEN YOU TENDS TO BE THOSE
SONGS FROM MIDDLE SCHOOL.
>> FROM THAT AGE, ABSOLUTELY.
>> THAT GIRL IS POISON ♪ ♪ YOU
SNOW.
>> YA.
>> THAT'S ANGIE'S AGE.
>> I KNOW?
>> I JUST GAVE IT AWAY.
>> AH.
>> OKAY, STILL TO COME, PLAN
TO RAISE TAXES ON THE PEOPLE
WHO MAKE THE MOST MONEY, A
MARYLAND COUNCILMAN PITCHED,
IN WILL EXPLAIN HIS PROPOSAL
AND THE POSSIBILITY OF THESE
BILLS PASSING IN MARYLAND.
>> ♪ ♪
Z3R4OZ Z16FZ
Y3R4OY Y16FY
>> BACK NOW WITH A LOOK AT
SOME OF THE TOP STORIES, RASH
EVERY VANDALISM AT HOWARD
UNIVERSITY.
SOMEONE SPRAY PAINTED SEVERAL
SIGNS, BEN CHEST AND ADVANCE
AROUND CAMPUS, WHAT APPEARS TO
BE A RED THREE, A CAMPUS
SPOKESPERSON SAYS IT IS
BELIEVED THIS HAPPENED OVER
THE WEEKENDS, HOWARD
UNIVERSITY POLICE ARE LOOKING
INTO IT AND WHEN IT TO COULD
MEAN.
>> KEVIN JOHNSON PORTRAYED IN
THE OSCAR NOMINATED MOVIE
HIDDEN FIGURES HAS DIED, WAS
101 YEARS OLD, NATIVE OF WEST
VIRGINIA PIONEER FOR THAT IS A
HER CONTRIBUTION WAS OFTEN
OVERLOOKED UNTIL HIDDEN
FIGURES CAME OUT IN 2016.
JOHNSON WAS A MITOME TIS WHO
WORKED ON COMPLEX SPACE
MISSIONS, PRETTY MUCH HUMAN
COMPUTER WHAT THEY CALLED HER,
FOR THAT IS, A INCLUDING
GIVING THE GO AHEAD FOR JOHN
GLENN'S MISSION INTO ORBIT.
>> HOW GREAT THAT SHE GOT TO
LIVE LONG ENOUGH, THOUGH, TO
BE APPRECIATED BY THE WORLD.
>> YES.
>> ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT
PLEADS NOT GUILTY AGAIN IT,
COMES MORE THAN A YEAR AFTER
HE SAID HE WAS THE VICTIM
AFTER RACIST AND HOMOPHOBIC
ATTACK.
CHARGED SMOLLETT IN THE CASE
LAST YEAR AFTER INVESTIGATORS
SAY HE STAGED THE ATTACK, THE
ATTORNEY'S OFFICE LATER
DISMISSED THE CASE, BUT A
JUDGE APPOINTS DOLLARS SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR TO RE-INVESTIGATE
LEADING TO SIX NEW CHARGES OF
DIS OFFERED ERRLY CONDUCT.
>> HERE IS A QUESTION.
SHOULD THE WEALTHY HAVE TO PAY
MORE IN TAXES?
IT IS SOMETHING WE'VE BEEN
HEARING UP AND DOWN THE 2020
PRESIDENT A.M. CAMPAIGN TRAIL,
AND NOW MONTGOMERY COUNTY
COUNCILMAN, PITCHED TWO BILLS
WHICH COULD POTENTIALLY RAISE
TAXES ON PEOPLE WHO MAKE MORE
MONEY.
FOX5 STEPHANIE RAMIREZ JOINS
US LIVE NOW WITH A BREAKDOWN,
HEY, STEPHANIE?
>> RIGHT NOW, INVOLVES HOMES
MORE EXPENSIVE HOMES IN THE
COUNTY, COUNCIL MEMBER WILL
PROPOSE IN THE BILL,
SUPPORTING TWO BILLS ACTUALLY
BEFORE THE STATE LEGISLATURE,
THIS WEEK, AND THEY BOTH TOUCH
ON WEALTH DISPARITY IN THE
COUNTY.
ONE BILL WOULD GIVE MARYLAND
COUNTY THE AUTHORITY TO
IMPLEMENT THEIR OWN SPECIAL
TAX RATE, BUT NOW THEY CAN'T,
BUT MUNICIPALITIES, AND THE
OTHER BILL CALLS FOR .3 RATE
CHANGE, WHERE PEOPLE MAKING
MORE THAN A MILLION TO RAISE
88.4 MILLION, PAY FOR THE
ESTIMATED $261 MILLION OVER
TEN YEAR PRICE TAG, THAT
MONTGOMERY COUNTY MAY HAVE TO
PAY UNDER THE KERWIN
COMMISSION.
THAT'S THE STATE OVERHAUL
PLAN.
SO THESE BILLS, THEY ARE
REALLY TO ADDRESS THE COUNTY
INCH MR. MEN TAKES OF TAXES,
BUT TAKES IT LITTLE FURTHER,
OUTLINING MORE DETAILS, WHERE
HE CALLS PROGRESSIVE PLANS,
HOUSE BILL 1276 THE BILL
DEALING WITH HIGHER TAXES ON
PROPERTIES BIGGER THAN 5,000
SQUARE FEET.
THE COUNCILMAN SAYS IT IS NOT
FAIR IF YOU OWN A MANSION, OR
A SMALL HOUSE, YOU STILL PAY
THE SAME TAX RATE.
ALSO CLAIMS THAT ADDING A DIME
TO THE PROPERTY TAX RATE ON
THOSE PLUS FIVE CASE
PROPERTIES COULD GIVE MAJORITY
EVERY COUNTY HOMEOWNERS
537-DOLLAR TAX CUT, THAT CAN
GO TO OTHER THINGS.
LIKE BILLS, MEDICATIONS, GUYS,
I CAN TELL YOU, THERE WAS PUSH
BACK TO THIS TODAY.
SOME COUNCIL MEMBERS SAY THIS
IS THE WRONG MESSAGE, THEY SAY
THE COUNTY SHOULD BE FOCUSED
ON GROWING THEIR TAX BASE,
INSTEAD OF RAISING TAXES.
OTHERS ARE INTERESTED IN
CHANGING HOW THEY IMPLEMENT
TAXES BUT THEY SAY JUST TOO
EARLY TO TALK ABOUT DETAILS,
SO I WAS TOLD TODAY THAT THE
COUNTY COUNCILS HILL VOTE
SIX-THREE, AGAINST THE
PROPERTY TAX BILL, BUT, IT IS
STILL GOING TO GO BEFORE THE
STATE LEGISLATURE, AND THE
WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE ON
THURSDAY.
ANKLEY?
>> YES, AND KNOWING WHAT WE
KNOW NOW, WHAT YOU JUST
RECORD, WHAT IS THE LIKELIHOOD
OF THESE BILLS PASSING?
ANY INDICATION?
>> YES, SO HE IS WORKING WITH
HOUSE DELEGATE JULIE CAR, AND
WE ASKED HER WHAT'S THE
LIKELIHOOD, SHE SAID SHE
REALLY COULDN'T ANSWER.
BUT WHAT SHE DID SAY IS THAT
THIS YEAR THERE ARE A LOT OF
BILLS, MORE THAN THEY HAVE
AVENUE SEEN, THAN THEY'VE EVER
SEEN BEFORE, TALKING ABOUT HOW
TO HELP PAY FOR THE KERWIN
COMMISSION, BECAUSE THAT'S
VERY IMPORTANT.
SHE ALSO SAID THAT THIS BILL
HAS BIPARTISAN SUPPORT, AND IT
ALSO HAS SUPPORT FROM THE
MONTGOMERY COUNTY TEACHERS
ASSOCIATION.
SO WE WILL HAVE TO LEARN MORE
ON THURSDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE WILL CHECK BACK IN
WITH YOU THEN.
THANKS, STEPHANIE.
>>> AND THIS IS GOING TO LEAD
US TO OUR FOX5 LIVE STAIN
POLE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD WEALTHIER RESIDENTS IN
THE DMV PAY MORE IN PROPERTY
TAXES, YOU CAN CAST YOUR VOTE
RIGHT NOW IN OUR FOX5DC APP.
JUST FINDS THE STAIN POLE IN
THE BROWS SECTION OF COURSE
WAY IN ON THE WEBSITE
FOX5DC.COM.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> TOUCHY SUBJECT, WHEN
EVERYONE FEELS LIKE THEY
ALREADY PAID TOO MUCH TAXES.
>> YES, 81% SAY NO RIGHT NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, STILL TO COME:
MARYLAND MIDDLE SCHOOL STUDENT
SHOWING OFF THEIR TECHNOLOGY
SKILLS.
>> YES,  THIS IS COOL.
WE WILL CHECK IN TO FREDERICK
COUNTY SCHOOL FAIR WHERE GARY
MOTORCYCLE BRADY IS LEARNING
ALL ABOUT THE STUDENTS, COOL
AND INNOVATIVE IDEAS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
We have a president who thinks
everything is about him.
His tweets, his golf courses,
his ego.
But I think the job is about
you.
Your healthcare, your schools,
your security, your families and
your future.
I'm Amy Klobuchar.
I'll be a president and a
commander in chief who restores
decency to the white house
and gets things done for you
That's why I approve this
message.
Z3R4OZ Z16FZ
Y3R4OY Y16FY
YOU.
>> WANT THE FUTURE.
MUSIC SCHOOLERS ARE SHOWING
OFF SOME COOL IDEAS, IN
TONIGHT'S TECH FAIR.
>> FOX5 GARY MOTORCYCLE BRADY
IS LIVE.
WHAT I LEARNED ABOUT MIDDLE
SCHOOLERS THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
TOLD THAT IT IS A DUMB IDEA
YET, SO THE SKY IS THE LIMIT
WITH WHAT THEY CAN THINK OF.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
THEY HAVEN'T REALIZED THEY CAN
SAY YOU'RE EXACTLY RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK THIS WILL WORK,
AND THEN KIND OF WALK AWAY.
SO THEY'RE ALL GOING TO BE
HERE TONIGHT.
LET ME SET THE STAGE.
TECHNICALLY SPEAKING WE ARE ON
THE CAMPUS EVERY FREDERICK
COMMUNITY COLLEGE BUT IT IS
CTC, IT IS CTE MONTH, ALL
THESE DIFFERENT AC CHRONIC
ELSE, I HAVE TO BRING IN
CORBIN SHOEMAKER, TEACHER
SPECIALLY HERE AT CTC.
FIRST OF ALL CTC, CAREER
TECHNOLOGY CENTER CORRECT.
>> THAT'S PART OF THE BIGGER
PICTURE OF CAREER TECHNOLOGY
EDUCATION.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, THE
TECH SNARE.
>> YES, 27TH ANNUAL TECH FAIR,
THIS IS MIDDLE SCHOOL
STUDENTS, COMPETING AT VARIOUS
DIFFERENT COMPETITIONS, AND
HERE WE HAVE THE ODD EX HE CAN
PROGRAM, HOFFER CRAFTS, OTHER
PROGRAMS, THEY HAVE ALL WOUND
UP VEHICLES, CODING
ACTIVITIES, COOKING
COMPETITIONS, MEDIA
CHALLENGES, MIDDLE SCHOOL
COMPETITIONS, THAT ARE BEING
POSTED HERE.
>> HOW MANY MIDDLE SCHOOLERS
TONIGHT?
>> SO IT WOULD BE OVER 200
STUDENTS, THAT NOT INCLUDING
STUDENTS THAT MAY HAVE
COMPETED OUTSIDE BEFORE THIS,
BEFORE COMING HERE, TOO.
>> OKAY.
CORBIN YOU HAD ME AT HOFFER
CRAFTER.
SO WE WILL HAVE DEMONSTRATION
HERE, WE'VE GOT MARRY --
LARRY.
DAVID, BOTH TEACHERS BY THE
WAY FREDERICK COMMUNITY AND
FREDERICK MIDDLE SCHOOL IS
HERE, HERE IT IS RIGHT HERE,
THIS LITTLE, NOT -- COME ON,
NOT BIG HOF ERR CRAFT.
NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
TRANSPORT ANYBODY ON IT.
BUT IT IS STILL VERY VERY
IMPRESSIVE.
TURN IT ON, LARRY.
>> YOU THERE GO.
>> SO THIS IS WHAT THE KIDS
WILL BE WORKING ON IN THIS
SECTION TONIGHT.
>> YES, SO THEY'RE COMING
HERE, AND THEY'RE GOING TO
BUILD FROM SCRATCH THIS HOFFER
CRAFT.
THEY'LL RACE IT TEN TIMES
AROUND HERE, TIME IT, TOP
THREE GET MEDAL YAN, THEN WE
GO TO TOP EIGHT, WE WILL GET
CERTIFICATES.
>> SO RIGHT OVER HERE, THE
KIDS AREN'T HERE YET.
THEY DON'T GET HERE UNTIL
5:00.
LITTLE PREVIEW.
LET'S LET, THERE GO, THIS IS
THE WORK STATIONS FOR THE
KIDDOS RIGHT HERE.
SO THEY'LL HAVE THE TEAMS.
THEY'LL -- THIS IS FOR A
PRICE,  THIS IS FOR SOMEBOY
WILL BE A WINNER.
>> WE HAVE THE BRAGGING
RIGHTS, WEAVER SCHOOLS
COMPETING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
THEN WE HAVE THE TOP, TOP
TEAMS, GET MEDAL YAN, AND
DESIGN BY STUDENTS ALSO, SO
EVERY YEAR WE'RE DOING THIS,
SO KIDS CAN COME AWAY, SIXTH,
SEVENTH, EIGHTH, MULTIPLE
YEARS AS WINNERS, TOO.
>> COMING UP AT 5:00 WE WILL
MOVE TO ANOTHER SECTION I
THINK AND TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ELSE THAT'S GOING ON REALLY
COOL HERE.
THESE ARE 3D PRINTED GUYS, DID
IT HERE, THIRD, FOURTH, LOTS
OF THINGS, LIKE, THAT ALL
ABOUT SCIENCE, ESPECIALLY KIDS
LEARNING MORE ABOUT SCIENCE,
AND A HOVER CRAFT.
HOW COOL IS THAT, GUYS?
HOVER CRAFTER.
>> YES, AND EVERY BIG HOVER
CRAFTER HAS TO START
SOMEWHERE, RIGHT, HAS TO START
SMALL LIKE THAT?
>> RIGHT, JUST A BABE.
>> I WE'VE COME SO FAR FROM
THE DAYS EVERY JUST DOING THE
POSTER BOARD WITH THE TWO SIDE
PANELS, I MEAN, HERE, I HEAR
THEY EVEN HAVE ESCAPE ROOMS TO
MARIO OUT, THERE DOING LIVE
FOOD CHALLENGE, PEOPLE HAVE TO
PREPARE FOOD, DO TASTE TEST F
YOU'RE GOING TO GO SEE SCIENCE
FAIR, TECH FAIR THERE IS SENT
TAKE, THIS IS WHAT GO TO SEE.
>> THAT'S AMAZING AND AMAZING
THEY'RE IN MIDDLE SCHOOL DOING
THIS, IMAGINE BE INNING HIGH
SCHOOL AND COLLEGE?
STILL TO COME, EMOTIONAL DAY
INSIDE THE STAPLES CENTER FOR
THE PUBLIC MEMORIAL TO KOBE
BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER GEE
ANN A WE ARE TALKING WITH
"TMZ" ABOUT.
THAT WILL AND NEW LAWSUIT
THAT'S BEEN ANNOUNCED BY VAN
ACE BRYANT ON THIS VERY DAY,
WE'LL HAVE THE DETAILS COMING
UP.
>> PLUS ACTRESS HILLARY DUFF
MAKING WAVES FOR CONFRONT AGO
PHOTOGRAPHER AT HER KIDS
FOOTBALL GAME.
IT WAS ALL CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
CAITLIN, WE WILL SHOW YOU
THAT.
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER THERE?
>> THANK YOU, ANGIE.
WRAPPING UP BEAUTIFUL
AFTERNOON.
TEMPERATURES STILL CLOSE TO 60 .
WE WILL KEEP THINGS MILD, BUT
WEREN'T DOUSING SOME RAIN
SHOWERS, SO LITTLE SOG TOY
START OFF YOUR TUESDAY.
WE'LL RUN FUTURE CAST, YOUR
FULL SEVEN DAY FORECAST COMING
UP WHEN FOX5 RETURNS.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
>> MEDFORD RIDERS BE ON THE
LOOK-OUT FOR POSSIBLE CHANGES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SARAH SIMMONS
HAS MORE ON THAT, AND WHAT
THEY'RE WORKING ON FOR THE
NEXT HOUR, HI, SARAH.
>> HI, GUYS, SOME OF THE TOP
STORIES WE'RE LOOKING AT COULD
LATE NIGHT SERVICE BE
RETURNING TO METRO?
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
MISSING IT SINCE THEY TOOK IT
AWAY A FEW YEARS AGO, THOUSAND
MIGHT COME BACK, BUT WILL
COST.
PLUS:  DC RANKS AT THE TOP
AFTER NEW LIST BASED ON THE
WORK THAT WE DO.
WE WILL EXPLAIN WHAT THAT IS
ALL ABOUT COMING UP AT 5:00.
SEEMS LIKE WE'RE ALWAYS MAKING
THE TOP OF THE LIST AND
USUALLY NOT A GOOD THING.
SO WE WILL SEE.
>> TAXES, TIME SPENT IN
TRAFFIC.
>> COST OF LIVING.
>> NEVER GOOD.
>> WHY ARE WE HERE AGAIN?
>> THAT'S A GREAT PLACE TO
LIVE, ANKLE.
>> I THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, OVER THE
WEEKENDS ACTRESS HILLARY DUFF
CONFRONTED PHOTOGRAPHER WHILE
AT HER SON'S BOOT GUAM GAME.
DID YOU HAVE HAS TWO CHILDREN,
SATURDAY MORNING SHE NOTICE
ADD MALE PHOTOGRAPHER TACKING
PHOTOS OF THE KIDS PLAYING.
HERE IS THE CONFRONTATION IN
WHICH SHE RECORDED AND SHARED
ON INSTAGRAM.
>> WHO ARE YOU HERE WITH?
>> I'M HERE WITH ME.
>> WITH YOU? DO YOU KNOW ANY
OF THE PEOPLE ON THE THEME.
>> NO.
>> OKAY, CAN YOU STOP TAKING
PICTURES OF THE KIDS PLEASE?
>> IT IS LEGAL.
>> IT IS MAKING ME FEEL REALLY
UN COMFORTABLE.
>> YOU SHOULDN'T FEEL
UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU WANT ME TO SHOW YOU.
D?
>> I AM NOT ASKING FOR ID I'M
ASKING TO YOU STOP TAKING
PICTURES OF OUR SEVEN YEAR OLD
CHILDREN IF YOU DON'T KNOW WIN
THAT'S HERE.
>> WELL IT IS LEGAL.
>> I'M ASKING YOU HUMAN TO
HUMAN AS A MOTHER IF YOU DON'T
KNOW ANYONE HERE CAN YOU
PLEASE STOP TAKING PICTURES OF
OUR CHILDREN PLAYING FOOTBALL?
>> I MEAN I'M WITH HER,
HILLARY DUFF OR NOT, FAMOUS
PERSON OR NOT.
>> YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
WHENEVER WE DO STORIES, EVEN
FOR THE NEWS, WE HAVE A
DISCLOSURE, KIDS.
>> ANYTHING.
>> BUT YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
DISCLOSURE, LITTLE --
>> TIMES JUST WEIRD.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND IT MAKES THE PARENTS
UNCOMFORTABLE, JUST NOT
APPROPRIATE.
>> WELL DID YOU HAVE WROTE
PAPARAZZI SHOOTING KIDS GO
PRACTICE PHOTOGRAPHY ON
ADULTS, CREEP.
THE PHOTOGRAPHER CLAIMS HE WAS
JUST THERE PRACTICING HIS
PHOTOGRAPHY, DUFFIN CYST
DOLLARS THAT HE WAS MAKING HER
UNCOMFORTABLE, AS YOU HEARD,
AND I THINK SHE WAS PROBABLY
NOT THE ONLY ONE THAT WAS
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> WHICH IF YOU DO WANT TO
PRACTICE YOUR PHOTOGRAPHY OF
COURSE MAYBE HE'LL BE SPORTS
PHOTOGRAPHER, ASK THE COACH
AHEAD OF TIME.
>> YES.
>> EXPLAIN WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
THAT WAY IF PARENTS ASK, IT IS
ALL ABOVE BOARD.
>> PROBABLY SHOULD JUST GO
TOOK TAKE A HIKE AND TAKE
PICTURES EVERY NATURE GLUE
TODAY 20,000 PEOPLE PACKED THE
STAPLES CENTER IN LOST ANGLER
KOBE BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER
GIANNA'S PUBLIC MEMORIAL.
>> VAN'S SUING THE COMPANY
THAT OWNED HELICOPTER IN THAT
CRASH.
"TMZ" ALL OVER THIS STORY.
LAURA JOINING US LIVER, AND
THIS CEREMONY WAS VERY
EMOTIONAL TODAY.
VAN'S BRYANT ACTUALLY SPOKE.
AND I BELIEVE WE HAVE SOME
VIDEO THAT FAR.
TELL US WHAT HAPPENED INSIDE
THE STAPLES CENTER.
>> YES, SO DURING THE
CELEBRATION OF LIFE TODAY,
EVEN JUST WATCHING IT, LIKE
PRETTY MUCH A TEARJERKER, THE
WHOLE TIME, BEYONCE OPENED IT
UP SINGING OPENING NUMBER
TALKING ABOUT HOW SHE WAS ONE
EVERY KOBE'S FAVORITE SONGS,
DID HER SONG HALO.
THE TONS OF STARS, IN
ATTENDANCE AS YOU CAN IMAGINE,
KIM AND KANYE, DUANE JUAN
GABRIELLE UNION, "MAGIC"
JOHNSON, JIMMY KIMMEL NINE
HOST OF THE CEREMONY AND SPOKE
AND DEUCE DOLLARS VAN'S BRYANT
WHO STOOD UP AND SHARED PRETTY
HEARTWARMING MEMORIES OF GIGI,
OF KOBE, AND I MEAN JUST TO
SEE HER STRENGTH, IT WAS AMAZE
TO GO SEE, AND THEN YOU ALSO
HAVE SHACK WHO SPOKE AND
SHARED SOME STORIES OF THE TWO
OF THEM, TALKING ABOUT FUNNY
MOMENTS, JUST BROUGHT PEOPLE
TOGETHER, AND KNOWING THAT
LIKE, YOU KNOW, THAT MA THAT
WAS BROTHER, WILL SEE HIM AT
SOME POINT AGAINST, LATER IN
ANOTHER LIFE.
AN I THINK WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT ALL OF THIS STUFF, AND
YOU THINK ABOUT THESE HUGE
CELEBRITIES THE FIRST PERSON
THAT COMES TO MINDS MICHAEL
JORDAN, EVERYONE KNOWS, AND HE
GOT UP AND SPOKE AS WELL TOO,
AND WAS FULL OF TEARS AS HE
SPOKE.
TALKED ABOUT HOW KOBE WOULD
REACH OUT TO HIM FOR ADVICE,
NOT JUST ABOUT BASKETBALL
EITHER.
>> WE WEREN'T ALLOW TO AIR ANY
CLIPS UNTIL IT WAS FINISH, SO
JUST FINISHED, WE WILL VERY
MUCH MORE COMING UP IN THE
LATER NEWSCAST, WE WANT TO GET
TO THE LAWSUIT THOUGH, VAN'S
BRYANT SUING THE OWNER OF THE
HELICOPTER COMPANY.
>> YES.
SO VAN'S BRYANT HAS SUED THE
HELICOPTER COMPANY THAT WAS --
IS RESPONSIBLE SHE IS SAYING
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR KILLING
KOBE AND GIGI AND SEVEN OTHERS
ON THE PLANE THE LAWSUIT
ALLEGES ISLAND EXPRESS WAS
ONLY ALLOWED TO FLY UNDER
VISUAL FLIGHT RULES.
AND THE CONDITIONS THAT DAY OF
THE CRASH WERE NOT CONDUCIVE
FOR THEM TO BE FLYING.
SO SHE, YOU KNOW; SAYING THAT
SHE IS ASKING FOR PUNITIVE
DAMAGES BUT THERE IS NO ACTUAL
NUMBER AND WHEN THAT COULD
MEAN BECAUSE IT COULD BE
MILLIONS.
YES, AND INTERESTING POINT
HERE, SHE POINTS OUT IN THE
LAWSUIT THE PILOT WAS
DISCIPLINED IN 2015 FOR
VIOLATE THE VISUAL FLIGHT RULE
MINIMUMS.
SO, CRASHES I GUESS WE HAVE
JUST HAVE TO SAY HOW THIS
PLAYS OUT.
>> I IMAGINE SHE WANTS THE
RULES CHANGED AS WELL WHICH IS
THE REASON SHE IS BRINGING
THIS LAWSUIT.
SHE DOESN'T NEED THE MONEY BUT
SUING FOR PUNITIVE DAMAGES AS
WELL.
LAUREN LAROSA, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>>> "TMZ" AIRS AT CLOCK 30
HERE ON FOX5 AFTER LIKE IT OR
NOT.
>> HELLO, LEONARDTOWN,
MARYLAND.
WELL, NO.
>> CLOSE.
>> MY HOW YOU'VE CHANGED OVER
THE WEEKENDS, GAITHERSBURG,
HI, MOVING ALONG HERE, AND
CAITLIN, I MEAN IT, LOOKS LIKE
EVERYTHING IS NICE AND DRY
RIGHT NOW.
BUT YOU ARE SAYING CHANGES ON
THE WAY?
>> SHOWERS MOVING N WAY AFTER
THE EVENING COMMUTE WHICH YOU
CAN STILL SEE LITTLE BIT OF
BLUE SKY, THERE SOME NICE
SUNSHINE, ON A BEAUTIFUL
MONDAY.
COMING OFF GREAT WEEKENDS.
I MEAN,  THIS IS WINTER, IN
2020, I GUESS.
WE HAVE HAD SOME COLD DAYS, WE
WILL GET NEW MORE, BUT MOST OF
THIS HAS BEEN COME PROS YOU
HAD OF WELL ABOVE NORMAL
TEMPERATURES, AND THAT
CONTINUED TODAY.
WE DO HAVE SOME SHOWERS MOVING
IN TONIGHT, MOST OF US THIS
WON'T BE UNTIL AFTER MIDNIGHT,
SO, THE EVENING HOURS SHOULD
BE FINE.
WE WILL HAVE KIM OF ROUNDS OF
RAIN, THROUGH WEDNESDAY NIGHT,
DRYING OUT AGAIN THURSDAY, BUT
THAT WILL BE FOLLOWED BY
ANOTHER BLAST OF SOME COLD
AIR.
SO WE'VE BEEN IN THIS PATTERN
MILD AND SHOWERY DURING THE
WEEK, AND THEN COLDER AND
SUNNY TO START THE WEEKEND.
WE WILL DO THAT YET AGAIN
HEADING INTO NEXT WEEKEND.
LOOK AT HIGH TEMPERATURES
TODAY, WE HIT ZERO SIX AT
REAGAN NATIONAL.
SIXTEEN DULLOS, 59 AT BWI.
AVERAGE HIGH LATE FEBRUARY,
49.
WELL ABOVE NORMAL YET AGAIN
AND DESPITE THE CLOUD COVER
HITTING 06 DEGREES PRETTY
IMPRESSIVE.
IN THE 50'S OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW.
STILL VERY COMFORTABLE.
FIFTY-SEVEN IN BALTIMORE.
FIFTY-NINE IN GAITHERSBURG, 61
IN FREDERICK.
FIVE WINCHESTER.
FIFTY-SIX IN CUMBERLAND.
MILD AIR ALL ACROSS THE
KNOTTER EAST.
WELL ABOVE FREEZING IN
CHICAGO.
48 DEGREES WHERE THEY'RE
SEEING RAIN SHOWERS.
LOOK AT NEW YORK 56.
LOOK AT BOSTON, 61.
I MEAN I THINK EVERYONE HAS
JUST ABOUT PUT A FORK IN THIS
WINTER BECAUSE WE DON'T SEE
ANYTHING EXCEPT SHOT OF COLD
AIR HEADED INTO THE WEEKEND T
WON'T BE ACCOMPANIED BY ANY
RISK FOR WET WEATHER.
HERE IS THE WET WEATHER MOVING
IN SHORTLY.
SATELLITE AND RADAR SHOWING
SPRAWLING LOW PRESSURE SYSTEM,
BACK ACROSS THE OHIO VALLEY,
PLENTY OF RAIN SHOWERS, THAT
ARE INCH.
INTO PARTS OF WEST VIRGINIA,
AND SOUTHWESTERN VIRGINIA.
APPROACHING ROANOKE WITHIN THE
NEXT HOUR.
THEN FROM THERE MOVING
SOUTHWEST TO NORTHEAST ACROSS
THE STATE.
SO FOR YOUR EVENING PLANNER,
TEMPERATURES ARE IN THE 50'S,
IT IS MILD, MOSTLY CLOUDY AT
7:00 P.M.
BY 11:00, MAYBE AREAS TOWARD
OUR SOUTH AND WEST STARTING TO
SEE SOME RAIN SHOWERS.
HERE IS FUTURE CAST.
WHICH SHOWS BY 10:00;
1:00 P.M., FREDERICK BERG,
MAYBE OVER, TOWARD THE 81
CORRIDOR, CHARLOTTESVILLE, YOU
GUYS STARTING TO SEE SOME RAIN
SHOWERS, FILLS IN OVERNIGHT,
THAT'S AS WE HEAD OUT TO THE
BUS STOP DRIVE IN TOMORROW
MORNING WE HAVE SOME WET
WEATHER AROUND.
SO COUNT ON IT BEING LITTLE
RAIN TOY START YOUR TUESDAY.
SHOWERS WILL BE OFF AND ON AS
THAT WARMFRONT LIFTS THROUGH.
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT THE CASE
IS WE WILL GET THE SHOWERS
FIRST AND THEN THE AFTERNOON
WILL PROBABLY JUST BE CLOUDY
FOGGY DAMP.
NOT VERY NICE.
BUT I THINK THE STEADIER RAIN
SHOWERS WILL BE IN THE FIRST
HALF OF THE DAY.
FAST FORWARDS TO WEDNESDAY.
WE HAVE ANOTHER LOW PRESSURE
SYSTEM ON THE HEALS THAT FAR
ONE ON TUESDAY.
WHICH WILL BRING IN ADDITIONAL
ROUND OF SOME SHOWERS.
OUT AHEAD OF IT, STILL VERY
MILD, 50'S, MAYBE EVEN SOME
60S, BUT, STEADY RAIN AND THEN
GUSTING WINDS BEHIND IT
WEDNESDAY NIGHT INTO THURSDAY.
SO THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS
HAVE THE UMBRELLA HANDY AND
THE RAIN GEAR, 52 TOMORROW,
SHOWERS MOSTLY IN THE MORNING
BUT COULD STILL SEE SPOTTY
DRIZZLE THROUGH THE AFTERNOON,
BREAK FIRST HALF OF WEDNESDAY
BUT THEN GUSTY RAIN SHOWERS
AFTER THAT HIGH TEMPERATURE OF
58 DEGREES.
SO LOOK AT YOUR SEVEN DAY,
BEHIND IT, WE TURN BREEZY,
COLDER ON THURSDAY AS WE DRY
THINGS OUT.
TEMPERATURES BACK TO NORMAL.
AND THEN COLD INTO THE
WEEKENDS, SO LAST FEW DAYS OF
FEBRUARY, HERE, WE ROUNDS IT
OUT WITH SOME CHILLY WEATHER
JUST SUNSHINE THOUGH WITH THE
COLD TEMPERATURES, IN THE
40'S, AND 20'S, OVER THE
WEEKENDS, AND INTO NEXT WEEK.
THAT'S A LOOK AT YOUR SEVEN
DAY FORECAST, FOX5 AT FOUR
WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
We made USAA insurance for
members like Kate.
A former Army medic, made of the
flexibility to handle
whatever Monday has in store and
tackle four things at once.
So when her car got hit, she
didn't worry.
She simply filed a claim on her
USAA app and said...
I got this.
USAA insurance is made the way
Kate needs it - easy.
She can even pick her payment
plan
so it's easy on her budget
and her life.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
This home is equipped with Gig
Speed Internet from Xfinity.
There's this game-time
Internetting room. So fun.
And then there's this work
-from-home Internetting room.
Finally, the open-concept
Internetting room.
This is not an open house.
But your front door was open,
so technically it is.
Get gig speed and the
coverage you need with Xfinity
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get $100
back with this great offer.
Plus, get a free
upgrade to Gig speed.
That's a savings of
$360. Switch today.
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any make, any model,
any age, any price ♪
♪ From 50 bucks to 100 grand ♪
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any, any, any, any ♪
your car is hassle-free
ing in our selling
with just three easy steps.
One, get your free
online valuation.
Two, drive to your local
car buying centre.
And three,
walk out with your check
in as little as 30 minutes.
So don't wait.
Get your free online
valuation now.
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
♪ At webuyanycar.com ♪
I like Liberty Mutual.
They get that no two people are
alike and customize your car
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
insurance so you only
pay for what you need.
What do you think?
I don't see it.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
.
>>> A GROUP OF COLLEGE UPSTATE
NEW YORK WENT TO STEAMY
HELPINGTH, THE ONLY CHICK-FIL-A
NEARBY IS AT THE ALBANY
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT, THEY
BOUGHT A PLANE THE TICKET, ONE
WENT THROUGH SECURITY TO BUY IT.
15 CHICKEN SANDWICHES 15 LARGE
FRIES, 156 NUGGETS, THEY PAID
ABOUT 550 FOR THE PLANE TICKET
AND $12 FOR THE FOOD.
I MEAN, THEY DID THE RIGHT MATH
AND THAT'S NOT BAD.
>> AS SOMEONE WHO FLY AS LOT.
THE AIRPORTS ARE NOT GOING TO
LIKE THIS, YOU HAVE 24 HOUR
CANCELATION ON SECURITY.
>> NEWS YOU CAN USE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US AT 4:00.
>> NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> AT 5:00, BACK-TO-BACK
CARJACKING INCIDENTS ONE AT
PENTAGON CITY, THE NEXT AT
PENTAGON ROW HAVE POLICE URGING
RESIDENTS TO BE VIGILANT AND BE
WHERE OF YOUR SURROUNDINGS.
DETAILS NEXT.
>>> A POSSIBLE SYRINGE ATTACK IN
MARYLAND CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
>>> AND A ROMANCE WITH METRO AT
THE HEART OF IT.
WHAT'S BEHIND UNUSUAL ENGAGEMENT
STORY, NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS NOW.
♪.
>>> OFF THE TOP AT 5:00, JUST
TWO HOURS