DELIVERYES, AMAZON MAKING A
BIG CHANGE.
BEST WAY TO MAKE SURE YOUR
GIFTS ARRIVE ON TIME.
"FOX5" MORNING AT 7 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>>  WELL, GOOD TUESDAY MORNING
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>> I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR.
>> IF YOU JUST WAKE UP HOBB A
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE RIGHT THERE
BEAUTIFUL CAPITAL WHEEL.
RAINY DAY ON TAP.
GRAB UMBRELLA AAND HEAD OUT.
WIND KICKS UP TODAY.
>>  THAT'S ONE OF THE KEYS
TODAY WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON
WHIPPED, RAIN, LOOKS NITION
NATIONAL HARBOR.
>> WE'LL SEE DRIZZLE OUT TH
THERE.
>>  YOU WILL NOTICE DRIZZLE
AND GRAY SKIES AND COOL
CONDITIONS.
ONLY IN 30s TO START THE DAY.
LISTEN SURPRISE AND WHIPPED
LATE THIS AFTERNOON AS THE
COLD FRONT COMES THROUGH.
>> COULD BE WORSE.
>>  TAKE UMBRELLA AHERE GOOD
NEWS COULD BE WORSE.
IT TEMPERATURES GENERALLY
ABOVE FREEZING.
WE'RE NOT DEALING WITH FROZEN
PRECIP OUT THERE.
SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST FOR
TUESDAY.
THINGS WILL LOOK BRIGHTER
TOMORROW.
I'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS
MOMENTARILY.
>> TRACKING ROADS AROUND THE
DMV AA LOT OF BRAKE LIGHT
BEHIND ME.
WE'LL BRAKE IT ALL DOWN AND
GET A LOOK BEHIND THE DMV
METRO NORMAL OUGHT BY GLE
GLENMONT.
>>> WE'LL START WITH DIS
DISTURBING STORY OUT OF
FAIRFAX COUNTY TWO TEACHERS
ARE AID OF ABUSING SEVERAL NON
VERBAL SPECIAL NEEDS CHILDREN.
>> MELANIE ALNWICK JOINS US
LIVE FROM VIENNA THIS MORNING
WITH MORE NOW.
MEL, GOOD MORNING.
>>  GOOD MORNING WHAT WE AS
FAR AS BUS AT FREEDOM HILL
HMENTRY SCHOOL IS STARTED LAST
SCHOOL YEAR.
EMPLOYEES NOTICED BRINGS ON
STUDENTS AND THAT'S WHEN AT
THE CONTACTED THE NEW
PRINCIPAL AND TOGETHER THAT IS
HOW THIS CASE GOT INTO THE
HANDS OF FAIRFAX COUNTY PO
POLICE.
AND SO NOW WE HAVE TWO TEACH
AGO SIGNATURE ANTS THAT WERE
IN THE SPECIAL ED CLASSROOM.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT SAMIRA GUS
GUS AND CECELIA BENAVIDES BOTH
TEACHING ASSISTANCE AND GASTAV
AND WE'RE TOLD THEY COULD GET
SUBSTANTIAL JAIL TIME.
SCOTT BLUM IS FOREMAN FREEDOM
HILL PRINCIPAL CHARGED WITH
FAILING TO REPORT SUSPECTSED
AABUSE TO CHILD PROTECTIVE
SERVICES OR POLICE AS REQUIRED
BY LAW.
GUS GASTAV AND BEP BEP ARE
ACCUSED OF ABUSING STUDENTS IN
THEIR CLASSROOM AND CRUELTY
AND WHEN FORMAL PRINCIPAL PLUM
WAS TOLD OF SUSPECTED ABUSE
WHEN HERE AT THE SCHOOL LAST
COOL YEAR HE HAD A
CONVERSATION WITH ONE OF THE
TEACHING ASSISTANTS ONE ON ONE
AND DID NOT CONTACT POLICE.
THE ALLEGATIONS ARE TOUGH TO
HEAR.
>>  I WAS SADDENED.
THERE'S NOT -- THIS IS NOT
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN IN THE
CLASSROOM.
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN AT
HOME.
THESE ARE THE MOST VULNERABLE
MEMBERS OF OUR COMMUNITY.
NOT ONLY ARE THEY ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL KIDS BUT THEY'RE NON
VERBAL.
>>  NOW GASTAV AND BENAVIDES
HAVE 20 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE
COMBINED IN SPESHLD OCCASIONS
AND TIMER ONE IS CLASSROOM
TEACHER.
THEY'RE BOTH TEACH AGO
SIGNATURE ANTS IN THE
CLASSROOM.
FAIRFAX PUBLIC SCHOOLS
APOLOGIZED IN A LETTER TO THE
COMMUNITY AND FAMILIES AND
REITERATED THEIR RAINING AND
SAID THEY WILL DO MORE TR
TRAINING TO MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY KNOWS THEIR DUTY
WHEN'S IT COMES TO SUSPECTSED
CHILD AUSE.
IT IMMEDIATELY REMOVED TWO
TEACH AGO SIGNATURE ANSWER AS
SOON AS THEY LEARNED OF
ALLEGATIONS AND THEN CONDUCTED
THEIR OWN INTERNAL
INVESTIGATION.
FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE SAY THEY
BELIEVE THEY ARE COMPLETELY
DONE WITH ALL THE INTERVIEWS
AND IDENTIFIED ALL OF THE
VICTIMS THIS THIS CASE AND
HOWEVER BECAUSE THE TWO
TEACHING ASSIST APTS HAVE
SPEND TIME IN FAIRFAX COUNTY
PUBLIC SCHOOLS THEY SAY IF
ANYONE HAS ANY KNOWLEDGE OF
ANY OTHER THINGS THEY SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT PLEASE CONTACT
POLICE.
>> GOOD AT VICE, MEL, THANK
YOU VERY MUCH.
>> NORTHERN NORP VIR TOWER TOY
MARYLAND STEPS UP PATROLS.
A DAY AFTER A WOMAN WAS
ASSAULTED THIS HAPPENED BEFORE
7 A.M. YESTERDAY IN THE 6 OF
00 BLOCK OF HANOVER PARKWAY.
THE VICTIM TOLD POLICE A MAN
DRESSED IN ALL BLACK GRABBED
HER FROM BEHIND AND DRAGGED
HER INTO WOODED AREA WHERE HE
TRIED TO SEXUALLY ASSAULT HER.
THE WOMAN USED PEPPER SPRAY ON
THE SPUTION SPEND AND HE TOOK
OFF.
>>  DESK OUT OF NEW YORK A
14-YEAR-OLD BELIEVED TO BE A
SUSPECT IN DEADLY TAPPING OF A
BARNAARD COLLEGE STUDENT FROM
VIRGINIA ON THE RUN.
WE'RE TOLD HE WAS IN A CAB
REQUEST LIZ MOTHER ON THE WAY
TO TURN HIMSELF INTO POLICE
WHEN HE JUNEED OUT OF THE CAB
AND RAN.
POLICE ARE NOW LOOKING FOR
HIM.
AND 1-YEAR-OLD TESSA MAJOR OF
CHARLOTTESVILLE WAS STABBED TO
DEATH LAST WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
POLICE ALREADY ARRESTED A
13-YEAR-OLD.
THEY SAY HE CONFESSED TO BEING
INVOLVED AND IS DUE IN COURT
TODAY.
>>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT THE
DEATH TOLL RISING AAS
TORNADOES WOMEN THROUGH THE
DEEP SOUTH LEAVING PARTS NIPD
LOUISIANA, ALABAMA, TEXAS.
THREE CONFIRMED DEAD AND A
DOZEN INJURED.
ONEISTER IS WAS ON THE GROUND
MORE THAN 60 MILES.
>>  UP USUAL TO GET TORNADOES
OF THAT UP TENSETY THIS TIME
OF YEAR.
THIS IS TYPICALLY A PRETTY
QUIET TIME OF YEARS.
>>  IT'S LOOSELY ASSOCIATED
WITH WARM WE'RE DEAL WITH
HERE.
>> LET'S HOP IN AND WE GOT
CLOUDY SKIES.
COOL CONDITIONS AND SOME LIGHT
DRIZZLE, RAIN, BLOOMY, BLAH,
BLARKS ALL THAT MORE OF THAT
TODAY.
>>  YES.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
>>  I DO.
>>  GOOD NEWS THIS IS THE LAST
DAY OF IT AND WE'LL BE BACK
FROM IT SUN SMIN TOMORROW.
TEMPS THIS IS CRITICAL.
YESTERDAY OF COURSE WE'RE
DEALING WITH SNOW ACROSS THE
AREA.
TODAY IT'S JUST A LIGHT RAIN.
37 REAGAN NATIONAL AND 35
DULLES AND 38 THIS MORNING BWI
MARSHALL.
MOST EVERYBODY SOKD IN THE
CLOUD COVER WITH FOG AND
DRIZZLE OUT.
THERE EVEN LIGHT SHOWERS
APASSING SOUTH AND EAST OF
TOWN SOUTHERN IT'S POSSIBLE
WITH THIS LITTLE PINK THERE
COULD BE LIGHT BREEZING
DRIZZLE TO HAIRINGZ TOWN AND
STRASBURG THAT'S IT FOR FROZEN
PRECIPITATION.
MOST OF OUR AREA IN THE CLEAR
WITH DEALING WITH ANYTHING
FROST ADVISORY EP.
COLD FRONT TO THE WEST AAND
ONCE WE GET THE BATCH EVER
SHOWERS EAST WE SHOULD SEE
CLEARING SKIES AND QUIETER
CONDITIONS.
AGAIN THAT TAKES MUCH OF THE
DAY TODAY.
LAST OF SHOWERS PROBABLY GET
THROUGH HERE 4, 5:00 THIS
AFTERNOON AND THINGS START TO
CLEAR OUT AND DRY OUT TONIGHT.
50.
LITTLE MILDER THAN YESTERDAY.
STILL, WITH CLOUD COVER EACH
SHOWERS FEELS LIKE CHILLY,
CHILLY DAY.
MAKING HE NERVOUS.
>>  WHY AIM MAKING YOU NER
NERVOUS.
>>  I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO JUMP ON ME.
>> IN YOUR DREAMS I WAS JUST
GETTING MY CLICKER.
270 SOUTHBOUND TO FREDERICK TO
BELTWAY.
WE HAVE HEAVY VOLUME
MONTGOMERY.
2 IT 1 MILE APP HOUR ARM AND
THEN AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY OUT
OUTER LOOP 10 MILE AN HOUR
AVERAGE IT 7, HEAVIER THERE.
GW PARKWAY SOUTHBOUND.
TWO LANES BLOCKED AFTER
MEMORIAL BRIDGE AND TRAFFIC
ANALYZE RESERVED.
OVERALL THAT SHOULD DISSIPATE
QUICKLY AND FAIRFAX COUNTRY
CRASH BLOCKED POPE'S HEAD.
395 LOOKING GOOD UNTIL YOU
GENT TO PENTAGON AND THEN SLOW
A BIT.
IT IT 9 THE 5 NORTHBOUND
BELTWAY ON THROUGH LABORATORY
ROAD.
HEAVY VOLUME.
SAY SAT IN THAT THE AREA DAY
WHEN WE WERE DRIVING AROUND
THAT'S A BRUTAL COMMUTE WITH
LOTS OF VOLUME.
METRO BACK TOOK ON TIME.
GLENMONT CLEARED ON RED LINE.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> MORE MOP CHURCH IN HOT
WATER FOR SOAKING ACCORDING TO
WASHINGTON POST FUND WERE
MRAKD TO THE IRS THAT IS WORTH
100 BILLION TLARZ.
WHISTLE BLOWERS ALLEGING
CHURCH AND INVESTMENT FORM
VIOLATED SEVERAL TAX LAWS AND
SHOULD PAY THE GOVERNMENT YONZ
FOR THOSE VIOLATIONS.
>>  HEALTH OFFICIALS IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA SAY
TRAVELERS AT LAX MAY HAVE BEEN
EXPOSED TO MEASLES.
A PASSENGER WITH VIRAL UP
INSPECTION TRAVELED THROUGH
THE AIRPORT LAST WEEK.
ANYONE WHO TRAVELED THROUGH
TERMINAL FOUR OR FIVE ON
DECEMBER 11 COULD BE AT RISK
OF DEVELOPING MEASLES.
>>> ON-CALL TOLL HILL THIS MAY
NOW BE IMPEACHMENT EAVE AS THE
HOUSE IS POISED FOR HISTORIC
VOTE AND DEMOCRATS ARE
EXPECTED TO PASS THE ARTICLE
OF IMPEACHMENT.
AND THERE ARE ALL RIGHT MEETS
TODAY TO SET TERMS OF
IMPREEVMENT VOTE OF HOW
HISTORIC PROS WILL PLAY OUT.
>>> THERE HAS NEVER BEEN DEALS
LIKE THIS PLAYED.
>>  IT'S BUSINESS AS USUAL
SEEMINGLY IMPOSSIBLE FOR WHAT
IS HAPPENING AT THE END OF THE
AVENUE SGLE CHUCK SCHUMER
ALREADY DEMANDING WITNESSES
FOR THE SENATE TRIAL THAT
WOULD FOLLOW TOMORROW'S
EXPECTED IMPEACH.
VOTE.
HE WANT TO HEAR FROM ACTING
WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF MIC
MULVANEY.
FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR JOHN BOLDEN AND BUDGET
OFFICIAL AND MULVANEY AID.
>> THERE IS NO REASON ON GOD'S
GREEN EARTH WHERE THEY SHOULD
NOT BE CALLED AND TESTIFY
UNLESS YOU'RE AFRAID OF WHAT
THEY MIGHT SAY.
>>  WE DON'T DO THINGS BECAUSE
SENATOR SHIRM ASKS US TO PLAY
THEM.
>>  IT REST MITCH MONTGOMERY
CONNELL.
>> I'LL BE VOTING VERY ON
OBSTRUCTION OF CONGRESS.
>>  MEANTIME MORE ARE WAIRING
ING IN.
>>  FOR SOME DEMOCRATS THIS
WILL BE TOUGH VOTE.
NEW JERSEY JEFF VAP DREW IS
EXPECTED TO SWITCH PARTIES AND
VOTE AGAINST IMPEEVEMENT AS
REPUBLICAN.
ALLISON.
>>  THANK U. 7:10 NOW STILL A
LOT OF CONCERNS YEARS AFTER A
KAEDLY EXPLOSION AT MONTGOMERY
COUNTRY APARTMENT COMPLEX.
WHAT RESIDENTS NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT A PUBLIC HEARING TON
TONIGHT.
BOB BARNARD HAS THAT NEXT.
>>  PLUS DAYS AFTER HIS
EMOTIONAL HEISMAN SPEECH LSU
QUARTERBACK HOME TOUXT THAT
STORY COMING UP:10.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
There was a time when health
care made house calls...
That time has come again.
Thanks to CVS Health.
With home infusion services.
In-home care managers.
Home delivery.
And video visits.
We're creating the future
of health care,
using a simple idea
form the past.
CVS Health.
Where health is everything.
>> YEAH THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
DEALING WITH THIS MORNING.
>>  IT'S NOT PRETTY OUT THERE
IS IT.
>>  TAKE YOUR TIME.
>>  THESE THINGS HIT I OUT OF
NOWHERE.
>>  I'M GOING TO BE HONEST.
SURPRISE SURPRISE.
>> IT'S OVERCAST AND GLOOMY
START TO DAY.
>>  AT LEAST THE TEMPERATURES
ARE UP A DEGREE OR TWO FROM
YESTERDAY.
>>  THERE MIINGING A POCKET OF
FREEZING DRIZZLE OFF TO THE
NORTH AND WEST THIS MORNING.
SO IF YOU'RE WATCHING FROM
WELL OFF NORTH AND WEST
THERE'S A LIVE LOOK AT
SATELLITE REIGN A DAR.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT WARM FRONT
COMING THROUGH AND
TEMPERATURES GET A BOOST
TODAY.
MID UP TOER 40s.
MAYBE WE'LL TOP 150 LATER THIS
AFTERNOON AND THEN WE'LL GET A
COLD FRONT BY MID TO LATE
AFTERNOON.
AND THAT WILL BE THE END OF
THIS SYSTEM.
SO BOTTOM LINE IS MUCH OF YOUR
TUESDAY WILL BE CLOUD FILLED
WITH OCCASIONAL SHOWERS AND
THEN AS THAT FRONT SWINGS
THROUGH LATER THIS AFTERNOON
WE START DRYING PROCESS AND
CLEARING OUT PROCESS TONIGHT.
THE WINDS PICK UP AND COLDER
AIR STARTS TO RUSH N TRAVELING
TODAY THE REAL TROUBLE UP AND
DOWN THE EASTERN SEA BOARD
IT'S SNOWING IN BOSTON.
JUST RAIN IN NEW YORK THIS
MORNING AND MOST -- LOOK HOW
QUIET MOST OF THE COUNTRY IS
ALL THE WAY OUT TO CALIFORNIA.
LIGHT RAIN LATER TONIGHT AND
FOR THE DAY ON WEDNESDAY.
>> 40 TOMORROW.
NICE WEEKP SUNSHINE.
IT WILL BE CHILLY AROUND HERE,
WEDNESDAY, THURSDAY, FRIDAY,
AND LET'S ALL CELEBRATE THE
FIRST DAVE WINTER TOGETHER
DAY.  4 2.  BY EARLY NEXT WEEK
WE'LL ADD DAY LIGHT EACH AND
EVERY DAY.
THERE'S SOMETHING TO LOCK
FORWARD TO.  ERIN, GOOD
MORNING.
>>  7:15 TUCKER IS IN BEST
MOOD EVER IT GIVES STRIINGLE
HE FEVINGT EVERYBODY BEING IN
A BETTER MOOD.
LEFT LANE BLOCKED AFTER KEY
BRIDGE.
THIS IS CRASH PREVIOUSLY GW
PARKWAY DEALING WITH VOLL NUM
THAT AREA.
GEORGETOWN MEMORIAL BRIDGE
HEAVY INBOUND AS WELL.
THERE'S SOUTHBOUND CRASH AFTER
MEMORIAL BRIDGE BLOCKING RIGHT
LANE.
SEVERAL CRASHS IN THAT AREA
USE CAUTION.
4 INBOUND HEAVY VOLUME AS WELL
AND BAY BRIDGE DON'T FORGET
LONG TERM CONSTRUCTION THAT'S
A NASTY LOOK AT EASTERN SHORE
TO ANNAPOLIS THIS MORNING.
AGAIN WHITE WESTBOUND LANE
REMAINS CLOSED AND MILES OF
BACKUPPED TRAFFIC THIPZ OPEN
TO 97.
KEEP ILL WORTH SO MILE AN HOUR
AVERAGE.
SOUTHBOUND PAST EASTERN AV
AVENUE.
50 INBOUND 202 TO 95, 11 MILES
AN HOUR.
AND JAMMED TO BW PARKWAY DOWN
FROM WRAP.
AVENUE.
INBOUND JACKED AND UPPER
MALBORO AND 301 AT THE 5 SPLIT
AAS USUAL JAMS UP IN IT
BRANDYWINE AND 270 SOUTHBOUND
YOU'RE HEAVY.
17 MILE AN HOUR AVERAGE 370 TO
SBLIT.
ANY QUESTIONS ERINFOX5DC ON
TWITTER METRO IS ON TIME BACK
TO YOU.
>>  STRIKING WORKERS AS BUS
GARAGE IN LORTON RETURNS TO
WORK WHILE UNION CONTINUES TO
FIGHTS FOR NEW CONTRACT.
SIRPD BED ROAD BUSH WORKERS
NEW NEGOTIATIONS SAID TO BE
RESULT OF FOUR-YEAR DEAL METRO
REACHED WITH UNION LEADERS.
>>.
LAW MAKE AERNZ UNION LEADERS
GAERMER EGG AT LAND-OVER TO
SHOW SUPPORT FOR AFFECTED
WORKERS BIR THE SHOPPER STORE
CLOSURES.
AND BECAUSE OF THE STORE
SHOPPERS PLAN TO SHUT DOWN
CLOSURES.
FOUR STORES IN THE D.C. REGION
SHOPPERS PLAN TO SHUT DOWN
AND BALTIMORE AND CELL 1 SELL
FOUR STORES IN THE D.C. REGION
13 OTHERS TO DIFFERENT OTHER
AND BALTIMORE AND CELL 1 SELL
DPROSRY KHAIPZ.
13 OTHERS TO DIFFERENT OTHER
>> HAPPENING TODAY D.C.
DPROSRY KHAIPZ.
COUNCIL AND BODY CAMERAS AND
>> HAPPENING TODAY D.C.
PUBLIC ACCESS TO THE VIDEO.
COUNCIL AND BODY CAMERAS AND
>>  AND UNDER THE CURRENT LAW
IN THE DISTRICT AND LEGAL
REPRESENTATION.
>>  TE MOOT ELING WILL BEGIN
AT 10 A.M.
>>  ELECTION DAY LESS THAN A
YEAR AAWAY AND WHEN MARYLAND
VOTESERS CASTING BALLOTS
THEY'LL GOT AA REDESIGNED I
VOTED STICKER.
STATE SPONS ORDER A CONTEST AT
MORE THAN 6 OF 00 PEOPLE
SUBMITTED ENTRIES AND THE
STATE USES THREE DIFFERENT
DESIGNS TWO CREATED BY
MONTGOMERY COUNTRY STUDENTS.
AAMELIA LE VI A
CONGRATULATIONS TO BOTH OF
THEM.
>>  RALLY NICE LOOKING.
MARYLAND PUBLIC SERVICE
COMMISSION SAID TO HIT A
COMMISSION FOR FEEDBACK ON
INVESTIGATION INTO DEADLY
EXPLOSION THAT ROCKED A SILVER
SPRING COMPLEX IN 2016.
>>  WASHINGTON GAS AT THE
CENTER OF THAT INVESTIGATION
AND SOME CLAIM THE COMPANY
FAILED TO TAKE STEPS THAT LED
TO EXPLOSION AND COST LIVES.
BOB BARNARD HAS MORE ON THE
HEARING.
>>  TONIGHT'S HEARING
SCHEDULED FOR 6:00 LONG BRANG.
LIKE REAR GARLAND AVENUE IN
SILVER SPRING.  THE GAS
EXPLOSION AND FIRE IN ONE
BUILDING THERE ON AUGUST 10,
016, KILLED 6 RESIDENCE AND
TWO CHILDREN AND INJURED 565
AOTHERS INCLUDING FIREF
FIREFIGHTERS.
NTSB FOUND FAULTY EQUIPMENT
INSIDE BASEMENT UTILITY ROOM
WAS TO PLAME FOR GAS LEAK
IGNITED BY A STILL UNKNOWN
SOURCE.
WASHINGTON GAS IS ORDERED TO
REPLACE WHAT ARE CALLED
MERCURY SERVICE REGULATORS AND
OVER TIME MOVE ALL THOSE
REGULATORS OUTSIDE OF
RESIDENTIAL BUILDINGS.
AND THE NTSB SAYS REGULATOR
INVOLVED IN THAT EXPLOSION AND
FIRE WAS NOT CONNECTED TO ITS
VENT LINE.
MARYLAND PUBLIC SERVICE
COMMISSION TONIGHT WANT TO
KNOW HOW WELL THE GAS COMPANY
IS MAKING RECOMMEND TAKINGS
FIXES AND BRING COMMUNITY UP
TO SPEED ON WHAT'S GOING ON.
NTSB CONCLUDED NOBODY CALLED
WASHINGTON GAS AFTER
FIREFIGHTERS WERE CALLED TO
CHECK OUT SMELL OF GOOSE THAT
BUILDING TWO WEEKS BEFORE THE
EXPLOSION, GUYS.
>>  THANK YOU AND SCHOOL BUS
SAFETY.
NEW TECHNOLOGY
She wanted to move someplace
warm.
But he wanted snow for the
holidays.
So we built a snow globe.
I'll get that later.
Dylan!
But the one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with homeowners
insurance.
What?
Switching and saving was
really easy!
I love you!
What?
Sweetie! Hands off the glass.
Ugh!!
Call GEICO and see how easy
saving on homeowners
and condo insurance can be.
I love her!
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
>> HISTORY LAST NIGHT NFL DREW
BREES BECAME LEAGUE ALL TIME
LEADER IN TOUCHDOWN PASSES,
540 CAREER TOUCHDOWN PASSES
AFTER THREW FOUR OF THEM LAST
NIGHT BREAKING PAY TOP MAN
MANNING'S RECORD.
DREW BREES ALSO BROKE A RECORD
FOR SUNGLELE XLEEINGTS 29 OF
30 PASS ATTEMPTS ONLY ONE PASS
INCOMPLETE THE ENTIRE GAME AND
THAT WAS MORE THAT
THREE-QUARTERS OF GAME PLAY.
>> ON TO THE CLEM LEVEL AND
NFL DRAFT JOE BURROWS ACCEPT
STANCE SPEECH OVER 300,000
DONATIONS AND LSU QUARTERBACK
WON AWARD THIS PAST WEEKEND HE
TALKED ABOUT GROWING UP IN
AMING EPS OHIO AND POVERTY
THERE.
SINCE THIS THE PANTRY IS
FLOODED WITH DONATIONS AND GO
FUND ME PAGE RAISED SEVERAL
HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS.
TRYING TO KEEP PEOPLE FROM
GOING HUNGRY.
>> HELLO TUCKER GREAT STORY.
>>  SPEAKS TO THE POWER OF
PUTTING IT OUT THERE.
AND SAYING WHAT THE NEED IS
AND YOU KNOW DEPOSIT ASK FOR
ANYTHING.
BUT IT TOUCHED PEOPLE AND I
THINK IT'S AMAZING.
WE HAVE THE POWER TO SPEAK.
GOOD JOB.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> MORE THAT JUST AN ATHLETE
LIKE YOU MORE THAN JUST A
WEATHER MAN.
>>  SWEET.
>>  RIGHT NOW I'M JUST THE
WEATHER MAN.
>> 37 WASHINGTON.
CLOUDY SKIES TO START THE DAY.
FEELING LIKE 3 WITH 2 IT.
GOOD NEWS THE ACTUAL AIR
TEMPERATURE IS 37.
OF COURSE WE NEED IT ABOVE
FREEZING WE'RE NOT DEALING
WITH SCHOOL DELAYS AND ICING
AND SHOWERS COP TIP, GRAY
SKIES, GLOOM, FOG, VISIBILITY
I'LL BE HONEST IS NOT GREAT.
ALL THAT SET FOR TUESDAY HERE.
OFF NORTH AND WEST SEE THE
PITCHING THERE THERE MAY BE A
TOUCH OF SPREEZING DRIZZLE BIG
PICTURE A WARM FRONT WILL
SWING THROUGH AND COLD FRONT
IN THE ARM WE SHOULD PUT APP
END TO SHOWER ACTIVITY WE
CLEAR THINGS OUT LATER THIS
EVENING.
TODAY MORE OF THE SAME.
IT WILL FEEL LIKE YESTERDAY.
50 DAYTIME HIGH.
WEDNESDAY, THURSDAY, FRIDAY,
SATURDAY, SURPRISED, LOOK AT
THAT BACK IN THE SURPRISE
SHEEN AND NICE QUIET WEATHER
PATTERN HERE TO END THE WEEK.
CHILLY, THURSDAY'S HIGH ONLY 3
WITH 4.
LET'S JAM THAT CAM.
>> I LIKE YOUR SOUND AFFECTS
THEY ADDED SOMETHING EXTRA
TODAY.
AS WE MOVE AROUND THE DMV
SOUTHBOUND 2 IT 95 SLOW.
95 SOUTHBOUND BY 198 HEAVY,
395 DUKE MAIN LANE AS TOUCH
AND UPPER LOOP IS SLOW ROLE,
BACK TO YOU.
>>  UP NEXT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT NEW TECHNOLOGY THAT
COULD MAKE SCHOOL PUSS A LOT
LOT A BIG DESILTION BY BOEING
TO TOP PRO BOUX.
WHAT IT WITH MEAN FOR THE
AMERICAN ECONOMY.
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
It's been reported that
there's a cyberattack
on business every 39 seconds.
Ouch.
I don't even want
to think about it.
Comcast Business has a solution.
We go beyond fast with a
cloud-based security system
that automatically updates,
so you always have
the latest protection.
Phishing. Malware.
Risky sites.
It can help block all of that.
It's one less thing
for us to worry about.
Comcast Business SecurityEdge
automatically protects
all the devices on your network.
Call 1-800-501-6000 today.
7:30.
I LOOKS LIKE IT'S STILL
NIGHTTIME BUT IT'S THE SUN IS
OFFICIALLY UPROOT NOW.
IT'S JUST HAVING A HARD TIME
SHINING THROUGH THE CLOUDS.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH THE WAY IT
WILL LOOK THROUGHOUT THE MORNING
A DREARY KIND OF DAY HERE IN THE
NATION'S CAPITAL BUT THE CAPITAL
WHEEL IS SHINING ITS LIGHT FOR
US THIS MORNING.
IT'S 7:30.
LET'S CHECK OUR TOP STORIES ON
THIS TUESDAY MORNING.
FIRST UP, TWO FAIRFAX COUNTY
ELEMENTARY TEACHERS OFF THE JOB
FACING SERIOUS CHARGES.
CYLMEERA GASTAV AND SEE CELIA
BENAVIDES ABUSED OF ABUSING SIX
NON VERBAL CHILDREN.
THE FORMER PRINCIPAL SCOTT BLOOM
ALSO FACING CHARGES FOR FAILING
TO REPORT THE SUSPECTED ABUSE
EVEN WHEN HE WAS AWARE OF THE
ALLEGATIONS.
>>> IT IS EXPECTED TO GET HEATED
AT A MEETING TO NIGHT IN SATISFY
FORWARD COUNTY WHERE THE BOARD
OF SUPERVISORS IS INVITING THE
PUBLIC TO DISCUSS THE COUNTY
BECOMING A SECOND AMENDMENT
SANCTUARY.
THE NEW LABEL IS A RESOLUTION TO
PROTECT GUN OWNERS AHEAD OF THE
NEW 11 OF LEEPS LIVE SESSION AS
BOTH CHAMBERS IN VIRGINIA ARE
CONTROLLED BY DEMOCRATS AND GUN
CONTROL LEGISLATION IS LIKELY TO
BE FRONT AND CENTER IN THE NEW
YEAR.
>>> 7:31 NOW.
LET'S GET OVER TO ALLISON.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, STEVE.
>>> WELL, IN THE PAST WEEK,
TRAGEDY HAS HIT MONTGOMERY
COUNTY INVOLVING TWO STUDENTS
BOTH STRUCK AFTER GETTING OFF
THE SCHOOLBUS.
A NINE-YEAR-OLD GIRL WAS KILLED
WHEN SHE WAS HIT BY THE BUS SHE
JUST CAME OFF OF, AND A TEENAGER
WAS HURT WHEN THEY WERE HIT BY A
CAR WHILE TRYING TO CROSS THE
STREET AFTER GETTING OFF THE BUS
THERE.
SO COULD A SIMPLE LIGHT HELP
INCIDENTS LIKE THIS FROM
HAPPENING?  23 STATES NOW USE
WHAT'S CALLED A GUARDIAN ANGEL
LIGHTING SYSTEM ON ITS SCHOOL
BUSES.
HOWEVER, MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA
ARE NOT AMONG THOSE STATES.
SO WHAT DOES THIS LIGHT DO AND
HOW DOES IT WORK?  JOINING US
NOW STEVE GARDNER THE PRESIDENT
OF GUARDIAN ANGEL AS WELL HIS
SON ANDREW WHO ALSO WORKS WITH
GUARDIAN ANGEL.
GOOD MORNING TO BOTH OF YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HELLO.
>> MAY I JUST SAY RIGHT OFF THE
BAT THE RESEMBLANCE IS UNCANNY.
DEFINITELY FATHER AND SON HERE.
BUT FATHER AND SON DOING GOOD TO
TRY TO MAKE SURE THAT NO OTHER
CHILD IS HURT WHEN IT COMES TO
SCHOOLBUS ACCIDENTS.
CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT THIS
LIGHTING SYSTEM?
>> YES, I INVENTED IT IN 2010.
HIGH A 35 CAREER INLY SCHOOLBUS
INDUSTRY FLEET SUPERVISOR AND A
MECHANIC.
IN 2010 A 15-YEAR-OLD GIRL
ATTEMPTED TO GET ON HER BUS IN
THE MORNING.
THE BUS OF COURSE HAD ITS RED
LIGHTS ACTIVATED AND A LADY HIT
HER AND KILLED HER.
SO THAT WAS A DAY GUARDIAN ANGEL
WAS INVENTED.
THE FIRST THING THE LADY THAT
STRUCK THAT CHILD SAID IS I
NEVER SAW HER.
>> WOW! OKAY.
SO THIS IS REALLY A LIGHT,
RIGHT?  HOW DOES THIS WORK
EXACTLY AND HOW DOES IT HELP TO
STOP THESE TRAGEDIES?
>> HOW IT WORKS, WHEN THE RED
LIGHTS ARE ACTIVATED ON A
SCHOOLBUS, THE LIGHT IS
AUTOMATICALLY ACTIVATE THE.
THERE'S NO EXTRA SWITCHES FOR
THE DRIVER TO DEAL WITH.
IT WORKS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE
SCHOOLBUS' RED WARNING LIGHT
SYSTEM SO WHEN A STOP SIGN COMES
OUT AND THE RED LIGHTS ARE
ACTIVATED, THERE IS A PATH OF
WHITE LIGHT PLACED RIGHT DOWN
DIRECTLY ON THE ROAD FOR THE
STUDENTS TO BE SEEN FOR THE
MOTORISTS IN FRONT OF THE BUS
AND BEHIND THE BUS.
THE BUS DRIVER CAN SEE THE BUS.
THE STUDENTS CAN SEE ANY
OBSTACLES IN THE ROAD SUCH AS
MUD PUDDLES OR ICE.
IT WORKS VERY WELL.
>> NOW, OKAY.
SO I WISH THAT WE VIDEO SO WE
CAN TAKE IT FOUL SEE JUST HOW
DOES IT WORK.
WHEN WE'RE TALK ABOUT HOW BRIGHT
THE LIGHT IS, IS IT DISTRACTING
AT ALL?  COULD IT CAUSE
ADDITIONAL ISSUES WITH PEOPLE
BEING DISTRACTED BY THE LIGHT?
>> NO.
I DON'T BELIEVE SO.
IT FOCUSES -- YOU COULD CLEARLY
SEE THE CHILDREN IF YOU WATCH
THE PROMOTIONAL VIDEO YOU CAN
CLEARLY SEE HOW IT WORKS.
>> THAT'S BEEN A QUESTION FOR
MANY DIFFERENT STATE PATROLS.
>> OKAY.
SPEAK MORE ON THAT.
WE'RE ACTUALLY LOOKING NOW AT
SOME VIDEO TO SHOW HOW THIS
WORKS AND IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
EVENING.
DOES IT WORK WELL WHEN, YOU
KNOW, IT'S IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
DAY, WHEN A LOT OF KIDS ARE
COMING HOME FROM SCHOOL?
>> THAT'S THE HIGH INTENSITY RED
FLASHING STROBE LIGHTS, THAT'S
WHY I INVENTED THOSE AND PUT
THOSE ON THE FRONT OF THE BUS
RIGHT ABOVE THE HEADLIGHTS.
I BELIEVE MOTORISTS LOOK NO
HIGHER THAN THE ROOF LINE OF
THEIR OWN CAR.
SCHOOLBUS IS RED FLASH SCHERS
ARE WAY UP HIGH.
AND I BELIEVE PLACED LOWER LIKE
ON FIRE TRUCKS EVEN TRASH TRUCKS
THEY'RE MORE VISIBLE FOR
MOTORISTS TO SEE.
IN THE DAYLIGHT.
>> SO WE MENTIONED NEITHER
MARYLAND NOR VIRGINIA YOU
HAVEN'T EITHER REACHED OUT OR
THESE STATES HAVEN'T REACHED OUT
TO YOU GUYS AND AS WE MENTIONED
THERE HAVE BEEN THESE TERRIBLE
TRAGEDIES HERE IN OUR AREA.
TELL US THE REACTION FROM THE
STATES THAT HAVE PUT THIS INTO
PLACE.
ARE THEY SEEING A DIFFERENCE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
TO DATE THERE'S BEEN NO CHILD
STRUCK OR INJURED WITH A BUS
EQUIPPED WITH GUARDIAN ANGEL
SCHOOLBUS LIGHTING SYSTEM.
I'M VERY PROUD OF THAT RECORD.
AND WE'VE HAD IT ON THE ROAD
SINCE 2011.
MICHIGAN WAS THE VERY FIRST
STATE TO HAVE IT, AND.
LATEST STATE OUR 23rd STATE
WAS IOWA.
JUST A FEW MONTHS AGO TO PROVE
IT.
>> BEFORE WE LET YOU GO, WE'RE
OUT OF TIME, BUT I JUST HAVE TO
ASK.
YOU SEEM TO BE SO PASSIONATE
ABOUT THIS.
TELL ME WHERE THAT COMES FROM.
>> I HAD A DAUGHTER THE SAME AGE
AS THAT KID THAT DIED AT THAT
TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> ENOUGH SAID.
MAY NO OTHER CHILD AND NO OTHER
FAMILY IS TO EVER DEAL WITH THE
TRAGEDY THAT COULD BE PREVENTED
LIKE THIS.
STEVE AND ANDREW GARDNER THE
FOUNDER, PRESIDENT AND INVENTOR
OF THE GUARDIAN ANGEL LIGHTING
SYSTEM.
THANK YOU BOTH FOR JOINING US.
HAPPIEST OF HOLIDAYS TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
THANKS SO MUCH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH.
I MEAN, TUCKER YOU'RE A PARENT.
YOU TOTALLY GET IT.
MAY NO OTHER CHILD EVER, YOU
KNOW G TO SCHOOL AND NOT COME
HOME AGAIN.
>> YEAH.
>> BACK TO YOU.
>> IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S HOP ON AND DO THE WEATHER
FOR YOU.
WAKING UP WITH CLOUDY SKIES,
DRIZZLE, FOG, YOU KNOW, MORE
DOOM AND GLOOM OUT THERE WEATHER
WISE EARLY THIS MORNING.
BUT DON'T DESPAIR.
WE'LL GET THE SUNSHINE BACK BY
TOMORROW AND MOST OF THIS WEEK
IS ACTUALLY GOING TO BE NICE AND
QUIET.
37 TO START YOUR MORNING.
IT IS STILL CHILLY BUT THE GOOD
NEWS IS, REGIONALLY MOST
EVERYBODY ABOVE FREEZING TO
START THE DAY.
SO WHAT PRECIPITATION WE'RE
GETTING FALLING LIGHT DRIZZLE
AND RAIN ACROSS THE REGION.
THERE YOU CAN SEE THAT
SATELLITE/RADAR.
SHOWER ACTIVITY AND AGAIN IT
WILL BE KIND OF SPOTTY ON AND
OFF HERE FOR THE MORNING HOURS.
THEN WE'LL GET IT BACK TO
SHOWERS THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
WITH A COLD FRONT WHICH IS OFF
TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
ONCE THAT FRONT SWINGS THROUGH,
DRIER AIR STARTS TO WORK IN AND
WE'LL START CLEARING IT OUT.
SO YOUR TWO DAY FORECAST.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SAY.
CAN'T GET THIS ANYWHERE ELSE.
50 TODAY, CLOUDS AND SHOWERS AND
THEN BACK TO SUNSHINE TOMORROW.
ALTHOUGH CHILLY TOMORROW.
ONLY ABOUT 40 DEGREES.
I'LL HAVE THE SEVEN DAY COMING
UP.
LET'S DO TRAFFIC AND ROADS AND
RAILS AND FIND OUT WHAT ERIN HAS
GOT ME FOR CHRISTMAS.
>> WHO NEEDS A SEVEN WHEN TUCKER
BARNES CAN DELIVER A TWO.
WE'RE SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> RIGHT?
>> UM-HMM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ALLISON, I'M SORRY.
HE MADE ME LAUGH.
TUCKER YOU'LL LOVE YOUR PRESENT.
IT'S ACTUALLY SOMETHING THAT'S
SPECIFICALLY TAILORED JUST FOR
YOU.
A LOT OF CONGESTION IN THE
DOWNTOWN AREA SURROUNDING
CONSTITUTION AVENUE.
THERE'S ANOTHER CRASH GW PARKWAY
AFTER THE MEMORIAL BRIDGE.
THAT'S CAUSING SOME SLOW DOWNS.
14th STREET BRIDGE INBOUND
VERY HEAVY TRAFFIC.
66 JAMS UP IN BAY BRIDGE INBOUND
COMING FROM THE EASTERN SHORE.
NASTY MESS OF TRAFFIC.
SORRY ABOUT THAT ONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY TODAY I JUST
HAVE THE LAUGHS.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> IT'S THE HOLIDAYS.
>> IT REALLY IS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANKS ERIN.
>> 7:37 MAX JETS WILL NOT BE
SEEING THE AIR ANY TIME SOON.
WHAT IT MEANS FOR THE AMERICA
ECONOMY.
>> HEALTH ALERT FOR ALL YOU
SPICY FOOD LOVERS.
THE SPICY FOOD THAT COULD BE
GOOD FOR YOUR HEART HEALTH.
STAY WITH US.
♪
♪♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Tuition goes up each
year ♪
♪ 5% so I hear ♪
♪ I really can't do math ♪
♪ But that's a lot,
I fear ♪
♪ And room and board ♪
(laughs)
- [Narrator] Invest529
gift cards make great gifts.
Learn more at
Invest529.com
- Ooh! (blows air)
I love that song.
(laughs)
Mmm, it tastes blue!
Every year,
air medical services save
hundreds of thousands of lives.
I love that song.
(laughs)
But after the emergency,
time and again,
insurance companies
deny coverage,
second guessing doctors,
nurses and first responders...
Now "big insurance"
is lobbying congress.
Asking for restrictions
on air medical services.
Eliminating patients'
access to life-saving care
and destroying jobs
all in exchange for bigger
profits for insurance companies.
Tell Congress,
put patients first,
not big insurance.
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
♪
>>> 7:40.
THE DEADLINE TO SIGN UP FOR
OBAMACARE OR THE AFFORDABLE CARE
ACT HAS BEEN EXTENDED UNTIL
TOMORROW AT 3:00 P.M.
THE ORIGINAL OPEN ENROLLMENT
PERIOD WAS SUPPOSED TO END ON
SUNDAY, BUT DUE TO SOME ISSUES
WITH THE WEBSITE, YOU NOW HAVE
SOME EXTRA TIME TO COMPLETE
ENROLLMENT FOR COVERAGE TO BEGIN
JANUARY 1st.
>>> GOOD NEWS IF YOU LIKE SPICY
FOOD AS NEW RESEARCH SUGGESTS
EATING CHILI PEPPERS DECREASES
THE RISK OF HEART DISEASE AND
STROKE.
STUDY SPLIT 23,000 PEOPLE INTO
TWO GROUPS.
ONE OF THE GROUPS HAD TO EAT
CHILI PEPPERS AT LEAST FOUR
TIMES A WEEK.
THE OTHER GROUP DID NOT EAT ANY
CHILI PEPPERS THOSE WHO DID EAT
THE CHILI PEPPERS REGULARLY HAD
A 40% LOWER RISK OF DYING FROM A
HEART ATTACK.
♪
>>> STILL AHEAD HOLIDAY SHIPPING
ALERT.
SPEED BUMP FOR YOUR PACKAGE
DELIVERIES MUCH THE BIG CHANGE
AMAZON IS MAKING.
>> TRYING TO GET TO YOU FASTER.
>> PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY FAMILY
BLAMING A MORTGAGE EXAM.
>> UT-OH.
>> AFTER THEY LOST THEIR HOME
AND THE MAN ACCUSED OF IN THE
CASE NO STRANGER TO SUCH A
SCHEME.
♪
SCHEM
♪ ♪
A lot's changed since
you were here.
It's called the Internet.
I'm gonna hit start now, OK?
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
♪
>>> 7:44.
TODAY'S BUSINESS BEAT MAJOR MOVE
FROM BOEING SUSPENDING
PRODUCTION OF TROUBLED 737 MAX
JETS.
JOINING US FROM THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK STUDIO TRACEE CARRASCO.
FIRST OF ALL, MORE RECORDS ON
WALL STREET.
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
BOEING NEWS, MAYBE NOT SO GOOD
FOR THAT COMPANY.
>> YES.
WE DID SEE SHARES OF BOEING
YESTERDAY DOWN MORE THAN 4%.
RIGHT NOW IT IS DOWN MORE THAN
1% IN THE PRIME MARKET THIS IS A
STOCK WE'LL BE WATCHING.
POTENTIALLY COULD DRAG DOWN THE
DOW TODAY.
BUT BOEING YESTERDAY ANNOUNCING
THAT THEY WOULD TEMPORARILY STOP
PRODUCTION OF THE GROUNDED 737
MAX PLANES.
WE KNOW THEY'VE BEEN GROUNDED
SINCE MARCH GLOBALLY FOLLOWING
THOSE TWO FATAL ACCIDENTS BACK
IN APRIL BOEING TEMPORARILY CUT
PRODUCTION BY 20%.
SO THIS IS A MOVE UNFORTUNATELY
BOEING SAYING THAT IT IS THE
LEAST DISRUPTIVE TO MAINTAIN
LONG-TERM PRODUCTION SYSTEM AND
SUPPLY CHAIN HEALTH THAT WAS
STATEMENT PUT OUT BY BOEING
YESTERDAY.
WE DID SEE SOME REACTION THIS
MORNING.
RIGHT NOW LOOKING AT SOUTHWEST
AIRLINES, THEY'RE ONE OF THE
U.S. AIR CARRIERS THAT OPERATE
THE 737 MAX.
THEY CAME OUT THIS MORNING AND
SAID THEY'RE PULLING THESE
PLANES FROM THEIR SCHEDULES
THROUGH APRIL 13th, 2020.
THE OTHER TWO AIR CARRIERS
AMERICAN AND UNITED.
THEY'VE PULLED THE PLANES
SINCE -- THROUGH MARCH.
>> WOW.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON WHAT'S
HAPPENING AND THERE IMPACT ON
PERHAPS THE REST OF THE MARKET
TODAY'S.
>>> SO A LOT OF COMPLAINTS
COMING FOR AMAZON FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
PEOPLE PAY FOR THEIR PRIME
MEMBERSHIPS THEY EXPECT TO GET
THAT QUICK SHIPPING.
SO SOME HAVEN'T QUITE HONESTLY.
WHAT'S APES GOING TO TRY TO DO
ABOUT IT.
>> AMAZON TODAY ISSUED A NOTICE
TO THIRD PARTY SELLERS ON ITS
PLATFORM SAYING THEY CAN NO
LONGER USE FED EX GROUND
SHIPPING FOR ITS PRIME SHIPMENTS
STARTING THIS WEEK BECAUSE OF
FED EX'S PERFORMANCE.
THEY SAY THAT THEY'VE SEEN THE
PERFORMANCE DECLINE AND UNTIL
FED EX CAN IMPROVE, THEY DON'T
WANT THEIR THIRD PARTY SELLERS
USING FED EX GROUND DELIVERY.
THEY SAY ESPECIALLY NOW THEY'RE
WORRIED ABOUT THE SHIPMENTS
GETTING TO CUSTOMERS IN TIME FOR
THE HOLIDAYS.
BUT THIS COMES AT AN INTERESTING
TIME BETWEEN THE TWO COMPANIES.
THEY'VE GOT A LITTLE BIT OF A
RIFT GOING ON.
BACK IN AUGUST, FED EX SAID THAT
IT WOULD NOT RENEW AMAZON'S
GROUND DELIVERY CONTRACT THEN IN
JUNE LAST JUNE THEY SAID THEY
WERE NOT GOING TO RENEW THE
SHIPPING CONTRACT.
SO ALL OF THIS WILL AMAZON TRIES
TO IF HE COULD YOU SAY ON
BUILDING UP ITS OWN DELIVERY
NETWORK.
WE'VE SEEN THE TWO COMPANIES
KIND OF SEPARATE A LITTLE BIT.
BUT SHARES OF AMAZON -- RATHER
SHARES OF FED EX DOWN YESTERDAY
ON THIS NEWS.
SO WE WILL SEE WHEN THEY WILL
RESUME, IF THEY DO IN FACT
RESUME USING FED EX GROUND
DELIVERY SERVICES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GETTING TO BE CRUNCH TIME TO GET
THOSE PACKAGES DELIVERED FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
>> YUP.
>> TRACEE, THANKS VERY.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING.
>> SHE'S LIKE I'M OUT.
>> OUT.
>> RIGHT.
>> ONE WAY TO GO.
>> PULL THE PLUG.
>> SEE YA.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WHO IS EXCITED FOR WINTER?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WINTER BEGINS IN FOUR DAYS.
FEELING LIKE WINTER THE LAST
COUPLE OF DAYS.
ARRIVES AT 11:19 P.M., YES, IF
YOU HAVE QUESTIONS ON WHY
EXACTLY 9:19 I'M HAPPY TO ANSWER
THEM.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
>> TUCKER FOX5.
>> I JUST ANSWERED HERE IN THE
STUDIO.
37 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
NORTH AND WEST NOTICE THE
TEMPERATURES FOR MOST EVERYBODY
ABOVE FREEZING.
REALLY IMPORTANT WE TEAM THESE
NUMBERS ABOVE FREEZING WE DON'T
GET ICY SPOTS.
THERE ARE A FEW EXCEPTIONS.
WINCHESTER, CUMBERLAND
32 DEGREES.
I'LL SHOW YOU RADAR HERE.
MOSTLY DRIZZLE AND LIGHT RAIN
FOR US THIS MORNING.
ALTHOUGH OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST IN A COUPLE OF SPOTS MAYBE
A LITTLE BIT OF FREEZING DRY
DRIZZLE UP TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN IN
TO PARTS OF PENNSYLVANIA THERE
FOR THE REST OF US CLOUDY SKIES
AND ON AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN
SHOWERS TAKE THE UMBRELLA HERE.
IT WILL BE A GLOOMY DAY.
I DON'T THINK IT WILL BE
TERRIBLY RAINY MORNING BUT A FEW
SHOWERS AROUND THIS AFTERNOON
COLD FRONT MOVES IN, WE GOT A
BETTER CHANCE OF RAIN SHOWERS SO
WE'LL GET ANOTHER ROUND OF RAIN
SHOWERS LATER TODAY AND THEN THE
DRYING PROCESS WILL START BEHIND
THAT FRONT.
THE WINDS WILL PICK UP.
WE'LL START TO CLEAR IT OUT AND
WE'LL BE BACK INTO SUNSHINE.
FULL SUNSHINE FOR THE DAY
TOMORROW.
THERE'S FUTURE CAST.
SHOWERS AROUND 1:00 O'CLOCK.
CHECKING BACK IN AT THREE, FOUR,
5:00 O'CLOCK THIS IS THE END OF
THE SHOWER ACTIVITY THAT'S THE
FRONT COMING THROUGH.
NOTICE THE CLEARING SKIES OFF TO
THE NORTH AND WEST WE'LL CLEAR
IT OUT OVERNIGHT AND BE IN FOR
AGAIN A NICE LOOKING WEDNESDAY
AND REALLY A NICE STREAK OF
WEATHER HERE.
I MEAN IT IS GOING TO BE CHILLY
AROUND HERE WITH TEMPERATURES
LITTLE BELOW NORMAL.
BUT WE'LL KEEP IT DRY AND A LOT
OF PEOPLE TRAVELING THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
THAT WILL BE GREAT FOR TRAVEL
WEATHER HITTING THE SHOPS AND
THAT KIND OF THING.
50 TODAY.
CLOUDS AND SHOWERS AND THEN 40
ON WEDNESDAY.
LOOK AT THURSDAY.
34 DEGREES.
OKAY.
ERIN WAS RIGHT HERE NOW SHE'S
GONE.
I THINK SHE'S AROUND.
>> I'VE BEEN MOVED TO THE OTHER
STUDIO.
HELLO.
7:48.
RIVER ROAD CRASH WESTBOUND AT
BELTWAY THAT'S CAUSING SOME BIG
DELAYS.
AS YOU HEAD INSIDE THE BELL WAY.
95 NORTHBOUND FREDERICKSBURG
THROUGH STAFFORD SOME VOLUME
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A LITTLE GRAY AND GLOOMY.
29 MILES PER HOUR AVERAGE
NORTHBOUND AND THEN 95 DALE CITY
TO THE BELTWAY SLOW ROLE PASSED
PRINCE GEORGE'S PARKWAY AS
USUAL.
INNER LOOP JAMS FROM THE
SPRINGFIELD INTERCHANGE PAST
BRADDOCK ROAD.
DELAYS ON 66 EASTBOUND THROUGH
MANASSAS PRETTY HEAVY VOLUME
THERE.
RIGHT NOW YOU NEED ABOUT 35
EXTRA MINUTES TO GET FROM
MANASSAS THROUGH FAIRFAX TO THE
BELTWAY.
INSIDE THE BELTWAY 395 EDSALL
ROAD TO THE 14th STREET
BRIDGE.
LOOKING A LITTLE BIT BACKED UP.
GW PARKWAY NORTHBOUND THERE IS A
CRASH BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE
AFTER THE KEY BRIDGE.
WE HAD A SOUTHBOUND CRASH AS
WELL.
A LOT OF VOLUME IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS.
BAY BRIDGE SUPER GRAY AND GLOOMY
ALMOST FOGGY OUT THERE LOW BEAMS
TAKE IT SLOW IF YOU ENCOUNTER
ANY FOG.
STACK UPS FROM THE RIGHT LANE
SHUT DOWN FOR CONSTRUCTION THE
WESTBOUND SIDE OF 50.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> PROPOSAL BY THE AIRPORT'S
AUTHORITY CAN HIT UBER AND LYFT
RIDERS IN THE POCKETBOOK.
THE BOARD WILL MEET TOMORROW TO
DISCUSS RAISING THE FEE THAT
UBER AND LYFT DRIVERS PAY WHEN
THEY DROP OFF AND PICK UP
PASSENGERS AT REAGAN NATIONAL
AND DULLES AIRPORTS.
THE PROPOSAL WOULD RAISE THE FEE
BY A DOLLAR TO $5 A RIDE.
IN THE PAST UBER AND LYFT HAVE
USUALLY PASSED ON THOSE FEES TO
PASSENGERS.
>>> AND RIDE SHARE COMPANY LYFT
STEPPING UP EFFORTS TO MAKE YOUR
RIDE SAFER.
LYFT SAYS IT'S NOW CONTINUOUSLY
SCREENING DRIVERS NATIONWIDE.
THE COMPANY WILL CLOSELY MONITOR
THEIR DRIVING RECORDS THROUGH
PARTNERSHIP WITH A COMPANY
CALLED MANY SAMBA SAFETY.
THE PARTNERSHIP WILL ALLOW THEM
TO RECOGNIZE SAFEST DRIVERS AND
TAKE FAST CORRECTIVE ACTIONS ON
THOSE WHO VIOLATE ITS SAFETY
STANDARDS.
>> IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY, A
FAMILY IS BLAMING A MORTGAGE
EXAM AFTER THEY LOST THEIR HOME
AND THE MAN ACCUSED OF IN THE
CASE IS NO STRANGER TO SUCH A
SCHEME.
IN FACT HE WAS CONVICTED LAUGH
YEAR IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
FOX5'S LINDH SEA WATTS SPOKE TO
A WOMAN IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY WHO SAID SHE FELL VICTIM
TO THE SAME MAN.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD WHEN I KNOW
MY MOTHER PLANNED ON LEAVING
SOMETHING FOR HER CHILDREN,
GRANDCHILDREN AND THIS WAS ONE
OF THE THINGS SHE PLANNED ON
LEAVING FOR SOMEONE.
>> Reporter: THIS DISTRICT
HEIGHTS HOME HOLDS NEARLY 20
YEARS OF MEMORIES.
>> IT'S TAPE FROM NOT JUST HER,
TAKEN FROM MY FAMILY.
THIS IS ALL MY CHILDREN KNOW.
>> Reporter: NO ONE IMAGINED
THEIR TIME WOULD END WITH AN
EVICTION NOTICE.
>> THAT'S WHEN WE KNEW THIS IS
REAL REPORT CLAYTON DOCKET'S
MOTHER PATRICIA OWNED THE HOUSE.
SHE SAYS SHE LOST ONE MUCH HER
TWO JOBS AND KNEW SHE NEEDED TO
REDUCE HER MORTGAGE PAYMENTS.
>> SO I SAID, OH, LORD, LET ME
GET MY MORTGAGE DOWN BECAUSE
I'LL JUST BE DOING ONE JOB.
SO THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO DO
THE MODIFICATION.
>> Reporter: A FRIEND
RECOMMENDED WILLIAM WHELAN.
HE TOLD HER HE WAS AN ATTORNEY
AND SHE PAID HIM MORE THAN
$7,000 TO REFINANCE HER MOR
MORTGAGE.
WHAT SHE DIDN'T KNOW IT'S
ILLEGAL NATIONWIDE FOR SOMEONE
TO CHARGE YOU UP FRONT FOR
MORTGAGE SERVICES.
>> HE TOLD HER TO STOP PAYING
HER MORTGAGE FEBRUARY OF LAST
YEAR.
>> Reporter: PATRICIA SAYS
WHELAN TOOK ALL THE MALE
REGARDING THE HOUSE AND SHE
TRUSTED HIM.
>> HE TOLD ME NEVER LOST A CASE.
>> Reporter: EVENTUALLY HE
STOPPED RESPONDING TO TEXTS AND
CALLS AND ONLY THEN SHE REALIZED
HER HOME WAS IN FORECLOSURE AND
IT HAD ALREADY BEEN SOLD AT
AUCTION.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN SLEEPING.
I HAVEN'T BEEN EATING.
>> I --
>> BECAUSE I'VE BEEN PACKING.
YOU TALK ABOUT 19 YEARS WORTH OF
STUFF.
>> Reporter: WE INTERVIEWED
THE DUCT'S WEEKS AGO JUST BEFORE
THEY MET WITH POLICE AND BEFORE
THEY HAD TO MOVE OUT.
NOW WE'VE LEARNED A GRAND JURY
HAS INDICTED WILLIAM WHELAN FIVE
COUNTS INCLUDING THEFT AND
PRETENDING TO BE A LAWYER.
BACK IN 2014, THE STATE BANNED
WHELAN FROM DOING ANY KIND OF
MORTGAGE SERVICES AFTER HE TOOK
UP FRONT PAYMENTS FROM MULTIPLE
PEOPLE.
IT DIDN'T STOP HIM, THOUGH.
LAST YEAR, HE WAS CONVICTED IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY ON MORTGAGE
FRAUD CHARGES.
BUT HE AVOIDED PRISON TIME.
>> WHEN IS ENOUGH ENOUGH?
>> LINDSAY WATTS REPORTING
THERE.
THE MAN SHE WAS TALKING TO WAS
ARRAIGNED ON FRIDAY.
TALKING ABOUT I SHOULD SAY.
HE WAS RELEASED ON BOND.
LINDSAY SPOKE TO HIM OVER THE
PHONE AND HE SAYS HE'S INNOCENT
OF ALL CHARGES.
HE'LL HAVE MORE TO SAY AFTER HIS
TRIAL WHICH WILL BE IN FEBRUARY.
7:53.
CHECK THIS OUT.
A GROUP OF THERAPY CRISIS AND
AIRPORT DOGS FROM AROUND THE
REGION DRESSED IN FESTIVE
HOLIDAY GEAR AND POSING FOR THIS
TWEET HOLIDAY CARD.
HELLO.
THIS IS A LOOK BEHIND THE SCENES
AT THE PHOTO SHOOT FOR THE GO
TEAM DOGS IN FREDERICK,
MARYLAND.
THE TEAM AND ITS HANDLERS OFTEN
VISIT HOSPITALS, ASSISTED LIVING
CENTERS AND DISASTER AREAS IN
NEED.
SO CUTE.
SIX -- EXCUSE ME 7:53.
LOOK AT THE GOOD DAY GUEST LIST.
STAR WARS WEEK CONTINUES TODAY.
KEVIN MCCARTHY ONE OF THE ONLY
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD TO SEE THIS
MOVIE LAST NIGHT.
WE'LL CHECK IN WITH HIM LIVE
THIS MORNING AND GET HIS FIRST
IMPRESSION OF THE FILM.
>>> JOINING US LIVE IN THE LOFT
FROM TOP CHEF THE AWARD WINNING
CHEF KWAME IS BACK WITH US
TODAY.
TONIGHT HE WILL JOIN SEVERAL
OTHER CELEBRITY CHEFS FOR THE
BREAKING BREAD EVENT AT SIXTH
AND I STREETS.
A NIGHT OF TRUE STORIES BY CELEB
IS THE CHEFS AND INDUSTRY
INSIDERS.
>> AND WE ARE CELEBRATING THE
SWEET TASTE OF HOLIDAY SEASON.
THE OPENER OF SIMPLE SWEETS WILL
SHOW US HOW TO CREATE THOSE
DELICIOUS DESSERTS JUST IN TIME
FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
>> AND TUCKER, SOMETHING JUST
FOR YOU SPEAKING OF DOGS ONE OF
D.C.'S MOST RECOGNIZABLE DOGS
CAPTAIN THE CAPS DOG WILL BE
WITH US IN THE LOFT ON GOOD DAY
TODAY.
>> STEVE, YOU'RE BURYING THE
LEAD THERE.
>> RIGHT.
I WAS SAVING IT FOR YOU.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
>> SAVE THE BEST FOR LAST.
>> GOT TO GET A PICTURE.
SEEN HIM WITH OVI THEY'RE
AMAZING TOGETHER.
>> CLOUDY SKIES TO START YOUR
DAY.
DRIZZLE, FOG, SHOWERS, MORE OF
THE SAME UNFORTUNATELY HERE TO
START YOUR MORNING.
AT LEAST THE BRIGHT SPOT IS THE
TEMPERATURES ABOVE 32 WE'RE NOT
DOING ICE AS IT'S JUST WET ROADS
OUT THERE FOR YOU EARLY THIS
MORNING.
MOST OF THE RAIN SHOWER ACTIVITY
PRETTY LIGHT.
MAN, IT WILL BE ON AGAIN OFF
AGAIN HERE FOR YOUR MORNING
HOURS.
AND OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST
HERE THE PINK YOU SEE MAYBE A
LITTLE BIT OF LIGHT FREEZING
DRIZZLE OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST.
THE BOTTOM LINE WITH TODAY,
CLOUDY SKIES, COOL TEMPS IN THE
40S AND WE'LL KEEP THE SHOWERS
IN THE FORECAST MID TO LATE
AFTERNOON THERE IS A COLD FRONT
OUT HERE AND WHEN THAT SLIDES
EAST OF US, BY LATE THIS
AFTERNOON WE'LL START TO DRY IT
OUT AND WE'LL CLEAR IT OUT LATER
TONIGHT AND BE BACK IN THE
SUNSHINE FOR YOU BY TOMORROW.
SO IT GETS BRIGHTER FROM HERE.
ONE MORE DAY OF THIS IT GETS
BRIGHTER.
50 TODAY AND LOTS OF SUNSHINE,
CHILLY TEMPERATURES.
LOOK AT YOUR HIGH ON THURSDAY.
34 DEGREES AND THEN FIRST DAY OF
WINTER, YEAH, GETS HERE ON
SATURDAY.
11:19 P.M.
PARTY.
>> WILL YOU BE AWAKE TO
CELEBRATE?
>> I STAY UP LATE FOR, YOU KNOW,
SOLSTICE PARTY.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
YOU CAN STAY UP UNTIL AT LEAST
MIDNIGHT.
>> BECAUSE OF THE WET ROADS AS
TUCKER MENTIONED RIVER ROAD
THERE'S A CRASH WESTBOUND AT THE
BELTWAY THAT'S CAUSING BIG
DELAYS ON THE INBOUND SIDE
TOWARD THE BELTWAY OF RIVER ROAD
SO BE PREPARED FOR THAT ONE.
95 NORTHBOUND LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
OMINOUS GRAY AND WET DOWN IN
FREDERICKSBURG OVERALL NO MAJOR
DELAYS INTO STAFFORD.
DELAYS PAST QUANTICO.
DALE CITY THE MAIN LANES ARE
STACKED STACKED UM WITH WET
CONDITIONS.
INNER LOOP JAMS FROM THE
SPRINGFIELD INTERCHANGE THROUGH
66 AND 66 DELAYS THROUGH
MANASSAS.
45 EXTRA MINUTES TO GET FROM
MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY RIGHT
NOW 270 IS ALSO SLOW FROM URBANA
DOWN TO THE BELTWAY.
METRO IS ON TIME.
BACK TO YOU.
>> ERIN THANKS SO MUCH.
MORE COMING UP IN OUR NEXT HOUR.
KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
8:00 O'CLOCK.
METRO NEW TECHNOLOGY TO MAKE
YOUR RIDE SAFER.
>> PLUS WHY FORMER PRESIDENT
BARACK OBAMA IS MAKING HEADLINES
FOR THE COMMENTS HE MADE ABOUT
WOMEN.
>> AND A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE.
IT IS FOG GO OUT THERE.
I MEAN SO FOGGY YOU CAN BARELY
SEE ANYTHING.
TRY TO TAKE A LOOK FROM THE
TOWER CAM.
JUST NOT WORKING.
NOT COOPERATING.
DETAILS FROM TUCKER COMING UP.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC RIGHT OFF
THE TOP AT 8:00 A.M.
♪
♪♪
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
8:00 A.M. ON THIS TUESDAY
MORNING.
ANOTHER RAINY AND DREARY START
TO THE DAY BUT THAT'S OKAY.
WE'RE HERE WITH YOU.
>> IT'S REALLY BEEN RAINING FOR
24 HOURS STRAIGHT.
BUT HAY AT LEAST IT'S NOT SNOW
LIKE WE HAD EARLY YESTERDAY.
THE GOOD NEWS SUNSHINE IS ON THE
WAY.
BUT IT WILL COME WITH A BIT OF
AN ARCTIC BLAST.
SO TUCKER AND ERIN ARE STANDING
BY WITH A FIRST CHECK OF THE
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
QUICK LOOK AT YOUR SATELLITE
PICTURES.
RAIN SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST AND
GLOOMY CONDITIONS OUT THERE.
TEMPS IN THE 30S AT THIS HOUR.
I'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS I
DON'T KNOW YOUR RAINY TUESDAY
FORECAST COMING RIGHT UP.
ERIN, GOD MORNING.
>> 8:00 O'CLOCK STRAIGHT UP.
GRAY, GLOOMY, SOME FOG, LOW
BEAMS TAKE IT SLOW.
WE ARE PARKED ON 66 EASTBOUND
THROUGH MANASSAS.
A FULL LOOK AROUND THE DMV AND
WITH METRO AS WE CONTINUE.
>>> GET TO OUR HEADLINES NOW ON
THIS TUESDAY MORNING.
WE BEGIN WITH A HORRIFIC STORY
TERRIBLE ALLEGATIONS OUT OF
FAIRFAX COUNTY.
TWO TEACHERS IN THE PUBLIC
SCHOOL SYSTEM ARE ACCUSED OF
DOING UNTHINKABLE ACTS.
>> THEY ALLEGEDLY ABUSED SEVERAL
NON-VERBAL SPECIAL NEEDS
CHILDREN AND MELANIE ALNWICK
JOINS US FROM VIENNA THIS
MORNING WITH THE DETAILS.
MEL, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> Reporter: SO WHAT WE
UNDERSTAND STEVE AND ALLISON IS
THAT APPARENTLY THE AB A STARTED
LAST SCHOOL YEAR AND THERE WERE
EMPLOYEES HERE AT FREEDOM HILL
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHO WERE
CONCERNED ABOUT IT.
AN EMPLOYEE BROUGHT THOSE
CONCERNS TO THE PRINCIPAL.
THE THEN PRINCIPAL AND THAT
PRINCIPAL THEN MOVED ON OVER THE
SUMMER.
SO IN SEPTEMBER, WE HAD A NEW
SCHOOL YEAR AND A NEW PRINCIPAL
AND THESE EMPLOYEES NOTICED
THESE SUSPECTED ABUSE AGAIN AND
THAT'S WHEN THEY WENT TO THE NEW
PRINCIPAL AND THEN TOGETHER THEY
WENT TO FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE
AND THAT'S HOW THIS
INVESTIGATION BEGAN.
SO NOW WE HAVE TWO SPECIAL ED HE
HAD TEACHING ASSISTANTS.
YOU'RE SEEING THE PRINCIPAL
HERE.
HE IS CHARGED WITH ONE COUNT,
AND THEN FAILURE TO REPORT THEN
THE TWO TEACHING ASSISTANTS
THERE CYLMEERA GAS STAFF AND
CECELIA BENAVIDES FACING 17
COUNTS OF NEL LONNIE AND
MISDEMEANOR ABUSE AND COULD GET
SUBSTANTIAL JAIL TIME.
THE FORMER PRINCIPAL SCOTT BLUM
CHACHARGED WITH ONE COUNT OF
FAILURE TO SUPPORT.
>> THEY'RE ALLEGED TO HAVE
ABUSED SIX NON VERBAL STUDENTS
INSIDE THE CLASSROOM.
THEIR INVESTIGATION REVEALED
INCIDENTS OF ASSAULT AND
BATTERY, CRUELTY AND INJURED TO
CHILDREN FROM APRIL TO SEPTEMBER
OF THIS YEAR.
AND WHEN THE FORMER PRINCIPAL
BLUM WAS TOLD OF THE SUSPECTED
ABUSE APPARENTLY HEED A
CONVERSATION, A ONE-ON-ONE TALK
WITH ONE OF THE TEACHING
ASSISTANTS BUT DID NOT CONTACT
POLICE AS REQUIRED TO DO SO BY
LAW.
FAIRFAX COUNTY SCHOOLS CHIEF
OPERATING OFFICER MARTY SMITH
SAID HE'S DEEPLY SADDENED BY
WHAT HAPPENED TO THESE CHILDREN.
>> THERE'S NO GREATER
RESPONSIBILITY OF A SCHOOL
SYSTEM THAN THE SAFETY AND
WELL-BEING OF OUR STUDENTS, AND
THE RESULT OF THIS TRAGIC
SITUATION WE HAVE LEARNED THAT
WE NEED TO DO MORE.
>> NOW GUSTAV AND BENAVIDES HAVE
20 YEARS COMBINED EXPERIENCE IN
SPECIAL EDUCATION.
THEY'RE NOT THE ACTUAL TEACHER
IN THE CLASSROOM.
THEY ARE BOTH ASSISTANTS IN THAT
CLASSROOM.
FAIRFAX COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
APOLOGIZED TO THE COMMUNITY IN A
LETTER OUTLINING THE SCHOOL
SYSTEM'S POLICIES REQUIRING MAN
DO TOWER REPORTING AND ALSO
TRAINING TO LET PEOPLE KNOW OF
THEIR DUTIES UNDER THE LAW.
SAYING THEY WILL DO MOREY
TRAINING TO MAKE SURE EVERYONE
KNOWS EXACTLY WHAT THEY NEED TO
DO.
THE SCHOOL SYSTEM SAID IT
IMMEDIATELY REMOVED BOTH OF
THOSE TEACHING ASSISTANTS FROM
THEIR POSITIONS AS SOON AS IT
LEARNED OF THE ALLEGATIONS.
NOW, FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE SAY
THAT THEY BELIEVE THAT THEY HAVE
IDENTIFIED ALL OF THE VICTIMS IN
THIS CASE BUT THEY WANT TO JUST
PUT IT OUT THERE THAT, AGAIN,
SCHOOLS HAVE MANDATORY REPORTING
REQUIREMENTS AND ANY TIME
SOMEONE SUSPECTS ABUSE THEY SAY
PLEASE CALL POLICE.
DON'T HESITATE.
♪
>>> WE HAVE NEW DETAILS THIS
MORNING INVOLVING THE ALLEGED
MURDER OF A BARNARD COLLEGE
STUDENT FROM VIRGINIA.
THERE'S A MASSIVE MANHUNT FOR
14-YEAR-OLD BELIEVED TO BE A
SUSPECT IN THE DEADLY STABBING.
THAT TEENAGER REPORTEDLY WAS IN
A CAB WITH HIS MOTHER YESTERDAY
ON THE WAY TO TURN HIMSELF IN TO
POLICE.
WHEN HE JUMP OUT OF THE CAB AND
RAN OFF.
POLICE ALREADY HAVE A
13-YEAR-OLD IN CUSTODY.
THEY SAY THAT 13-YEAR-OLD
CONFESSED TO BEING INVOLVED AND
IS DUE IN COURT TODAY.
THAT VICTIM IS FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
>>> PUBLIC HEARING WILL BE HELD
IN THE INVESTIGATION OF
WASHINGTON REGARDING THAT DEADLY
EXPLOSION AT AN APARTMENT
COMPLEX IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY
YEARS AGO.
HEARING WILL TAKE PLACE TONIGHT
AND THE LONG BRANCH LIBRARY AT
6:00 P.M.
WASHINGTON GAS HAS FACED STEEP
CRITICISM EVER SINCE MARYLAND'S
PUBLIC SERVICE COMMISSION SAID
THE COMPANY DIDN'T TAKE STEPS TO
REPAIR FAILED EQUIPMENT AT THE
FLOWER BRANCH AMOUNTS IN SILVER
SPRING.
SEVEN PEOPLE DIED IN THAT 2016
EXPLOSION.
>>> ALSO, TODAY, STEPPED UP
PATROLS NEAR A BUS STOP IN GREEN
BELT DAY AFTER A WOMAN WAS
ASSAULTED THERE.
THIS HAPPENED AROUND 6:00 45 ON
MONDAY AM ON MONDAY IN THE 6900
BLOCK OF HANOVER PARKWAY.
NOW THAT VICTIM TOLD POLICE THAT
A MAN WHO WAS DRESSED IN ALL
BLACK GRABBED HER FROM BEHIND
AND DRAGGED HER INTO A WOODED
AREA WHERE HE ATTEMPTED TO
SEXUALLY ASSAULT HER.
THAT WOMAN USED PEPPER SPRAY ON
THE SUSPECT AND THAT SUSPECT
TOOK OFF.
♪
>>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT THE DEATH
TOLL RISING TORNADOES PLOWED
THROUGH THE DEEP SOUTH OVERNIGHT
LEAVING A TRAIL OF DESTRUCTION
IN PARTS OF MISSISSIPPI,
LOUISIANA, ALABAMA AND TEXAS.
ONE TWISTER IN LOUISIANA ON THE
GROUND FOR MORE THAN 60 MILES.
♪
>>> THEY'RE NOT DONE WITH THREAT
THERE.
THEY'VE GOT A NEW TORNADO WATCH
IN PARTS OF THE PANHANDLE OF
FLORIDA AND ALABAMA EARLY THIS
MORNING.
DON'T WANT TO HEAR THAT NEWS.
>> BIG STORMS.
VERY UNUSUAL IN DECEMBER TO BE
TALKING ABOUT YOU ABOUT
TORNADOES.
>> RIGHT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
AROUND HERE I MEAN THIS WEATHER
A LITTLE TYPICAL FOR THE MIDDLE
OF DECEMBER.
IT'S GLOOMY OUT THERE.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE NOT DOING
SCHOOL DELAYS BECAUSE WE'RE
DOING JUST RAIN.
>> THAT IS GOOD NEWS.
>> YUP.
CLOUDY WITH SHOWERS AND CHILLY
TEMPERATURES RIGHT NOW WE'RE
37 DEGREES HANGING IN THE 30S
FOR THE PAST 24 HOURS.
35 DULLES.
38 THIS MORNING BWI MARSHALL.
ALL RIGHT.
MOST OF US GETTING LIGHT
SPRINKLES AND RAIN SHOWERS.
THE EXCEPTION WESTERN MARYLAND.
EXTREME WESTERN MARYLAND PUT A
NEW WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY OUT
THERE CONCERNED ABOUT FREEZING
DRIZZLE FOR THE REST OF US,
CLOUDY SKIES, COOL TEMPS.
IN THE 40S THIS AFTERNOON.
OH ON AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN
SHOWERS ALTHOUGH THE RAIN
SHOWERS SHOULD COME TO AN END BY
LATE AFTERNOON AS OUR COLD FRONT
SWINGS THROUGH AND THEN WE'LL
START TO CLEAR IT OUT AND I
PROMISE THAT TOMORROW WILL BE A
MUCH BRIGHTER DAY.
MAYBE I'LL I'LL WRITE A SONG
ABOUT IT SUN COMING OUT
TOMORROW.
>> UM-HMM.
>> DO YOU GUYS THINK I COULD --
>> I THINK SO.
NO COPYRIGHT ISSUES.
NO PROBLEM.
>> I'LL WRITE A SONG.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ERIN, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> BEEP BEEP.
>> NASTY OUTSIDE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF BAD TRAFFIC
BECAUSE OF THE GRAY GLOOMY WET
CONDITIONS.
WATCH OUT FOR FOGGY PATCHES
CAUSING VISIBILITY PROBLEMS.
LOW BEAMS, TAKE IT SLOW, RIVER
ROAD A CRASH WESTBOUND RIGHT AT
THE BELTWAY.
SO AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY ENNUIED
SIDE THE BELTWAY TOWARD THE
BELTWAY YOU'LL HIT THAT ISSUE.
A LOT OF BRAKE LIGHTS.
95 AT A CRAWL PAST PRINCE
WILLIAMPARKWAY IN THE MAIN
LANES.
66 EASTBOUND 54 MINUTES FROM
MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY.
YOU CAN SEE HOW SLOW YOU ARE
REALLY GRAY AND YUKKY AND GLOOMY
OUT THERE.
42 MINUTES RIGHT NOW ON THE 395
STRETCH FROM EDSALL ROAD TO THE
14th STREET BRIDGE.
MAIN LANES ARE JUST VERY CROWDED
WITH A LOT OF CONGESTION FROM
THE PENTAGON TO THE 14th
STREET BRIDGE.
YOU JAM IN BOTH DIRECTIONS THE
FREEWAY TO AND FROM THE THIRD
STREET TUNNEL.
TUCKER, 132 MINUTES TO GET FROM
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY.
THAT IS WELL OVER --
>> TWO HOURS 12 MINUTES.
>> I WAS GOING TO GET THERE.
I WAS JUST YOU TO STALL SO I CAN
DO THE MATH IN MY HEAD OR ON MY
FINGER.
YOU KNOW I'M A MATH GENIUS.
THAT'S A TERRIBLE DRIVE TIME.
MORE TRAFFIC IN A MINUTE.
>> HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE RALLIED
LAST NIGHT IN SILVER SPRING
AGAINST MARYLAND GOVERNOR LARRY
HOGANS $9 BILLION PLAN TO WIDEN
THE CAPITAL BELTWAY AND I270.
THE GOVERNOR'S PLAN -- THE
GOVERNORS PLAN WITH NEW TOLL
LANES HIT A ROADBLOCK.
HOGAN POSTPONED A VOTE SCHEDULED
FOR TOMORROW BECAUSE CONTROLLER
PETER FRANCHOT DID NOT LIKE THE
CHANGES MADE TOTTER PLAN HE
NEEDS THE SUPPORT.
THE DELAYED VOTE WILL NOW PUSH
THE DEBATE INTO EARLY NEXT YEAR
WHEN MARYLAND'S GENERAL ASSEMBLY
GOES BACK INTO SESSION.
>> YOU THAT IT THERE WOULD BE A
BETTER SYSTEM IN PLACE FOR LIKE
SUCH A MAJOR AREA IN A TRI-STATE
AREA.
>> POLITICS ARE INVOLVED IN THE
MARKETPLACE --
>> YES.
CONGESTION.
I HAVE SOME FRIENDS THAT HAVE TO
DRIVE IN EVERY DAY FROM --
FURTHER NORTH.
>> NOT FUN?
>> NO, NOT FUN.
>> MARYLAND DEMOCRATS STATE
LAWMAKERS SAY THAT THEY WILL
PUSH LEGISLATION WHICH COULD
SLOW DOWN THE PROCESS EVEN MORE.
>>> BOEING HALTING PRODUCTION OF
737 MAX JETLINER IN JANUARY.
THE COMPANY HAS BEEN ASSEMBLING
ABOUT 40 PLANES A MONTH SINCE
THE MAX WAS GROUNDED IN MARCH
AFTER TWO CRASHES.
BOEING HAS 400 OF THE NEW
COMPLETED PLANES IN STORAGE.
IT'S BEEN SEEKING REGULATORY
APPROVAL FOR THE MAX TO RETURN
TO SERVICE BUT THAT APPROVAL
FROM AIRLINES AND GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS MAY NOT COME UNTIL
FEBRUARY AT THE EARLIEST.
>>> FORMER PRESIDENT BARACK
OBAMA MAKING HEADLINES THIS
MORNING FOR COMMENTS HE MADE
ABOUT WOMEN AT AN EVENT
YESTERDAY IN SINGAPORE.
>> THE FORMER PRESIDENT PRAISING
THE LEADERSHIP QUALITIES OF
WOMEN AND SHARING HIS THOUGHTS
ON THE TYPE OF LEADERSHIP THE
WORLD NEEDS.
>> HOLLY IS STANDING BY WITH A
CLOSER LOOK AT WHAT THE FORMER
PRESIDENT HAD TO SAY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> I THINK THE MUSIC THAT WAS
MEANT TO BE PLAYED THERE WHO
RUNS THE WORLD?
>> GIRLS.
GIRLS.
>> RIGHT.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SPEAKING AT A
PRIVATE EVENT FOR SEVERAL
THOUSAND PEOPLE.
THEY GATHERED JUST OH OF TO HEAR
HIM SPEAK.
MR. OBAMA REMARKED THAT IF WOMEN
WERE IN CHARGE OF EVERY COUNTRY
FOR THE NEXT TWO YEARS, THE
WORLD WOULD SEE GAINS ON JUST
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
AND SAID MANY OF THE WORLD'S
PROBLEMS ARE DUE TO OLD MEN NOT
GETTING OUT OF THE WAY.
ACCORDING TO SINGAPORE MEDIA THE
FORMER PRESIDENT SAID THE WORLD
NEEDS PEOPLE WHO ARE COMFORTABLE
AND UNDERSTAND COMPLEXITY AND
THAT LEADERS OFTEN REFLECT THEIR
CONSTITUENTS THAT INSECURITY.
THE MEANT WERE REPORTED AGAIN BY
THE SINGAPORE MEDIA.
PRESIDENT OBAMA ALSO REPORTEDLY
SAID "THERE WOULD BE LESS WAR,
KIDS WOULD BE TAKEN BETTER CARE
OF AND THERE WOULD BE A GENERAL
IMPROVEMENT IN LIVING STANDARDS
AND OUT COMES.
NOW WOMEN I JUST WANT YOU TO
KNOW YOU ARE NOT PERFECT BUT
WHAT I CAN SAY PRETTY INN
DISPUTABLELY IS THAT YOU ARE
BETTER ".
>> THE FORMER PRESIDENT WAS
THERE TO DISCUSS LEADERSHIP IN
HIS LIFE IN THE OVAL OFFICE.
THE EVENT WAS THE FINAL STOP IN
A TOUR OF ASIAN COUNTRIES BY MR.
THEY ARE PROMOTING THE OBAMA
FOUNDATION'S EFFORTS TO FOSTER
LEADERSHIP AND ACTIVISM.
SOUNDS LIKE HE SHOULD BE
CAMPAIGNING FOR A WOMAN
CANDIDATE, RIGHT?
>> SOUNDS LIKE IT TO ME.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLLY, THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> 8:10.
STILL AHEAD MAKING METRO SAFER.
WHY METRO IS TEAMING UP WITH TSA
TO DO SO.
>> PLUS OUR HOLIDAY CARDS
BECOMING OUTDATED?  ONE WOMAN'S
ARGUMENT TO STOP SENDING THEM.
HERE'S A HINT.
IT HAS TO DO WITH SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AS WE HEAD
TO BREAK RIGHT NOW.
ANOTHER RAINY AND GLOOMY AND
FOGGY MORNING.
THERE'S YOUR HEADLINE.
CAN'T SEE ANYTHING OUT THERE.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC COMING UP ON
THE 5'S NEXT.
♪
♪♪
(Military Mom)
Love you, miss you guys!
(Military Mom's Family)
Love you!
♪
(Joy Ofodu)
We got this!
♪
(Kids)
Wow! Santa was here!
(Military Mom's Husband)
Whoa.
How did this happen?
(Military Mom)
I think I know.
(Military Mom's Husband)
Merry Christmas honey.
(Military Mom)
Merry Christmas!
(Kids)
Look, it's snowing.
♪
There was a time when health
care made house calls...
That time has come again.
Thanks to CVS Health.
With home infusion services.
In-home care managers.
Home delivery.
And video visits.
We're creating the future
of health care,
using a simple idea
form the past.
CVS Health.
Where health is everything.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ Blow a kiss into the sun ♪
♪ We need someone to lean on ♪
♪ All we needed
somebody to lean on ♪
First payment is on us
when you lease the new XC90.
Starting at $529 a
month for 36 months
with $4350 due at signing.
>>> 8:13.
TALK ABOUT BEING IN THE RIGHT
PLACE AT THE RIGHT TIME.
A MALNOURISHED DOG SPOTTED ON
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO WANDERING
INTO A HOME IN PHILADELPHIA
DURING A RAINSTORM IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT.
>> WHY DOES THIS NEVER HAPPEN TO
ME?
>> THE COUPLE WOKE UP.
THEY SAW THE DOG INSIDE.
THEY REMEMBER BAFFLED AFTER
WATCHING THE SECURITY CAMERA
FOOTAGE THEY REALIZED THE WIND
BLEW OPEN THEIR FRONT DOOR.
>> HE WAS MEANT TO BE THERE.
>> THE LITTLE GUY WANDERED
INSIDE.
THE DOG DID NOT HAVE A COLLAR.
THE DOG WAS COLD.
MALNOURISHED HAD FLEAS.
THE COUPLE TOOK HER MY APOLOGIES
TO THE VET WHO DETERMINED SHE
WAS ABOUT NINE YEARS OLD.
>> AWW.
SHE'S A PUMPKIN.
>> SHE DID HAVE HEALTH CONCERNS.
HEART MURMUR AND SOME OTHER
HEALTH ISSUES BUT DESPITE ALL
THE TROUBLE, THE COUPLE FELL IN
LOVE WITH THE DOG AND THEY'VE
DECIDED TO KEEP HER.
>> OF COURSE THEY DID.
>> NAMED HER SUZIE.
SUZIE.
>> WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE WOULDN'T
KEEP HER.
>> ENJOY THE REST OF YOUR DAYS.
>> MEANT TO BE, RIGHT?  DEAR
SANTA CLAUS,.
>> WALKED INTO THEIR LIFE.
>> PLEASE LET ME HUMBLE AND
STUMBLE ACROSS AN ANIMAL WHO
NEEDS ME.
>> DON'T LEAVE YOUR DOOR OPEN
WAITING FOR IT, THOUGH.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT I HOPE YOU GET -- I MIGHT
GET --
>> ANOTHER ADDITION TO --
>> FOXES OR RACCOONS.
>> SPEAKING OF SWEET SURPRISES,
MISSISSIPPI WOMAN WELCOMED NEW
BABY JUST DAYS AFTER FINDING OUT
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
>> YET AGAIN THIS NEVER HAPPENED
TO ME.
LAUREN CHALK FOUND OUT SHE WAS
PREGNANT AT 38 WEEKS AND FIVE
DAYS.
SHE WENT TO THE DOCTOR AT HER
MOTHER'S ADVICE.
THE LITTLE BABY FOR SYMPTOMS SHE
DESCRIBES AS BEING GROUCHY.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> BEEN THERE SISTER.
>> I'M PREGNANT.
>> BUT OTHER THAN THAT, SHE SAYS
SHE DIDN'T HAVE ANY TYPICAL
PREGNANCY SYMPTOMS.
LAST WEEK SHE GAVE BIRTH TO A
HEALTHY BABY BOY.
SHE NAMED THAT BABY WYATT.
>> ISN'T IT FRUSTRATING WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT ALL THE, YOU KNOW,
HEALTH THINGS THAT YOU COULD
HAVE AVOIDED IF IT WAS SUDDENLY
LIKE GUESS WHAT, A WEEK TO GO,
HERE'S YOUR BABY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> HI.
>> ALLISON, HOW ABOUT -- WHY ARE
YOU DOING YOUR CUTE POSE.
>> ARE YOU LOOKING FOR FOR A SON
WHO MIGHT WALK INTO YOUR LIFE.
>> A LITTLE BIT YOUNGER PERHAPS
THAN YOU.
I DON'T NEED A GROWN MAN WALKING
INTO MY LIFE.
>> OR HER HOUSE FOR THAT MATTER.
>> OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT ACTUALLY HOOPED MY MOM.
SHE HAD A DOG WALK ON HER
PROPERTY IT NEVER LEFT.
SHE ADOPTED IT SHE TRIED TO FIND
ITS HOME.
>> MAKE SURE THAT THE PUMP PEE
IS NOT LOST.
HOW SWEET.
>> SHE HAD THE DOG FOR 10 YEARS.
>> CLOUDY SKIES AND RAIN SHOWERS
ACROSS THE AREA.
IT'S GOING TO BE A COOL DAY ONLY
IN THE 30S.
AT THIS HOUR WE'LL TOP OUT IN
THE 40S LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
SO LAYERS AND, YEAH,
UNFORTUNATELY THE UMBRELLA HAS
GOT TO COME BACK TODAY AS WE'RE
GOING TO BE SLOW TO WARM IT UP.
SATELLITE/RADAR MOST OF THE
SHOWER ACTIVITY FAIRLY LIGHT.
A COUPLE OF SHOWERS SPOTTY
SHOWERS SOUTHERN MARYLAND AND
COUPLE SHOWERS NORTH AND WEST UP
TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN AND SOUTHERN
PENNSYLVANIA.
WE WILL SEE THE SHOWERS FILL IN
LATER THIS MORNING AND THIS
AFTERNOON AS A COLD FRONT
APPROACHES AND ONCE THAT FRONT
SWINGS THROUGH THE REGION YOU
CAN SEE IT OUT TO THE WEST.
WE WILL BE DONE WITH THE SHOWERS
AND WE WILL CLEAR IT OUT MOST OF
THE COUNTRY HAY IF YOU'RE
TRAVELING TODAY MOST OF THE
COUNTRY FAIRLY QUIET.
MIAMI LOOKS GREAT.
HOUSTON, DALLAS LOOK GOOD.
ONE TROUBLE SPOT DOWN IN PARTS
OF GEORGIA AND ALABAMA AND
FLORIDA WHERE THEY'VE JUST GOT A
BRAND NEW TORNADO WATCH THAT WAS
ISSUED BUT MOST OF THE COUNTRY
IF YOU'RE TRAVELING NICE AND
QUIET LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
50 WE KEEP IT COOL AND SHOWERY
THIS AFTERNOON.
WE'LL CLEAR IT OUT TONIGHT BACK
INTO FULL SUNSHINE FORT END OF
THE WEEK.
WEDNESDAY, THURSDAY, FRIDAY ALL
LOOK GOOD.
ERIN, HI.
>> GOOD MORNING.
THAT WAS THE MOST SUBDUED TOSS
EVER.
WHERE DID ALL THE ENERGY GO.
>> I'LL GOT TO TO MIX IT UP.
>> MY GOODNESS, 270 SOUTHBOUND A
LITTLE RAIN, GRAY GLOOMY FOGGY
CONDITIONS AND YOU ARE IN FOR
TUCKER BARNES 153 MINUTE RIDE
FROM 70 DOWN --
>> GOT WORSE.
THAT IS WELL OVER TWO HOURS,
RIGHT?
>> YES.
TWO HOURS WOULD BE --
>> TWO AND A HALF HOURS.
>> IMAGINE THAT.
>> NOPE.&
>> MY MATH SKILLS ARE ON POINT
TODAY.
AND YOUR RIDE IS MISERABLE.
WATCH OUT FOR BAILOUT TRAFFIC ON
355.
AGAIN OVER TWO AND A HALF
COMMUTE 70 DOWN TO THE SPLIT.
MAD CROWDED.
JUST CAME OUT BECAUSE IT'S SO
BAD.
OUTER LOOP RIGHT NOW 8 MILES AN
HOUR AVERAGE 95 OVER TO GEORGIA
AVENUE.
VERY SLOW ABOUT 45 MINUTE SLOW
DOWN.
WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF CONGESTION
BOTH DIRECTIONS BW PARKWAY TO
AND FROM 32.
GW PARKWAY NORTHBOUND LEFT LANE
BLOCK AFTER THE KEY BRIDGE.
METRO IS ON TIME.
A LOT RODE BEHIND ME JAM PACKED
DAY AROUND THE DMV.
BACK TO YOU.
>> ♪
>>> STEVE, FIRST OF ALL --
>> YES.
>> IT'S CHRISTMASTIME.
>> I KNOW.
WEEK AWAY.
>> IS THIS SO AWESOME.
>> ALWAYS IS.
I LOVE IT.
OKAY.
SO HERE'S A QUESTION.
IS GRIN CHI TO GIVE UP A HOLIDAY
TRADITION.
ONE GOOD HOUSEKEEPING WRITER IS
MAKING THE CASE FOR NOT SENDING
OUT CHRISTMAS CARDS.
>> SHE SAYS SHE IS GIVING UP
SENDING CARDS THIS YEAR BECAUSE
SHE SAID THERE ARE BETTER WAYS
TO SHOW THOUGHT AND CARE.
SHE ALSO ARGUED SOCIAL MODE YA
ALREADY KEEPS US CONNECTED
THROUGHOUT THE YEAR.
SO WHY TAKE THAT EXTRA EFFORT TO
HAND WRITE AND PERSONALIZE A
CARD?
>> I ADDED THAT LAST PART BUT
CHRISTMAS CARDS ARE RARELY EVER
PERSONAL SHE ARGUES.
INSTEAD SHE ENCOURAGES PEOPLE TO
CONNECT ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS
LIKE THROUGH PERSONAL E-MAIL OR
PERHAPS A WAIT FOR IT PHONE C
CALL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> LAST NIGHT THE FOX5 LIKE IT
OR NOT CREW WEIGHED IN.
>> I GET THE POINT THAT WE DO
LIVE IN A DAY AND AGE WHERE WE
CAN GET STATUS UPDATE OF EVER
EVERYBODY'S LIVES INCLUDE WAGON
YOU'RE HAVING FOR DINNER TONIGHT
PROBABLY JIM.
>> RIGHT.
>> WE DON'T NEED -- SALAD.
>> UPDATE AND THE LETTER SOME
PEBBLE STILL SEND I STILL HAVE
FRIENDS THAT SEND THE TWO PAGE
LETTER WITH THE UPDATE I READ IT
AND IT'S NICE, BUT, YES, IS
THERE REAL NEED FOR THAT ANNUAL
UPDATE?  MAYBE NOT SO.
>> I HATE CHRISTMAS CARDS.
I'M PROBABLY NEVER GOING TO GET
ONE AGAIN.
>> OFF THE LIST.
I THROW THEM OUT.
I LOOK AT SOME.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, AL?
>> I'M JUST -- YEAH.
I LOVE CHRISTMAS CARDS.
>> I DO TOO.
>> RIGHT.
OKAY.
>> WE WANT TO BRING SOME OF THE
MORNING SHOW CREW IN TO WEIGH
IN.
MIKE AND ERIN ARE WITH US.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
>> GOOD MORNING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M ON BOARD WITH
THE WHOLE CHRISTMAS CARD
TRADITION.
YOU KNOW WHY.
>> BECAUSE ALL I GOT NET
FRIGGING MAIL ANY MORE IS BILLS
AND, YOU KNOW, ADVERTISEMENTS
THINGS I DON'T WANT TO SEE.
SO EVERY HOLIDAY SEASON WHEN
CHRISTMAS CARDS COME ALONG, I
FINALLY GET SOMETHING THAT'S
ENJOYABLE AND I'M NOT FOLLOWING
EVERYBODY ON FACEBOOK 24/7.
SO IT'S NICE SOMETIMES TO SEE
PARTICULARLY EXTENDED FAMILY
THAT SENDS THE CARDS IN.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE HOW THEY'RE
DOING.
ERIN, WHAT DO YOU THINK.
>> I JUST GOT A CHRISTMAS CARD
YESTERDAY FROM MY BEST FRIEND
KEN AND HIS WIFE REBECCA WHO
LIVE IN FLORIDA WITH THEIR TWO
LITTLE BABIES ON IT I LOVE THE
CHRISTMAS CARDS EVERY YEAR AND
KEEPING TRACK OF MY FRIENDS
CHILDREN GROWING UP OVER THE
YEARS.
AND MY NIECE AND NEPHEW BRINGS A
SMILE TO MY FACE AND MY
REFRIGERATOR I HANG THEM ALL UP
AND IT MAKES ME HAPPY EVERY TIME
I GET A SNACK.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVE CHRISTMAS CARDS.
>> KNEE.
>> I RECEIVED TWO CHRISTMAS
CARDS THIS YEAR TYPICALLY MY
TEAM THAT I FOLLOW AND THE OTHER
FROM MY DENTIST WHICH I MAY OR
MY NOT ENJOY.
AND THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
SO I WELCOMED THE CARDS BECAUSE
IT'S KIND OF NICE TO HEAR FROM
PEOPLE.
>> I DO -- SO THE SOCIAL MEDIA
ARGUMENT IS REAL.
SO WHEN I SEND OUT, UM, PHOTO
CHRISTMAS CARDS I JUST MAKE SURE
IT'S A PICTURE NOBODY HAS SEEN
AND IT'S NICE TO SEE JUST FOR A
SECOND PEOPLE STOP, THEY LOOK,
YOU KNOW, HOPEFULLY WHEN YOU
SEND THE CARD.
OKAY.
UP.K HOW THE GIRLS HAVE BROKEN-
LOOK AT ALLISON AND MARK.
THEY'RE UP THIS YEAR, THEY'RE
DOWN THIS.
>> I LOVE THIS TRADITION SO MUCH
WE PUT ONE OUT THIS YEAR IN THE
WEATHER DEPARTMENT.
>> LET'S SEE IT.
>> I THINK WE HAVE THAT FOR YOU.
>> AWW.
>> LOOKING GOOD, GUYS.
>> SO NICE.
WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO GET THIS IN
THE MALE?  COME ON.
YET YOU KNOW YOU MIGHT THINK,
THIS IS JUST SOMETHING DONE FOR
TV.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I GOT EM.
THEY'RE GOING OUT TO EVERYBODY.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T GET YOU
ANYTHING.
>> I LOVE IT!
>> HASH TAG AWKWARD FAMILY PH
PHOTO.
>> AWKWARD?  COME ON.
>> MIKEY AND TUCK KEY.
THAT IS SO CUTE.
>> AUTHENTIC A SMILE AS YOU CAN
BUY IN THIS DEPARTMENT.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
>> FEELING A LITTLE NEGLECTED
OVER THERE, STEVE.
>> I DO THINK TUCK KEY IS GOING
TO STICK.
VIA HUNCH.
DEFINITELY WILL STICK.
>> THANKS EVERYBODY.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
LIKE IT OR NOT TRUE --
>> KEEP THE CARDS COMING.
>> WE'LL WEIGH IN AT
7:00 O'CLOCK EVERY DAY.
CHECK THEM OUT THERE.
>> NEW MEANING TO MARITAL BLISS.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE HOW LONG THIS
COUPLE HAS BEEN MARRIED IN FACT
IT IS SUCH A LONG TIME, THEY ARE
NOW WORLD RECORD HOLDERS.
WE'LL SHARE THEIR SECRET TO LONG
LASLASTING LOVE NEXT.
>> MAUREEN GETTING INTO THE
HOLIDAY SPIRIT SHE'S IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD
MORNING, GUYS.
YES WE'RE AT THE RESTON TOWN
CENTER IT'S LOOKING A LOT LIKE
CHRISTMAS.
WE'VE GOT A ABOUT WEEK TO GO
BEFORE THE BIG DAY.
BUT, YOU'VE GOT TO COME OUT HERE
BECAUSE WE'VE GOT SO MUCH IN
STORE FOR THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE SIGHTS AND
SOUNDS RESTON TOWN CENTER AS
WE'RE CELEBRATING CHRISTMAS AND
COUNTING DOWN TO THE BIG DAY.
THAT AND MUCH MORE COMING UP ON
FOX5 MORNING NEWS.
♪
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
I'm Jimmy Dean and thank you
very much for lettin'
at no additional
charge.
us become just a little
part of your holiday.
And we sincerely hope
that Jimmy Dean sausage
might make your holiday just
a little bit brighter.
Happy Holiday to ya.
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
BACK NOW 8:24.
HERE'S THE STORY FOR YOU THIS
MORNING.
IF YOU WANT SOME INSPIRATION,
ONE COUPLE IN TEXAS CELEBRATING
QUITE THE ANNIVERSARY.
THEIR 80th WEDDING
ANNIVERSARY.
>> WHAT?
>> 106 YEARS OLD IS JOHN
HENDERSON.
105 YEARS OLD HIS WIFE CHARLOTTE
CURTIS.
THEY MET AT THE UNIVERSITY OF
TEXAS BACK IN 1934.
FIVE YEARS LATER THEY GOT
MARRIED.
THEIR SECRET, SIMPLE.
BE KIND TO EACH OTHER.
THEY NOW LIVE TOGETHER AT A
RETIREMENT COMMUNITY AND THEY
NOW HAVE THE GUINNESS RECORD AS
THE OLDEST LIVING MARYLAND COME.
105 AND 106 YEARS OLD MARRIED
FOR 80 YEARS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> I MEAN, THEY'RE REALLY NO
WORDS INCREDIBLE.
HE IS, OKAY HE'S UP WALKING AND
PUSHING HIS WIFE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT UM OOH SAYING.
>> LIKE ABLE BODIED AND --
>> THE FACT THAT THEY'RE
TOGETHER KEEPS THEM I GUARANTEE
IT GIVES THEM A COUPLE EXTRA
DECADES.
>> TRUE.
>> SO CUTE.
MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN MARRIED 37
YEARS THEY GO ON DATES ON THE
WEEKEND TOGETHER IT'S SO SWEET
IT GIVES ME HOPE THAT MARRIAGE
CAN WORK.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SO SWEET.
>> HOW MANY YEARS HAVE YOU BEEN
MARRIED?
>> WHO ME?
>> YES.
>> NEXT YEAR IT WILL BE 20
YEARS.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> BEG ONE.
>> BIG ANNIVERSARY.
>> FOX5 PARTY.
>> CONGRATS TO YOU AND MARK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
APRIL 15th, 2020, 20 YEARS.
>> GET ON IT, TUCK.
>> IF WE WERE MARRIED 80 YEARS
LET'S SEE I'D BE -- PROBABLY NOT
GOING TO MAKE IT 80 YEARS.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE YOU WERE
GOING WITH THAT.
>> FANTASTIC.
>> I'M JUST SAYING -- YOU'D HAVE
TO GET MARRIED AT LIKE 20 YEARS
OLD.
>> THEY GOT MARRIED AT 25.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE GOING TO --
GOTTEN MARRIED AT LIKE 15 AND 16
BUT, YOU KNOW, 25 AND 26 OR
SOMETHING.
>> INCREDIBLE.
>> THEY'RE JUST ASKING ERIN
MAYBE IN 80 YEARS SHE'LL ACCEPT
THAT.
>> WE GOT A FEW SHOWERS AROUND
TODAY.
PARTICULARLY THIS AFTERNOON COLD
FRONT COMES THROUGH IT WILL STAY
COOL THE SUN GETS BACK TOMORROW.
ONE MORE GLOOM MOW DAY THE SUN
IS BACK TOMORROW.
ERIN, GOOD MORNING.
>> AND 8:26 RIGHT NOW.
INNER LOOP LOOK AT THAT, NASTY
DELAYS.
17 MILES PER HOUR FROM THE
SPRINGFIELD INTERCHANGE UP
THROUGH 66.
IT IS MEGA CROWDED OUT THERE.
WE'RE SEEING REALLY NASTY
CONDITIONS.
LET'S SEE.
CAN YOU HAND ME MY CLICKER I'LL
SHOW YOU SOMETHING ELSE.
WE HAVE 66 DELAYS ALMOST AN HOUR
FROM MANASSAS THROUGH THE
BELTWAY.
395, 43 MINUTES AND 270 WELL
OVER TWO HOURS FROM 70 TO THE
SPLIT.
GUYS, OOH I DON'T LOVE TODAY'S
DRIVE.
>> UM-UM.
ALL RIGHT.
>>> 8:30 COMING UP AT 8:30 I
SHOULD SAY MAKING METRO SAFER.
>> ALL KNEW THIS MORNING METRO
ANNOUNCING ITS NEW PLAN TO
IMPROVE SAFETY POUR PASSENGERS
TEAMING UP WITH TSA.
THE NEW TECHNOLOGY THAT METRO
PLANS ON USING.
WE WILL SHOW YOU.
WE'LL DISCUSS IT COMING UP IN
JUST A COUPLE OF MINUTES.
♪
cohe
mpetition
and we broke through.
You've tried retinol,
but you have never tried one
like this.
Olay's Retinol24 complex
hydrates
better than the #1 retinol.
Visibly smoother brighter skin
in just 24 hours.
A skin upgrade?
Crushed it.
New Olay Retinol24.
Face Anything.
Olay.
Now available with retinol serum
and retinol eye cream.
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
♪
>> MAYBE IF YOU HEAD DOWN TO
SAINT MARY'S COUNTY THE FOG WILL
LIFT EVER SO SLIGHTLY, AL.
YOU CAN AT LEAST SEE THE
PAVEMENT THERE.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LITTLE BIT BETTER THAN WHAT
WE'VE BEEN SEEING UP HERE.
IT'S BEEN THIS WAY FOR THE LAST
SEVERAL HOURS.
SO JUST GIVE YOURSELF EXTRA TIME
AND TRAFFIC IS A MESS JUST
BECAUSE VISIBILITY IS LIMITED.
>> LOOK OUT FOR PEDESTRIANS, T
TOO.
HOSE HEADLIGHTS ON.
>> THAT'S LEONARDTOWN.
GOOD MORNING TO EVERYBODY DOWN
THERE.
IN THE MEANTIME, METRO AND TSA
TEAMING UP TO MAKE OUR METRO
RAILWAYS SAFER.
>> BOTH ARE TESTING NEW DEVICE
TAT IS HAVE THE POTENTIAL TO
DETECT EXPLOSIVE DEVICES AND
OTHER DANGEROUS ITEMS BEFORE
THEY END THE TRANSIT SYSTEM.
>> THOSE DEVICES ARE BEING TE
TESTED TODAY AT THE PENTAGON
CITY METRO STATION.
THAT'S WHERE WE FIND FOX5 BOB
BARNARD.
BOB JOINS US LIVE WITH MORE ON
THIS NEW TECHNOLOGY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD
MORNING, GUYS.
YES, WE ARE AT THE PENTAGON CITY
METRO STATION.
BUSY PLACE THIS MORNING.
YOU SEE METRO TRANSIT POLICE
ALREADY HAS K9 TEAMS HERE IN THE
STATION, AND OFFICERS ON FOOT
JUST KIND OF LOOKING OUT FOR
STUFF.
BUT HERE JUST AROUND THE CORNER
I WANT TO SHOW YOU THIS NEW
TECHNOLOGY.
IT'S BASICALLY FROM TSA THE
FOLKS WHO WORK AT THE AIRPORT.
GUYS CAN WE SPLIT THE DIFFERENCE
AND SHOW OUR VIEWERS WHAT WE'VE
GOT HERE?  THIS IS A MOBILE
UNIT.
IT'S GOT A CAM A YOU SEE PEOPLE
WALKING BY, OF COURSE, THERE'S
NOBODY W WALKING BY RIGHT NOW.
CAN ONE OF YOU TALK PASSED HERE
THANK YOU WE GOT A NEW MODEL.
THIS BLACK CUT OUT SCREEN SEE IT
LOOKS LIKE AN INFRARED IMAGE
THAT IS WHAT IS PART OF THIS NEW
PROGRAM TO KIND OF HELP DETECT
PERHAPS SOMETHING THAT METRO
DOESN'T WANT IN THE TRANSIT
SYSTEM.
JOINING US TO TALK ABOUT THIS IS
JIM BAMBERGER, AMOUNT JIM
BAMBERGER WITH TSA I LAID IT FOR
OUR VIEWERS THERE, JIM.
TELL ME ABOUT THIS TECHNOLOGY IN
PARTICULAR.
>> SURE, SURE.
BE HAPPY TO.
SO THIS IS A TECHNOLOGY CALLED
MILL MY METER WAVE TECHNOLOGY.
WHAT IT DOES, IT CREATES AN
AVATAR OF A PERSON AND THEN CAN
SHOW IF THERE'S SOMETHING
BENEATH THEIR CLOTHING LIKE A
SUICIDE VEST OR A LARGE WEAPON.
>> AND WHAT IS THE TECHNOLOGY?
THIS NOT RADIOLOGICAL IMAGING OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT, IS IT.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
IT'S PURELY PASSIVE WHAT I MEAN
BY THAT IT JUST RECEIVES THE
NATURALLY OCCURRING ENERGY THAT
COMES OFF YOUR BODY AND SHOWS
WHERE IT'S BEING BLOCKED.
SO IT CAN DETECT IF SOMETHING
BENEATH YOUR CLOTHING BUT IT'S
PURELY PASSIVE.
IT DOES NOT EMIT ANYTHING
NEGATIVE.
>> YOU GUYS ARE TESTING THAT
THIS OUT HERE AT PENTAGON CITY.
IT'S A MOBILE UNIT.
IT COULD BE USED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
THIS IS USED WITH AMTRAK AND
OTHER PLACES ALREADY, IS THAT
CORRECT?
>> YES, IT IS.
IT'S USED THROUGHOUT THE COU
COUNTRY.
AS A MATTER OF FACT LA METRO
PURCHASED SOME OF THEM.
AND IT'S ONE TOOL, ONE PIECE OF
EQUIPMENT THAT GIVES THE
OFFICERS HERE ANOTHER PIECE OF
INFORMATION TO HELP THEM MAKE A
DECISION.
>> Reporter: WE WERE TALKIN
BEFORE WE WENT ON TV HERE THAT
IT'S NOT FOOLPROOF BECAUSE IF
THE OFFICERS HERE HAPPEN TO LOOK
AWAY WHEN THE PERSON WITH
WHATEVER WALKS THROUGH AND WOULD
BE HIGHLIGHTED THERE ON THE
SCREEN, IF THEY DON'T ACTUALLY
SEE IT, THAT PERSON GOES RIGHT
ON BY.
>> RIGHT.
GOOD POINT.
NO PIECE OF TECHNOLOGY IS
FOOLPROOF.
IT HAS TO BE VIEWED REAL TIME
BUT IT ALSO GIVES THE OFFICERS
ANOTHER PIECE OF TECHNOLOGY,
ANOTHER TOOL, ANOTHER WEAPON, IF
YOU WILL, TO HELP THEM MAKE A
DECISION ON WHETHER A PERSON
COULD BE CARRYING SOMETHING
THAT'S DANGEROUS TO THE
TRAVELING PUBLIC.
>> Reporter: JIM, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
METRO TRANSIT POLICE OFFICERS
TAKING A LOOK AT THIS.
AS WE LEAVE YOU GUYS, TAKE A
LOOK.
THIS IS A BUSY METRO STATION.
YOU HAVE A LOT OF POLICE
OFFICERS HERE.
A LOT OF PASSENGERS, PEOPLE AND
THEY'LL TELL YOU THE BEST THING
OUR OWN EYES IF YOU SEE
SOMETHING THAT LOOKS SUSPICIOUS,
SAY SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
BUT AS WELL AS THE POLICE K9S
AND THE OFFICERS THERE'S NOW
THIS NEW TECHNOLOGY TO HELPER
HAPPENS PREVENT SOMETHING
TERRIBLE HAPPENING IN OUR METRO
SYSTEM HERE IN THE GREATER
WASHINGTON AREA.
GUYS?
>> BOB, THANKS VERY MUCH 8:34
I'M SURE THEY'LL TAKE ANYTHING
THEY CAN TO KEEP PEOPLE SAFE AT
THIS POINT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>>> SO DADS WILL BE DADS.
GIRL SHOWED PICTURES ON SOCIAL
MEDIA OF HER DAD PICKING HER UP
FROM FROM THE AIRPORT IN
MISSOURI AND AS YOU CAN SEE HE
HAS A NEW SIGN FOR EVERY TIME
SHE COMES HOME.
SOME OF THEM SUPPORTING --
SPORTING BIG-TIME NAMES LIKE THE
KARDASHIANS MIRANDA LAMBERT BUT
MANY ON SOCIAL MEDIA ENVY THE
GIRL BECAUSE HER DAD IS JUST SO
RELIABLE.
LOOK AT THE ONE ON THE RIGHT.
SANTA.
>> AWW.
>> DAD GIVES THAT EXTRA EFFORT
TO GO TO THE AIRPORT AND PICK
YOU UP YOU GOT TO LOVE IT.
>> THAT IS SO CUTE.
HE'S SO HAPPY TO HAVE HER HOME.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
ALL RIGHT.
TUCKER BARNES, GOOD MORNING,
SIR.
>> I LEAK THE HAND RIGHT 10
KARDASHIAN SIGN ACTUALLY THAT'S
BIG TIME, RIGHT.
>> THAT'S GREAT STORY.
ALL RIGHT.
NATIONAL HARBOR WE GOT THE
CLOUDY SKIES.
GOT SOME LIGHT DRIZZLE.
WE GOT VERY COOL CONDITIONS OUT
THERE.
37 NOW TO START YOUR MORNING
HERE IN WASHINGTON, AND NO DOUBT
ABOUT IT THAT CHILLY RAW FEELING
WE HAD AROUND HERE YESTERDAY
THAT CONTINUES TODAY AS WE AWAIT
THE ARRIVAL OF A COLD FRONT
WHICH WILL SWEEP IN LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
JUST A FEW SPRINKLES AND SHOWERS
EARLY.
THE GOOD NEWS IT'S ALL LIQUID
HERE WITH TEMPERATURES IN THE
MID 30S BUT VERY CHILLY RAIN.
OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST THERE
IS  A NEW WINTER WEATHER ADVISOY
FOR EXTREME WESTERN MARYLAND IF
YOU'RE DRIVING IN THAT
DIRECTION, THERE MAY BE SOME
FROZEN RAIN OR FREEZING RAIN OUT
THERE.
OKAY.
WHAT CAN WE EXPECT THIS
AFTERNOON.
>> WE CAN EXPECT MORE OF THE
SAME CLOUD COVER, EVENTUALLY THE
LAST BATCH OF SHOWERS IS GOING
TO ROLL IN HERE WITH A COLD
FRONT KIND OF MID AFTERNOON.
WE'LL KEEP SHOWERS IN THE
FORECAST THROUGH LATE THIS
AFTERNOON AND THEN THINGS WILL
START TO DRY OUT.
THE WINDS WILL PICK UP THE
COLDER AIR WILL START TO RUSH IN
BEHIND THAT FRONT AND WE'LL BE
IN FOR A MUCH COOLER DAY
TOMORROW.
BUT BACK TO SUNSHINE.
50 TODAY, CLOUDS AND SHOWERS AND
THEN BACK TO SUNSHINE FOR YOUR
WEDNESDAY 40.
IT WILL BE EVEN COLDER THAN THAT
ON THURSDAY.
I'LL HAVE THE SEVEN DAY COMING
RIGHT UP.
DO ANOTHER ROUND OF ROADS AND
IT'S NOT BEEN AN EASY MORNING.
ERIN HAS DETAILS.
>> TERRIBLE OUT THERE.
8:36.
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE WESTBOUND
CRASH BLOCKS THE RIGHT LANE OF
THE RAM TOM 295 SOUTHBOUND.
295 IS PARKED INTO RIVERDALE
RK
6 MILES AN HOUR AVERAGE.
52 TO 295 JAMMED.
SUITLAND PARKWAY PARKED AS YOU
MAKE YOUR WAY TO SOUTH CAPITAL
FROM ALABAMA AVENUE IN SOUT
SOUTHEAST.
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE SO HEAVY IN
ADDITION TO THAT CRASH.
NEW YORK AVENUE JAMS INBOUND
VERY SLOW.
295 -- 270 I SHOULD SAY
NORTHBOUND THERE'S A CRASH
INVOLVING AN OVERTURNED VEHICLE
BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE IN YOU
ARE BEEN IN A AFTER 109 CAUSING
SOME HEAVY NORTHBOUND TRAFFIC.
THERE'S A RUBBERNECK DELAY
SOUTHBOUND IN ADDITION TO JUST
VERY HEAVY TRAFFIC.
LUCKILY WE'VE DIPPED TO UNDER AN
HOUR AND A HALF FROM 70 DOWN TO
THE SPUR BUT WE'RE STILL SEEING
GRAY, GLOOMY CONDITIONS, FOG OUT
THERE CAUSING VISIBILITY
PROBLEMS.
LOW BEAMS TAKE IT SLOW.
HAVE SOME PATIENCE.
IT'S STILL A JAM PACKED RIDE
AROUND THE DMV.
BACK TO YOU.
>> STILL AHEAD THE DRINK COMPANY
LAUNCHING A MONTHLY SUBSCRIPTION
SERVICE.
>> OPRAH AND WEIGHT WATCHERS
KEEPING THEIR PARTNERSHIP GOING.
THE PERK THE BIG O WILL RECEIVE
AS PART OF AN EXTENDED DEAL WITH
♪
♪♪
>>> BACK NOW 8:39.
OPRAH WINFREY STICKING WITH
WEIGHT WATCHERS ADDING ANOTHER
FIVE YEARS TO HER DEAL WITH THE
COMPANY.
WINFREY WILL REMAIN ON THE BOARD
AND CONTINUE AS AN ADVISER IN
MAJOR SHAREHOLDER THROUGH MAY OF
2025.
NOW SHE JOINED THE BOARD YOU'LL
REMEMBER IN OCTOBER OF 2015 AND
BOUGHT A 10% STAKE IN THE
COMPANY WORTH $43 MILLION.
SHE'S SOLD OFF SOME OF HER STAKE
IN THE PAST FEW YEARS AND
CURRENTLY HAS AN 8% STAKE AS
PART OF HER EXTENDED DEAL
WINFREY HAS THE OPTION OF
INCREASING HER STAKE ONCE AGAIN.
JUST BECAUSE I WANT TO SAY IT
AGAIN, STAKE.
OKAY.
COCA-COLA PLANNING ROLL OUT ITS%
SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE TO GIVE
SODA LOVES THE FIRST TASTE OF
NEW FLAVORS.
THE SERVICE WILL COST $10 A
MONTH.
OVER THOSE FOUR WEEKS USERS
COULD SAMPLE 20 OR MORE NEW
BEVERAGES.
YOU GOT TO REALLY LOVE SOME
COCA-COLA TO DO THAT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE.
HOW YOU WORK STAKE INTO A WEIGHT
WATCHERS STORY.
S-T-A-K-E.
NO E.
NO MIDDLE E.
>> I HEARD WHAT I WANTED TO.
8:41.
STILL AHEAD WE'LL RING IN THE
HOLIDAY SEASON IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA OR SHOULD WE SAY SING
IN THE HOLIDAY SEASON AS WE'RE
LIVE AT RESTON TOWN CENTER WITH
MUSICAL CHRISTMAS TREE.
♪
♪♪
Welcome to our
Lipton tea factory.
Where these sun-soaked
tea leaves
are picked at the peak
of freshness.
For a naturally smooth taste.
And drinking Lipton
every day
can help support a
healthy heart!
>>> WE'RE JUST ABOUT 15 MINUTES
AWAY FROM GOOD DAY DC.
LET'S GIVE YOU A PEEK WHAT'S
COMING UP TODAY JOINING US LIVE
IN THE LOFT FROM TOP CHEF KWAME
WILL JOIN SEVERAL OTHER
CELEBRITIES TONIGHT FOR BREAKING
BREAD AT SIXTH AND I BREAKING
BREAD NIGHT OF STORIES BY
CELEBRITY CHEF AND INDUSTRY
INSIDERS BUT HE'LL STOP BY THE
LOFT AND WE'LL CHAT WITH HIM ON
GOOD DAY.
>> WE ARE CELEBRATING THE SWEET
TASTE OF THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
OWNER OF SEMSEM SUITES WILL JOIN
US TO SHOW US THOU CREATE
DELICIOUS DESSERTS JUST IN TIME
FOR CHRISTMAS MORNING.
GOOD DAY D.C. YOU DON'T WANT TO
MISS IT.
>> AND THE WASHINGTON CAPITALS
DOG CAPTAIN GOING TO BE WITH US
HERE IN THE LOFT.
>> AWESOME.
>> THAT'S A MUST SEE.
>> REALLY IS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT TO GET TO WINTER BEFORE
WE GET TO SPRING, GUYS.
GETS HERE IN FOUR DAYS.
>> HOW IS THAT, BET
PRESENTATION.
>> THAT IS AWESOME.
>> OKAY.
ARRIVES AT 11:19.
WINTER SOLSTICE BEGINNING HERE
WE'LL STARTED AING LIGHT EARLY
NEXT WEEK TO EACH AND EVERY DAY.
SO THERE'S SOME GOOD NEWS FOR
YOU.
37 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
LEONARDTOWN 37.
38 UP IN BALTIMORE.
MOST EVERYBODY ABOVE FREEZING
THAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT HERE
BECAUSE WE'VE HAD DRIZZLE AND
LIGHT RAIN OVERNIGHT STILL 32 IN
WINCHESTER AND OUT IN CUMBERLAND
OUT TOWARDS CUMBERLAND WE GOT
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY AS
THERE'S A CONCERN HERE THERE'S
STILL COULD BE FROZEN PATCHES
AND LITLE ICING OUT THERE.
FOR THE REST OF US CLOUDY SKIES
TO START YOUR DAY.
CLOUDY SKIES TO FINISH YOUR DAY
AS WE'LL REMAIN MURRAY AND
OVERCAST AND QUIET CHILLY OUT
THERE TODAY.
DAYTIME HIGHS ONLY IN THE 40S.
SO WE'LL ACTUALLY GET LITTLE
WARMER THAN WHERE WE'RE AT NOW
IT WON'T BE A MIDDLE DAY WITH
ALL THE CLOUD COVER AND ONE MORE
BATCH OF SIGNIFICANT RAIN
SHOWERS KIND OF MID AFTERNOON
WITH A COLD FRONT.
ONCE THAT COLD FRONT GETS EAST
OF US WE'LL START THE PROCESS OF
DRYING THINGS OUT.
SO THIS IS THE LAST DAY.
REAL QUICK NEW YORK GETTING RAIN
AT THIS HOUR UP TOWARDS BOSTON
STILL SNOW.
IF YOU'RE FLYING UP TOWARDS
BOSTON TODAY THAT'S REALLY OUR
BIG TROUBLE SPOT AS FAR AS BIG
CITIES.
AT LAND TO GETTING SOME RAIN AS
WELL THAT SHOULD BE EAST OF
ATLANTA THE NEXT COUPLE OF
HOURS.
ALL RIGHT.
FUTURE CAST FOR US, THERE'S YOUR
RAIN SHOWER ACTIVITY ASSOCIATED
WITH A COLD FRONT AT
2:00 O'CLOCK.
MOST OF IT'S EAST OF US BY FOUR,
FIVE, 6:00 O'CLOCK.
THERE WE GO.
WE'RE STARTING TO GET THE
CLEARING AND THE WINDS WILL PICK
UP AND COLDER AIR WILL START
RUSHING IN I PROMISE TOMORROW
WILL BE A MUCH BRIGHTER DAY.
IT WILL BE CHILLY DAY TOMORROW.
WITH HIGHS ONLY ABOUT
40 DEGREES.
BUT BACK INTO SUNSHINE AND A
NICE QUIET WEATHER PATTERN HERE.
SO TODAY IS THE END OF IT.
CLOUDS AND SHOWERS 50 MANY BACK
INTO SUNSHINE AND A NICE QUIET
WEATHER PATTERN AS WE GET INTO
THE FIRST DAYS OF WINTER.
42 ON SATURDAY.
AND THEN BELIEVE IT OR WE'LL BE
MILD.
REAL QUICK.
WHILE I'VE GOT YOU HERE.
I THINK CHRISTMAS DAY MID 50S
WITH SUNSHINE.
ERIN, YOU APPROVE?
>> MORE THAN OF A POPE, TUCKER
THIS IS MY FAVORITE TIME OF YEAR
I WILL BE IN GOOD MOOD FROM NOW
UNTIL, I DON'T KNOW, NEW YEAR'S
DAY WHEN I'M TIRED BECAUSE HAVE
I TO WORK BUT I WILL SAY
UNFORTUNATELY FOR OUR DRIVERS,
IT'S BEEN A REALLY ROUGH WEEK.
WE HAD WINTRY MIX YESTERDAY.
IT'S TUESDAY, FOG OUT THERE MUCH
WATCH OUT FOR VISIBILITY
PROBLEMS.
LOW BEAMS.
TAKE IT SLOW THIS MORNING.
SLICK SPOTS AS WELL.
BUMPER TO BUMPER BW PARKWAY
SOUTHBOUND PAST BRADDOCK HE HAD.
EXCUSE ME PASSED THE BROCK TH
SO BAD ALL THE ROADS AND DELAYS
ARE MIXING TOGETHER FOR ME.
WE HAVE DELAYS ON THE INNER LOOP
PASSED 210 OUT IN PRINCE
WILLIAM -- PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY.
LOOK AT THAT NOW I'M SPEAKING OF
VIRGINIA AND MARYLAND.
SOMEBODY SEND ME HELP.
WE ALSO HAVE PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE
CRASH WESTBOUND BLOCKING THE
RIGHT LANE ON THE RAMP TO 295
SOUTHBOUND.
50 JAMS 202 TO 295.
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE SO JAMMED UP
AND THEN AS WE MAKE OUR WAY OUT
ON 270 NORTHBOUND THERE'S AN
OVERTURNED VEHICLE CRASH WATCH
OUT FOR SLICK SPOTS AFTER 109.
REALLY SIGNIFICANT DELAYS THERE.
HOP OFF, HOP ON 355 TO GET
AROUND THAT.
SOUTHBOUND SIDE WE'RE STILL I
DON'T HAVE AN HOUR DELAY FROM
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY.
THAT'S WHAT WE GOT NOW.
AT LEAST IT'S BETTER THAN OVER
TWO HOUR DELAY.
BACK TO YOU.
>> OUR LIFE ON LOCATION HOLIDAY
SERIES CONTINUES THIS MORNING
AND TODAY WE'RE IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
WE'RE PAYING A VISIT TO A
MUSICAL CHRISTMAS TREE.
WHAT'S MORE FESTIVE THAN THAT,
RIGHT?  MAUREEN IS CHECKING IT
OUT AT THE RESTON TOWN CENTER.
HELLO, FRIEND.
>> Reporter: HELLO, FRIEND.
CAN YOU HEAR IT?  CAN YOU HEAR
IT?  THIS IS MUSICAL CHRISTMAS
TREE.
RESTON TOWN CENTER IT REALLY
JUST SETS THE MOOD FOR WONDERFUL
WONDERFUL SEASON.
FOLKS ARE JUST STARTING TO STIR
AROUND HERE.
THE LIGHTS ARE SHINING BRIGHTLY.
I WANT TO TELL YOU RESTON TOWN
CENTER HAS TO OFFER.
THERE'S SO MUCH FOR FOR OF YOU
WANTING TO DO LAST MEANT
SHOPPING OR FAMILY MEMBERS IN
TOWN.
THIS IS THE MARKING DIRECTOR FOR
BOSTON PROPERTIES.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING US THIS
MORNING.
>> THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
>> THE MOOD HAS BEEN SET.
WALK ME THROUGH RESTON TOWN
CENTER.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO OFFER THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> MANY GREAT TRADITIONS THAT
DATE BACK 30 YEARS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> WE HAVE OUR NEW CHRISTMAS
TREE.
30 FEET HIGH.
>> OH WOW.
>> ALMOST 20,000 LIGHTS.
>> IT'S A NEW FEATURE THIS YEAR?
>> WELL, WE'VE ALWAYS HAD THE
TREE BUT THIS IS A NEW TREE
WHICH IS INTERACTIVE MUSICAL AND
AS YOU CAN SEE THE LIGHTS LINE
UP WITH THE MUSIC.
>> YEAH.
>> SO IT'S PROGRAMMED ALONG WITH
THE HOLIDAY MUSIC.
700 ORNAMENTS ON THE TREE.
>> IT'S GORGEOUS.
IT'S GORGEOUS.
>> OF COURSE, WE'RE PLAYING IT
EARLY BECAUSE -- IT DOESN'T PLAY
DAY ROUND BUT YOU HAVE MAINLY ON
THE WEEKENDS, RIGHT.
>> WE PLAY IT STARTING AT
6:00 O'CLOCK ON WEEKDAYS EVERY
30 MINUTES ON THE WEEKENDS IT
STARTS AT 5:00.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEN THIS WEEKEND WE HAVE
HORSE DRAWN CARRIAGE RIDES.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> SATURDAY AND WE HAVE MINI
TRAIN RIDES FOR THE FAMILIES ON
SUNDAY.
>> UM-HMM.
>> AND THOSE WE'VE BEEN DOING
FOR YEARS AS WELL.
>> I LOVE JUST THE SCENE.
IT FEELS LIKE YOU'VE GOT A
THOUSAND LIGHTS.
>> YES.
>> HERE ON EVERY TREE, EVERY
POLES, DECORATED JUST REALLY
SETTING THE MOOD.
>> WE REALLY TRY TO MAKE THE
WHOLE TOWN CENTER FESTIVE.
NOT JUST THIS AREA AROUND THE
TREE.
SO OUR RINK IS LIT.
STREETS ARE LIT ALL THE TREES
ARE LIT.
IT'S VERY MAGICAL HERE.
>> HOW MANY SHOPS AND
RESTAURANTS DOES THIS PROPERTY
HAVE?
>> WE HAVE MANY.
WE HAVE OVER 60 SHOPS AND
RESTAURANTS, AND WE HAVE SOME
NEW ONES THAT JUST OPENED, AND
OF ONE HAS GOT SPECIAL HOLIDAY
DEALS.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND MENUS.
REALLY A FUN TIME TO BE AT THE
TOWN CENTER.
>> I DO.ET TO BE OUT HERE DAILYú
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PART OF
THIS WONDERFUL, BEAUTIFUL SCENE
IT FEELS ALMOST LIKE AN OLD TOWN
ROAD THAT YOU CLOSE DOWN AND
LIKE A HALLMARK CHRISTMAS MOVIE
ALMOST.
>> IT REALLY IS.
>> FILMED ON THIS BOULEVARD.
>> I THINK IT'S THE TRADITION.
MEET SO MANY PEOPLE WHO ARE
ADULTS NOW WHO SAID AS A KID I
WOULD COME AND ICE SKATE AT
RESTON TOWN CENTER AND NOW I
BRING MY KIDS TO DO THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST LOVE THERE'S SO MANY
TRADITION.
LAST MONTH WE HAD OUR 29th
ANNUAL HOLIDAY PARADE THE DAY
AFTER THANKSGIVING.
AND THOSE ARE JUST SUCH
WONDERFUL TRADITIONS THAT THE
PEOPLE OF RESTON AND THE
SURROUNDING COMMUNITY REALLY
ENJOY AND LOVE.
>> THE FAMILY FEEL.
I LOVE IT.
SHE MENTIONED ICE SKATING.
RIGHT BEHIND DAVE RIGHT HERE
THAT'S GOING TO BE 9:00 O'CLOCK
HOUR.
WE'RE GOING TO PERHAPS TAKE ICE
SKATING LESSON NOT FOLKS CAN
COME DOWN AND ICE SKATE SOME.
WHAT SAYS CHRISTMAS MORE THAN
ICE RINK AND BEAUTIFULLY IT WILL
TREES AND A BOULEVARD.
A SITING CHRISTMAS TREE.
THAT'S WHAT RESTON TOWN CENTER
HAS TO OFF AND SO MUCH MORE.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE KIDDOS START
GETTING OUT OF SCHOOL THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS COME ON DOWN HERE
WITH THE FAMILY WONDERFUL WHOLE
SOME GOOD TIME, RIGHT.
>> YES.
SO MUCH FUN FOR ALL AGES.
>> INDEED IT IS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> THAT'S IT FOR NOW FOR THIS
HOUR.
NEXT HOUR ICE SKATING.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS TO EVERYONE OUT
THERE.
BACK IN TO YOU.
>> MAUREEN, THANK YOU.
LIKES LIKE SO MUCH FUN.
I'VE BEEN OUT THERE FOR SOME OF
THEIR FESTIVITIES BEFORE.
>> I NEED TO GO.
>> YOU SHOULD GO.
>> RESTON TOWN CENTER MUCH
THANKS MO.
>> WHAT BETTER THAN HEARING A
FEEL GOOD STORY DURING THE
HOLIDAYS.
PARTICULARLY WHEN IT HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH THE POWER
OF GIVING.
OVER THE WEEKEND, A GROUP OF
PEOPLE ATE AN IHOP IN NEW JERSEY
AND EACH CHIPPED IN AN EXTRA 100
BUCKS TO GIVE THE SERVER A
$1,200 TIP.
THE GOOD DEED WAS INSPIRED BY A
POST THAT ONE OF THE GIVERS SAW
ON FACEBOOK.
>> LOVE IT.
PAYING IT FORWARD AND MUCH
APPRECIATED.
>>> 8:52.
UP NEXT, WELL THE WAIT IS OVER
NOW.
AT LEAST FOR KEVIN WHOS ALREADY
HAD HIS FIRST CHANCE TO SEE THE
NEW STAR WARS MOVIE.
HE WAS ON THE RED CARPET FOR THE
BIG PREMIER AND WE'LL CHAT WITH
HIM LIVE NEXT TO SEE WHAT HE
THOUGHT.
♪
8:54.
STILL TRYING TO AWAKE KEN THE
FORCE.
WE'LL GET TO KEVIN IN JUST A
SECOND.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE OVER HERE D
I DO SOMETHING WRONG.
>> WE DID SOMETHING WRONG WITH
THE FORCE.
>> WE WANT TO BE CLOSE TO YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE.
>> THAT'S NOT WEATHER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH, BOY.
LET ME JUST SKIT OUT.
>> LET'S JUST BE SAFE.
BETTING LINES.
THEY'RE LEGAL NOW.
>> THEY ARE.
THAT'S TRUE.
>> GAME IS ON SUNDAY.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WAS LOOKING AT THE WINTER
SOLSTICE.
>> YOU ACTUALLY WERE.
50 LATER TODAY.
RAIN SHOWERS SET TO CONTINUE FOR
MUCH MUCH YOUR DAY.
COLD FRONT WILL KEEP THROUGH
HERE LATER THIS AFTERNOON THAT
WILL CLEAR US OUT WHICH IS GREAT
NEWS BUT IT IS GOING TO BE
OVERCAST AND RATHER RAW DAY OUT
THERE WITH THE SHOWER ACTIVITY.
SUNSHINE RETURNS TOMORROW AND
GETS TO BE BEAUTIFUL AROUND HERE
ALTHOUGH VERY CHILLY FOR THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
BY WEDNESDAY, THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY LOOK AT YOUR DAYTIME
HIGHS.
35 TO 40 WITH OVERNIGHT LOWS
BELOW FREEZING FOR EVERYBODY.
WINTER GETS HERE, GUYS,
SATURDAY.
TIME TO PARTY.
ERIN?
>> PARTY LIKE IT'S WINTERTIME.
THAT MEANS A LOT OF LAYERS.
MAYBE SOME HOT CHOCOLATE.
>> RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
FOR SURE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL MOVE OVER TO LOOK AT YOUR
ROADS.
270 SOUTHBOUND AN HOUR AND SEVEN
MINUTES FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY
WE HAD OVERTURNED VEHICLE CRASH
BLOCKING ALL LANES 270 OUT BY
109.
THAT SINCE HAS STILL BEEN OUT
I'D ADVISE 355.
INNER LOOP DELAYS 95 TO
6620 MILES AN HOUR AVERAGE.
GRAY, GLOOMY FOG CAUSING VISIBLE
PROBLEMS LOW BEAMS TAKE IT SLOW.
48 MINUTE TRIP MANASSAS TO THE
BELTWAY UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE
SEEING A LOT OF BACKED UP ROADS
BECAUSE OF THESE WEATHER
CONDITIONS.
NOT TO BLAME TUCKER BUT YOUR
FAULT.
42 MINUTES EDSALL ROAD TO THE
14th STREET BRIDGE.
THIRD STREET TUNNEL JAMS UP.
METRO BACK TO BEING ON TIME,
GUYS.
>> WE HAVE FOUND THE FORCE.
>> YES, WE HAVE.
>> THAT MEANS KEVIN IS WITH US.
TIME FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA MCC
MCCARTHY.
I HEARD KEVIN HAD ALLOWS SEE
TIME LAST NIGHT, AL.
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT.
>> WOO WHAT A WILD RUMOR MORE.
LET'S CHECK IN WHAT A TERRIBLE
NIGHT YOU MUST HAVE HAD, KEV.
>> IS THERE SOME ALTERNATE
UNIVERSE WE LIVE IN THE WORD
TERRIBLE MEANS AWESOME?  I'M
CURIOUS.
DID THAT CHANGE SOMEHOW.
>> WE'RE TEASING.
WE'RE SUPER JEALOUS I LOVE WHAT
THEY DID WITH HOLLYWOOD
BOULEVARD.
I FOLLOWED YOU ON SOCIAL MEDIA
AND IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD AN
AMAZING EXPERIENCE AND IT SOUNDS
LIKE AT LEAST ON FIRST
IMPRESSION THE FILM DID NOT
DISAPPOINT.
>> NO, THE MOVIE HERE'S THE
THING WE'LL DIVE INTO A FULL
REVIEW.
I LOVE I'VE BEEN STANDING ON
THIS CORNER FOR THE PAST 10
MINUTES IT'S BEEN COMPLETELY
SILENT AND ALL THE TRUCKS ARE
DECDECIDING TO GO BY RIGHT NOW S
I'M DOING MY LIVE SHOT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR DOING
THAT.
>> OF COURSE.
>> THE MOVIE ITSELF WAS AMAZING
I CANNOT WAIT TO GET NO A FULL
REVIEW OF IT.
WE'LL GIVE OUR FULL REVIEW AND
STAR RATING LATER ON IN THIS
WEEK BUT THE FILM DID NOT
DISAPPOINT.
FOR ME AS FORCE AWAKENS FAN AN
FAN OF THIS TRILOGY I THINK JJ
ABRAMS DONE SOMETHING VERY
SPECIAL HERE AND KIND OF REALLY
JUGGLING 42 YEARS OF STORY
TELLING AND BRINGING THAT TO AN
END OF THE SKY WALKER GAG AND
OBVIOUSLY THAT'S THE MOVIE RISE
OF SKY WALKER I'LL GET INTO NO
ALL THAT ONCE I CAN WITH MY FULL
REVIEW BUT IT WAS A CRAZY
EXPERIENCE.
THIS IS A WILD PREMIER TO BE AT
ONE OF THE COOL THINGS ABOUT
GOING TO A PREMIER LIKE THIS,
AND I'M -- I'VE NEVER BEEN TO AN
EPISODE OF A STAR WARS PREMIER.
I'VE BEEN TO A SOLO PREMIER
WHICH IS A SPIN OFF.
I'VE BEEN TO THE AVENGERS
PREMIERES VERY LUCKY TO DO THAT.
BUT GOING INTO AN EPISODE
PREMIER IT BRINGS OUT PEOPLE WHO
AREN'T EVEN INVOLVED IN THESE
MOVIES.
STEVEN SPIELBERG WAS HERE LAST
NIGHT.
I WAS JUST RANDOMLY WALKING BY
SLASH AT ONE POINT, STEVE.
I WAS THINKING OF YOU I -- I'VE
NEVER SEEN SCENE SLASH IN
PERSON.
RANDOMLY WALKING BY HIM.
MARK HAMILL OBVIOUSLY WAS THERE.
IT WAS A HUGE, HUGE NIGHT.
THAT'S ACTUALLY WHERE EVERYTHING
HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
SO THERE WERE THREE THEATERS
PLAYING THE FILM.
DOLBY THEATER WHICH IS WHERE THE
OCEAN CARS TAKE PLACE.
YOU HAVE THE TCL CHINESE THEATER
AS LOT OF MOVIE PREMIERES TAKE
PLACE AND YOU HAVE THE HE WILL
CAPTAIN DOWN THERE A LOT OF FILM
PREMIERES TAKE PLACE AS WELL FOR
DISNEY.
BUT THAT LITTLE TENT RIGHT THERE
WAS WHERE ALL THE RED CARPET
ACTION WANT ALL THE ACTORS AND
CELEBRITIES.
IT WAS INSANE ARSON FORD WALKED
RIGHT BY ME AT ONE POINT.
I'M STILL COMING DOWN FROM THE
PREMIER.
I JUST WENT TO BED ABOUT FOUR
HOURS AGO.
I MEAN THIS HAS BEEN AMAZING
EVENT BUT HERE'S THE THING.
MY -- THIS REVIEW I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET INTO THIS WHEN WE CAN
ACTUAL DOLLAR THE FULL REVIEW ON
THE AIR.
THIS IS A FILM THAT I JUST
REALLY REALLY WANTED TO --
WANTED TO BE GREAT.
I REALLY WANT THE IT TO BE
GREAT.
I DID NOT LOVE THE LAST JEDI.
SO I WANTED TO GIVE ME
PERSPECTIVE I LOVE THE FORCE A
QUICKENS.
DID NOT LIKE THE LAST JEDI THIS
FILM TO ME DELIVERED.
I CANNOT WAIT TO GET INTO THE
FULL SCOPE OF THAT REVIEW LATER
ON THIS WEEK.
I LOVE YOU GUYS AND MISS YOU
GUYS IN STUDIO, AND THIS IS
CRAZY BEING ON HOLLYWOOD
BOULEVARD HERE IN LA.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME ON AS
ALWAYS.
>> YOUR PICTURES WITH MARK
HAMILL AND CHEWY ARE GREAT
KNOWING THAT YOU SAW SLASH I'M
EVEN MORE JEALOUS NOW.
>> DUDE, IT WAS SO RANDOM.
YOU WALK BY PEOPLE SO
NONCHALANTLY AS IF IT'S JUST
NORMAL.
I CAN'T -- I CAN'T DO THAT AS A
FAN.
I'M LIKE HOW AM I WALKING BY
GUNS AND ROSES GUITAR PLAYER
RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS WEIRD TO ME.
SO STRANGE.
>> SAFE SOME OF THE STORIES FOR
GOOD DAY.
WE GOT TO GO.
WE'LL PHLEGM IT RIGHT ON TO THE
NEXT SHOW.
>> THE NEWS IS NON-STOP.
GOOD DAY D.C. AT 9:00 A.M.
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
♪