BREAKING HER SILENCE ON THE
SUDDEN DEATH OF HER HUSBAND
AND DAUGHTER.
AND MORE TRIBUTES FROM THE
SPORTS WORLD.
HOW THE CAPITALS HONORED
NUMBER 24 ON THE ICE.
>>> THE LAST AMERICAN
STANDING.
A SHOCKER AT THE AUSTRALIAN
OPEN OVERNIGHT.
ALSO AHEAD, SUPER BOWL FUN.
WHAT OUR ANGIE GOFF IS UP TO
TODAY.
PLUS, THE YACHTS DOCKED IN
MIAMI AHEAD OF THE BIG GAME.
AND ARE YOU GOING TO WORK ON
MONDAY?  FOX5 MORNING AT 7:00
A.M. STARTS NOW.
>> ♪
>> THURSDAY MORNING, THANKS
FOR BEING WITH US THIS
MORNING.
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>> I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR AND IF
YOU'RE JUST WAKING UP THIS
MORNING, HOW ABOUT A BEAUTIFUL
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE ON THIS
CHILLY JANUARY MORNING?  IT'S
JANUARY 30TH.
>> CHILLY BUT BRIGHT.
WELL, HELLO THERE.
THAT WILL WAKE YOU UP.
QUICK CHECK ON WEATHER AND
TRAFFIC.
WE'LL START THINGS OFF WITH
TUCKER.
>> LOVE THAT SUNRISE.
BEAUTIFUL.
CHILLY OUT THERE GUYS.
TEMPERATURES OVERNIGHT FALLING
BACK INTO THE 20'S AND LOW
30'S AND AFTER A COLD START, A
CHILLY AFTERNOON.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO IMPRESS
YOU.
MAYBE THAT WILL.
THERE YOU GO SOME TEMPERATURES
YOU CAN SEE THEM.
TEENS AND 20'S OUT THRE.
ALL THE DETAILS ON THE
FORECAST.
A LOOK AT THE WEEKEND COMING
UP.
STACEY.
>> HEADS UP ON NEW YORK AVENUE
INBOUND.
POLICE ACTIVITY BLOCKING THE
RIGHT LANE AT BLADENSBURG
ROAD.
ADVISING YOU TO USE CAUTION IN
THE AREA.
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT AND
OF COURSE GIVE YOU A COMPLETE
LOOK AT THE DMV COMING UP.
>> DIVE RIGHT INTO OUR TOP
STORIES THIS THURSDAY.
THERE'S A BATTLE OVER TRAFFIC
ENFORCEMENT IN FAIRFAX COUNTY.
NOW, CRITICS BELIEVE THAT
SPEEDERS ARE TAKING OVER JEFF
TODD WAY.
JEFF TODD WAY IS A POPULAR CUT
THROUGH NEAR FORT BELVOIR.
>> THE COUNTY AND THE ARMY ARE
OVER ODDS AT WHO SHOULD PATROL
THE ROAD.
>> Reporter: FAIRFAX COUNTY
WOULD LIKE THEIR POLICE
JURISDICTION BASICALLY OVER
THIS ROADWAY.
JEFF TODD WAY HERE AND YOU CAN
TAKE A LOOK, NOT MUCH IN THE
WAY OF STREET LIGHTS.
IT'S A 40 MILES AN HOUR ZONE,
ROUGHLY FOUR AND A HALF MILES
OF OPEN ROAD WAY HERE AND WE
CAN SHOW YOU A MAP THAT SHOWS
JEFF TODD WAY GOING FROM THE
SOUTHEAST TO THE NORTHWEST
BETWEEN ROUTE 1 AND TELEGRAPH
ROAD HERE NEAR FORT BELVOIR.
THIS IS A ROADWAY THAT OPENED
BACK IN 2014 TO HELP EASE
TRAFFIC IN THIS AREA.
OTHER CUT THROUGHS AT FORT
BELVOIR WERE CLOSED AFTER 9/11
AND THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN
THIS AREA WHO TAKE THIS
ROADWAY AND YOU SEE IT'S VERY
DARK BECAUSE OF NO STREET
LIGHTS HERE, PEOPLE SPEED
CONSTANTLY.
AGAIN, IT'S A 40 MILES AN HOUR
ZONE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF ACCIDENTS
HERE.
AND COUNTY OFFICIALS SAY THEY
WANT THE ARMY CORPS OF
ENGINEERS TO HAND OVER
JURISDICTION OF THIS ROAD TO
FAIRFAX COUNTY.
HERE NOW VIA SKYPE IS DAN
STORR WHO IS THE FAIRFAX
COUNTY SUPERVISOR FROM THE
DISTRICT.
>> AT THIS POINT WE'RE JUST
INCREDIBLY FRUSTRATED THAT
SOMETHING THIS SIMPLE, FRANKLY
IT IS THIS SIMPLE COULD TAKE
THIS LONG.
IT'S NOT JUST TRAFFIC.
THERE'S OTHER ENFORCEMENT
ISSUES THAT HAPPEN ALONG A
ROAD LIKE THIS THAT THE POLICE
NEED TO BE ABLE TO -- TO
MONITOR AND INTERVENE.
>> Reporter: NOW, MR. STORK
SAYS HE'S WRITTEN A LETTER TO
THE ARMY SAYING THEY WANT THIS
HANDOVER TO HAPPEN
IMMEDIATELY.
WE'LL SEE, GUYS.
WE'VE REACHED OUT TO THE ARMY
VIA FORT BELVOIR AND ARE
WAITING TO HEAR BACK.
>> ALL RIGHT, BOB, WE'LL WAIT
FOR THAT UPDATE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> MEANTIME POLICE IN
ARLINGTON COUNTY ARE
INVESTIGATING AFTER A SWASTIKA
DRAWING WAS FOUND AT A MIDDLE
SCHOOL.
A STUDENT AT THOMAS JEFFERSON
MIDDLE SCHOOL RECEIVED A
DRAWING ON A PIECE OF PAPER ON
TUESDAY.
STAFF NOTICE NOTIFIED THE
EXILE RESOURCE OFFICER.
THE PRINCIPAL SENT A LETTER
HOME TO PARENTS SAYING THE
ADMINISTRATION MET WITH THE
STUDENT INVOLVED AND THAT
INTOLERANCE IS NOT ACCEPTED AT
THE SCHOOL.
>> SOME NEW DETAILS COMING OUT
IN PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
AFTER THE POLICE OFFICER
CHARGED -- HAS BEEN CHARGED
WITH THE SHOOTING DEATH OF A
MAN IN TEMPLE HILLS.
THAT OFFICER IS GOING STAY
BEHIND BARS.
CORPORAL MICHAEL OWEN IS HELD
WITHOUT BOND ACCUSED OF
SHOOTING AND KILLING WILLIAM
GREEN WHILE GREEN WAS
HANDCUFFED INSIDE OF THE
POLICE CRUISER ON MONDAY
NIGHT.
THAT'S CORPORAL OWEN THAT.
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME OWEN
HAS BEEN INVOLVED IN A DEADLY
SHOOTING.
IN 2011 HE KILLED -- SHOT AND
KILLED RODNEY EDWARDS BUT WAS
NOT CHARGED.
PROSECUTORS NOW IN PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY SAY THEY'RE
GOING TO REVIEW THAT CASE TO
SEE IF ANY CHARGES MAY BE
WARRANTED.
IN THE MEANTIME MANY ARE
QUESTIONING WHY OWEN WAS NOT
WEARING A BODY CAMERA DURING
>> WE HAVE PARTIAL DEPLOYMENT
OF BODY CAMERAS ACROSS OUR
DEPARTMENT.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN FULLY IN
SUPPORT OF DEPLOYING
ADDITIONAL BODY CAMERAS&
THROUGHOUT OUR DEPARTMENT.
>> THAT'S THE CHIEF STALKING TAG
ABOUT IT.
HE'S IN SUPPORT OF IT.
ACCORDING TO POLICE
ADMINISTRATORS ONLY 80 OUT OF
1500 ARE EQUIPPED WITH BODY
CAMERAS DESPITE THE SUPPORT TO
ADD MORE THE COUNTY MAINLY
CITES THE BUDGET AS THE REASON
ROLLING OUT THE CAMERAS FOR
OFFICERS IS SLOWER THAN OTHER
AREA AGENCIES.
>> A SUSPICIOUS DEATH
INVESTIGATION IN UNDER WAY IN
LANHAM, MARYLAND, AFTER A
WOMAN'S BODY WAS FOUND INSIDE
OF A HOUSE.
SKYFOX OVER THE SCENE ON
LAMONT DRIVE.
POLICE WERE WORKING A MISSING
PERSONS CASE IN THAT
NEIGHBORHOOD YESTERDAY MORNING
WHEN THEY MADE THIS DISCOVERY.
NO WORD YET IF THE BODY IS
RELATED TO THAT CASE.
>> ♪
>> ALL RIGHT, COMING UP ON
7:05 RIGHT NOW.
GOOD MORNING, TUCKER BARNES.
>> GOOD MORNING.
COLD START TO THE DAY.
COLDEST DAY OF THE WEEK HERE,
SO OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE
TEENS AND 20'S.
>> ONLY GET WARMER TO HERE.
>> COUNTDOWN TO SPRING.
>> ARE WE COUNTING.
>> YEAH WE'RE DONE.
>> I THINK WE HAVE A MILLION
MORE THAN 30.
METEOROLOGICAL SPRING STARTS
MARCH 1ST.
>> DOES NOT FEEL LIKE IT EARLY
THIS MORNING.
COLDEST DAY OF THE WEEK WITH
HIGH PRESSURE BUILDING IN TO
THE NORTH.
AND CLEAR SKIES OVERNIGHT WE
HAD A CHANCE TO COOL IT DOWN.
EVERYBODY BELOW FREEZING EARLY
THIS MORNING.
HERE ARE YOUR AIRPORT TEMPS.
I JUST WANT TO MENTION THESE
ARE SOME OF YOUR WARMER
NUMBERS SO THERE ARE PLENTY OF
LOW 20'S OUT THERE.
REAGAN NATIONAL 31.
29 THIS MORNING IN BALTIMORE
AT BWI MARSHALL.
SATELLITE AND RADAR NICE AND
QUIET.
ALTHOUGH WE'RE GETTING SOME
CLOUDS MAKING FOR A BEAUTIFUL
SUNRISE UP IN ABOUT 15 MINUTES
AND A LITTLE STORM SYSTEM
BEING PUSHED OFF TO OUR SOUTH
AND EAST.
NO RAIN FOR US BUT WE'LL GET
SOME OF THAT CLOUD COVER
TODAY.
YESTERDAY AFTERNOON TURNED
INTO A BEAUTIFUL AFTERNOON
WITH THE SUNSHINE.
TODAY A FEW MORE CLOUDS THAN
YESTERDAY.
AND COOL AND AGAIN, FROM HERE
WE'RE GOING TO WARM THE
TEMPERATURES UP STARTING
TOMORROW BACK NEAR 50 AND THEN
50'S THIS WEEKEND AND THEN BY
EARLY NEXT WEEK, SOME 60'S.
I'LL HAVE DETAILS COMING UP.
LET'S DO SOME ROADS AND FIND
OUT IF YOU'RE GOING TO GET TO
WORK ON TIME WITH STACEY.
>> THANKS, TUCKER.
I AM TRYING TO GET YOU THERE.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'VE GOT SOME
INNER LOOP DELAYS.
IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT 15
MINUTES JUST TO GET FROM
BRANCH AVENUE TO THE WILSON
BRIDGE.
SO, IT'S A SLOW RIDE THERE.
MOVING OVER TO NEW YORK
AVENUE, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
THIS EARLIER.
NEW YORK AVENUE THE RIGHT LANE
IS SHUT DOWN BECAUSE OF POLICE
ACTIVITY.
THIS IS RIGHT AT BLADENSBURG
ROAD.
USE CAUTION IF YOU ARE IN THAT
AREA.
LOOKING AT 395 NORTHBOUND,
SMOOTH SAILING.
THERE'S SOME GOOD NEWS.
SMOOTH SAILING FROM EDSALL
ROAD TO THE 14TH STREET
BRIDGE.
AS WE LOOK AT 95 NORTHBOUND, A
LOT OF PEOPLE ON THE ROAD AND
YOU GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS OF
TRAFFIC AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY.
66 WESTBOUND, HOWEVER, LOOKS
REALLY GOOD AS YOU MAKE YOUR
WAY FROM MANASSAS AND FINALLY,
270 SOUTHBOUND, IT WILL TAKE
YOU ABOUT AN HOUR TO MAKE IT
FROM FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> STACEY, THANKS VERY MUCH.
IT'S 7:MINUTES PAST THE HOUR.
ON THE ICE LAST NIGHT, THE
CAPITALS HONORED KOBE BRYANT
HIS DAUGHTER AND THE OTHER
SEVEN VICTIMS OF SUNDAY'S
HELICOPTER CRASH WITH A MOMENT
OF SILENCE BEFORE THE CAPS
GAME.
ALEX OVECHKIN WEARING NUMBER
24.
OVIE SWAPPED OUT HIS NUMBER
EIGHT JERSEY FOR NUMBER 24.
BOTH THE NUMBERS THAT KOBE
WORE FOR THE LAKERS.
SPECIAL NUMBER 24 JERSEY WILL
NOW BE AUCTIONED OFF.
PROCEEDS WILL GO TO THE KOBE
AND VANESSA BRYANT FAMILY
FOUNDATION.
UNFORTUNATELY ON THE ICE CAPS
LOST THE GAME BUT THEY WERE
WINNING THE REST OF THE
EVENING.
>>> IN LOS ANGELES THE LAKERS
HELD THEIR FIRST PRACTICE
FOLLOWING KOBE'S DEATH.
KOBE'S NUMBER EIGHT AND 24
ILLUMINATED ON THE WALL OF THE
GYM DURING THE PRACTICE
SESSION S THE LAKERS WILL HOST
THE TRAILBLAZERS TOMORROW.
THAT WILL BE THE FIRST GAME AT
STAPLES CENTER SINCE THE
TRAGEDY.
OF COURSE THE GAME AGAINST THE
CLIPPERS THAT WAS SCHEDULED
EARLIER THIS WEEK WAS
POSTPONED.
>>> ALSO WE'RE HEARING FROM
VANESSA BRYANT FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
SHE SPOKE OUT LAST NIGHT VIA
INSTAGRAM SHARING A FAMILY
PHOTO WITH AN EMOTIONAL
MESSAGE READING IN PART "I'M
NOT SURE WHAT OUR LIVES HOLD
BEYOND TODAY AND IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE TO IMAGINE LIFE
WITHOUT THEM.
BUT WE WAKE UP EACH DAY TRYING
TO KEEP PUSHING BECAUSE KOBE
AND OUR BABY GIRL GIGI ARE
SHINING ON US TO LIGHT THE WAY."
SHE THANKED THE FANS FOR
SHARING THEIR GRIEF AND
SUPPORT AND ANNOUNCED A NEW
FUND TO HELP THE OTHER
FAMILIES IMPACTED BY THE
CRASH.
AS FAR AS WHERE THE
INVESTIGATION STANDS, THE
WRECKAGE FROM THE HELICOPTER
IS MOSTLY CLEARED NOW FROM THE
CRASH SITE LOADED INTO A BAGS
TAKEN TO ARIZONA WHERE IT WILL
NOW BE STUDIED AT AN AIRCRAFT
YARD IN PHOENIX WHERE THEY
HOPE TO GET ENOUGH CLUES TO
FIGURE OUT EXACTLY WHAT CAUSED
THAT FATAL CRASH.
>> 7:08.
TODAY ON CAPITOL HILL SENATORS
WILL GET ONE LAST SHOT AT
QUESTIONING HOUSE MANAGERS AND
THE DEFENSE TEAM IN THE
PRESIDENT'S IMPEACHMENT TRIAL.
THEN TOMORROW SENATORS ARE SET
TO VOTE ON WHETHER TO BRING IN
WITNESSES.
DEMOCRATS WANT THEM ESPECIALLY
FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER JOHN BOLTON WHO
REPORTEDLY HAS DETAILS IN AN
UPCOMING BOOK LINKING
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO THE UKRAINE
AID THAT WAS HELD AND THIS
MORNING WE'VE LEARNED THE
WHITE HOUSE HAS ISSUED A
FORMAL THREAT TO BOLTON TO
KEEP HIM FROM PUBLISHING HIS
BOOK.
THE PRESIDENT ARGUING THAT THE
BOOK IS NOT TRUE AND ALSO THAT
IT'S FULL OF CLASSIFIED
SECURITY SECRETS.
LET'S SWITCH GEARS NOW TO THE
PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
NEW THIS MORNING, WE'VE
LEARNED THAT D.C. MAYOR MURIEL
BOWSER WILL ENDORSE MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG FOR THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINATION.
BLOOMBERG WILL BE IN THE
DISTRICT TODAY TO DELIVER A
SPEECH ON AFFORDABLE HOUSING.
MAYOR BOWSER WILL ALSO BE
THERE AND IS EXPECTED TO MAKE
HER ANNOUNCEMENT AT THAT TIME.
>>> AND FORMER VICE PRESIDENT
JOE BIDEN ALREADY KNOWS WHO HE
WANTS AS A RUNNING MATE IF HE
WINS THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL NOMINATION AND
THERE'S YOUR CLUE.
FORMER FIRST LADY MICHELLE
OBAMA.
AND HE MADE THE STATEMENT AT A
CAMPAIGN STOP IN IOWA WHERE
THE CANDIDATES ARE GEARING UP
FOR THE CAUCUSES IN IOWA
MONDAY.
>> THE VIRGINIA SENATE
APPROVED LEGISLATION THAT
WOULD ROLL BACK RESTRICTIONS
ON ABORTION.
THE NEW DEMOCRATIC MAJORITY
WANTS TO GET RID OF
REQUIREMENTS LIKE A 24 HOUR
WAITING PERIOD BEFORE AN
ABORTION AN REQUIREMENT THAT
WOMEN SEEKING AN ABORTION
UNDERGO AN ULTRASOUND AND
COUNSELING.
THE HOUSE PASSED A SIMILAR
MEASURE.
EACH CHAMBER NEEDS TO PASS THE
OTHER'S VERSION.
>>> STILL AHEAD, WHY THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IS
GROUNDING HUNDREDS OF DRONES.
>> PLUS, CORONAVIRUS CONCERNS.
MELANIE ALNWICK IS ON THE
CAMPUS OF A LOCAL UNIVERSITY
WITH THAT.
MEL.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
YEAH, COLLEGES AND
UNIVERSITIES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY HAVING AN IMPACT NOW
ON THEIR STUDY ABROAD PROGRAMS
INCLUDING MANY HERE IN THE
D.C. AREA.
WE'LL ALSO TALK ABOUT AS
THEY'RE BRINGING THOSE
STUDENTS HOME WHAT THEY'RE
DOING TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE NOT
BRINGING THE VIRUS WITH THEM.
M.
So I was at Marshalls
just browsing,
and I see this jean jacket.
I put it on,
popped the collar
and looked at the brand.
And when I saw the price tag
I was like,
oh yeah,
this is a keeper.
It goes with everything.
If I'm wearing yoga pants,
I wear my jean jacket.
If I'm going out,
I can go on a dinner dates
with my husband,
like to the movies,
and it just works.
It's my, it's my go to jacket.
Brands that wow.
Prices
that thrill.
Marshalls. Your Surprise
Is Waiting!
>> SO ANGIE GOFF HAS BEEN BUSY
ALL WEEK DOWN IN MIAMI TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF ALL THE SUPER
BOWL FESTIVITIES.
SHE TOURED LITTLE HAVANA
STOPPED BY DOMINOS PARK A
CIGAR SHOP AND GOT A SALSA
LESSON.
COMING UP ON GOOD DAY ANGIE
WILL JOIN US LIVE TELL US WHAT
SHE'S UP TO TODAY AND LATER
SHE'S GOING TO CHAT WITH J-LO
AND SHAKIRA ABOUT THE HALFTIME
SHOW.
REMEMBER FOX5 THE ONLY PLACE
TO WATCH YOUR SUPER BOWL.
ALL YOUR COVERAGE RIGHT HERE
ON FOX.
>>> CHECK OUT SOME OF THE
YACHTS THAT ARRIVED IN MIAMI.
THAT THE LARGER OF THE LARGE
YACHTS.
THE BIG GIANT ONE ON THE END.
THAT'S JERRY JONES' YACHT.
THE COWBOYS OWNER.
>> THAT LOOKS LIKE A CRUISE
LINER.
>> FUN FACT.
LONGER THAN A FOOTBALL FIELD.
>> MY GOODNESS.
>> 357 FEET.
VALUED AT $250 MILLION.
THE MEGA YACHT WAS ALMOST TOO
LONG FOR THE DOCK.
NOT ONE BUT TWO HELI PADS AND
ROOM FOR A 30 PERSON CREW.
CAN'T IMAGINE HOW MUCH THE
FUEL COSTS WOULD BE.
>> THAT IS NOT A CONCERN.
>> THAT'S INSANE.
>> IF YOU HAVE TO ASK --
>> YEAH, DON'T EVEN TRY TO
AFFORD IT.
NICE.
>> I'M TOTALLY NOT THE GUY TO
BRAG BUT I HAVE A KAYAK.
>> IT IS NICE THOUGH.
>> YOU SHOULD PULL IT UP NEXT
TO JERRY JONES YACHT.
>> I THINK I SAW THAT LITTLE
DINGY LAST TIME I WAS IN
ANNAPOLIS.
>> IT'S A TWO PERSON KAYAK.
IT'S ON THE NICER SIDE OF
THINGS.
>> OKAY.
>> HE'S OFFERING RIDES, AL.
YOU SHOULD TAKE HIM UP ON IT.
>> I WILL.
>> I'LL TAKE YOU OUT ANY TIME.
JERRY JONES WOULD GIVE YOU A
MUCH BETTER ADVENTURE.
NORTH AND WEST WE GOT A 23 IN
GERMANTOWN.
YOU GET THE SENSE HERE --
WELL, YOU DON'T GET THE SENSE
BUT I'M GOING TO LET YOU KNOW
IT'S COLD THIS MORNING AS THIS
HAS BEEN OUR COLDEST START
THIS WEEK.
COLONIAL BEACH 30 DEGREES AND
A GOOD 10 TO 15 DEGREES COOLER
THAN WHERE WE WERE AT 24 HOURS
AGO.
SO, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT, LOOKING
AT SOME TEENS BREAKING OUT.
MARTINSBURG 19 DEGREES.
CHILLY START TO THE DAY AN
COOL AFTERNOON EXPECTED.
MID 40'S AROUND HERE LATER
THIS AFTERNOON.
AND WE'LL GET A FEW MORE
CLOUDS THAN YESTERDAY.
WE'VE GOT THIS LITTLE PIECE OF
ENERGY HERE GETTING PUSHED OFF
THE NORTH CAROLINA COAST AND
SOME CLOUDS ACROSS OUR REGION
TO START THE DAY SO, YEAH, IT
WON'T BE A RAINY AFTERNOON BUT
WE WILL SEE MORE CLOUDS THAN
YESTERDAY AS AGAIN IT WILL BE
COOL HERE WITH FILTERED
SUNSHINE ACROSS THE REGION.
WEEKEND SET UP.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS
SYSTEM THE LAST COUPLE DAYS.
IT WILL BRING US LIGHT RAIN
SHOWERS I THINK OR AT LEAST
PARTS OF THE AREA LIGHT RAIN
SHOWERS SATURDAY MORNING.
BEST CHANCES ARE GOING TO BE
KIND OF SOUTH AND EAST OF
TOWN, SOUTH AND EAST OF 95
DOWN ACROSS THE LOWER EASTERN
SHORE, SOUTHERN MARYLAND,
CENTRAL VIRGINIA.
YOU GUYS HAVE THE BEST CHANCES
FOR SOME RAIN SHOWERS.
THAT WILL PUSH OFF TO THE
NORTH AND EAST DURING THE DAY
ON SATURDAY AND WE SHOULD GET
SOME CLEARING LATE IN THE DAY
ON SATURDAY WITH HIGHS IN THE
40'S AND THEN A NICE DAY FOR
SUNDAY.
PARTIAL SUNSHINE, HIGH
PRESSURE TO OUR SOUTH, LOW
50'S AND I'M GOING TO GET OUT
OF YOUR WAY AND LET YOU SEE
THE SEVEN-DAY FORECAST.
LET ME GET OUT OF YOUR WAY.
LOOK AT EARLY NEXT WEEK.
MONDAY, TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY,
THE 60'S ARE BACK.
SPRINGTIME NOT OFFICIAL BUT
IT'S GOING TO FEEL LIKE IT
AROUND HERE WITH THOSE
TEMPERATURES WELL ABOVE
NORMAL.
GOOD 15 TO 20 DEGREES ABOVE
NORMAL EARLY NEXT WEEK.
WINTER, WHERE A HAVE YOU GONE?
>> WHO CARES, TUCKER.
>> STACEY I KNEW YOU WERE
GOING TO HAVE THAT REPLY.
>> RIGHT, ALLISON.
DOESN'T MATTER.
WE'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT
WINTER.
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT NEXT
WEEK.
ALL RIGHT, 295 SOUTHBOUND HAS
AN INCIDENT THIS MORNING.
WE HAVE A CRASH REPORTED AT
BENNING ROAD.
SOMETHING TO LOOK OUT FOR.
OF COURSE WE WILL KEEP YOU UP
TO DATE AS MORE INFORMATION
COMES IN.
MOVING OVER TO 395 NORTHBOUND,
AS YOU CAN SEE, A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE ON THE ROAD BUT
IT'S SMOOTH SAILING AS YOU
MAKE YOUR WAY FROM EDSALL ROAD
TO THE 14TH STREET BRIDGE.
95 NORTHBOUND LOOKS PRETTY
GOOD.
I MEAN, IT'S A SLOW AND STEADY
RIDE.
YOU GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS OF
TRAFFIC.
EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD EXPECT
FOR 7:17 ON A THURSDAY
MORNING.
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY FROM DALE
CITY TO THE BELTWAY.
ALSO, USUAL POCKETS OF TRAFFIC
ON 66 WESTBOUND MANASSAS TO
THE BELTWAY.
AND FINALLY, IT WILL TAKE YOU
ABOUT AN HOUR TO MAKE IT FROM
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY IF
YOU'RE HEADED ON 270
SOUTHBOUND.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
BACK TO YOU, STEVE.
>> HUNDREDS OF DRONES USED BY
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT HAVE
BEEN GROUND EED DUE TOO CONCERN
OVER CYBER SECURITY.
THESE ARE NONEMERGENCY DRONES.
THEY GROUNDED CHINESE DRONES
IN ITS FLEET IN OCTOBER.
THEY'RE USED IN A VARIETY OF
GOVERNMENT MISSION S INCLUDING
SURVEILLANCE AND RESCUE
OPERATIONS.
>> HAPPENING IN THE DISTRICT
THE LATE LEGENDARY
AFRICAN-AMERICAN JOURNALIST
GWEN IFILL WILL BE
COMMEMORATED BY THE UNITED
STATES POSTAL SERVICE WITH
THIS NEW STAMP.
IT'S THE 43RD STAMP IN THE
BLACK HERITAGE SERIES.
D.C.'S MAYOR MURIEL BOWSER
WILL ALSO BE ON HAND FOR THE
DEDICATION CEREMONY AND WILL
HONOR IFILL'S LEGACY BY
DECLARING TODAY GWEN IFILL DAY
IN THE DISTRICT.
>> THERE ARE GROWING FEARS
HERE IN THE U.S. AND AROUND
THE WORLD AS THE CORONAVIRUS
SHOWS NO SIGN OF SLOWING DOWN.
SEVERAL UNIVERSITIES INCLUDING
SOME IN OUR AREA HAVE ASKED
STUDENTS STUDYING ABROAD IN
CHINA TO COME BACK HOME.
FOX5's MELANIE ALNWICK JOINS
US LIVE FROM CAMPUS WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, MEL.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
AND YOU KNOW, WHETHER THESE
FEARS ARE OVERBLOWN OR NOT,
THEY'RE STILL FEELING THEM.
SOME STUDENTS HERE AT CAMPUSES
WE TALKED TO CONCERNED THAT IF
THOSE STUDENTS ARE COMING HOME
FROM INFECTED AREAS, THAT THEY
COULD BRING SOMETHING WITH
THEM.
UNIVERSITIES AND COLLEGES
AROUND THE COUNTRY ARE DEALING
WITH KIND OF -- THIS KIND OF A
SITUATION AS THEY HAVE VERY
LARGE INTERNATIONAL STUDY
PROGRAMS AND EXCHANGE
PROGRAMS.
HERE AT UNIVERSITY OF
MARYLAND, THEY HAVE CANCELED
THE EUROPEAN -- NOT EUROPEAN,
THE EDUCATION ABROAD PROGRAM
THAT THEY HAVE IN CHINA FOR
THIS COMING SPRING SEMESTER
AND OTHER COLLEGES ARE
BRINGING THEIR STUDENTS BACK.
ANOTHER THING THAT UNIVERSITY
OF MARYLAND IS DOING THEY ARE
STAFFING UP THE STUDENT HEALTH
CENTER BECAUSE PEOPLE WILL GO
IN WITH EXTRA CONCERNS OR
CALLING A LOT.
THEY'RE REMINDING THE
COMMUNITY TO PRACTICE GOOD
HYGIENE AND HIGH TOUCH
SURFACES AROUND THE CAMPUS ARE
GETTING ADDITIONAL
DISINFECTION AND CLEANING.
MARYLAND AND GEORGETOWN
UNIVERSITY HAVE ISSUED
MORATORIUMS ON ALL TRAVEL TO
CHINA.
AMERICAN UNIVERSITY DOING THE
SAME AS WELL AS WORKING TO
BRING NINE STUDENTS HOME WHO
ARE CURRENTLY STUDYING IN
BEIJING.
GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY
OFFICIALS TELL US THEY'RE IN
CONTACT WITH THEIR STUDENTS IN
CHINA AND MONITORING THEIR
DEPARTURES AND RETURN HOME.
BUT AS YOU'VE SEEN LIKE THIS
RAPID SPREAD OF THE VIRUS
MEANS RAPID SPREAD OF FEAR.
THERE ARE NO CONFIRMED CASES
OF NOVEL CORONAVIRUS IN
MARYLAND, VIRGINIA OR THE
DISTRICT THOUGH TEST RESULTS
ARE PENDING FOR A FEW PEOPLE
SICK WITH RESPIRATORY
ILLNESSES INCLUDING THAT ONE
PERSON AT GEORGE MASON
UNIVERSITY THAT WE TOLD YOU
ABOUT ON MONDAY.
THOSE TEST RESULTS STILL HAVE
NOT BEEN RETURNED YET SO WE
CAN'T TELL WAS THAT STATUS IS.
I DID JUST CHECK THIS MORNING
TO THE VIRGINIA DEPARTMENT OF
HEALTH WEB SITE TO SEE IF THEY
HAD AN UPDATE YET AND THERE IS
NOT ONE.
NOW, ALL THE UNIVERSITIES
CONTACTED DID TELL US THAT
THEY HAVE SYSTEMS IN PLACE FOR
MONITORING STUDENTS AND
STAFFER WHO COME HOME, MAKE
SURE THAT THEY REMAIN HEALTHY
AND HAVE PROCEDURE IN PLACE
FOR WHAT TO DO IF THOSE
STUDENTS START TO FEEL ILL.
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND SETTING
UP A DEDICATED WEB SITE, JUST
ONE PLACE FOR ITS CAMPUS
COMMUNITY TO GO WHEN THEY HAVE
CONCERNS OR QUESTIONS ABOUT
THIS NEW CORONAVIRUS.
>> MELANIE, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> IT IS 7:20 NOW.
COMING UP NEXT, A SHOCKER DOWN
UNDER.
THE YOUNG AMERICAN WHO JUST
FACED OFF AND BEAT THE NUMBER
ONE WOMAN IN THE WORLD AT THE
AUSTRALIAN OPEN.
>> ALSO WE'RE TALKING VAPING
CONCERNS AND THE GROWING TREND
AMONG STUDENTS AT 7:30, MORE
DETAILS ABOUT SUBSTANCE ABUSE
IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY SCHOOLS.
IT'S 7:21.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
I know you're not supposed to
look straight at it but...
Man, it looks delicious.
Get ready for a whole new way
to start the day.
Introducing the great tasting,
plant-based Beyond sausage
sandwich.
Only at Dunkin'.
Dunkin' coffee,
you get a cup of can-do.
Girl Scout Cookie™
inspired flavors are at Dunkin'.
Try a Thin Mints®
and Coconut Caramel today.
And get medium latte
or cappuccino
for $2 from 2 to 6 pm.
America runs on Dunkin'.
>> ♪
>> AMERICAN SOFIA KENIN HEADED
TO HER FIRST GRAND SLAM FINAL
AFTER A STUNNING VICTORY OVER
AUSTRALIA'S NUMBER ONE SEED
AND THE HOME FAVORITE.
THE 21-YEAR-OLD GREW UP IN
FLORIDA SAID HER PHONE HAS
BEEN BLOWING UP.
SHE'S ENJOYING EVERY SINGLE
MOMENT IN THE SPOTLIGHT.
THE FINAL IS THIS SATURDAY AND
ACTUALLY THE WOMAN SHE'S
PLAYING JUST UPSET HALEP.
ONE IS GOING TO WIN.
GOOD LUCK.
SHOULD BE A GOOD FINAL ON
SATURDAY.
>>> COLLEGE HOOPS NOW.
TOOK GEORGE WASHINGTON FOUR
OVERTIMES TO BEAT DAVIDSON
LAST NIGHT HERE IN D.C.
JACK WITH CAREER HIGH 35
POINTS.
FINAL 107 TO 104.
WONDER IF STEPH CURRY WAS
WATCHING THAT ONE SEEING HIS
OLD TEAM PLAYING HERE IN D.C.
>> WE CAN ONLY IMAGINE.
>> HE'S GOT SOME TIME ON HIS
HANDS, YOU KNOW STILL HEALING.
>> TUCKER, WELL, GOOD MORNING.
>> ALLISON, GOOD MORNING.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M -- I'M GREAT.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
WE HAVE JUST A BEAUTIFUL
SUNRISE ACROSS THE AREA.
OFF TO A NICE START.
A COLD START TO THE DAY NO
DOUBT ABOUT IT.
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK GENERALLY
IN THE 20'S FOR MUCH OF THE
AREA.
31 AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH AND
EAST HERE AT 8.
YOU CAN SEE SOME OF THE HIGH
CLOUDS.
THAT'S WHAT WE'LL BE
CONTENDING WITH KIND OF A MIX
OF CLOUDS AND SUN.
MORE CLOUDINESS THAN
YESTERDAY.
DISTURBANCE TO OUR SOUTH
LITTLE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE
BEING PUSHED OUT OF OUR REGION
AS HIGH PRESSURE IS IN CHARGE
BUT IT'S CLOSE ENOUGH WE'RE
GOING TO GET SOME CLOUDS THIS
AFTERNOON.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE AND A
COOL DAY TODAY.
ONLY LOW 40'S.
TODAY THE COLDEST OF THE NEXT
SEVEN AS WE'LL HAVE A NICE
WARMING TREND AND PLAIN OLD
SPRING WEATHER AROUND HERE BY
EARLY NEXT WEEK.
GET READY.
42 TODAY.
48 TOMORROW.
LOOKS LIKE SOME SHOWERS TO
KICK OFF OUR WEEKEND
ESPECIALLY EAST AND SOUTH OF
95.
WE'LL TALK MORE ABOUT THAT
COMING UP.
50.
BUT THEN LET ME GET OUT OF
YOUR WAY.
YOU CAN BASK IN THE 60'S
AROUND HERE BY EARLY NEXT
WEEK, MONDAY, TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY.
>> BASKING IN THE 60'S.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A HEAT
WAVE.
>> I'LL TAKE THAT.
>> JAM IT.
>> HOW ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT, SO TALKING ABOUT
THAT JAM CAM.
THIS IS A LOOK ON 295
SOUTHBOUND.
WE'VE GOT A CRASH REPORTED AT
BENNING ROAD.
AS YOU CAN SEE, IT IS A SLOW
GO IN THAT AREA.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UP TO DATE AS
WE RECEIVE MORE INFORMATION
REGARDING THAT CRASH.
ALSO SLOW AND STEADY ON 395
NORTHBOUND AS YOU COMMUTE FROM
EDSALL ROAD TO THE 14TH STREET
BRIDGE.
MOVING OVER TO 95 NORTHBOUND,
YOU'VE GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS
OF TRAFFIC FROM DALE CITY TO
THE BELTWAY.
IN THE THICK OF THINGS YOU'RE
DOWN TO ABOUT 20 MILES PER
HOUR.
LOOKING AT 66 WESTBOUND,
HOWEVER, IT'S SMOOTH SAILING
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY TOWARDS
THE BELTWAY.
AND 270 SOUTHBOUND, IT WILL
TAKE YOU ABOUT AN HOUR TO MAKE
IT FROM FREDERICK TO THE
BELTWAY.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
ANY QUESTIONS, STACEY FOX5
D.C. ON TWITTER.
>> UP NEXT AT 7:30 WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT VAPING AND
SUBSTANCE ABUSE CONCERNS IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY SCHOOLS.
>> PLUS, IT ISN'T TOO LATE TO
KICK THE HABIT.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT SMOKING
STILL AND HOW QUITTING CAN
REVERSE THE DAMAGE DONE TO
YOUR LUNGS.
>> ♪
♪
>> COMING UP ON 7:30 BUT LOOK
YOU NEED TO STOP AND TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS BEAUTIFUL SHOT OF
GORGEOUS SUN GETTING ON UP THERE
IN THE SKY AT ALMOST 7:30 NOW.
IT IS THURSDAY, JANUARY 30th.
IT'S 31 SUNNY DEGREES OUT THERE.
HOPE OFF GREAT DAY.
>>> LET'S CHECK OUR TOP STORIES
NOW FOR YOU THOUGH ON THIS
THURSDAY.
>>> UNFORTUNATELY STARTING OFF
WITH BAD NEWS.
MARINE KILLED IN ACTION DURING
WORLD WAR II WILL BE BURIED WITH
FULL MILITARY HONORS TODAY AT
ARLINGTON NATIONAL CEMETERY.
A FLAG DRAPED CASKET CARRYING
THE REMAINS OF PRIVATE FIRST
CLASS MICHAEL COMPANY COP PEE
ARRIVED AT BWI MARSHALL LAST
WEEK.
NOW THE PRIVATE ORGANIZATION
THAT LOCATED HIS GRAVE ALSO
FOUND A BOX WITH A ROSARY THE
PRIVATE HAD CARRIED.
HE WAS JUST 20 YEARS OLD AT THE
TIME OF HIS DEATH.
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
>>> A NEW STUDY REVEALS THAT
QUITTING SMOKING CAN REVERSE
LUNG DAMAGE.
RESEARCHERS AT THE SANGOR
INSTITUTE FOUND THOSE WHO
STOPPED SMOKING SHOWED SIGNS
THEY WERE GROWING NEW CELLS IN
THEIR AIRWAYS.
THE NEW CELLS CAN EVENTUALLY OUT
WEIGH THE DAMAGED ONES HELPING
DECREASE THE RISK OF DEVELOPING
LUNG CANCER.
NEVER TOO LATE TO QUIT, STEVE,
OVER TO YOU NO NOT AT ALL A
ACCORDING TO THE CDC VAPING HAS
BECOME A TREND AMONGST TEENS AS
YOUNG AS 13.
MARYLAND ENFORCE ADD 21 AND OVER
AGE RESTRICTION ON VAPING AND
TOBACCO PRODUCTS.
IN THIS FIXING THE ISSUE ABOUT
SCHOOL BASED SUBSTANCE ISSUES?
>> AHEAD OF TODAYS JOINT
EDUCATION AND HEALTH COMMITTEE
MEETING COUNCIL MEMBER JUWAN
TODAY JOINS US LIVE TO TALK
ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF STUDENTS
VAPING IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
COUNCILMAN, GOOD TO SEE YOU THIS
MORNING.
>> TALK ABOUT THE NEED TO
COLLECT MORE NEWER INFORMATION
TO EVEN WHAT YOU'RE DEALING
WITH.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A BIG CHALLENGE
FOR US.
THE LAST DATA WE HAVE IS FROM
2016.
WE KNOW IN THE LIFE OF YOUNG
PEOPLE PARTICULARLY TRENDS LIKE
VAPING THAT'S A LONG TIME.
AND SO WE'VE SEEN A LOT OF
INCREASE IN THAT TIME PERIOD.
SO TODAY WE'RE GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT THE STEPS THAT OUR
HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICE
DEPARTMENT IN OUR SCHOOL SYSTEM
CAN BE TAKING AND ARE TAKING TO
UPDATE THAT DATA TO CONFIRM WHAT
WE ALREADY KNOW IS AN INCREASE
AND UNFORTUNATELY OUR MIDDLE
SCHOOLS AND HIGH SCHOOLS WITH
VAPING, EVEN THOUGH WE'VE SEEN A
DECREASE IN OTHER TYPES OF
DRUGS, ALCOHOL USE, TOBACCO,
MARIJUANA IN MIDDLE -- IN THE
HIGH SCHOOL WE'RE SEEING THOSE
INCREASE IN MIDDLE SCHOOLS.
THAT'S A DISTURBING TREND, SO WE
NEED TO DIG INTO, THAT WILL HELP
US TODAY TAKE THE FIRST STEP
GETTING MORE DATA SO THAT WE CAN
COME UP WITH SOME POSITIVE
SOLUTIONS TO LIMIT THIS PROBLEM.
>> NOT JUST A MEMBER OF COUNCIL
BUT A PERSONAL CONNECTION YOU
HAVE KIDS IN THE SCHOOL SYSTEM.
THE DATA COLLECTION COMES FROM
THAT INITIAL NEED THAT WE HEAR
ABOUT.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING FROM THE
SCHOOL SYSTEMS HOW PREVALENT OF
A PROBLEM THIS MIGHT BE?
>> WELL, UNFORTUNATELY, A HUGE
RISE.
LIKE ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND SOME
OF OUR HIGH SCHOOLS I'VE HEARD
KIDS REFER TO THE BATHROOMS AS
VAPE ROOMS.
THEY HAVE TRASH CANS OVERFLOWING
WITH THESE CARTRIDGES AND WE
KNOW THAT THESE CARTRIDGES FOR
VAPING HAVE A LOT MORE NICOTINE
IT'S AN ADDICTIVE DRUG AND IT
MESSES WITH THE BRAIN AND THE
DEVELOPMENT OF OUR YOUNG PEOPLE
AND THE FACT THAT IT'S
INCREASING IN MIDDLE SCHOOL IS
REALLY TROUBLING.
WE'RE IN FRONT OF A MIDDLE
SCHOOL HERE RIGHT NOW IN WHITE
OAK AND WE NEED TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE'RE DOING ALL THAT WE CAN
TO LIMIT THE ACCESS TO N AND
THEN ALSO HAVE A ROBUST
EDUCATION CAMPAIGN BUT IT STARTS
WITH KNOWING THE HARD DATA AND
THEN LEVERAGING ALL OF OUR
RESOURCES AT THE FEDERAL, STATE
AND LOCAL LEVEL TO ATTACK THIS
PROBLEM.
WE STARTED WITH TWO POLICIES --
I'M SORRY G AHEAD.
>> I WAS JUST GOING TO ASK YOU
GET INTO THE POLICY IN A SECOND
BUT I WANT TO PAIR THAT WITH
YOUR ROLE THERE IN COUNCIL
BECAUSE ONCE YOU GET THIS DATA
HOPEFULLY FROM THE SURVEY
SHOWING WHAT THE EXTENT OF THE
PROBLEM IS, IS THE COUNCIL
WILLING TO EITHER ALLOCATE NEW
FUNDING OR FIND THE FUNDING
SOMEWHERE TO HELP OUT BECAUSE
IT'S GOING TO COST SOMETHING TO
COMBAT THE PROBLEM?
>> WE WILL, AND IT'S GOING TO
HAVE TO BE A JOINT EFFORT.
I MEAN THE GOOD NEWS ON THIS IS
THAT EVEN COMING OUT OF THIS
WHITE HOUSE AND AT THE STATE
LEVEL WITH THE GOVERNOR AND
LOCALLY WE ALL RECOGNIZE THIS IS
A HUGE PROBLEM, AND SO WE'RE
GOING TO NEED TO ALLOCATE
RESOURCES.
WE'VE ALREADY TAKEN A FEW STEPS
AS FAR AS RESTRICTING THE SALE
OF VAPING PRODUCTS WIN PROXIMITY
OF A SCHOOL.
THOSE BILLS ARE WORKING THEIR
WAY THROUGH, UM, AND ALSO THE
FLAVORED PRODUCTS WHICH ARE A
BIG PROBLEM WHICH WE SAW IN
TOBACCO YEARS AGO.
WE'RE TAKING THE STEPS WE CAN
LOCALLY BUT WE'LL NEED TO
PARTNER WITH OUR STATE AND
FEDERAL PARTNERS AND WE'RE
WILLING TO PUT UP MONEY TO OUR
HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
DEPARTMENT IN THIS BUDGET TO
ATTACK THIS PROBLEM.
THINGS LIKE MORE SCHOOL NURSES.
MORE THERAPISTS.
OTHER PEOPLE THAT CAN COME IN
AND INTERVENE BECAUSE IT'S NOT
JUST ACCESS PROBLEM IT'S ALSO
MENTAL HEALTH.
IT'S ALSO HEALTH WITH NURSES
ADDRESSING THIS EARLY ON.
SO WE'LL BE ATTACKING IT FROM
EVERY WAY, AND IT CERTAINLY WILL
BE A BUDGET PRIORITY AS WE HEAD
INTO THE BUDGET IN THE NEXT
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
>> COUNCILMAN SINCE YOU
MENTIONED WORKING WITH THE STATE
OFFICIALS AS WELL LET ME THROW
THIS AT YOU AS WE HAVE YOU HERE.
THIS BACK AND FORTHWITH SCHOOL
START TIMES NOW, YOU KNOW,
SCHOOL DISTRICT FINALLY MADE A
CALL.
WE'LL START SCHOOL BEFORE LABOR
DAY AND THEN THE GOVERNOR COMES
OUT AND SAYS HOLD ON A MINUTE,
WE'RE GOING TO DO SCHOOL AFTER
LABOR DAY.
WHERE DO YOU STAND ON THIS
DEBATE?
>> WELL, I'M A HUNDRED% WITH OUR
SCHOOLS LEADERS.
SCHOOLS HAVE AND SHOULD BE --
THAT SHOULD BE A LOCAL DECISION.
WE HAVE THE LARGEST SCHOOL
SYSTEM HERE IN MARYLAND, 167,000
STUDENTS, 14th LARGEST IN THE
COUNTRY.
WE SHOULD BE DECIDING WHEN OUR
KIDS GO TO SCHOOL BASED ON OUR
LOCAL NEEDS.
THAT'S WHY A LOCAL LEADERS LIKE
OUR SCHOOL BOARD WAS ELECTED,
AND I THINK THAT'S THE RIGHT
POLICY, AND I'M DISAPPOINT THE
THAT THE GOVERNOR IS TRYING TO
DOUBLE DOWN ON THIS.
THE OTHER THING YOU HAVE TO
THINK ABOUT, A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE HURT LAST SUMMER THAT
COULDN'T PAY FOR THAT EXTRA WEEK
OF CAMP OR VACATION AND DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH THEIR KIDS
IN THOSE TWO WEEKS BETWEEN
AUGUST AND LABOR DAY AND THAT'S
SOMETHING THAT WE HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT HERE WITH A THIRD OF OUR
STUDENTS ON FREE AND REDUCED
LUNCH IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY
IT SHOULD BE A LOCAL DECISION
AND I'M HOPING THAT WE CAN KEEP
THAT DECISION WHERE IT IS AND
CONVINCE THE GOVERNOR TO JUST
BACK OFF ON THIS POINT.
>> AS OF NOW, SHOULD PARENTS
STILL PLAN FOR THAT
AUGUST 30th START DATE NEXT
YEAR?  THAT'S CORRECT.
THAT'S WHAT THE SCHOOL SYSTEM
HAS SAID AND WE'RE NOT PLANNING
ON CHANGING IT ABSENT A COURT
ORDER AND I DON'T THINK THAT
WILL COME.
THE POLICY IS CLEAR LOCAL
CONTROL SCHOOLS IS A LONG-
LONG-STANDING PRECEDENT AND
TRADITION AND SOMETHING THAT
SHOULD BE UPHELD.
>> WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON IT.
COUNCIL MEMBER, THANKS FOR
JOINING US THIS MORNING.
WE DO APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
>> THANK YOU.
7:36 RIGHT NOW.
>>> LET'S GET A CHECK ON THE
FORECAST.
TODAY TUCKER, I BELIEVE YOU WILL
SAID THIS IS THE COLDEST DAY
WE'LL SEE THIS WEEK.
>> NOTHING TOO EXTREME HERE.
HIGHS IN THE LOW 40, STEVE,
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE TEENS
AND 20S.
31 AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
BUT IT WAS NO DOUBT ABOUT IT,
OUR COLDEST START SO FAR THIS
WEEK.
GENERALLY 10 PLUS DEGREES COLDER
THAN WHERE WE WERE AT 24 HOURS.
10 IN BINGHAMTON.
25 IN NEW YORK CITY.
22 BOSTON.
COLD AIR IN PLACE HERE ACROSS
NEW ENGLAND, AND DOWN INTO THE
MID ATLANTIC THIS MORNING.
LITTLE COASTAL LOW PUSHING OFF
THE SOUTHEAST COAST THERE OFF
THE CAROLINA COAST.
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO DRAG SOME
CLOUDS INTO OUR REGION, AND
WE'LL KIND OF PARTLY SUNNY AND
COOL THIS AFTERNOON.
HIGH TEMPERATURES IN THE LOW
40S.
AND THEN WE'LL START A WARMING
TREND AROUND HERE STARTING
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
WE WON'T CLOUD UP TOMORROW.
TALK ABOUT SOME OUR CHANCES FOR
RAIN SHOWERS HERE SATURDAY
MORNING.
SATURDAY MORNING AND A BIG
WARMUP.
WHEN WILL THAT ARRIVE?  I'LL
HAVE DETAILS.
STACEY?
>> THANKS TUCKER.
HEADS UP ON THE BAY BRIDGE THIS
MORNING.
IN ADDITION TO THAT LONG-TERM
ROAD WORK, WE'VE GOT A CRASH
BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE I'M JUST
GOING TO MOVE OVER TO THE SIDE.
THAT CAMERA IT IS NOT FROZEN.
IT'S LITERALLY STOPPED ON THE
BRIDGE.
SO USE YOUR PATIENCE IF YOU ARE
CROSSING HEADING WESTBOUND.
MOVING OVER TO 295 SOUTHBOUND,
WE'VE GOT A CRASH REPORTED AT
BENNING ROAD CAUSING SOME SLOW
DOWNS THIS MORNING.
395 NORTHBOUND IS ALSO SLOW AND
STEADY AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY FROM
EDSALL ROAD TO THE 14th STREET
BRIDGE, AND 95 NORTHBOUND DALE
CITY TO THE BELTWAY YOU'VE GOT
YOUR USUAL POCKS FOR THIS TIME
OF THE MORNING.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> COMING UP THE NUMBER OF
PEOPLE WHO WILL NOT BE GOING TO
WORK ON MONDAY.
>> PLUS TWITTER IS OUT WITH A
NEW FEATURE AHEAD OF THE BIG
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
WE'LL FILL YOU IN DURING TODAY'S
BUSINESS BEAT.
♪
♪♪
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
diery now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Los necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Get what works for you. And pay
for what you want.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Mix and match your perfect Fios
plan.
Only on Verizon.
♪
>>> BACK NOW AT 7:40.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN FOUR
YEARS, LIVE EXPECTANCY ACTUALLY
GOING UP IN THE UNITED STATES.
AS THE NUMBER OF FATAL DRUG
OVERDOSES IN SIX OF THE 10
LEADING CAUSES OF DEATH
DECLINED.
THE CDC REPORTS A .1 BUMP IN AGE
TO 78.7 YEARS.
HAD BEEN 78.6.
SINCE THE SPREAD OF THE
CORONAVIRUS OVER THE LAST COUPLE
OF WEEKS, GOOGLE HAS SEEN A
MAJOR SPIKE IN SEARCHES FOR BEER
VIRUS AND CORONA BEER VIRUS.
THE BEER, OF COURSE, HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE VIRUS BUT SOME
PEOPLE APPEAR TO BE A LITTLE,
YOU KNOW, CONFUSED.
>> IN MIAMI THE MAYOR WELCOME
THE SUPER BOWL TEAMS WITH THE
FLIP OF A SWITCH ON A NEW
60-STORY $600 MILLION TOWER SAID
TO BE THE WORLD'S MOST
FUTURISTIC AND LUXURIOUS
REASONABLE BUILDING.
COMPLETE WITH A FLYING CAR SKY
PORT, ALLISON, FORK YOUR FLYING
CAR SOON TO BE.
>> HMM.
>> PRETTY AWESOME LED DISPLAY
UNLESS IT'S RIGHT OUTSIDE YOUR
WINDOW.
LIGHTING SYSTEM TOOK THREE YEARS
TO PLAN AND DESIGN.
>>> I KNOW.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?  YEAH.
OKAY.
WHAT A WEEK FOR BILLY EILISH.
THE SINGER COMING OFF HER BIG
NIGHT AT THE GRAMMYS.
THE OSCARS ARE NOW CALLING.
>> INTERESTING.
A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AS WE HEAD
TO BREAK ON THIS THURSDAY
MORNING.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
IT'S 7:42.
♪
VO: 700,000 more New Yorkers
have health care coverage
because Mayor Bloomberg
got it done.
He'll build on Obamacare
with universal coverage
and lower the cost
of prescription medicine.
Mike will get it done.
MB: I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
VO: The gun lobby's worst
nightmare.
Mike Bloomberg founded and led a
gun safety organization that's
helped pass lifesaving laws
across the nation.
On gun safety Mike
will get it done.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and
I approve this message.
7:44.
IN GOOD'S BUSINESS BEAT TWITTER
ADDING A NEAR FUTURE AHEAD OF
THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
JOINING US TRACEE CAR ROSCO ON A
THURSDAY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> TWITTER IS DOING WHAT THEY
CAN THEY SAY TO TRY TO GET REAL
INFORMATION OUT THERE AHEAD OF
THE BIG ELECTION.
>> YEAH, TWITTER IS STEPPING UP
ITS EFFORTS TO FIGHT BACK
AGAINST THE SPREAD OF
MISINFORMATION.
TWITTER GIVING USERS THE ABILITY
TO FLAG TWEETS THEY THINK
CONTAIN MISLEADING INFORMATION
ABOUT HOW TO VOTE OR HOW TO
ENGAGE IN OTHER CIVIC ACTI
ACTIVITIES.
TWITTER USERS CAN FLAG THIS
TWEET -- A TWEET THEY FIND
MISLEADING JUST LIKE THEY CAN
FLAG A TWEET THAT MIGHT CONTAIN
HARASSMENT OR SPAM.
SO THIS IS THE FIRST TIME THAT
TWITTER IS ALLOWING THIS FEATURE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
ANY FLAGGED TWEET WILL BE
REVIEWED AND THEN IF TWITTER
THINKS THEY NEED TO TAKE IT
DOWN, THEN THEY WILL.
SO THE REASON BEHIND THIS, THEY
WANT TO STOP VOTER SUPPRESSION
AND I THINK WE'RE GOING TO SEE
MORE OF THIS AS WE GET CLOSER TO
THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
AS WE ARE JUST MONTHS AWAY NOW.
NOT JUST FROM TWITTER BUT
PROBABLY SOME OF THE OTHER
SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES AS WELL.
>> OKAY.
LET'S MOVE ON TO WHAT'S
HAPPENING THIS SUNDAY WHICH OF
COURSE IS THE BIG SUPER BOWL
GAME.
LOTS OF OUR FELLOW AMERICANS
MIGHT BE FEELING A LITTLE UNDER
THE WEATHER ON MONDAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> A LITTLE SUPER BOWL FEVER ON
MONDAY PERHAPS.
ACCORDING TO THE WORK FORCE
INSTITUTE  THEY FOUND
11.1 MILLION PEOPLE WILL BE
USING A PRE-APPROVED DAY OFF ON
MONDAY.
THE DAY AFTER THE SUPER BOWL.
HOWEVER, 4.7 MILLION PEOPLE
THEY'RE GOING TO BE CALLING OUT
SICK ON MONDAY.
THERE'S STILL A BIG CHUNK ABOUT
7.9 MILLION THAT SAY THEY'RE NOT
SURE WHAT THEY'RE GOING TO DO ON
MONDAY.
MAYBE THEY'LL COME TO WORK,
MAYBE THEY WON'T.
SO IF YOU NOTICE THE OFFICE
LOOKING A LITTLE MORE EMPTY THAN
USUAL, THAT IS PROBABLY WHY.
I THINK THIS IS REASON ENOUGH TO
MAYBE MOVE THE SUPER BOWL TO A
SATURDAY.
I KNOW THERE'S BEEN SOME TALK
ABOUT THAT HAPPENING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
>> I DO, TOO.
PEOPLE -- WE'RE JUST SO LIKE
STEEPED IN SOME TRADITIONS AND
THEN OTHER TRADITIONS LIKE WE'RE
LIKE, GET RID OF IT.
OKAY.
FOR NOW IT'S ON A SUNDAY.
>> WE'LL BE AT WORK ON MONDAY,
RIGHT, ALLISON.
>> DEFINITELY BE HERE.
ALL BLURRY I'D BUT I'LL BE HERE.
THANKS SO MUCH.
LET'S LEAVE IT THERE.
>> THANKS.
>> EIFFEL JUST LOVE THE IDEA OF
BEING ABLE TO SLEEP IN AFTER THE
SUPER BOWL.
WHETHER IT'S SATURDAY OR SUNDAY
ON NOBODY WORKS MONDAY BEING
ABLE TO ENJOY IT IT.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE HARD TO
CHANGE THE DAY AND WE'D ALL GET
USED TO IT.
>> MY SIB NOT THAT I'M HUNG OVER
I EAT ALL KINDS OF FOOD.
>> BUT YOU'RE UP LATE WATCHING
THE GAME.
>> I EAT FOUR BAGS OF FRITOS AND
CAULIFLOWER WEIRD BUFFALO DIP
AND --
>> YOUR STOMACH --
>> I HAVE A STOMACH ACHE FOR TWO
DAYS.
>> BUBBLE GUT.
>> SYMPATHY 24 HOURS OFF AFTER
HAVING TO ENDURE ALL THAT FOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER COLD AND QUIET DAY.
TEENS AND 20S OUT THERE EARLY.
WE ARE 31 IN TOWN.
BUT MUCH OF THE AREA HERE AGAIN
WAKING UP TO NUMBERS IN THE LOW
20S.
TODAY WILL BE A COOL DAY.
SATURDAY SHOWERS FIRST HALF OF
THE DAY I'LL SHOW THAT YOU SETUP
HERE IN JUST A MINUTE AND THEN
60S NEXT WEEK.
EXCLAMATION POINT.
NOT QUESTION MARK.
I'M GOING TO GUARANTEE IT JOE
NEMETH STYLE THAT'S A SUPER BOWL
REFERENCE.
ALL RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN I WON'T BE
HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> GUARANTEED A LOT OF THINGS.
30 LEONARDTOWN NORTH AND WEST
LET'S DO 20S.
GAITHERSBURG 23.
WINCHESTER 21.
19 THAT'S OUR COLD SPOT.
MARTINSBURG, GOOD MORNING, 24 IN
CULPEPER.
TAKE THE JACKET.
EVEN WITH THE MORNING SUNSHINE
WE'LL ONLY BE IN THE LOW 40S
LATER TODAY.
TODAY WILL BE THE COOLEST OF THE
NEXT SEVEN OR SO.
DON'T BE TOO CONCERNED ABOUT
THIS.
THIS WILL BE PUSHED TO OUR SOUTH
AND EAST AND I DON'T THINK MUCH
OF THAT'S TOUCHING THE GROUND
WE'LL GET SOME CLOUDS THIS
AFTERNOON SO PARTLY SUNNY AND
AGAIN A COOL DAY.
HERE'S THE BIG PICTURE, AND A
LITTLE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE OFF
NORTH CAROLINA COAST GETTING
PUSHED AWAY FROM OUR REGION.
SO IT SHOULD DRAG THIS CLOUD
COVER WITH IT LATER TODAY
ALTHOUGH WE WILL HAVE MORE
CLOUDS THAN YESTERDAY.
OKAY.
WEEKEND SETUP.
AREA OF LOW PRESSURE EAST OF
CAPE HATTERAS, AND RAIN SHOWERS
I THINK CERTAINLY A POSSIBILITY
THE FIRST HALF OF THE DAY ON
SATURDAY.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE SOUTH AND
EAST OF 95.
SO D.C. SOUTH AND EAST.
SOUTHERN MARYLAND, LOWER EASTERN
SHORE SOUTHEAST VIRGINIA.
BEST CHANCES FOR RAIN IF YOU'RE
CLOSER TO THAT AREA OF LOW
PRESSURE THEN WE SHOULD GET IT
OUT OF HERE IN THE AFTERNOON
HOURS AND WE'RE SETTING UP FOR A
NICE SUNDAY.
LOW 50S HERE SUPER BOWL AND
PLENTY OF SUNSHINE, AND THEN THE
REAL NICE STUFF IF YOU LIKE THE
SPRINGTIME WARMTH EVEN THOUGH
IT'S EARLY FEBRUARY I PROMISE
YOU'LL LOVE EARLY NEXT WEEK.
STACEY THE FOX5 TIP JAR WILL
RETURN TO THE CORNER.
NOT THAT I'VE BEEN TIPPED
ANYTHING YET BUT EVENTUALLY
SOMEBODY WILL HAVE TO PUT
SOMETHING IN THERE.
42 TODAY.
THERE YOU GO.
MONDAY, TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY 60S.
>> FOR THE 60S I'LL WRITE I WAS
CHECK FOR THAT TIP JAR.
>> OKAY.
MAKE SURE IT'S GOT L LOTS OF ZES
AND READY TO GO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE GOOD NEWS REGARDING THAT
CRASH ON THE BAY BRIDGE.
WE HAD A CRASH WESTBOUND THAT
WAS BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE.
IT IS STILL BLOCKING THE LEFT
LANE AND YOU'VE GOT SOME DELAYS
BECAUSE OF THAT.
THE GOOD NEWS IS I THOUGHT IT
WAS CLEARED BUT ACCORDING TO
THIS RIGHT NOW IT IS NOT CLEAR.
STILL THERE LEFT LANE STILL
BLOCK.
I'LL KEEP YOU UPDATED AS MORE
INFORMATION COMES IN, OF COURSE.
MOVING OVER TO 66 WESTBOUND,
SLOW AND STEADY FROM MANASSAS TO
THE BELTWAY IT WILL TAKE YOU
ABOUT AN HOUR AS WE LOOK AT 95
NORTHBOUND AS YOU CAN SEE A LOT
OF PEOPLE ON THE ROAD BUT IT'S
MOVING MAKING YOUR WAY FROM DALE
CITY TO THE BELTWAY.
FINALLY, ON THE OUTER LOOP, YOU
KNOW WHAT IT'S LOOKING LIKE FOR
THIS TIME OF THE MORNING.
LOTS OF PEOPLE ON THE ROAD AND
YOU'VE GOT LOTS OF JAMS THERE.
SLOW AND STEADY ON THE OUTER
LOOP AS WELL AS THE BALTIMORE
WASHINGTON PARKWAY.
AND FINALLY, ON 270 SOUTHBOUND,
IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT AN HOUR
TO MAKE IT FROM FREDERICK TO THE
BELTWAY.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
ANY QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C.
ON TWITTER.
>> BURGLAR IN CALIFORNIA DECIDED
TO BREAK INTO A LIQUOR STORE
THROUGH THE ROOF AND FELL
THROUGH THE CEILING.
STILL MANAGED TO STEAL A LARGE
AMOUNT OF LOTTERY TICKETS BEFORE
THIS ROBBERY THE SAME MAN ALSO
BROKE INTO AN AUTO REPAIR SHOP
BUT DID NOT TAKE ANYTHING.
>>> OH, BOY.
>> MAKE AN ENTRANCE.
>>> AFTER DAYS OF DELAYS DUE TO
THE WEATHER SPACE X LAUNCHED ITS
FOURTH BATCH OF 60 STARLING
SATELLITES INTO ORBIT FROM CAPE
CANAVERAL FOLLOWING THE
SUCCESSFUL LAUNCH FALCON NINE
ROCKET TOUCHED DOWN ON SPACE X
DRONE SHIP LANDING PLATFORM IN
THE ATLANTIC OCEAN.
NOW THE MISSION TO BUILD A
STRONG SATELLITE NETWORK CAPABLE
OF PROVIDING WIRELESS INTERNET
SERVICES TO THE WORLD.
>>> 7:50 RIGHT NOW.
>>> IT'S PERFECT TIME TO GIVE
YOU A LOOK AT THE GOOD DAY GUEST
LIST.
WE ALL KNOW THAT SERVICE DOGS
PROVIDE MUCH NEEDED HELP TO
THOSE IN NEED.
WELL, THE CAPS AND MONUMENTAL
SPORTS AGENCY DECIDED THAT THEY
CAN PROVIDE SERVICE DOGS WITH A
PERFECT TRAINING GROUND.
SO TODAY WE'LL GET TO KNOW THEIR
NEWEST MEMBER SCOUT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALSO AHEAD WE'RE PAYING IT
FORWARD.
WE WILL MEET A 19-YEAR-OLD
FOOTBALL PLAYER WHO PARTICIPATED
IN A BONE MARROW DRIVE AND
BECAME A MATCH FOR AN INFANT WHO
REALLY NEEDED IT.
>>> WE'LL HAVE THE INCREDIBLE
STORY COMING UP ON GOOD DAY.
>>> AND WE'RE SUPER BOWL
PRE-GAMING IT WITH DC RESTAURANT
THE BRIGHTON THEY WILL SERVE UP
COCKTAILS AND FOOD TO SHOW YOU
HOW THEY PLAN TO CELEBRATE THE
BIG GAME ON SUNDAY.
ALL THIS AND MUCH MORE AHEAD ON
GOOD DAY D.C.
>> SPEAK OF SATELLITES, THE TWO
SATELLITES WE TALKED ABOUT
YESTERDAY THE NEAR COLLISION.
>> WHAT HAPPENED.
>> THEY DID NOT HIT EACH OTHER.
EXPECTED TO PASS BETWEEN 50 FEET
OF EACH OTHER.
THEY CONNED ON THEIR WAY.
>> HOW BIG SPACE IS AND 50 FEET.
>> FOLLOW UP TO YESTERDAY'S
STORY, HI, KEV.
>> HOW YOU DOING TODAY.
>> DOING SUPER.
ALLISON YOU TEASED BEFORE THE
BREAK ABOUT BILLY EILISH NOT
ONLY DID SHE HAVE A MASSIVE WIN
AT THE GRAMMYS, SHE MADE
HISTORY.
SHE WAS THE FIRST WOMAN TO EVER
WIN ALL BIG FOUR AWARDS THE
MAJOR FOUR AWARDS RECORD, SONG,
ALBUM OF THE YEAR AND -- THIS IS
INCREDIBLE ELEMENT AND SHE'S
ALSO YOUNGEST PERSON TO EVER DO
THAT.
NOW, SHE IS CONFIRMED TO PERFORM
AT THE OSCARS ON FEBRUARY 9th.
NOW, SMART MOVE BY THE OSCARS.
THIS IS AN AMAZING ARTIST WHO'S
VERY POPULAR RIGHT NOW.
SHE'S A VERY, VERY BIG AUDIENCE.
YOUNGER AUDIENCE AS WELL, RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO BRING YOUNGER
AUDIENCES TO THE OSCARS THAT'S
KIND OF THE POINT.
ALSO, AT THE SAME TIME SHE IS
GOING TO BE DOING THE SONG FOR
BOND.
SO NO TIME TO TIE.
>> OKAY.
>> REMEMBER WE SAW ADELE DO THE
SONG FOR SKY FALL.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO BILLY EILISH IS LIKE
HAVING THE BEST TIME RIGHT NOW.
GRAMMY WINNER, PERFORMING AT THE
OSCARS AND SHE'S DOING THE BOND
SONG WHICH COMES OUT IN APRIL.
>> WINNING -- WINNING, WINNING
AND WINNING.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
I LIKE THIS MOVE BY THE ACADEMY
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT MIGHT
BRING -- LET'S SAY BILLY EILISH
HAS A DONE OF FANS WHO AREN'T
NECESSARILY OSCAR FANS OR MOVIE
FANS.
>> THEY'LL TUNE IN.
>> THEY'LL TUNE IN FOR IT.
>> I'M NOT THE BIGGEST BILLY
EILISH FAN.
I MADE THAT CLEAR.
>> I ADMIRE HER.
>> SHE'S VERY THEATRICAL.
FOR THE OSCARS THAT'S NOT A BAD
CALL.
SHE'LL BE HEADING THE FIRE FLY
FESTIVAL UP IN DELAWARE CLOSE TO
D.C.
>> OKAY.
>> HONESTLY I WOULD BE
INTERESTED IN SEEING HER LIVE.
I KNOW I ONLY KNOW THAT ONE SONG
BAD GUY I'M NOT FAMILIAR WITH
HER MUSIC.
DO YOU LIKE HER SONGS?  I THINK
THEY'RE -- YEAH.
>> THEY'RE INTERESTING.
>> MY GIRLS LIKE HER.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON I KNOW.
>> SHE'S YOUNG AND TALENTED AND
IT'S REALLY COOL.
>> SHE'S EDGY.
>> I AGREE.
I THINK IT'S GOOD FOR THE OS
OSCARS.
>>> NEXT STORY, STRANGER THINGS
STAR APOLOGIES IF I'M BOTCHING
HIS NAME GRATTON -- I WILL
DOUBLE CHECK ON THAT.
EGG POSTING ABOUT SURGERY HE'S
BEEN GETTING THE FOURTH SURGERY
FOR CCD.
SO THIS IS SOMETHING IF YOU'RE
NOT FAMILIAR WITH THIS A RARE
BONE DISORDER AND HE SAID
SURGERY NUMBER FOUR I BELIEVE WE
HAVE HIS POST IF WE HAVE IT.
GO BACK TO HIS INSTAGRAM POST HE
BASICALLY TALKED ABOUT THE
IDEA -- WE DON'T HAVE THE POST.
IF YOU GO TO HIS INSTAGRAM HE
POSTED A PHOTO OF HIM IN THE
HOSPITAL BED.
HE SAID THIS IS THE BIG ONE.
THIS IS HIS FOURTH SURGERY FOR
CCD.
IF YOU'RE NOT FAMILIAR WITH
THIS, IT IS A QUOTE SKELETAL
DISORDER CHARACTERIZED BY
OPEN -- HELP ME ON THAT ONE.
>> FONDER UNLESS.
>> SOFT SPOT IN YOUR HEAD.
>> ABSENT CLAVICLES AND MULTIPLE
DENTAL ABNORMALITYINGS GENERIC
BIRTH DEFECT CAUSED BY MUTATIONS
TO THE RUN X2 GENE.
IT'S AN INTERESTING -- ONLY
CURSE IN ONE -- EVERYONE MILLION
BIRTHS.
IT CAN BE PASSED FROM AN
AFFECTED PARENT OR CAN BE RANDOM
MUTATION MANIFESTATIONS MAY VARY
AMONG INDIVIDUALS IN THE SAME
FAMILY.
VERY RARE BUT HE'S TALKED ABOUT
IT A LOT.
HE BROUGHT A LOT OF ATTENTION IT
TO ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
IT'S ACTUALLY PART OF THE SHOW.
DON'T THEY INCORPORATE THAT INTO
HIS CHARACTER.
>> OKAY.
I NEEDED TO SOME MORE RESEARCH.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE ACTOR
WITHLY CURLY HAIR.
>> IN THE COMMERCIALS A LOT.
>> YEAH.
>> WE DIDN'T REALLY SHOW HIM.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE SHOWED THE OTHER ACTOR A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY IT'S NOT
WORKING THERE'S A FULL SCREEN IF
YOU GO TO INSTAGRAM OF HIM IN
THE BED.
IT'S THE CHARACTER ON THE SHOW
WITH THE CURLY HAIR.
>> BECAUSE HIS TEETH, THEY MAKE
A BIG THING BECAUSE IT LOOKS
LIKE HE HAS BABY TEETH.
>> CORRECT.
>> SO I APOLOGIZE FOR NOT --
>> YOU SEE HIM DOING THE
WIRELESS COMPANY COMMERCIALS.
>> HE'S EVERYWHERE.
IF YOU SAW HIS FACE YOU WOULD
KNOW IT.
I PULLED UP STRANGER THINGS.
>> WISHING HIM THE BEST AND I'M
GLAD HE'S TAKING THAT IMPACTED
HIM AND TRYING TO RAISE
AWARENESS.
>> ME, TOO.
>> SOUND LIKE A MOM HE SEEMS
LIKE SUCH A NICE YOUNG MAN.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU 100% MUCH
THAT'S THE NEWS RIGHT NOW.
>> THANKS, KEV.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
>> TUCK, OVER TO YOU WITH A
CHECK OF THE FORECAST.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
COLD TEMPERATURES TO START YOUR
DAY.
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN SOME
CASES THE TEENS.
LOTS OF 20'S OUT THERE EARLY
THIS MORNING AS WELL.
NOTICE THE HIGH, THIN
CLOUDINESS.
WE'LL HAVE MORE CLOUDS TODAY SO
KIND OF A PARTLY SUNNY DAY.
YOU'LL GET SOME SUNSHINE AS
WELL.
31 TO KICK OFF YOUR MORNING
HERE.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH AND EAST
AT EIGHT.
A COOL AFTERNOON.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
LOW 40S FOR DAYTIME HIGHS.
STORMINESS OFF THE SOUTHEAST
COAST.
YOU CAN SEE IT THERE OFF THE
CAROLINA COAST.
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO PUSH AWAY
FROM OUR REGION.
SO NO RAIN FOR US TODAY.
BUT WE'LL HAVE MORE CLOUDS THAN
YESTERDAY AND DAYTIME HIGHS IN
THE LOW 40S.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY FORECAST.
42 TODAY.
48 TOMORROW.
A LITTLE RAIN SATURDAY MORNING
WILL GIVE WAY TO SHINE LIE LATE
IN THE DAY.
SUNDAY LOOKS GOOD.
NEXT WEEK 60S!
>> STACEY.
>> 60S.
>> BINGO!
>>> ALL RIGHT.
SO I HAVE UPDATE REGARDING THE
BAY BRIDGE CRASH.
THE CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED ON
THE BRIDGE.
HOWEVER, AS YOU CAN SEE IN THAT
SHOT AS WELL AS FROM THE
SPEEDOMETER IT IS SLOW MOVING.
WE'VE GOT SOME MAJOR RESIDUAL
DELAYS BECAUSE OF THAT.
SO HEADS UP IF YOU'RE CROSSING
THE BAY BRIDGE THIS MORNING.
66 WESTBOUND IS STEADY AND SLOW
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY FROM
MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY.
IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT AN HOUR
TO GET THERE.
AND 95 NORTHBOUND ALSO SLOW AND
STEADY DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY
EXPERIENCING ITS USUAL POCKS OF
TRAFFIC.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
>> KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
MORNING.
SO MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR
8:00 O'CLOCK HOUR.
LOOK, ARE YOU TRAVELING FOR
SPRING BREAK?  MAKING THE PLANS
NOW.
IF YOU'RE STILL WAITING TO BOOK
A TRIP, WE'VE GOT SOME TIPS.
>> AHEAD NEXT HOUR HAVE YOU
HEARD OF THE WASHINGTON JUSTICE.
IT'S D.C.'S E SPORTS TEAM.
IT IS A HUGE INDUSTRY IF YOU'RE
NOT AWARE OF IT YOU'LL LEARN ALL
ABOUT IT.
MIKE THOMAS CHECKING IT OUT FOR
US THIS MORNING.
♪
♪♪
MY MONEY SHOULD WORK
AS HARD AS I DO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD
TO BUY ALL THE
LATEST TECH STUFF.
TODAY, I'M EARNING ON A CHARGER.
SO, JUST THE CHARGER THEN?
UMMM...
♪ ♪ ♪
YEAH!
(SARCASTICALLY) FANTASTIC.
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CHASE. MAKE MORE
OF WHAT'S YOURS.
♪
>>> PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP'S
IMPEACHMENT TRIAL CONTINUES
TODAY AS LAWMAKERS ON BOTH SIDES
OF THE AISLE CONTINUE THEIR
QUESTIONING.
BUT THERE'S A BIG QUESTION STILL
UP IN THE AIR.
>>> WILL FORMER NSA ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON BE CALLED TO TESTIFY?
IT'S NOT THE ONLY STORY WE'RE
KEEPING KEEPING AN EYE ON.
THE DEADLY ADVISE CLAIMED THE
LIVES OF 170 PEOPLE IN CHINA.
SEVERAL UNIVERSITIES HERE IN THE
D.C. AREA ASKED STUDENTING
STUDYING ABROAD IN CHINA TO COME
HOME AND THE FIGHT CONTINUES
OVER TRAFFIC ENFORCEMENT IN
FAIRFAX COUNTY.
SOME BELIEVE THAT SPEEDERS ARE
TAKING OVER A POPULAR ROAD BUT
WHO IS IN CHARGE OF PATROLLING
THAT AREA?
>>> AND JUST INTO THE NEWSROOM
WE TAKE LIVE LOOK AT WHITE
HOUSE, D.C. MAYOR MURIEL BOWSER
IS ENDORSING FORMER NEW YORK
MAYOR MICHAEL BLOOMBERG FOR
PRESIDENT.
SHE SAYS HE'S A PROBLEM SOLVER
WITH A PROVEN TRACK RECORD OF
GETTING THINGS DONE.
HE'S ALSO GOING TO BE IN D.C.
>> ALSO IN SUPPORT OF D.C.
STATEHOOD.
BEFORE WE DIG INTO THE
HEADLINES, LET'S GET A CHECK OF
THE FORECAST FROM TUCKER AND A
LOOK AT THE MORNING COMMUTE FROM
STACEY.
GOOD MORNING, TEAM.
>> GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
IT'S COLD OUTSIDE.
LOOK AT THOSE NUMBERS.
EVERYBODY BELOW FREEZING EARLY
THIS MORNING.
GOING TO BE A COOL AFTERNOON BUT
WE'VE GOT A NICE WARMUP ON THE
SEVEN DAY.
HOW WARM WILL IT GET?  I'LL HAVE
DETAILS COMING UP.
>> STACEY.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
IT IS A SLOW RIDE ON THE BAY
BRIDGE THIS MORNING.
WE HAD AN EARLIER CRASH WITH A
LANE BLOCKAGE.
THE CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED BUT
AS YOU CAN SEE, SPEEDS ARE JUST
DOWN TO A MILE PER HOUR WITH
RESIDUAL DELAYS.
I'LL TELL ALL ABOUT IT AND GIVE
YOU A FULL LOOK AT THE DMV
COMING UP.
>> GROWING FEARS HERE IN THE
U.S. AND AROUND THE WORLD AS THE
CORONAVIRUS SHOWS NO SIGN OF
SLOWING DOWN.
>> SEVERAL UNIVERSITIES
INCLUDING ONES IN OUR AREA HAVE
ASKED STUDENTS STUDYING ABROAD
IN CHINA TO COME BACK HOME.
FOX5'S MELANIE ALNWICK JOINS US
NOW WITH MORE ON THIS PUSH.
MEL?
>> GOOD MORNING, A LOT OF THIS
WAS PREDICATED BECAUSE THE CDC
YESTERDAY UPGRADED ITS TRAVEL
ADVISOR ASKING THAT PEOPLE JUST
CANCEL ALL NON-ESSENTIAL TRAVEL
TO CHINA.
THEREFORE, THE UNIVERSITIES
DECIDED WITH SO MANY EXCHANGE
STUDENTS AND INTERNATIONAL
PROGRAMS THAT THIS WOULD BE THE
BEST THING FOR THEM TO DO.
THAT INCLUDES HERE AT UNIVERSITY
OF MARYLAND, WHERE THEIR
EDUCATION A BROAD PROGRAM IN
CHINA FOR THE SPRING OF 2020 HAS
NOW BEEN CANCELED.
SOME OTHER MEASURES BEING TAKEN
HERE AT UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND
INCLUDE STAFFING UP THE STUDENT
HEALTH CENTER JUST IN CASE MORE
PEOPLE COME IN CONCERNED ABOUT A
COUGH OR THE FLU.
ALSO REMINDING THE COMMUNITY TO
PRACTICE GOOD HYGIENE.
HIGH TOUCH SURFACES AND
RESTROOMS AROUND THE CAMPUS ARE
GETTING ADDITIONAL CLEANING AND
DISS INFECTION.
MARYLAND AND GEORGETOWN
UNIVERSITY HAVE ISSUED
MORATORIUM ON ALL UNIVERSITY
TRAVEL TO CHINA.
AMERICAN UNIVERSITY IS DOING THE
SAME AS WELL AS WORKING TO BRING
HOME NINE STUDENTS CURRENTLY
STUDYING IN BEIJING.
GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY
OFFICIALS TELL US THEY ARE IN
CONTACT WITH THEIR STUDENTS IN
CHINA AND MONITORING THEIR
DEPARTURES AND RETURNS HOME.
THE RAPID SPREAD OF THE VIRUS
AND THE RETURN OF STUDENTS FROM
POTENTIALLY INFECTED AREAS HAS
SOME STUDENTS A LITTLE NERVOUS.
>> DEFINITELY AM KIND OF
CONCERNED ABOUT STUDENTS JUST
RETURNING WITHOUT ANY KIND OF
SCREENING OR ANY KIND OF
PREVENTION MEASURES TO MAKE SURE
THAT STUDENTS ARE SAFE AND THEY
DON'T CARRY THE VIRUS.
>> WE KNOW WE HAVE TO WEAR MASKS
OR WE HAVE TO WASH OUR HANDS,
BUT I REALLY WANT THE UNIVERSITY
LIKE TO DO SOME PROTECTIONS.
>> Reporter: AND THERE ARE NO
CONFIRMED CASES AT THIS POINT OF
THE NOVEL CAR RONA VIRUS IN
D.C., MARYLAND OR VIRGINIA
THOUGH A TEST RESULTS ARE
PENDING ON A FEW PEOPLE WHO ARE
SICK WITH RESPIRATORY ILLNESSES
INCLUDING THAT ONE PERSON AT
GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY THAT WE
TOLD YOU ABOUT ON MONDAY.
I'VE CHECKED WITH THE VIRGINIA
DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH THEY SAY
THEY DO UPDATE THEIR STATISTICS
ON THURSDAY SO WE'LL CONTINUE TO
FOLLOW THAT, AND SEE WHEN WE DO
HAVE THOSE TEST RESULTS.
ALSO, ALL OF THE UNIVERSITIES
THAT WE CONTACTED SAID THAT THEY
DO SYSTEMS IN PLACE TO MONITOR
THESE PEOPLE THAT ARE COMING
BACK FROM CHINA AND THEIR
CONTACTS AND MAKE SURE THAT
THEY'RE STAYING IN TOUCH WITH
THEM IN CASE THEY DO START TO
FEEL ILL AND THEY KNOW WHAT TO
DO.
THE CDC SAYS AT THIS POINT THEY
HAVE 92 POSSIBLE PATIENTS PEOPLE
BEING -- SYMPTOMS BEING
INVESTIGATED IN 32 STATES.
>> MELANIE ALNWICK AT U M.D.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MEANWHILE, FAIRFAX COUNTY POLICE
SAY IT APPEARS THAT ONE MUCH
THEIR SWAT OFFICERS WAS IN FACT
JUSTIFIED IN SHOOTING A DRUG
SUSPECT.
THIS HAPPENED TUESDAY NIGHT
DURING A RAID IN FALLS CHURCH.
DAVID VO WAS SHOT IN THE LEG.
HE'S FACING A NUMBER OF WEAPONS
AND NARCOTICS CHARGES AND THEY
SAY THAT HE WAS POINTING HIS
ASSAULT STYLE RIFLE THIS ONE AT
OFFICERS WHILE THEY WERE EXE
EXECUTING SEARCH AND ARREST
WARRANTS.
THAT OFFICER WHO SHOT VO IS ON
ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE.
>> POLICE IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY LOOKING INTO WHAT THEIR
CALLING A SUSPICIOUS DEATH.
OFFICERS FOUND A WOMAN'S BODY
INSIDE A LAND HAM HOME.
SKYFOX OVER THAT SCENE ON LAMONT
DRIVE LAST NIGHT.
POLICE WORKING A MISSING
PERSON'S CASE WHEN THEY MADE
THAT DISCOVERY, BUT THEY'RE NOT
SAYING IF THE BODY IS RELATED TO
THE INITIAL CASE.
>>> 8:05 NOW.
LET'S GET TO THE LATEST ON THE
PRESIDENT'S IMPEACHMENT TRIAL.
TODAY IS THE SECOND AND FINAL
DAY OF THE QUESTION AND ANSWER
PHASE.
SENATORS POSING DOZENS OF
QUESTIONS TO THE HOUSE MANAGERS
AND THE PRESIDENT'S DEFENSE TEAM
YESTERDAY.
BOTH PARTIES HAVE A TOTAL OF 16
HOURS FOR WRITTEN QUESTIONS.
THERE'S STILL A DIVIDE, THOUGH,
OVER WHETHER THE SENATE SHOULD
HEAR FROM ANY ADDITIONAL
WITNESSES OR DOCUMENTS.
DEMOCRATS ARGUE THE TESTIMONY
SHOULD HAPPEN.
IT'S STILL UNCLEAR IF THERE ARE
ENOUGH VOTES TO BE ABLE TO ISSUE
ANY SUBPOENAS.
>>> FIVE PAST THE HOUR.
TUCKER, WHAT ARE WE DEALING WITH
TODAY?
>> I MEAN, CHILLY TEMPERATURES
TO START THE DAY.
>> OKAY.
>> COLD OUT THERE, AND IT WILL
BE OUR COOLEST DAY OF THE WEEK,
BUT LET'S ALL BE HONEST.
IF WINTER FELT LIKE THIS HE HAVE
YEAR IT WOULDN'T BE SO BAD.
>> WE'D BE OKAY.
I'D BE LIKE COME ON WINTER.
>> YOU'D LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
>> WINTER, WHERE ARE YOU?  I'D
BE LIKE WINTER IS COMING.
>> THAT'S SO SWEET.
>> UM-HMM.
>> OKAY.
NOTHING TOO EXTREME HERE TODAY.
A CHILLY AFTERNOON AN COLD START
TO THE DAY.
31 IN WASHINGTON HERE TO START
YOUR MORNING.
AND MOST OF THE AREA IN THE
UPPER 20S.
YOU CAN SEE THE 28 STILL AT
DULLES AS WE'RE A GOOD 10,
15 DEGREES COLDER THAN WE WERE
24 HOURS AGO.
SATELLITE/RADAR MORE CLOUDINESS
THAN YESTERDAY.
YESTERDAY WE BROKE OUT IN THE
SUN DURING THE AFTERNOON FELT
GREAT.
TODAY, YEAH, SOME MORE HIGH THIN
CLOUDS BUT WE SHOULD KEEP IT DRY
FOR YOUR AFTERNOON HOURS.
SO NO CONCERN WITH ANY RAIN.
DAYTIME HIGHS ONLY IN THE LOW
40S.
SO WORKING OUTDOORS, YOU KNOW,
MAKE SURE YOU GOT THE HEAVIER
JACKET READY TO GO WE WILL NOT
WARM IT UP A WHOLE LOT LATER
THIS AFTERNOON.
YOUR TWO-DAY OUTLOOK,.
>> BIG TWO.
>> THE BIG TWO.
42 TODAY.
48 TOMORROW.
MORE CLOUDS TOMORROW AS WE HAVE
APPROACHING SYSTEM FROM THE
SOUTH AND EAST.
SOUTH AND WEST.
IT WILL PASS US TO THE SOUTH AND
EAST.
AND I'LL LET YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
WILL DO TO OUR WEEKEND AND YOU
MAY HAVE HEARD THE RUMOR MORE,
60S ON THE SEVEN DAY.
LET YOU KNOW WHEN THOSE ARRIVE
COMING UP.
>> ANY SNOW ON THE... ANY SNOW
ON THE SEVEN DAY.
>> NO SNOW ON THE SEVEN DAY.
>> GIVE ME SOME.
>> I KNOW YOU DON'T LIKE IT.
>> I JUST WANTED TO HEAR HIM SAY
NO SNOW.
>> STACEY.
AMEN TO THAT, ALLISON.
>> IT'S A PAIN.
>> I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO NEXT
WEEK.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>>> IT IS JAM PACKED ON THE BAY
BRIDGE.
WESTBOUND THIS MORNING WE HAD
EARLIER CRASH THAT LEFT SOME
MAJOR DELAYS BECAUSE OF THAT
AGAIN THE CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED
BUT IT IS SLOW MOVING BECAUSE OF
THAT CRASH.
STILL TRYING TO RECOVER THERE.
MOVING OVER TO 270 SOUTHBOUND,
IT IS SMOOTH SAILING FROM
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY AS YOU
CAN SEE IT'S ABOUT 50 MINUTES TO
MAKE YOUR WAY.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE ON THE
ROAD ON THE OUTER LOOP THIS
MORNING.
USUAL POCKETS OF TRAFFIC EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WOULD EXPECT FOR THIS
TIME OF THE MORNING.
295 SOUTHBOUND IS REBOUNDING
FROM EARLIER CRASH AS WELL.
THIS WAS AT BENNING ROAD.
AGAIN, THAT HAS BEEN CLEARED AND
IT LOOKS LIKE THINGS ARE BACK TO
NORMAL IN THE CITY THERE.
AND FINALLY ON 66 WESTBOUND
HEADING FROM MANASSAS TO THE
BELTWAY, IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT
60 -- IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT 60
MINUTES ABOUT AN HOUR.
ANY QUESTIONS IN THE MEANTIME
STACEY FOX5 D.C. ON TWITTER.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
>>> NOW TO DEVELOPING STORY OUT
OF PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY WHERE
THE POLICE OFFICER CHARGED WITH
MURDER IN THE SHOOTING DEATH OF
A MAN HANDCUFFED IN HIS POLICE
CAR WILL STAY BEHIND BARS.
DENIED BOND YESTERDAY.
TALKING ABOUT CORPORAL MICHAEL
OWEN ACCUSED OF SHOOTING WILLIAM
GREEN SEVEN TIMES MONDAY NIGHT.
THE PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
STATE'S ATTORNEY SAID SHE WILL
NOW REVIEW ANOTHER DEADLY
SHOOTING CASE FROM 2011 THAT
INVOLVED CORPORAL OWEN.
HE HAS NOT BEEN CHARGED IN THAT
SHOOTING.
NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT WHY HE WAS
NOT WEARING A BODY CAMERA MONDAY
NIGHT AS WELL.
>> WE HAVE PARTIAL DEPLOYMENT OF
BODY CAMERAS ACROSS OREIDE
DEPARTMENT.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN FULLY IN
SUPPORT OF DEPLOYING ADDITIONAL
CODE OF BODY CAMERAS THROUGHOUT
OUR DEPARTMENT.
>> THAT'S THE CHIEF TALKING
ABOUT IT.
HE SAYS OUT OF MORE THAN 1500
OFFICERS IN THE COUNTY, ONLY 80
HAVE THE BODY CAMERAS.
THE CHIEF SUPPORTS THE MOVE.
THE COUNTY CITES BUDGETARY
REASONS FOR NOT ROLLING OUT THE
CAMERAS IN MORE OFFICERS.
>>> HEAD TO NORTHERN VIRGINIA
NOW A BATTLE IS BREWING OVER
TRAFFIC ENFORCEMENT IN A PART OF
FAIRFAX COUNTY.
CRITICS BELIEVE THAT SPEEDERS
ARE TAKING OVER JEFFED TO WAY
IT'S A POPULAR CUT THROUGH NEAR
FORT BELVOIR.
THE COUNTY AND THE ARMY ARE AT
ODDS WHO SHOULD PATROL THIS
ROAD.
BOB BARNARD JOINS US LIVE NOW.
BOB IS LIVE WITH THE DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: HEY, ALLISON,
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
THIS IS A CASE WHERE I THINK
PEOPLE HAVE JUST GROWN
FRUSTRATED BECAUSE THIS IS A
VERY POPULAR ROADWAY.
YOU SEE A LOT OF CARS HERE GOING
OFF TO WORK.
A LOT OF SCHOOL BUSES HEADER TO
GO SCHOOL.
JEFF TODD WAY RUNS SOUTHEAST TO
NORTHWEST HERE BETWEEN ROUTE 1
AND TELEGRAPH ROAD.
I CAN SHOW YOU A MAP AN AERIAL
MAP OF THIS.
THIS IS A ROUGHLY SIX-YEAR-OLD
ROADWAY THAT WAS OPENED IN 2014
TO HELP EASE TRAFFIC IN THIS
AREA.
OTHER CUT THROUGHS AT FORT
BELVOIR WERE CLOSED AFTER 9/11.
THE PROBLEM IS THIS.
AND YOU SEE, YOU KNOW, BEFORE
DAWN AND AT NIGHT IT'S A VERY
DARK ROAD.
THERE ARE REALLY NO STREET
LIGHTS HERE, AND IT'S A 40-MILE
AN HOUR ROADWAY BUT THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE AROUND HERE SAY PEOPLE
ARE SPEEDING CONSTANTLY.
THERE ARE ACCIDENTS, AND
BASICALLY, THE ARMY HAS
JURISDICTION.
THE ARMY CORPS OF ENGINEERS HAS
JURISDICTION OVER THIS ROADWAY.
THE FOLKS WHO LIVE HERE AND
COUNTY OFFICIALS FAIRFAX COUNTY
OFFICIALS WANT FAIRFAX COUNTY
POLICE TO START ENFORCING THE
TRAFFIC LAWS AND TAKE OVER.
HERE'S SOME OF THE REACTION FROM
SOME WHO LIVE AND TAKE THIS
ROADWAY.
>> SOMETIMES I HAVE TO WAIT 15
MINUTES TO CROSS THE ROAD.
>> IT'S HARD TO MAKE YOUR LEFT
TURN AND PEOPLE ARE WALKING,
CROSSING THE STREET, CARS ARE
COMING FAST.
>> Reporter: NOW, DAN STORK IS
THE MOUNT VERNON SUPERVISOR WITH
THE FAIRFAX COUNTY BOARD OF
SUPERVISORS.
HE SAYS HE WANTS THE AREA AND
HE'S ASKED THEM TO TAKE
IMMEDIATE ACTION TO TRANSFER
JURISDICTION OVER THIS ROADWAY.
JEFF TODD WAY TWO FAIRFAX COUNTY
POLICE HE SAYS THE MILITARY HAS
MANY OTHER PRIORITIES AND THAT
THIS ROADWAY HAS BEEN IGNORED
FOR FAR TOO LONG.
GUYS?
>> BOB, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE'LL SEE WHAT COMES OUT OF T
THAT.
>> THE AUTHOR OF THIS MONTH'S
OPRAH BOOK CLUB BOOK IS CALLING
OFF HER BOOK TOUR.
SHE'S LOCAL.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK NOW AT THE
DECISION TO CALL OFF THE BOOK
TOUR AND HER TIES TO THE D.C.
AREA.
>> AND KOBE BRYANT'S WIDOW
VANESSA BREAKING HER SILENCE
NOW.
WHAT SHE SAID ON SOCIAL MEDIA
ABOUT THE SUDDEN AND TRAGIC
PASSING OF BOTH HER HUSBAND AND
HER DAUGHTER.
♪
♪♪
>> TUCKER IS KEEPING AN EYE ON
COLD TEMPERATURES OUT THERE THIS
MORNING.
BUT WE HAVE A BEAUTIFUL SKY.
HOW CHILLY IS IT GOING TO BE THE
REST OF THE DAY?  I KNOW SOME OF
YOU IN THE 20S RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL GET AN UPDATE.
STACEY HAS A LOOK AT THE ROADS
AND METRO AS WE PEER OUT OVER
NORTHWEST D.C.
IT'S 8:11.
♪
♪♪
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Los necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Get what works for you. And pay
for what you want.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Mix and match your perfect Fios
plan.
Only on Verizon.
>> LOCAL AUTHOR WHOSE NOVEL WAS
RECENTLY PROMOTED BY OPRAH
WINFREY BEING FORCED TO CANCEL
HIS BOOKSTORE NOW.
JANINE CUMMINGS PUBLISHER SAYS
IT'S DUE TO SAFETY CONCERNS.
THE BOOK IS AMERICAN DIRT TELLS
THE STORY AVENUE MEXICAN MIGRANT
WHO LEAVES HER HOME WITH HER SON
TO ESCAPE A DRUG CARTEL.
BUT THE BOOK HAS BEEN CRITICIZED
BY SOME WHO FEEL THE NOVEL
CONTAINS STEREO TYPICAL
DEPICTIONS OF MEXICANS.
CUMMINGS IS A GAITHERSBURG HIGH
SCHOOL ALUM.
SPENT FIVE YEARS WRITING THE
BOOK.
OPRAH RECENTLY ANNOUNCED
AMERICAN DIRT WOULD BE THE NEXT
READ IN HER BOOK CLUB.
>> HUNDREDS OF DRONES WILL NOT
BE TAKING TO THE SKY.
YESTERDAY THE DEPARTMENT OF
INTERIOR MADE THAT ANNOUNCEMENT
GROUNDING ALMOST 800 OF THE N
NON-EMERGENCY DRONES SIGHT
CITING CONCERNS OVER CYBER
SECURITY.
BACK IN OCTOBER, THE DEPARTMENT
OF INTERIOR PREVIOUSLY GROUNDED
CHINESE MADE DRONES IN ITS
FLEET.
DRONES ARE USED IN VARIETY OF
GOVERNMENT MISSIONS INCLUDING
SURVEILLANCE OF FEDERAL LANDS
AND RESCUE OPERATIONS.
>>> 8:15 RIGHT NOW.
GOOD MORNING, TUCKER BARNES.
>> I FEEL LIKE I NEED A DRONE.
THAT'S SOMETHING MISSING IN MY
LIFE.
I'VE NEED MY OWN DRONE.
>> THINK ABOUT WERE YOU'D DO
WITH IT.
>> I'M THINKING ABOUT IT NOW.
>> AND.
>> ALL KINDS OF THINGS.
>> OKAY.
>> FOLLOW ME.
>> SOUND LIKE PETER GRIFFIN
RIGHT NOW.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
20S NORTH AND WEST.
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
25 IN GAITHERSBURG.
20S NORTH AND WEST.
MANASSAS 25 DEGREES.
25 IN GAITHERSBURG.
YEAH, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT GOTTEN
MANASSAS 25 DEGREES.
COLD OVERNIGHT.
YEAH, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT GOTTEN
NUMBERS ARE ABOUT 10 DEGREES
COLD OVERNIGHT.
COLDER THAN WHERE WE WERE AT 24
NUMBERS ARE ABOUT 10 DEGREES
HOURS AGO.
COLDER THAN WHERE WE WERE AT 24
TODAY WILL BE THE COOLEST DAY OF
HOURS AGO.
THE WEEK HIGHS ONLY IN THE LOW
TODAY WILL BE THE COOLEST DAY OF
40S, AND MIX OF CLOUDS AND SUN
THE WEEK HIGHS ONLY IN THE LOW
EXPECTED TODAY.
40S, AND MIX OF CLOUDS AND SUN
AND CERTAINLY MORE CLOUDS THAN
EXPECTED TODAY.
WHAT WE GOT YESTERDAY AFTERNOON
AND CERTAINLY MORE CLOUDS THAN
WHEN WE BROKE OUT IN FULL
WHAT WE GOT YESTERDAY AFTERNOON
SUNSHINE.
WHEN WE BROKE OUT IN FULL
SO AREA OF LOW PRESSURE OFF THE
SUNSHINE.
CAROLINA COAST BRING SOME RAINS
SO AREA OF LOW PRESSURE OFF THE
TO EXTREME NORTH CAROLINA.
CAROLINA COAST BRING SOME RAINS
AND AS THAT PUSHES AWAY FROM THE
TO EXTREME NORTH CAROLINA.
REGION, OUR CONDITIONS SHOULD
AND AS THAT PUSHES AWAY FROM THE
GRADUALLY IMPROVE BUT WE'VE GOT
REGION, OUR CONDITIONS SHOULD
SOME CLOUDS TO START THE DAY I
GRADUALLY IMPROVE BUT WE'VE GOT
THINK WE'LL KIND OF REMAIN
SOME CLOUDS TO START THE DAY I
PARTLY SUNNY HERE LATER THIS
THINK WE'LL KIND OF REMAIN
AFTERNOON.
PARTLY SUNNY HERE LATER THIS
ALL RIGHT.
AFTERNOON.
LET'S TALK WEEKEND.
ALL RIGHT.
TOMORROW MORE CLOUDS UPPER 40S
LET'S TALK WEEKEND.
AND THEN WE'LL KICK OFF OUR
TOMORROW MORE CLOUDS UPPER 40S
WEEKEND WITH SOME RAIN SHOWERS
AND THEN WE'LL KICK OFF OUR
AT LEAST THE POSSIBILITY OF RAIN
WEEKEND WITH SOME RAIN SHOWERS
SHOWERS ACROSS THE AREA.
AT LEAST THE POSSIBILITY OF RAIN
THE FIRST HALF OF SATURDAY.
SHOWERS ACROSS THE AREA.
AS THAT AREA OF LOW PRESSURE
THE FIRST HALF OF SATURDAY.
GETS EAST OF US DURING THE
AS THAT AREA OF LOW PRESSURE
AFTERNOON HOURS, WE SHOULD GET
GETS EAST OF US DURING THE
SOME CLEARING AND THEN BE IN FOR
AFTERNOON HOURS, WE SHOULD GET
A NICE DAY FOR SUPER BOWL SU
SOME CLEARING AND THEN BE IN FOR
SUNDAY.
A NICE DAY FOR SUPER BOWL SU
DAYTIME HIGHS IN THE LOW 50S AS
SUNDAY.
HIGH PRESSURE BUILDS IN FROM THE
DAYTIME HIGHS IN THE LOW 50S AS
SOUTH AND WEST.
HIGH PRESSURE BUILDS IN FROM THE
THAT SAME AREA OF HIGH PRESSURE
SOUTH AND WEST.
IS GOING DELIVER 60S AROUND HERE
THAT SAME AREA OF HIGH PRESSURE
BY EARLY NEXT WEEK.
IS GOING DELIVER 60S AROUND HERE
FEBRUARY HEAT WAVE!
BY EARLY NEXT WEEK.
>> 60S AROUND MONDAY, TUESDAY,
FEBRUARY HEAT WAVE!
WEDNESDAY.
>> 60S AROUND MONDAY, TUESDAY,
>> ALL RIGHT.
WEDNESDAY.
I'M GOING TO WRAP I STACEY, GOOD
>> ALL RIGHT.
MORNING.
I'M GOING TO WRAP I STACEY, GOOD
>>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
MORNING.
HEADS UP IN THE FORESTVILLE
>>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
AREA.
HEADS UP IN THE FORESTVILLE
WE'VE GOT A SITUATION ON THE
AREA.
INNER LOOP INVOLVING A CRASH
WE'VE GOT A SITUATION ON THE
THAT THIS IS RIGHT AFTER
INNER LOOP INVOLVING A CRASH
MARYLAND FOUR.
THAT THIS IS RIGHT AFTER
THE TWO RIGHT LANES ARE BLOCKED
MARYLAND FOUR.
BECAUSE OF THAT.
THE TWO RIGHT LANES ARE BLOCKED
SO YOU'LL HAVE SOME DELAYS AS
BECAUSE OF THAT.
YOU MAKE YOUR WAY AROUND THE
SO YOU'LL HAVE SOME DELAYS AS
TEMPLE HILLS AREA.
YOU MAKE YOUR WAY AROUND THE
SPEAKING OF THE INNER LOOP
TEMPLE HILLS AREA.
YOU'VE ALSO HAVE DELAYS FROM
SPEAKING OF THE INNER LOOP
SAINT BARNABAS ROAD ALL THE WAY
YOU'VE ALSO HAVE DELAYS FROM
TO THE WILSON BRIDGE.
SAINT BARNABAS ROAD ALL THE WAY
DEFINITELY SLOWING YOU DOWN AND
TO THE WILSON BRIDGE.
AFFECTING YOUR COMMUTE.
DEFINITELY SLOWING YOU DOWN AND
95 TO THE LEGION BRIDGE,
AFFECTING YOUR COMMUTE.
HOWEVER, IS SLOWLY BUT STEADY
95 TO THE LEGION BRIDGE,
MOVING.
HOWEVER, IS SLOWLY BUT STEADY
NO MAJOR ISSUES THERE.
MOVING.
395 NORTHBOUND LOOKS GOOD FROM
NO MAJOR ISSUES THERE.
EDSALL ROAD TO THE 14th STREET
395 NORTHBOUND LOOKS GOOD FROM
BRIDGE.
EDSALL ROAD TO THE 14th STREET
AND AS WE LOOK AT 270
BRIDGE.
SOUTHBOUND, IT WILL TAKE YOU
AND AS WE LOOK AT 270
ABOUT AN HOUR TO MAKE IT FROM
SOUTHBOUND, IT WILL TAKE YOU
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY.
ABOUT AN HOUR TO MAKE IT FROM
LOOKING AT THE OUTER LOOP, IT
FREDERICK TO THE BELTWAY.
HAS BEEN PRETTY TIGHT ALL
LOOKING AT THE OUTER LOOP, IT
MORNING WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE ON
HAS BEEN PRETTY TIGHT ALL
THE ROAD.
MORNING WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE ON
YOU'VE GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS OF
THE ROAD.
TRAFFIC.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS OF
IT'S A STEADY RIDE ON 95 NO
TRAFFIC.
PROBLEMS JUST YET ON THE
IT'S A STEADY RIDE ON 95 NO
BALTIMORE WASHINGTON PARKWAY.
PROBLEMS JUST YET ON THE
AND AS WE LOOK AT 295
BALTIMORE WASHINGTON PARKWAY.
SOUTHBOUND, WE HAVE A CRASH
AND AS WE LOOK AT 295
EARLIER.
SOUTHBOUND, WE HAVE A CRASH
THIS WAS RIGHT AT BENNING ROAD.
EARLIER.
THAT CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED OF
THIS WAS RIGHT AT BENNING ROAD.
THE NO MAJOR RESIDUAL DELAYS
THAT CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED OF
THUS FAR BECAUSE OF THAT.
THE NO MAJOR RESIDUAL DELAYS
66 WESTBOUND IS A LITTLE JAMMED
THUS FAR BECAUSE OF THAT.
THIS MORNING FROM MANASSAS TO
66 WESTBOUND IS A LITTLE JAMMED
THE BELTWAY.
THIS MORNING FROM MANASSAS TO
IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT AN HOUR
THE BELTWAY.
AND THEN FINALLY, 95 NORTHBOUND
IT WILL TAKE YOU ABOUT AN HOUR
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY
AND THEN FINALLY, 95 NORTHBOUND
TRAFFIC IS JUST ABOUT AT SPEED.
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
TRAFFIC IS JUST ABOUT AT SPEED.
BACK TO YOU AT THE DESK.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
♪
BACK TO YOU AT THE DESK.
>> 8:18 NOW.
♪
KOBE BRYANT'S WIDOW VANESSA
>> 8:18 NOW.
BREAKING HER SILENCE ON THE
KOBE BRYANT'S WIDOW VANESSA
DEATH OF HER HUSBAND AND THEIR
BREAKING HER SILENCE ON THE
DAUGHTER.
DEATH OF HER HUSBAND AND THEIR
IN A LENGTHY INSTAGRAM POST
DAUGHTER.
VANESSA BRYANT SAYS SHE AND HER
IN A LENGTHY INSTAGRAM POST
THREE SURVIVING DAUGHTERS ARE
VANESSA BRYANT SAYS SHE AND HER
COMPLETELY DEVASTATED BY THIS
THREE SURVIVING DAUGHTERS ARE
TRAGEDY AD ADDING THAT THERE ART
COMPLETELY DEVASTATED BY THIS
ENOUGH WORDS TO DESCRIBE THEIR
TRAGEDY AD ADDING THAT THERE ART
PAIN.
ENOUGH WORDS TO DESCRIBE THEIR
BRYANT WENT ON TO SAY SHE TAKES
PAIN.
COMFORT IN KNOWING HAD KOBE AND
BRYANT WENT ON TO SAY SHE TAKES
GIGI WERE DEEPLY LOVED.
COMFORT IN KNOWING HAD KOBE AND
>> KOBE WILL BE HONORED DURING
GIGI WERE DEEPLY LOVED.
SUPER BOWL LIV ON SUNDAY.
>> KOBE WILL BE HONORED DURING
COMMISSIONER GOODELL SAID THE
SUPER BOWL LIV ON SUNDAY.
LEAGUE WILL PAY TRIBUTE TO
COMMISSIONER GOODELL SAID THE
BRYANT IN IN FORM DURING THE
LEAGUE WILL PAY TRIBUTE TO
GAME ANNOUNCING THE NEWS DURING
BRYANT IN IN FORM DURING THE
THE PRE-SUPER BOWL PRESS
GAME ANNOUNCING THE NEWS DURING
CONFERENCE MUCH BRYANT'S FORMER
THE PRE-SUPER BOWL PRESS
LAKERS TEAMMATE SHAQUILLE O'NEAL
CONFERENCE MUCH BRYANT'S FORMER
WILL HONOR HIM DURING SUPER BOWL
LAKERS TEAMMATE SHAQUILLE O'NEAL
WEEKEND.
WILL HONOR HIM DURING SUPER BOWL
AS THE WORLD CONTINUES TO HONOR
WEEKEND.
THE MEMORY OF THE LATE KOBE
AS THE WORLD CONTINUES TO HONOR
BRYANT, THE TRIBUTES HAVEN'T
THE MEMORY OF THE LATE KOBE
BEEN LIMITED TO JUST BASKETBALL.
BRYANT, THE TRIBUTES HAVEN'T
WASHINGTON CAPITALS STAR ALEX
BEEN LIMITED TO JUST BASKETBALL.
OVECHKIN PAID HOMAGE TO THE
WASHINGTON CAPITALS STAR ALEX
LAKERS LEGEND LAST NIGHT BY
OVECHKIN PAID HOMAGE TO THE
WEARING NUMBER 24 ON HIS WARMUP
LAKERS LEGEND LAST NIGHT BY
JERSEY.
WEARING NUMBER 24 ON HIS WARMUP
HE WORE IT BEFORE THE GAME
JERSEY.
AGAINST THE NASHVILLE PREDATORS.
HE WORE IT BEFORE THE GAME
OVECHKIN TYPICALLY WEARS NUMBER
AGAINST THE NASHVILLE PREDATORS.
EIGHT THE JERSEY BRYANT STARTED
OVECHKIN TYPICALLY WEARS NUMBER
HIS NBA CAREER WITH, BUT MADE
EIGHT THE JERSEY BRYANT STARTED
THE PRE-GAME SWITCH TO NUMBER 24
HIS NBA CAREER WITH, BUT MADE
IN ORDER TO SHOW RESPECT TO
THE PRE-GAME SWITCH TO NUMBER 24
BRYANT.
IN ORDER TO SHOW RESPECT TO
THE JERSEY WAS SIGNED AND WILL
BRYANT.
BE AUCTIONED OFF TO BENEFIT THE
THE JERSEY WAS SIGNED AND WILL
KOBE AND VANESSA BRYANT FAMILY
BE AUCTIONED OFF TO BENEFIT THE
FOUNDATION.
KOBE AND VANESSA BRYANT FAMILY
CLASSY MOVE RIGHT THERE.
FOUNDATION.
>>> VIRGINIA SENATE APPROVED
CLASSY MOVE RIGHT THERE.
LEGISLATION WOULD ROLL BACK
>>> VIRGINIA SENATE APPROVED
RESTRICTIONS ON ABORTION.
LEGISLATION WOULD ROLL BACK
CLOSER LOOK AT THE CHANGES.
RESTRICTIONS ON ABORTION.
>> TUCKER HAS DETAILS ABOUT THE
CLOSER LOOK AT THE CHANGES.
LAST CHILLY THURSDAY IN JANUARY.
>> TUCKER HAS DETAILS ABOUT THE
STACEY HAS YOUR DRIVE TIMES
LAST CHILLY THURSDAY IN JANUARY.
COMING UP AS WELL.
STACEY HAS YOUR DRIVE TIMES
>> AHEAD MIKE THOMAS LIVE ON
COMING UP AS WELL.
LOCATION WITH THE WASHINGTON
>> AHEAD MIKE THOMAS LIVE ON
JUSTICE.
LOCATION WITH THE WASHINGTON
OH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
JUSTICE.
>> HEY, MIKE.
OH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>>> HEY, GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
>> HEY, MIKE.
GOOD MORNING, STEVE.
>>> HEY, GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
WE ARE GETTING YOU READY FOR
GOOD MORNING, STEVE.
D.C.'S NEWEST E SPORTS TEAM.
WE ARE GETTING YOU READY FOR
WHAT IS E SPORTS?  HOW BIG IS
D.C.'S NEWEST E SPORTS TEAM.
IT?  WE'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
WHAT IS E SPORTS?  HOW BIG IS
THAT AND HOW YOU CAN CHECK OUT
IT?  WE'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
AND SUPPORT YOUR LOCAL TEAM, THE
THAT AND HOW YOU CAN CHECK OUT
WASHINGTON JUSTICE.
AND SUPPORT YOUR LOCAL TEAM, THE
THAT'S COMING UP RIGHT AFTER THE
WASHINGTON JUSTICE.
BREAK.
THAT'S COMING UP RIGHT AFTER THE
WE'LL SEE YOU HERE IN JUST A FEW
BREAK.
MINUTES.
WE'LL SEE YOU HERE IN JUST A FEW
♪
MINUTES.
♪♪
822.
LET'S GO TO ARLINGTON COUNTY
POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING AFTER A
HATE SYMBOL DRAWING WAS FOUND AT
A MIDDLE SCHOOL.
A STUDENT REPORTEDLY DREW A
SWASTIKA ON A PIECE OF PAPER
GAVE IT TO CLASSMATE AT THOMAS
JEFFERSON MIDDLE SCHOOL.
STAFF NOTIFIED THE SCHOOL
RESOURCE OFFICER.
THE PRINCIPAL SENT HOME A LETTER
TO PARENTS SAYING THE
ADMINISTRATION MET WITH THAT
STUDENT INVOLVED AND SAYS
INTOLERANCE NOT ACCEPTED AT THAT
SCHOOL.
OR IN THE DISTRICT.
>>> VIRGINIA SENATE APPROVED
LEGISLATION THAT WOULD ROLL BACK
RESTRICTIONS ON ABORTION.
THE NEW DEMOCRATIC MAJORITY
WANTS TO GET RID OF REQUIREMENTS
INCLUDING A 24 HOUR WAITING
PERIOD BEFORE AN ABORTION AND A
REQUIREMENT THAT WOMEN SEEKING
AN ABORTION UNDERGO ULTRASOUND
AND COUNSELING THE HOUSE PASSED
SIMILAR MEASURE EACH CHAMBER
STILL WOULD NEED TO PASS THE
OTHER'S VERSION.
♪
>>> ALL RIGHTY.
GOOD MORNING TO BOTH OF YOU.
DYNAMIC DUO OF WEATHER AND
TRAFFIC.
>> GOOD MORNING.
PRACTICAL INFORMATION.
I'M GETTING TWEETS CAN I WASH MY
CAR TODAY?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
GO WASH YOUR CAR.
>> UM-HMM.
>> AND WILL THERE BE ANY RAIN IN
THE NEAR FUTURE?
>> NOT TILL SATURDAY.
JUST A FEW SHOWERS.
>> NOT BAD THEN.
>> YOU TIME IT RIGHT I WONDER
COULD YOU LATHER OF IT UP AND
LET MOTHER NATURE WASH IT OFF.
>> ALLISON, I LOVE YOU.
>> YES.
YOU'D HAVE TO DO THAT SATURDAY
MORNING.
GET IT JUST RIGHT.
>> THINKING IF YOU TAKE THE
EFFORT TO LATTER YOU COULD ALSO
RINSE IT.
>> WHY WASTE THE WATER IF MOTHER
NATURE IS GOING TO DO IT.
>> MOTHER NATURE, STEVE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO WEIGH INTO
THIS CONVERSATION.
THEY'RE ALWAYS RIGHT.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
YEAH, YOU'LL BE JUST FINE.
HI.
>> HI.
>> YOU'LL BE JUST FINE WASHING I
DON'T CAR TODAY ALTHOUGH IT WILL
BE CHILLY OUT THERE LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
HIGHS ONLY BE IN THE LOW 40S AND
YOU SEE THE HIGH THIN CLOUDINESS
THAT'S ASSOCIATED WITH SOME RAIN
SHOWERS AND A STORM SYSTEM TO
OUR SOUTH AND EAST THIS MORNING.
31 TO START YOUR DAY.
EVERYBODY BELOW FREEZING OUT
THERE EARLY.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH AND EAST
AT 8 MILES AN HOUR.
LOOKING AT OUR SATELLITE PICTURE
YOU CAN SEE THE RAIN SHOWERS
ALONG THE CAROLINA COAST AND A
FEW LIGHT SNOW FLURRIES BACK
INTO WEST VIRGINIA AND NORTHERN
VIRGINIA THERE.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S TOUCHING
THE GROUND AND AGAIN THAT'S THE
BACK PIECE OF ENERGY HERE GIVING
US CLOUD COVER.
MORE CLOUDS THAN YESTERDAY.
A COOL DAY.
HIGHS ONLY IN THE LOW 40S BUT A
RAIN FREE AFTERNOON FOR US SO IF
YOU WANT TO WASH THE CAR IF
YOU'LL BE WORKING OUTDOORS
YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE LATER TO
TODAY.
IT WILL JUST BE OUR COOLEST DAY
OF THE WEEK WE'LL REBOUND THE
TEMPERATURES BY TOMORROW
AFTERNOON BACK NAT UPPER 40S.
LOOKING FOR RAIN SHOWERS, I
THINK FIRST HALF OF SATURDAY
WILL PROBABLY HAVE SOME SHOWER
ACTIVITY BEST CHANCES WILL BE
SOUTHERN MARYLAND LOWER EASTERN
SHORES THAT STORM PASSES TO OUR
EAST.
AND THEN SUPER BOWL LOOKS GOOD
FOR YOUR PARTY.
STACEY.
>> YES.
>> YOU HAVEN'T INVITED ME TO YET
AND 60S, MONDAY TUESDAY AND
WEDNESDAY.
>> DID I SAY 60.
>> I DID.
>> YES, DID YOU.
YOU SAID TODAY WAS THE COLDEST
DAY THURSDAY FAR, RIGHT.
>> COLDEST DAY OF THIS WEEK.
>> OF THIS WEEK.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
TUCKER, I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU
THAT.
BECAUSE I'LL TELL YOU IN A
MINUTE.
FIRST I WANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT
THIS.
DO YOU THINK OF SOUTH CAPITAL
STREET NORTHBOUND A CRASH
BLOCKING EVIDENT LEFT AT I
STREET SOUTHEAST.
WHAT I WANTED TO TELL YOU IS
THAT YOU ARE CORRECT ABOUT IT
BEING REALLY CHILLY.
WE'VE GOT A WARNING IN NORTHEAST
D.C. WE'VE GOT ICY CONDITIONS ON
BURROUGHS AVENUE AT DIVISION
AVENUE.
WE'VE GOT SALT TRUCKS ON THE
SCENE.
>> I WONDER IF WATER IS LEAKING
SOMEWHERE.
>> YEAH.
>> FREEZING ON THE PAVEMENT
THERE.
>> PLEASE USE CAUTION IN THAT
AREA.
AND THEN FINALLY, JUST WANT TO
GIVE YOU HEADS UP REGARDING THE
INNER LOOP.
RIGHT IN THE FORESTVILLE AREA.
WE'VE GOT THE TWO RIGHT LANES
BLOCKED AFTER MARYLAND FOUR
BECAUSE OF A CRASH.
SO DEFINITELY GOING TO TIE UP A
BIT THIS MORNING.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>>> OH, OKAY.
THANK YOU STACEY.
THE GOVERNOR OF MARYLAND WANTS
TO CHANGE WHEN THE SCHOOL YEAR
STARTS.
DETAILS ON HIS EFFORTS TO HAVE
EVERY SCHOOL START THE SAME DAY.
>> SPRING BREAK WILL BE HERE
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW TO PLAN
THE PERFECT GET AWAY.
WE GOT TRAVEL TIPS COMING UP
NEXT.
♪
♪♪
Uh oh! - What?
I think I forgot to
lock my Buick.
Got it.
I bet you lunch you can't
make it in there.
I'm thinkin' sushi.
Alexa, ask Buick to
start my SUV.
(SUV starts)
You can do that?
-You can do that?
Yeah, with a Buick.
What?
At the heart of every Buick SUV
...is you.
Find out why Buick is number one
in dealer sales and service
satisfaction.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick SUV models
plus current eligible GM owners
get $750 purchase allowance.
HOW ABOUT WE SAY GOOD MORNING TO
SAINT MARY'S COUNTY AND START
YOU OFF WITH LIFE PICTURE FROM
LEONARDTOWN THIS MORNING.
GOOD MORNING TO EVERYBODY THERE.
HOPE YOU HAVE A FANTASTIC DAY
TODAY.
>>> SUNSHINE ALL OVER THE DMV.
MARYLAND GOVERNOR LARRY HOGAN
RENEWING HIS EFFORT TO FORCE
EVERY SCHOOL IN MARYLAND TO HAVE
THE SAME START DATE AFTER LABOR
DAY.
NOW THIS HAS BEEN POLITICAL TUG
OF WAR BETWEEN STATE AND LOCAL
LEADERS.
SUPPORTERS SAY LONGER SUMMER
BREAKS GIVE FAMILIES MORE TIME
TOGETHER.
CRITICS SAY IT SHORT CHANGES
EDUCATION.
THE BILL WOULD REQUIRE
LEGISLATIVE APPROVAL AND I CAN
TELL YOU FROM TALKING WITH
MONTGOMERY COUNTY OFFICIALS AT
LEAST ONE OF THEM THIS MORNING
THEY'RE SAYING MONTGOMERY COUNTY
STILL PLANS ON STARTING BEFORE
LABOR DAY.
AL, KEEP AN EYE ON IT AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> SOUNDS GOOD, STEVE THANKS.
>>> WELL, SPRING SPEAKING OF
SPRING BREAK AND DAYS OFF FROM
SCHOOL STILL MORE THAN SIX WEEKS
AWAY.
BUT YOU SHOULD START PLANNING
RIGHT NOW SO HERE TO TALK ABOUT
THE LATEST HOTTEST DESTINATIONS
IF YOU TRAVEL PRODUCTS PRODUCT
JOURNALIST WHO JUST CAME FROM
THE NEW YORK TIMES TRAVEL SHOW
WE REMAIN JEALOUS OF EVERYTHING
THAT YOU DO.
HOW WAS THE SHOW?
>> THE SHOW WAS AMAZING.
>> AT THE SHOW WHAT IS IT LIKE
PLACES TO GO?
>> YEAH.
>> PLACES TO GO.
>> PRODUCTS.
>> PRODUCT AS LITTLE BIT OF
EVERYTHING.
OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, THE ECONOMY
IS DOING WELL.
>> YEAH.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE LOOKING
TO TRAVEL THIS YEAR.
>> WHAT WAS THE COOLEST THING
THERE THIS YEAR.
>> COOLEST THING THERE THIS
YEAR.
>> I THINK IT WAS INTERESTING TO
SEE SOME OF THE NON TRADITIONAL
DESTINATIONS WE'RE SEEING A LOT
MORE PEOPLE HEADING OUT TOWARDS
ASIA AND PLACES LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH.
THAT WAS KIND OF NICE AND THEY A
LOT OF TRADITIONAL DANCERS AND
THINGS THERE TO TRY TO TRACT
YOU.
>> RIGHT.
REALLY ENJOYED SEEING THAT.
>> WHEN YOU SAY ASIA, HUGE,
HUGE, HUGE, HUGE --
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT BEFORE WE
MOVE ON, ADDRESSING ANY CONCERNS
MAYBE PEOPLE ARE A LITTLE
FREAKED OUT NOW ABOUT TRAVELING
WITH THE CORONAVIRUS.
>> YES.
I THINK PEOPLE HAVE EVERY RIGHT
TO BE CONCERNED OBVIOUSLY.
THE CDC IS SAYING THAT AMERICAN
TRAVELERS HAVE VERY LITTLE RISK
IF ANY ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE TO
THE GOING TO CHINA.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOW, SPRING BREAK IS SIX TO
12 WEEKS AWAY DEPENDING OH AND
WHEN YOUR SPRING BREAK IS.
THINGS COULD CHANGE.
YOU KNOW, PAY ATTENTION TO
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> UM-HMM.
>> PAY ATTENTION TO PUBLIC
HEALTH ALERTS.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU ARE TRAVELING
I BROUGHT MY SANITIZING GEL AND
MY WIPES OVER THERE.
YOU KNOW THE BEST THING TO DO
JUST PRACTICE GOOD HYGIENE.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'D BE MORE CONCERNED ABOUT
THE FLU VIRUS GOING AROUND RIGHT
NOW.
>> IT'S GOING AROUND IN HERE,
TOO.
>> DON'T WORRY, I'M GOOD.
I GOT MY FLU SHOT.
>> GOOD.
LET'S TALK ABOUT PLACES TO GO
AND WHAT WE NEED TO DO NOW IF WE
KNOW WE'LL TRAVEL.
WE NEED TO START BOOKING NOW,
RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
THIS IS THE SWEET SPOT.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW YOU'RE SEEING
SOME GOOD RATES AND GOOD OPT
OPTIONS.
AS WE GET CLOSER TO SPRING BREAK
YOU'LL SEE THE PRICES GOING UP
AND SEE YOUR OPTIONS NARROW.
LOOK AND BOOK NOW ONE OF THE KEY
MESSAGES I HAVE OUT THERE OF THE
THE OTHER AND THAT YOU WANTED TO
MAKE SURE YOU THOROUGHLY
UNDERSTAND THE DESTINATION
YOU'RE HEADING TO WEEK OF SPRING
BREAK A LOT DIFFERENT SOME
PLACES THAN IT IS THE REST OF
THE YEAR.
>> OH YEAH.
>> KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GETTING 92.
THE OTHER THING AND YOU KNOW,
KIND OF RELATES TO THE
CORONAVIRUS AND THINGS, IF
THINGS POP UP GET THAT TRAVEL
INSURANCE.
IT'S ONLY A FEW EXTRA DOLLARS.
>> SHOULD WE GET IT?
>> YES IT'S ONLY A FEW EXTRA
DOLLARS.
GET IT.
PEACE OF MIND.
>> OKAY.
>> RUN INTO PROBLEMS.
>> I'M GOING TO GET IT.
>> GET IT.
>> YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
NOTHING HAPPENS.
I'M SO MAD.
>> YOU'RE SO MAD.
>> SUPPOSE SOMETHING DID HAPPEN.
>> IF SOMETHING DOES HAPPEN.
IN TERMS OF DESTINATIONS, I'M
HOT ON A COUPLE DIFFERENT
PLACES.
ONE, DOMINICAN REPUBLIC.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE DR.
>> COMPLETELY CLEARED.
NO ISSUES THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK PROBLEM WAS YOU HAD A
FEW DEATHS IN A MICROSCOPE GOT
PUT ON THAT.
>> YES.
>> IF WE LOOKED AT THE NUMBER OF
PEOPLE WHO DIED IN CANADA WE'D
BE SHOCKED BY THE NUMBER OF
AMERICANS WHO DIED WHILE
VACATIONING.
>> THE FBI INVESTIGATED
COMPLETELY CLEAR.
WHAT THAT MEANS AWESOME DEALS.
PEOPLE STAYED AWAY.
>> UM-HMM.
>> PRICES DROPPED.
WE NEED TO GO BACK DOWN THERE.
SAME THING WITH THE BAHAMAS.
HURRICANE DORIAN CAME THROUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> DEVASTATED THE BAHAMAS.
EVERYONE I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
BEST WAY TO HELP GO BE A
TOURIST.
>> HELP THE ECONOMY.
>> NASSAU WAS NOT HURT AT ALL.
>> OKAY.
PARADISE ISLAND NOT HURT AT ALL.
>> WHICH IS WHERE A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE GO ANYWHERE
WAY.
>> GREAT OPTION FOR THIS CALLED
BAHAMAS PARADISE CRUISE LINE.
>> OKAY.
>> STARTS OUT IN WEST PALM BE
BEACH.
DO YOU TWO DAY CRUISE OVER TO
THE BAHAMAS YOU CAN ELECT TO
STAY IN THE BAHAMAS OR CRUISE
BACK THE FOR FOLKS TEMPTED TO
THINK ABOUT GOING ON A CRUISE
BUT AREN'T SO --
>> NEVER BEEN ON A CRUISE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN.
I REALLY DO WANT TO GO.
>> GREAT WAY TO DO THAT.
GO DOWN EXPERIENCE THAT CRUISING
BUT YOU'RE NOT CAPTURED FOR
SEVEN, EIGHT DAYS.
>> RIGHT.
>> PLUS.
>> BUT YOU GET THAT EXPERIENCE
>> RIGHT.
AND YOU CAN THEN BOOK END STAY A
>> BUT YOU GET THAT EXPERIENCE
FEW EXTRA DAYS IN THE BAHAMAS
AND YOU CAN THEN BOOK END STAY A
STAY IN WEST PALM BEACH.
FEW EXTRA DAYS IN THE BAHAMAS
THAT'S WHERE SPRING BREAK
STAY IN WEST PALM BEACH.
TRAINING IS HAPPENING.
THAT'S WHERE SPRING BREAK
IF YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE A VERY
TRAINING IS HAPPENING.
EARLY SPRING BREAK MAYBE CATCH A
IF YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE A VERY
BASEBALL GAME.
EARLY SPRING BREAK MAYBE CATCH A
SEE OUR NATS.
BASEBALL GAME.
>> LAST PLACE THAT YOU HAVE ON
SEE OUR NATS.
YOUR LIST BEFORE WE GET TO THE
>> LAST PLACE THAT YOU HAVE ON
PRODUCTS IS NASHVILLE.
YOUR LIST BEFORE WE GET TO THE
>> , ASHVILLE.
PRODUCTS IS NASHVILLE.
SPRINGTIME IN ASHVILLE TURNING
>> , ASHVILLE.
GREEN.
SPRINGTIME IN ASHVILLE TURNING
BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS.
GREEN.
YOU KNOW, ASHVILLE HAS BEEN JUST
BEAUTIFUL FLOWERS.
A GREAT PLACE TO VISIT FOR A
YOU KNOW, ASHVILLE HAS BEEN JUST
LONG TIME BECAUSE YOU HAD BUILT
A GREAT PLACE TO VISIT FOR A
MORE ESTATE DOWN THERE AND
LONG TIME BECAUSE YOU HAD BUILT
THINGS THE HUNGER GAMES CAME AND
MORE ESTATE DOWN THERE AND
ALL THESE CELEBRITIES DECIDED 93
THINGS THE HUNGER GAMES CAME AND
DISCOVERED ASHVILLE.
ALL THESE CELEBRITIES DECIDED 93
AND SO YOU'RE SEEING GREAT ART
DISCOVERED ASHVILLE.
SCENE.
AND SO YOU'RE SEEING GREAT ART
THEY JUST BUILT A
SCENE.
24 MILLION-DOLLAR ASHVILLE ART
THEY JUST BUILT A
MUSEUM DOWN THERE.
24 MILLION-DOLLAR ASHVILLE ART
>> $24 MILLION?
MUSEUM DOWN THERE.
>> $24 MILLION.
>> $24 MILLION?
>> IT'S ASHVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA
>> $24 MILLION.
BUT A GREAT ART SCENE DOWN
>> IT'S ASHVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA
THERE.
BUT A GREAT ART SCENE DOWN
>> I LOVE THE CAROLINAS.
THERE.
BEFORE WE LET YOU GO, WHAT DID
>> I LOVE THE CAROLINAS.
YOU BRING.
BEFORE WE LET YOU GO, WHAT DID
>> I BROUGHT YOUR DAY PACKS.
YOU BRING.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST THREATS TO
>> I BROUGHT YOUR DAY PACKS.
TRAVELERS ESPECIALLY AMERICAN
ONE OF THE BIGGEST THREATS TO
TRAVELERS ISN'T, YOU KNOW, THIS
TRAVELERS ESPECIALLY AMERICAN
VIOLENT CRIMES AND THING IT'S
TRAVELERS ISN'T, YOU KNOW, THIS
PICKPOCKETING.
VIOLENT CRIMES AND THING IT'S
IT'S THOSE LITTLE THINGS.
PICKPOCKETING.
THE WORST THING TO DO COME WACK
IT'S THOSE LITTLE THINGS.
FROM YOUR VACATION REALIZE YOUR
THE WORST THING TO DO COME WACK
CAMERA WAS STOLEN OR SOMETHING
FROM YOUR VACATION REALIZE YOUR
LIKE THAT.
CAMERA WAS STOLEN OR SOMETHING
>> TERRIBLE.
LIKE THAT.
>> I HAVE PRODUCTS.
>> TERRIBLE.
PACK SAVE TRAVEL ON LOUIS AND
>> I HAVE PRODUCTS.
CLARK ALL OF THESE PRODUCTS HAVE
PACK SAVE TRAVEL ON LOUIS AND
THESE ZIPPERS THAT HAVE EXTRA
CLARK ALL OF THESE PRODUCTS HAVE
LITTLE LOCKS ON THEM THAT MAKE
THESE ZIPPERS THAT HAVE EXTRA
IT JUST REALLY DIFFICULT FOR
LITTLE LOCKS ON THEM THAT MAKE
SOMEONE TO JUST CASUALLY COME BY
IT JUST REALLY DIFFICULT FOR
AND STEAL FROM YOU.
SOMEONE TO JUST CASUALLY COME BY
>> RIGHT.
AND STEAL FROM YOU.
PICKPOCKET SEES ALL OF THIS, WHY
>> RIGHT.
YOU GOING TO WORK THAT HARD.
PICKPOCKET SEES ALL OF THIS, WHY
>> EXACT.
YOU GOING TO WORK THAT HARD.
THESE ARE WATERPROOF, THEY'RE
>> EXACT.
REALLY NICE TO HAVE.
THESE ARE WATERPROOF, THEY'RE
EVEN IF YOU'RE GOING TO GO OUT
REALLY NICE TO HAVE.
AND BUY A DAY PACK OR SOMETHING
EVEN IF YOU'RE GOING TO GO OUT
LIKE THAT, TAKE THAT INVESTMENT
AND BUY A DAY PACK OR SOMETHING
AND FIND ONE THAT WILL KEEP YOU
LIKE THAT, TAKE THAT INVESTMENT
SECURE AND YOUR ITEMS SECURE.
AND FIND ONE THAT WILL KEEP YOU
THIS ONE I LOVE FOLDS UP IN A
SECURE AND YOUR ITEMS SECURE.
PACK.
THIS ONE I LOVE FOLDS UP IN A
THIS ONE CONVERTS INTO A
PACK.
BACKPACK.
THIS ONE CONVERTS INTO A
THIS ONE MADE OUT OF RECYCLED
BACKPACK.
BOTTLE WATER.
THIS ONE MADE OUT OF RECYCLED
SAVE THE ENVIRONMENT AND YOUR
BOTTLE WATER.
PRODUCTS.
SAVE THE ENVIRONMENT AND YOUR
YOU HAVE REALLY GREAT OPTIONS
PRODUCTS.
HERE THE KEY THING WITH SPRI&-úR
YOU HAVE REALLY GREAT OPTIONS
BEST DEALS.
HERE THE KEY THING WITH SPRI&-úR
>> HOW DO PEOPLE GET IN TOUCH
BEST DEALS.
WITH YOU.
>> HOW DO PEOPLE GET IN TOUCH
>> FOLLOW ME ONLINE I AM THE GAY
WITH YOU.
TRAVELER AS YOU KNOW.
>> FOLLOW ME ONLINE I AM THE GAY
SO I'LL HAVE MORE INFORMATION
TRAVELER AS YOU KNOW.
ABOUT ALL THESE PRODUCTS UP
SO I'LL HAVE MORE INFORMATION
THERE ON MY SOCIAL MEDIA AND
ABOUT ALL THESE PRODUCTS UP
STUFF.
THERE ON MY SOCIAL MEDIA AND
BUT REALLY I THINK, YOU KNOW,
STUFF.
GREAT OPPORTUNITIES TO TRAVEL
BUT REALLY I THINK, YOU KNOW,
RIGHT NOW DON'T BE AFRAID OF
GREAT OPPORTUNITIES TO TRAVEL
CORONAVIRUS.
RIGHT NOW DON'T BE AFRAID OF
JUST, YOU KNOW, TAKE THOSE
CORONAVIRUS.
PRECAUTIONS.
JUST, YOU KNOW, TAKE THOSE
>> TROY, YOU'RE THE BEST.
PRECAUTIONS.
THANKS.
>> TROY, YOU'RE THE BEST.
WE LOVE IT WHEN YOU COME SPEND
THANKS.
TIME WITH US.
WE LOVE IT WHEN YOU COME SPEND
>> THANKS, ALLISON.
TIME WITH US.
>> TUCKER OVER TO YOU.
>> THANKS, ALLISON.
>> ALLISON THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> TUCKER OVER TO YOU.
COLD START TO YOUR DAY BY COLD I
>> ALLISON THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MEAN TEENS AND 20S FOR MOST OF
COLD START TO YOUR DAY BY COLD I
THE AREA.
MEAN TEENS AND 20S FOR MOST OF
THERE'S A LIVE SHOT NATIONAL
THE AREA.
HARBOR NOTICE THE HIGH THIN
THERE'S A LIVE SHOT NATIONAL
CLOUDS WE'LL HAVE FEW MORE
HARBOR NOTICE THE HIGH THIN
CLOUDS TODAY THAN YESTERDAY BUT,
CLOUDS WE'LL HAVE FEW MORE
YOU KNOW, FROM TIME TO TIME HERE
CLOUDS TODAY THAN YESTERDAY BUT,
YOU SHOULD GET LOTS OF SUNSHINE
YOU KNOW, FROM TIME TO TIME HERE
AS WE'RE GETTING THERE ON THE
YOU SHOULD GET LOTS OF SUNSHINE
POTOMAC EARLY THIS MORNING.
AS WE'RE GETTING THERE ON THE
NICE LOOKING START TO OUR DAY.
POTOMAC EARLY THIS MORNING.
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
NICE LOOKING START TO OUR DAY.
NOTICE REGIONALLY ACROSS
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
PENNSYLVANIA AND NEW ENGLAND,
NOTICE REGIONALLY ACROSS
COLD TEMPERATURES TO START THE
PENNSYLVANIA AND NEW ENGLAND,
MORNING.
COLD TEMPERATURES TO START THE
HIGH PRESSURE TO OUR NORTH.
MORNING.
BINGHAMTON 11 THIS YEAR.
HIGH PRESSURE TO OUR NORTH.
NEW YORK IS 26.
BINGHAMTON 11 THIS YEAR.
23 IN BOSTON.
NEW YORK IS 26.
SO PLENTY OF COLD AIR AND LET ME
23 IN BOSTON.
JUST MENTION EVERYBODY LOCALLY
SO PLENTY OF COLD AIR AND LET ME
BELOW FREEZING TO START YOUR
JUST MENTION EVERYBODY LOCALLY
MORNING HERE SO MAKE SURE YOU'VE
BELOW FREEZING TO START YOUR
GOT LAYERS ON AS IT WILL BE A
MORNING HERE SO MAKE SURE YOU'VE
COOL DAY AND AT TIMES A CLOUDY
GOT LAYERS ON AS IT WILL BE A
DAY.
COOL DAY AND AT TIMES A CLOUDY
WE HAVE CLOUDS OFF TO THE SOUTH
DAY.
AND WEST THAT WILL PINWHEEL UP
WE HAVE CLOUDS OFF TO THE SOUTH
INTO OUR REGION.
AND WEST THAT WILL PINWHEEL UP
LOOSELY ASSOCIATED WITH THIS
INTO OUR REGION.
AREA OF LOW PRESSURE DOWN HERE
LOOSELY ASSOCIATED WITH THIS
ACROSS THE CAROLINA COAST AND
AREA OF LOW PRESSURE DOWN HERE
PARTLY SUNNY AND COOL AFTERNOON
ACROSS THE CAROLINA COAST AND
FOR US LOW 40S FOR DAYTIME HI
PARTLY SUNNY AND COOL AFTERNOON
HIGHS.
FOR US LOW 40S FOR DAYTIME HI
BUT IT WILL STAY DRY.
HIGHS.
NOT EXPECTING ANY RAIN LATER
BUT IT WILL STAY DRY.
TODAY AS CONDITIONS REMAIN QUIET
NOT EXPECTING ANY RAIN LATER
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
TODAY AS CONDITIONS REMAIN QUIET
LOOKS LEAK OUR NEXT CHANCE FOR
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
RAIN ARRIVES ON SATURDAY.
LOOKS LEAK OUR NEXT CHANCE FOR
42 THIS AFTERNOON.
RAIN ARRIVES ON SATURDAY.
PARTLY SUNNY.
42 THIS AFTERNOON.
MOSTLY CLOUDY TOMORROW.
PARTLY SUNNY.
48.
MOSTLY CLOUDY TOMORROW.
AND WE'LL LOOK AT THE WEEKEND
48.
FORECAST AND SEVEN DAY FORECAST
AND WE'LL LOOK AT THE WEEKEND
I'VE BEEN TWEETING IT OUT TUCKER
FORECAST AND SEVEN DAY FORECAST
FOX5 60S ON IT IT SEEMS TO BE
I'VE BEEN TWEETING IT OUT TUCKER
WELL RECEIVED.
FOX5 60S ON IT IT SEEMS TO BE
SO WE'LL LOOK AT THAT AS WELL.
WELL RECEIVED.
STACEY?
SO WE'LL LOOK AT THAT AS WELL.
>> YOU'RE A ROCK STAR TUCKER FOR
STACEY?
THAT FORECAST.
>> YOU'RE A ROCK STAR TUCKER FOR
THAT'S FOR SURE.
THAT FORECAST.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
KEEPING YOU UP TO SPEED
ALL RIGHT.
REGARDING YOUR MORNING COMMUTE.
KEEPING YOU UP TO SPEED
LET'S START WITH 28 IF YOU'RE
REGARDING YOUR MORNING COMMUTE.
HEADING NORTHBOUND.
LET'S START WITH 28 IF YOU'RE
WE HAVE A CRASH THIS IS ON THE
HEADING NORTHBOUND.
ON-RAMP TO TOLL ROAD.
WE HAVE A CRASH THIS IS ON THE
SOMETHING TO LOOK OUT FOR THIS
ON-RAMP TO TOLL ROAD.
MORNING.
SOMETHING TO LOOK OUT FOR THIS
LOOKING AT 123 IF YOU'RE HEADING
MORNING.
NORTHBOUND WE ALSO HAVE A CRASH
LOOKING AT 123 IF YOU'RE HEADING
THAT'S BLOCKING THE TWO LEFT
NORTHBOUND WE ALSO HAVE A CRASH
LANES.
THAT'S BLOCKING THE TWO LEFT
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER OLD BRIDGE
LANES.
ROAD.
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER OLD BRIDGE
DEFINITELY CAUSING SOME DELAYS.
ROAD.
THAT'S ALSO SOMETHING TO BE
DEFINITELY CAUSING SOME DELAYS.
AWARE OF.
THAT'S ALSO SOMETHING TO BE
HEADS UP ON 95 NORTHBOUND YOU'VE
AWARE OF.
GOT YOUR USUAL POCKS OF TRAFFIC
HEADS UP ON 95 NORTHBOUND YOU'VE
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY FROM DALE
GOT YOUR USUAL POCKS OF TRAFFIC
CITY TO THE BELTWAY.
AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY FROM DALE
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO JUST ABOUT 3T
CITY TO THE BELTWAY.
POINT.
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO JUST ABOUT 3T
LOOKING AT SOUTH CAPITOL STREET
POINT.
NORTHBOUND WE HAVE A CRASH
LOOKING AT SOUTH CAPITOL STREET
BLOCKING THE TWO LEFT LANES.
NORTHBOUND WE HAVE A CRASH
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER THE STREET
BLOCKING THE TWO LEFT LANES.
SOUTHEAST AND THOSE DELAYS
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER THE STREET
EXTEND ALL THE WAY BACK TO
SOUTHEAST AND THOSE DELAYS
BRANCH AVENUE.
EXTEND ALL THE WAY BACK TO
SO HEADS UP IN THE AREA.
BRANCH AVENUE.
ALSO, 295 SOUTHBOUND AT EASTERN
SO HEADS UP IN THE AREA.
OF A THE RIGHT LANE IS BLOCKED
ALSO, 295 SOUTHBOUND AT EASTERN
BECAUSE OF AN INCIDENT INVOLVING
OF A THE RIGHT LANE IS BLOCKED
A VEHICLE.
BECAUSE OF AN INCIDENT INVOLVING
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
A VEHICLE.
BACK TO YOU.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
>>> IT BROKE THE INTERNET AND WE
BACK TO YOU.
ARE TALKING ABOUT OLD BAY HOT
>>> IT BROKE THE INTERNET AND WE
SAUCE.
ARE TALKING ABOUT OLD BAY HOT
GOOD LUCK FINDING IT.
SAUCE.
SOLD OUT HOW QUICKLY?  WELL TELL
GOOD LUCK FINDING IT.
YOU COMING UP.
SOLD OUT HOW QUICKLY?  WELL TELL
♪
♪♪
A DAY AFTER THE OLD BAY HOT
SAUCE WAS ANNOUNCED IT SOLD OUT
ONLINE ALREADY.
>> OY BOY.
MCCORMICK WHICH OPENS THE
POPULAR SEASONING ONLINE STORE
SOLD OUT IN AN HOUR.
THE COMPANY THANKED BUYERS FOR
BEING WILLING TO TRY SOMETHING
NEW AND PROMISED TO RESTOCK THE
LIMITED TIME OFFERING.
MC COURIC DESCRIBES THE OLD BAY
HOT SAUCE AS TANGY WITH A KICK
HEAT.
>> IF YOU GO ON THE WEBSITE YOU
CAN SIGN UP FOR THE MAILING LIST
TO FINE OUT WHEN IT WILL BE
AVAILABLELY.
>> GET THE BIG JUG.
>> YOU HAVE TO AT THIS POINT.
>> SO YOU DON'T EVER RUN OUT.
>> NO MORE WILL BE RELEASED AT
LEAST TODAY.
WE'LL SEE.
>> MY QUESTION WHAT TOOK SO
LONG?
>> RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I'M ON THE WAITING LIST, AL.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW IF WE GET ANY
I'LL SHARE WITH YOU.
>>> IF YOU WERE ONE OF THE LUCKY
ONES GOT YOUR HANDS ON FOR THE
SUPER BOWL PARTY, GREAT JOB
WATCH THE GAME RIGHT HERE ON
FOX5 CONTINUING COVERAGE FROM
MIAMI LEADING UP TO THE BIG
GAME.
ANGIE WILL JOIN US ON GOOD DAY
LATER THIS MORNING FROM MIAMI.
TO MAKE SURE TO FOLLOW ALONG ON
OUR SOCIAL MEDIA PAGES.
>> LET'S GET TO LIFE PICTURE
RIGHT NOW FROM NATIONAL HARBOR.
TUCK WILL BE BACK WITH A LOOK AT
THE FORECAST COMING UP NEXT.
NOT TOO BAD.
JUST CHILLY TEMPERATURE RIGHT
AROUND THE FREEZING MARK.
>> STACEY WILL HAVE A LOOK AT
THE ROADS TOO AND HOUR MIKE
THOMAS IS LIVE ON LOCATION WITH
ONE OF D.C.'S NEWEST
PROFESSIONAL TEAMS.
HE SHOWS US THEIR NEW PRACTICE
CENTER.
STAY WITH US.
♪
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
I need every sports channel
possible.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios
with internet starting at just
$39.99 per month.
Plus, you'll get up to $200 in
Visa prepaid cards
based on the plans you pick.
Eso existe? Los necesitamos.
Want internet? Pick your speed.
Want just TV? Pick the plan
that's right for you
No two households are the same,
so no two plans should be the
same.
We should get what we want.
And now, no matter what you
choose,
you get a year of Disney+ on us.
Boom! Sign me up.
I love that.
Finally, get internet and TV
your way
with internet starting at $39.99
per month -
no extra fees, no annual
contracts.
No surprises on my cable bill?
I'll take that.
Finally! Plans that just make
sense.
Mix and match your perfect Fios
plan and pay for what you want.
Only on Verizon.
Z3PC3Z Z16FZ
Y3PC3Y Y16FY
♪
>> TIME NOW 8:44.
LET'S GIVE YOU A LOOK AT THE
GOOD DAY GUEST LIST FOLLOWING
THE BIGGEST GAME OF THE YEAR YOU
CAN CATCH THE BIGGEST PREMIER OF
THE YEAR THE MASK SINGER RETURNS
TO FOX FOR THIRD SEASON RIGHT
AFTER THE SUPER BOWL WE'RE
GIVING YOU A SPECIAL PREVIEW ON
GOOD DAY.
>> WE ALSO TALKED WITH ACTOR ROB
LOWE AND WE ARE GOING TO PLAY
THIS OR THAT WITH A TOP FIVE
SUPER BOWL EDITION WITH HIM AND
FIND OUT THE QUESTION THAT
ALLISON ASKED HIM THAT MADE HIS
EYES BUG OUT.
>> AND THE CAPITALS MONUMENTAL
SPORTS PROVIDING SERVICE DOGS
WITH PERFECT TRAINING GROUNDS
TODAY WE'LL GET TO KNOW THEIR
NEWEST MEMBER IT WILL LITTLE
SCOUT.
>> BECAUSE CAPTAIN IS SUCH A
GOOD PUP.
CUTE LITTLE BIT OLDER.
TODAY WE'RE PAYING IT FORWARD.
WE'LL MEET A 19-YEAR-OLD
FOOTBALL PLAYER WHO PARTICIPATED
IN A BONE MARROW DRIVE AND
BECAME A MATCH FOR AN INFANT WHO
REALLY NEEDED HIM.
THAT INCREDIBLE STORY COMING UP
ON GOOD DAY.
>> ANGIE GOFF MAKING MIAMI BY
STORM.
LEADING UP TO THE SUPER BOWL.
WE'LL HAVE MORE OF HER CRAZY
ESCAPADES AND FIND OUT WHAT ELSE
SHE'S GETTING INTO AS THE PARTY
ROLLS ON.
>> SHE'S ABOUT TO MAKE A TACKLE
IN THAT PICTURE.
DON'T MESS WITH HER.
>> COMING AT YOU.
WE WILL NOT.
>> HI, TUCK.
GOOD MORNING.
>> COLD TEMPERATURES TO START
THE DAY.
I THINK MANY OF US THAT AREN'T
BIG WINTER WEATHER LOVERS
PROBABLY COULD GET USED TO THIS
WEATHER IN JANUARY.
ALTHOUGH IT IS COLD EARLY THIS
MORNING, AND WE'LL BE IN FOR A
COOL AND QUIET AFTERNOON.
FEW MORE CLOUDS THAN YESTERDAY.
SHOWERS NEXT CHANCE SATURDAY
MORNING.
BEST CHANCES ARE GOING TO BE
SOUTH AND EAST OF TOWN I'LL SHOW
YOU WHY HERE IN JUST A SECOND
AND 60S NEXT WEEK.
YEAH, I MEAN NOT JUST ONE DAY OF
IT A COUPLE DAYS OF IT, AS
MONDAY THROUGH WEDNESDAY NEXT
WEEK LOOKS TO BE 60 OR BETTER.
OKAY.
WE'RE NOT THERE TODAY.
AND WE WILL NOT BE THERE THIS
AFTERNOON.
COLD START TO THE DAY.
32 IN LEONARDTOWN.
31 WASHINGTON.
NOTICE LOTS OF 20S WEST AND
NORTH.
GAITHERSBURG 25.
MANASSAS WHY.
COLD SPOT THIS MORNING 19 IN
MARTINSBURG AND THIS IS WITH THE
SUN HAVING BEEN UP OVER AN HOUR.
SO YOU GET AN IDEA HERE GRADUAL
WARMUP AND EVEN WITH SOME
SUNSHINE THIS AFTERNOON OH 40S
FOR DAYTIME HIGHS.
CLOUDS WE'LL GET THOSE AS WELL
THIS AFTERNOON.
PARTLY CLOUDY CONDITIONS
EXPECTED.
WE'LL GET SOME CLOUDS AROUND
HERE LATER TODAY.
WE HAVE AN AREA OF LOW PRESSURE
HERE OFF THE CAROLINA COAST.
IT'S BEING PUSHED AWAY FROM OUR
REGION BY HIGH PRESSURE THAT'S
OFF TO OUR NORTH.
BUT SOME OF THE CLOUDS ARE GOING
TO CONTINUE TO KIND OF GET
DRAGGED IN HERE FOR OUR
AFTERNOON HOURS.
SO YOU KNOW JUST MAKE SURE YOU
GOT THE JACKET READY TO GO.
CERTAINLY GOING TO BE A COOL
DAY.
IT WILL BE A DRY AFTERNOON FOR
YOU.
AS WE'RE NOT LOOKING FOR RAIN
UNTIL PERHAPS SATURDAY MORNING.
THEN EVEN SATURDAY MORNING A FEW
SHOWERS.
BEST CHANCES FOR A STEADY RAIN
WILL BE SOUTH AND EAST OF TOWN.
WHY?  LOW PRESSURE TALKING ABOUT
THIS GUY FOR THE LAST COUPLE OF
DAYS, AND THE POSSIBILITY OF IT
PHASING.
THAT DOESN'T LOOK TO HAPPEN SO
TEMPERATURES ARE GOING TO BE TOO
MILD TO SUPPORT ANYTHING OTHER
THAN SOME RAIN.
FIRST HALF OF SATURDAY.
WE'LL GET THAT GUY OUT OF HERE
SATURDAY AFTERNOON PERHAPS LATE
DAY SUN ON SATURDAY WITH HIGHS
NEAR 50.
THEN SUPER BOWL SUNDAY LOOKS
GREAT.
HIGH PRESSURE OFF TO OUR SOUTH
AND WEST AND TEMPS IN THE LOW
50S AROUND HERE FOR SUPER BOWL
SIN DAY AND DRY CONDITIONS.
DRIVING OUT TO THE PARTY.
YOU WANTED TO A LITTLE
BARBECUING ON THE BACK PORCH, I
THINK YOU'LL BE FINE WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE LOW 50S, AND
THAT WILL GIVE WAY TO THIS.
HIGH PRESSURE OFF TO OUR SOUTH
AND WITH A NICE STRONG FLOW OUT
OF THE SOUTH AND WEST EARLY NEXT
WEEK.
MONDAY, TUESDAY AND THAT LOOKS
LIKE WEDNESDAY.
WE'LL DO 60S.
I MEAN THAT'S 15 PLUS DEGREES
ABOVE NORMAL.
SO FEBRUARY IS GOING TO START ON
A QUIET NOTE.
I CAN'T GUARANTEE IT WILL END ON
BUT AT LEAST THE NEXT WEEK OR SO
A QUIET NOTE.
NO WINTER WEATHER ON THAT SEVEN
BUT AT LEAST THE NEXT WEEK OR SO
DAY FORECAST.
NO WINTER WEATHER ON THAT SEVEN
42 TODAY.
DAY FORECAST.
IT WILL BE CHILLY.
42 TODAY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I WISH?  I WISH
IT WILL BE CHILLY.
YOU HAD A HAND-HELD MISM C WHEN
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I WISH?  I WISH
YOU SAY 60S NEXT WEEK YOU CAN
YOU HAD A HAND-HELD MISM C WHEN
JUST DROP THE MIC AND WALK OFF.
YOU SAY 60S NEXT WEEK YOU CAN
>> OH, WELL -- WON THAT BE COOL.
JUST DROP THE MIC AND WALK OFF.
>> I HAVE ONE IN MY DRAWER.
>> OH, WELL -- WON THAT BE COOL.
I'LL FINE IT.
>> I HAVE ONE IN MY DRAWER.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD DO THAT.
I'LL FINE IT.
I THINK IT WARRANTS THAT.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD DO THAT.
60 DEGREES IN FEBRUARY MUCH
I THINK IT WARRANTS THAT.
THAT'S AMAZING.
60 DEGREES IN FEBRUARY MUCH
LET'S START WITH 28 NORTHBOUND
THAT'S AMAZING.
REGARDING YOUR MORNING COMMUTE.
LET'S START WITH 28 NORTHBOUND
WE'VE GOT A CRASH.
REGARDING YOUR MORNING COMMUTE.
THIS IS ON THE ON-RAMP TO THE
WE'VE GOT A CRASH.
DULLES TOLL ROAD CAUSING SOME
THIS IS ON THE ON-RAMP TO THE
SLOW DOWNS FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
DULLES TOLL ROAD CAUSING SOME
ON 123 NORTHBOUND WE ALSO HAVE A
SLOW DOWNS FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
CRASH.
ON 123 NORTHBOUND WE ALSO HAVE A
THIS IS AFTER OLD BRIDGE ROAD.
CRASH.
BECAUSE OF THAT THE TWO LEFT
THIS IS AFTER OLD BRIDGE ROAD.
LANES ARE BLOCKED RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE OF THAT THE TWO LEFT
HOPEFULLY THEY'LL GET THAT
LANES ARE BLOCKED RIGHT NOW.
CLEARED AWAY FOR YOU MOMEN
HOPEFULLY THEY'LL GET THAT
MOMENTARILY.
CLEARED AWAY FOR YOU MOMEN
95 NORTHBOUND IS SLOW AND STEADY
MOMENTARILY.
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY AS
95 NORTHBOUND IS SLOW AND STEADY
YOU CAN SEE IN THAT LIVE SHOT
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY AS
AND ON SOUTH CAPITOL STREET IN
YOU CAN SEE IN THAT LIVE SHOT
THE CITY, NORTHBOUND WE HAVE A
AND ON SOUTH CAPITOL STREET IN
CRASH THAT IS BLOCKING THE TWO
THE CITY, NORTHBOUND WE HAVE A
LEFT LANES RIGHT AFTER K STREET
CRASH THAT IS BLOCKING THE TWO
SOUTHEAST.
LEFT LANES RIGHT AFTER K STREET
SO SOMETHING TO WATCH OUT FOR IF
SOUTHEAST.
YOU'RE IN THAT AREA.
SO SOMETHING TO WATCH OUT FOR IF
ON 295 SOUTHBOUND, THIS IS RIGHT
YOU'RE IN THAT AREA.
AT EASTERN AVENUE.
ON 295 SOUTHBOUND, THIS IS RIGHT
THE RIGHT LANE IS BLOCKED BUT IT
AT EASTERN AVENUE.
LOOKS LIKE TRAFFIC IS SLOWLY BUT
THE RIGHT LANE IS BLOCKED BUT IT
SURELY MOVING AROUND THAT AREA
LOOKS LIKE TRAFFIC IS SLOWLY BUT
BUT, AGAIN, SOMETHING TO BE
SURELY MOVING AROUND THAT AREA
AWARE OF.
BUT, AGAIN, SOMETHING TO BE
ALSO, JUST LIKE WHAT TUCKER WAS
AWARE OF.
SAYING ABOUT THE COLD DAY TODAY,
ALSO, JUST LIKE WHAT TUCKER WAS
WE'VE GOT ICY CONDITIONS ON
SAYING ABOUT THE COLD DAY TODAY,
BURROUGHS AVENUE AT DIVISION
WE'VE GOT ICY CONDITIONS ON
AVENUE.
BURROUGHS AVENUE AT DIVISION
SALT TRUCKS ARE ON THE WAY AND
AVENUE.
ON THE SCENE BUT JUST PLEASE USE
SALT TRUCKS ARE ON THE WAY AND
CAUTION IN THAT AREA.
ON THE SCENE BUT JUST PLEASE USE
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
CAUTION IN THAT AREA.
ANY QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
ON TWITTER.
ANY QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C.
>> CALLING ALL GAMERS THE DMV
ON TWITTER.
HAS A NEW E SPORTS HOME TEAM.
>> CALLING ALL GAMERS THE DMV
THE WASHINGTON JUSTICE AND
HAS A NEW E SPORTS HOME TEAM.
THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD ALREADY.
THE WASHINGTON JUSTICE AND
NEXT MONTH THEY'LL HOST THE
THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD ALREADY.
FIRST ROUND OF HOME GAMES FOR
NEXT MONTH THEY'LL HOST THE
THE YEAR THIS MORNING MIKE
FIRST ROUND OF HOME GAMES FOR
THOMAS LIVE ON LOCATION IN
THE YEAR THIS MORNING MIKE
ROSELYN WHICH IS TRAINING CAMP I
THOMAS LIVE ON LOCATION IN
GUESS FOR THE -- FOR JUSTICE,
ROSELYN WHICH IS TRAINING CAMP I
RIGHT, MIKE.
GUESS FOR THE -- FOR JUSTICE,
>> STEVE YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT, MIKE.
RIGHT.
>> STEVE YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
THIS WILL BE THEIR NEW TRAINING
RIGHT.
FACILITY HERE FOR THE WASHINGTON
THIS WILL BE THEIR NEW TRAINING
JUSTICE WHICH IS D.C.'S NEWEST
FACILITY HERE FOR THE WASHINGTON
SPORTS TEAM.
JUSTICE WHICH IS D.C.'S NEWEST
YES, I MEAN IT SPORTS TEAM.
SPORTS TEAM.
LISTEN, YOU MIGHT NOT THINK IT
YES, I MEAN IT SPORTS TEAM.
AND I KNOW, YOU KNOW, EVEN MY
LISTEN, YOU MIGHT NOT THINK IT
GENERATION OLDER GENERATIONS
AND I KNOW, YOU KNOW, EVEN MY
WHEN YOU THINK VIDEO GAMES YOU
GENERATION OLDER GENERATIONS
MIGHT NOT THINK COMPETITIVE
WHEN YOU THINK VIDEO GAMES YOU
SPORTS, BUT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
MIGHT NOT THINK COMPETITIVE
MORE VIEWERS FOR E SPORTS THAN
SPORTS, BUT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
THERE WILL BE FOR THE NBA
MORE VIEWERS FOR E SPORTS THAN
FINALS.
THERE WILL BE FOR THE NBA
FOR THE NHL FINALS.
FINALS.
E SPORTS IS REALLY TAKING OVER
FOR THE NHL FINALS.
AND NOW D.C. IS GOING TO HAVE
E SPORTS IS REALLY TAKING OVER
ONE OF ITS VERY OWN OVER WATCH
AND NOW D.C. IS GOING TO HAVE
SPORTS TEAMS HERE FOR E SPORTS.
ONE OF ITS VERY OWN OVER WATCH
GRANT HERE.
SPORTS TEAMS HERE FOR E SPORTS.
HE IS THE VP OF OPERATIONS HERE
GRANT HERE.
FOR THE WASHINGTON JUSTICE.
HE IS THE VP OF OPERATIONS HERE
>> SO TELL ME, FIRST OFF, FOR
FOR THE WASHINGTON JUSTICE.
FOLKS AT HOME WHO MIGHT JUST BE
>> SO TELL ME, FIRST OFF, FOR
CURIOUS.
FOLKS AT HOME WHO MIGHT JUST BE
WHAT ARE E SPORTS.
CURIOUS.
>> IT'S COMPETITIVE VIDEO
WHAT ARE E SPORTS.
GAMING.
>> IT'S COMPETITIVE VIDEO
WE HAVE A TEAM OF EIGHT PLAYERS,
GAMING.
FOUR COACHES, OUR BRAND NEW
WE HAVE A TEAM OF EIGHT PLAYERS,
PRACTICE SPACE AND THEY PRACTICE
FOUR COACHES, OUR BRAND NEW
VIDEO GAMES EIGHT TO 12 HOURS A
PRACTICE SPACE AND THEY PRACTICE
DAY.
VIDEO GAMES EIGHT TO 12 HOURS A
>> INCREDIBLE.
DAY.
LOOK WE'RE TELLING PARENTS AT
>> INCREDIBLE.
HOME IF YOUR KIDS GOOD AT VIDEO
LOOK WE'RE TELLING PARENTS AT
GAMES.
HOME IF YOUR KIDS GOOD AT VIDEO
>> YES.
GAMES.
>> IT COULD BE A CAREER.
>> YES.
TELL ME ABOUT THE JUSTICE
>> IT COULD BE A CAREER.
THEMSELVES.
TELL ME ABOUT THE JUSTICE
HOW DID YOU GUYS GET YOUR START.
THEMSELVES.
>> SURE, WE WERE AN EXPANSION
HOW DID YOU GUYS GET YOUR START.
TEAM LAST SEASON.
>> SURE, WE WERE AN EXPANSION
THE WASHINGTON LEAGUE ADDED FOUR
TEAM LAST SEASON.
TEAMS.
THE WASHINGTON LEAGUE ADDED FOUR
WE'RE MOVING HOME AWAY FOR NAT
TEAMS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER DC
WE'RE MOVING HOME AWAY FOR NAT
RESIDENTS CAN COME DOWN TO THE
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER DC
ANTHEM FEBRUARY 22nd AND CHECK
RESIDENTS CAN COME DOWN TO THE
OUT THEIR HOME TEAM PLAY LIFE.
ANTHEM FEBRUARY 22nd AND CHECK
>> ALL RIGHT.
OUT THEIR HOME TEAM PLAY LIFE.
WE'RE LOOKING AT A LOT OF
>> ALL RIGHT.
HARDWARE HERE IN THIS ROOM.
WE'RE LOOKING AT A LOT OF
THIS IS YOUR NEW PRACTICE
HARDWARE HERE IN THIS ROOM.
FACILITY HERE IN ROSELYN.
THIS IS YOUR NEW PRACTICE
TELL US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT IT.
FACILITY HERE IN ROSELYN.
>> YEAH.
TELL US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT IT.
SO I MEAN WE WANT THE BEST IN
>> YEAH.
CLASS FOR OUR ATHLETES, RIGHT?
SO I MEAN WE WANT THE BEST IN
I THINK WE'VE GONE SO FAR PASSED
CLASS FOR OUR ATHLETES, RIGHT?
THE DAYS OF PLAYING IN YOUR
I THINK WE'VE GONE SO FAR PASSED
BASEMENT AND EATING CHEETOS.
THE DAYS OF PLAYING IN YOUR
WE HAVE A FORM --
BASEMENT AND EATING CHEETOS.
>> STYLE DO THAT BY THE WAY.
WE HAVE A FORM --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> STYLE DO THAT BY THE WAY.
>> STILL A FUN TIME.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE HAVE A FORMAL PRACTICE SPACE.
>> STILL A FUN TIME.
VERY WORK LIFE ENVIRONMENT OUR
WE HAVE A FORMAL PRACTICE SPACE.
PLAYERS LIVE IN TWO BEDROOM
VERY WORK LIFE ENVIRONMENT OUR
APARTMENTS THEY'RE TWO MINUTE
PLAYERS LIVE IN TWO BEDROOM
WALK AWAY THEY COME TO WORK
APARTMENTS THEY'RE TWO MINUTE
EVERY DAY AND THEN THEY
WALK AWAY THEY COME TO WORK
PRACTICE.
EVERY DAY AND THEN THEY
EIGHT TO 14 HOURS A DAY.
PRACTICE.
THEY SCRIMMAGE OTHER TEAMS
EIGHT TO 14 HOURS A DAY.
ACROSS THE LEAGUE.
THEY SCRIMMAGE OTHER TEAMS
THEY HAVE REVIEW WITH OUR
ACROSS THE LEAGUE.
COACHING STAFF AN WIDE ARRAY OF
THEY HAVE REVIEW WITH OUR
HEALTHY SNACKS.
COACHING STAFF AN WIDE ARRAY OF
WE CATER ALL THEIR MEALS.
HEALTHY SNACKS.
SO THEY'RE TREATED LIKE
WE CATER ALL THEIR MEALS.
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES.
SO THEY'RE TREATED LIKE
THEY EARN SALARIES, YOU KNOW,
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES.
NORTHWARDS OF $90,000 ON AVE
THEY EARN SALARIES, YOU KNOW,
AVERAGE.
NORTHWARDS OF $90,000 ON AVE
>> HOW ABOUT THAT, RIGHT?
AVERAGE.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> HOW ABOUT THAT, RIGHT?
>> IT LITERALLY COULD BE A
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
CAREER.
>> IT LITERALLY COULD BE A
THESE PLAYERS, THEY'RE LIVING
CAREER.
THEIR DREAMS HONESTLY.
THESE PLAYERS, THEY'RE LIVING
>> YES.
THEIR DREAMS HONESTLY.
>> SO TELL US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
>> YES.
THE GAME THEY PLAY BECAUSE THE
>> SO TELL US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
WASHINGTON JUSTICE SPECIFICALLY
THE GAME THEY PLAY BECAUSE THE
PLAYS THE GAME CALLED OVER
WASHINGTON JUSTICE SPECIFICALLY
WATCH.
PLAYS THE GAME CALLED OVER
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
WATCH.
>> OVER WATCH IS PUBLISHED BY
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
BLUE ACCU VISION ONE OF THE MOST
>> OVER WATCH IS PUBLISHED BY
RENOWNED PUBLISHER ANYWHERE AND
BLUE ACCU VISION ONE OF THE MOST
66 COMPETITIVE TEAM BASED
RENOWNED PUBLISHER ANYWHERE AND
ACTION.
66 COMPETITIVE TEAM BASED
SO YOU HAVE SIX PLAYERS ON ONE
ACTION.
SIDE AGAINST SIX PLAYERS ON THE
SO YOU HAVE SIX PLAYERS ON ONE
OTHER SIDE YOU ALWAYS HAVE TWO
SIDE AGAINST SIX PLAYERS ON THE
TANKS, TWO HEALERS AND TWO KIND
OTHER SIDE YOU ALWAYS HAVE TWO
OF DAMAGE TYPE CHARACTERS AND
TANKS, TWO HEALERS AND TWO KIND
THEY HAVE AN OBJECTIVE.
OF DAMAGE TYPE CHARACTERS AND
THEY TRY TO CAPTURE A POINT,
THEY HAVE AN OBJECTIVE.
PUSH A CART, AND ONE TEAM ALWAYS
THEY TRY TO CAPTURE A POINT,
WALKS OUT ON TOP.
PUSH A CART, AND ONE TEAM ALWAYS
>> NOW IF YOU'RE CONFUSED BY ANY
WALKS OUT ON TOP.
OF THAT TERMINOLOGY, TANKS,
>> NOW IF YOU'RE CONFUSED BY ANY
HEALERS WE'LL TALK TO SOME OF
OF THAT TERMINOLOGY, TANKS,
THE PLAYERS ON GOOD DAY D.C. AND
HEALERS WE'LL TALK TO SOME OF
GO THROUGH THE DETAILS FOR FOLKS
THE PLAYERS ON GOOD DAY D.C. AND
AT HOME.
GO THROUGH THE DETAILS FOR FOLKS
>> YUP.
AT HOME.
>> WALK THEM THROUGH.
>> YUP.
THESE GAMES ARE AVAILABLE TO
>> WALK THEM THROUGH.
EVERYBODY.
THESE GAMES ARE AVAILABLE TO
FOLKS AT HOME THEIR KIDS MIGHT
EVERYBODY.
PLAY THIS GAME.
FOLKS AT HOME THEIR KIDS MIGHT
>> YEAH.
PLAY THIS GAME.
>> IF THEY WANT TO GET INVOLVED,
>> YEAH.
YOU CAN DO THIS WITH YOUR KIDS
>> IF THEY WANT TO GET INVOLVED,
AT HOME.
YOU CAN DO THIS WITH YOUR KIDS
MAYBE NOT AT THE LEVEL THAT
AT HOME.
THESE PLAYERS ARE DOING IT.
MAYBE NOT AT THE LEVEL THAT
TELL US ABOUT YOUR HOME.
THESE PLAYERS ARE DOING IT.
WHERE ARE YOUR HOME GAMES
TELL US ABOUT YOUR HOME.
BECAUSE YOU CAN ACTUALLY HAVE
WHERE ARE YOUR HOME GAMES
FOLKS COME OUT AND WATCH.
BECAUSE YOU CAN ACTUALLY HAVE
>> YES.
FOLKS COME OUT AND WATCH.
TICKETS ARE ACTUALLY ON SALE
>> YES.
RIGHT NOW.
TICKETS ARE ACTUALLY ON SALE
SO WE HAVE FIVE HOME MATCHES OF
RIGHT NOW.
THE.
SO WE HAVE FIVE HOME MATCHES OF
THE FIRST THREE WILL BE AT THE
THE.
ANTHEM DOWN AT THE WHARF ONE OF
THE FIRST THREE WILL BE AT THE
THE VENUES ANYWHERE IN THE U.S.
ANTHEM DOWN AT THE WHARF ONE OF
AND NEXT TWO AT EVENT D.C. NEW
THE VENUES ANYWHERE IN THE U.S.
ARENA OUT IN ELIZABETH.
AND NEXT TWO AT EVENT D.C. NEW
CHECK OUT THE HOMETOWN.
ARENA OUT IN ELIZABETH.
IT WILL BE REALLY FUN WEEKEND.
CHECK OUT THE HOMETOWN.
YEAH, LET'S GO, JUSTICE.
IT WILL BE REALLY FUN WEEKEND.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YEAH, LET'S GO, JUSTICE.
>> LET'S GO JUSTICE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'LL MEET SOME OF THE BEST
>> LET'S GO JUSTICE.
PLAYERS IN THE WORLD AT THIS
WE'LL MEET SOME OF THE BEST
GAME.
PLAYERS IN THE WORLD AT THIS
COMING UP DURING GOOD DAY D.C.
GAME.
MAKE SURE YOU JOIN US THEN,
COMING UP DURING GOOD DAY D.C.
GUYS.
MAKE SURE YOU JOIN US THEN,
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK RIGHT AFTER
GUYS.
THIS BREAK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK RIGHT AFTER
♪
>> TIME FOR LIGHTS CAMERA
MCCARTHY.
KEV WHAT YOU GOT FOR US TODAY.
>> ABOUT LAST WEEK I BELIEVE
JAMES CORDEN -- KEESHON US MAO
JAMES CORDEN WAS UNDERNEATH A
SCANDAL IN REGARDS TO CARPOOL
KARAOKE.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
BEFORE WE GET TO THIS VIDEO LET
ME SET THIS UP.
SOMEBODY RECORD ADD VIDEO OF
JAMES CORDEN DOING THIS CARPOOL
KARAOKE RECORDING WITH JUSTIN
BEIBER IT WAS A VIDEO ON A CELL
PHONE WHICH YOU'LL SEE IN THIS
VIDEO SHORTLY, AND PEOPLE WERE
GENUINELY BLOWN AWAY THAT HE
QUOTE UNQUOTE DOESN'T DRIVE HIS
OWN VEHICLE BECAUSE IN THE VIDEO
HE'S BEING TOWED.
SO JAMES GORDAN ADDRESSED THIS
THE VIDEO GOT 13 MILLION VIEWS
AND THERE WERE A LOT OF THINK
PIECES AND ARTICLES ABOUT BEING
PEOPLE DEVASTATED THAT HE
DOESN'T DRIVE HIS OWN CAR.
>> OKAY.
>> WHICH IS ACTUALLY NOT TRUE.
95% OF THE TIME HE DOES DRIVE
THE CAR.
WATCH THIS.
>> A FEW DAYS AGO, SOMEBODY
TWEETED THIS VIDEO.
>> YO, IT'S THE BIEBS.
YOUR CARPOOL KARAOKE.
>> THAT IS SO FUNNY.
>> HEY, BEIBER.
>> JUSTIN BEIBER.
>> AND JAMES CORDEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I KNOW THIS LOOKS BAD.
>> BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY RIGHT
[ LAUGHTER ]
NOW, THAT I ALWAYS DRIVE THE CAR
>> BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY RIGHT
UNLESS WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
NOW, THAT I ALWAYS DRIVE THE CAR
WHERE WE THINK IT MIGHT NOT BE
UNLESS WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
SAFE.
WHERE WE THINK IT MIGHT NOT BE
LOOK I'M JUST SHOCKED.
SAFE.
I'VE DONE SOMETHING THAT UPSET
LOOK I'M JUST SHOCKED.
PEOPLE MORE THAN CATS.
I'VE DONE SOMETHING THAT UPSET
[ LAUGHTER ]
PEOPLE MORE THAN CATS.
>> 95% OF THE TIME I REALLY AM
[ LAUGHTER ]
ENDANGERING THE LIVES OF WORLD'S
>> 95% OF THE TIME I REALLY AM
BIGGEST POP STARS, OKAY?
ENDANGERING THE LIVES OF WORLD'S
[ LAUGHTER ]
BIGGEST POP STARS, OKAY?
>> BUT THIS IS A TV SHOW.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NOT EVERYTHING IS REAL.
>> BUT THIS IS A TV SHOW.
OUR SHOW DOESN'T TAPE AFTER
NOT EVERYTHING IS REAL.
MIDNIGHT.
OUR SHOW DOESN'T TAPE AFTER
WE TAPE AT 5:00 P.M. AND PRETEND
MIDNIGHT.
THAT IT'S LATE.
WE TAPE AT 5:00 P.M. AND PRETEND
HERE IS A LIST OF EVERY CARPOOL
THAT IT'S LATE.
KARAOKE WHERE I HAVE USED A TOW.
HERE IS A LIST OF EVERY CARPOOL
AND THIS IS A LIST OF EVERYONE
KARAOKE WHERE I HAVE USED A TOW.
WHERE I WAS DRIVING THE CAR.
AND THIS IS A LIST OF EVERYONE
OKAY?
WHERE I WAS DRIVING THE CAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SO THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT WAS LAST NIGHT.
SO THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
LET'S REWIND BACK TO FEBRUARY OF
>> THAT WAS LAST NIGHT.
2018 WHEN I SAT DOWN WITH JAMES
LET'S REWIND BACK TO FEBRUARY OF
CORDEN TO ASK THIS EXACT
2018 WHEN I SAT DOWN WITH JAMES
QUESTION.
CORDEN TO ASK THIS EXACT
WATCH THIS.
QUESTION.
>> IS THE PATH ALWAYS MAPPED
WATCH THIS.
OUT?  ARE YOU ALWAYS DRIVING AS
>> IS THE PATH ALWAYS MAPPED
WE'RE SEEING YOU DRIVING?
OUT?  ARE YOU ALWAYS DRIVING AS
>> YES.
WE'RE SEEING YOU DRIVING?
>> HOW DO YOU NOT GET
>> YES.
DISTRACTED?  ARE YOU WORRIED
>> HOW DO YOU NOT GET
ABOUT GETTING INTO AN ACCIDENT??
DISTRACTED?  ARE YOU WORRIED
>> WELL, NO, BECAUSE IT'S ALL
ABOUT GETTING INTO AN ACCIDENT??
VERY SAFE.
>> WELL, NO, BECAUSE IT'S ALL
IN TRUTH WE'RE NEVER REALLY EVER
VERY SAFE.
DRIVING OVER I THINK, LIKE, 15
IN TRUTH WE'RE NEVER REALLY EVER
OR 16 MILES AN HOUR.
DRIVING OVER I THINK, LIKE, 15
>> DO YOU HAVE POLICE CARS
OR 16 MILES AN HOUR.
AROUND YOU DOING IT.
>> DO YOU HAVE POLICE CARS
>> NOPE, WE HAVE -- THERE'S
AROUND YOU DOING IT.
BASICALLY THREE CARS SO THERE'S
>> NOPE, WE HAVE -- THERE'S
A CAR IN FRONT, A CAR BEHIND AND
BASICALLY THREE CARS SO THERE'S
THEN A CAR THAT WILL SORT OF
A CAR IN FRONT, A CAR BEHIND AND
MOVE AROUND US, AND THEN WE
THEN A CAR THAT WILL SORT OF
PREDOMINANTLY DRIVE, UM, IN A
MOVE AROUND US, AND THEN WE
COMPLETELY STRAIGHT LINE AWAY
PREDOMINANTLY DRIVE, UM, IN A
FROM THE SUN.
COMPLETELY STRAIGHT LINE AWAY
WE'RE VERY, VERY FORTUNATE THAT
FROM THE SUN.
WE DRIVE IN LOS ANGELES WHERE
WE'RE VERY, VERY FORTUNATE THAT
THERE ARE ROADS THAT ARE LONGER
WE DRIVE IN LOS ANGELES WHERE
THAN YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
THERE ARE ROADS THAT ARE LONGER
>> THE WHITE HOUSE ONE WAS
THAN YOU COULD EVER IMAGINE.
REALLY COOL BY THE WAY.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE ONE WAS
>> THAT WAS JUST GOING AROUND IN
REALLY COOL BY THE WAY.
A CIRCLE AND THEN THE ONE WE DID
>> THAT WAS JUST GOING AROUND IN
IN LONDON WITH ADELE WAS, UM, WE
A CIRCLE AND THEN THE ONE WE DID
WERE JUST IN PREDOMINANTLY HIDE
IN LONDON WITH ADELE WAS, UM, WE
PARK.
WERE JUST IN PREDOMINANTLY HIDE
SO, YEAH.
PARK.
IT'S ALWAYS VERY MUCH SAFETY
SO, YEAH.
FIRST.
IT'S ALWAYS VERY MUCH SAFETY
>> SO HE SAYS SAFETY FIRST AND
FIRST.
ALLISON AND I WERE DISCUSSING
>> SO HE SAYS SAFETY FIRST AND
THIS EARLIER IT'S PROBABLY AT
ALLISON AND I WERE DISCUSSING
THE REQUEST OF THE ARTIST.
THIS EARLIER IT'S PROBABLY AT
I MEAN I WOULD IMAGINE JUSTIN
THE REQUEST OF THE ARTIST.
BEIBER PROBABLY HAS PEOPLE
I MEAN I WOULD IMAGINE JUSTIN
FOLLOWING HIM AROUND ALL THE
BEIBER PROBABLY HAS PEOPLE
TIME PAPARAZZI.
FOLLOWING HIM AROUND ALL THE
THEY'RE DRIVING IN A STRAIGHT
TIME PAPARAZZI.
LINE.
THEY'RE DRIVING IN A STRAIGHT
HE SAID 15 TO 16 MILES PER HOUR.
LINE.
HE DID TELL YOU THAT THE FIVE OR
HE SAID 15 TO 16 MILES PER HOUR.
SIX PEOPLE HE'S TOWED THEY'VE
HE DID TELL YOU THAT THE FIVE OR
HAD TOWED.
SIX PEOPLE HE'S TOWED THEY'VE
SO HERE'S THE THING.
HAD TOWED.
THIS IS MIGHT NOT BE A STORY WHY
SO HERE'S THE THING.
ARE WE DISCUSSING THIS?  THIS
THIS IS MIGHT NOT BE A STORY WHY
WAS A GENUINE TWITTER MANY
ARE WE DISCUSSING THIS?  THIS
MASSIVE VIRAL THING.
WAS A GENUINE TWITTER MANY
PEOPLE WERE ACTUALLY DEVASTATED
MASSIVE VIRAL THING.
TO HEAR HE DID DIDN'T DRIVE HIS
PEOPLE WERE ACTUALLY DEVASTATED
CAR.
TO HEAR HE DID DIDN'T DRIVE HIS
>> ME PERSONALLY.
CAR.
>> YEAH.
>> ME PERSONALLY.
>> I'M SURPRISED THAT HE DOES
>> YEAH.
DRIVE AS MUCH AS DOES HE.
>> I'M SURPRISED THAT HE DOES
>> ME, TOO.
DRIVE AS MUCH AS DOES HE.
>> I ASSUMED IT WAS MORE OF A
>> ME, TOO.
TOW AND A CAMERA CAR.
>> I ASSUMED IT WAS MORE OF A
>> THAT'S EXACTLY -- ONE THING
TOW AND A CAMERA CAR.
HE SAYS IN THE VIDEO WE DIDN'T
>> THAT'S EXACTLY -- ONE THING
PUT I ALSO -- HE GOES I ALSO
HE SAYS IN THE VIDEO WE DIDN'T
DON'T HAVE TO GET TO WORK NEED
PUT I ALSO -- HE GOES I ALSO
HELP GETTING TO WORKS WHICH IS
DON'T HAVE TO GET TO WORK NEED
THE WHOLE THING OF CARPOOL CAR
HELP GETTING TO WORKS WHICH IS
YOLK GET INTO MORE ON THAT ON
THE WHOLE THING OF CARPOOL CAR
GOOD DAY.
YOLK GET INTO MORE ON THAT ON
>> GOOD STUFF.
GOOD DAY.
TWO YEARS AHEAD OF THE TREND.
>> GOOD STUFF.
>> COME ON.
TWO YEARS AHEAD OF THE TREND.
NEWS NON-STOP OF COURSE.
>> COME ON.
GOOD DAY D.C. AT 9:00 O'CLOCK
NEWS NON-STOP OF COURSE.
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
GOOD DAY D.C. AT 9:00 O'CLOCK
♪
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD,