SNOW, WISE, RAIN, THIS WINTRY
MIX COULD IMPACT THE RUSH HOUR
COMMUTE.
THE AREAS OF BIGGEST CONCERN
AND THE SCHOOLS TAKING NO
CHANCES.
TUCKER HAS THE LATEST TRACK.
>>> AND TELLS US HOW MUCH SNOW
HAS ALREADY FALLEN.
>> TOLL LANE TROUBLE.
A PROPOSAL TO EASE TRAFFIC ON
A PORTION OF MARYLAND'S
BUSIEST HIGHWAYS HIT A SNAG
OVER THE WEEKEND AND TODAY A
BIG RALLY IS THAT PLANNED IN
SILVER SPRING.
>>> AND OUR FOX5 HOLIDAY
SERIES CONTINUES LIVE IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
MIKE IS COMING UP WITH THE TOP
FIVE THINGS TO DO IN PRINCE
WILLIAM COUNTY THIS FESTIVE
TIME OF YEAR.
FOX5 MORNING AT 7:00 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>> ♪
>> GOOD MONDAY MORNING TO YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US.
IT'S DECEMBER 16TH AND I'M
ALLISON SEYMOUR.
>> I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
IF YOU'RE JUST JOINING US
LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
THIS MORNING WHERE THE SNOW
CONTINUES TO ROLL INTO PARTS
OF THE D.C. REGION.
SOME OF THE WESTERN SUBURBS
AND NORTHERN SUBURBS UNDER A
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY AND WE
HAVE SCHOOL CLOSINGS AS WELL.
IN VIRGINIA LOUDOUN COUNTY,
PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY,
FAUQUIER COUNTY ALL CLOSED.
IN MARYLAND, MONTGOMERY COUNTY
PUBLIC SCHOOLS ARE NOW CLOSED.
>> JUST MADE THAT CHANGE NOT
TOO LONG AGO.
YOU CAN FIND A LIST OF ALL THE
IMPACTED SCHOOLS AT THE BOTTOM
OF YOUR SCREEN ON THE FOX5
WEATHER APP OR AT FOX5DC.COM.
>> IT'S ONE THING TO LOOK AT
THE RADAR, IT'S ANOTHER THING
TO BREAK IT DOWN.
ERIN IS ON THE ROADS, TUCKER
HAS GOT THE FORECAST.
WHAT'S GOING ON TUCK.
>> LET'S HOP RIGHT INTO THAT
RADAR.
LOTS OF COLORS ON THERE
INDICATING LOTS HAPPENING.
WE GOT SNOW FLYING, WE GOT
SOME RAIN SHOWERS, MAYBE EVEN
A LITTLE SLEET MIXING IN.
BOTTOM LINE IS ANY WINTER
WEATHER WE'RE GETTING ACROSS
THE REGION AT THE MOMENT
SHOULD TRANSITION TO A LIGHT
RAIN HERE IN THE NEXT COUPLE
HOURS.
SO THINGS WILL START TO
IMPROVE BIG TIME AROUND HERE.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT
TEMPERATURES AND THAT WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORY COMING UP BUT
AGAIN MOSTLY JUST A RAIN EVENT
FROM HERE GOING FORWARD AS WE
GET INTO THE AFTERNOON HOURS.
AGAIN, TEMPERATURES WILL BE
NEAR 40.
QUICK LOOK AT YOUR WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORY AND WE'LL
TAKE A CLOSER LOOK AT
EVERYTHING IN JUST A MINUTE.
LET'S HIT THOSE ROADS GET THE
LATEST FROM ERIN.
>> BIG CRASH BY NUTLEY STREET
PREVIOUSLY BLOCKING ALL LANES.
RIGHT NOW THEY HAVE OPENED UP
SEVERAL.
BLOCKING THE LEFT SHOULDER,
LEFT LANE PART OF THE RIGHT
SHOULDER AS WELL.
RUBBERNECK DELAY DELAY HEAVY
ON THE EASTBOUND SIDE.
28 NORTHBOUND MANASSAS BIG
CRASH BLOCKING ALL LANES.
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE ON THE
ROADS THIS MORNING.
FOX5's MELANIE ALNWICK
TRACKING THINGS OUT IN
FREDERICK, MARYLAND.
HOW IS IT SHAPING UP FOR YOU?
> WE'RE HAVING A LITTLE
TROUBLE WITH HER SHOT BUT
SHE'S TRACKING IT AS WELL.
>> IT WILL PROBABLY GET
MELANIE'S SHOT IN THERE BUT
WE'LL GET IT BACK FOR YOU.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY THE WEATHER
CAUSING A FEW DELAYS OUT
THERE.
SPEAKING OF WEATHER, WHILE WE
HAVE YOU WE WANT TO REMIND YOU
TO CHECK OUT OUR FOX5 D.C.
WEATHER APP.
CHECK YOUR RADAR, THE ALERTS
ON THE GO AND ANY
CANCELLATIONS OR CLOSINGS WILL
NOT ONLY BE CRAWLING BOTTOM OF
YOUR SCREEN BUT WE'LL HAVE
THEM ON THE FOX5 WEATHER APP.
IT'S FREE TO DOWNLOAD AND WE
SURE HOPE YOU DO.
>> ♪
>> 7:02.
HAPPENING TODAY IN CHARLES
COUNTY, A BOND HEARING WILL BE
HELD FOR THE MAN POLICE SAY
KIDNAPPED A WOMAN FROM HER
HOME AND THEN FORCED HER TO
GET INTO A CAR AND WITHDRAW
MONEY AT SEVERAL ATM'S.
THIS HAPPENED LAST WEDNESDAY
IN WALDORF.
INVESTIGATORS SAY CHRISTOPHER
BROWN HAD JUST BROKEN INTO A
WOMAN'S HOME WHEN SHE SUDDENLY
ARRIVED HOME.
OFFICIALS SAY BROWN EVENTUALLY
DROPPED THAT WOMAN OFF IN
ACCOKEEK AND SHE WAS ABLE TO
CALL FOR HELP.
>>> AND JUST A TERRIFYING
SCENE AT A SHELL GAS STATION
IN GERMANTOWN.
THAT'S A CAR INTO A STORE
THERE.
AN SUV CRASHED INTO THE FRONT
OF THE STORE.
THIS HAPPENED LAST NIGHT
AROUND 6:30 ON FREDERICK ROAD.
A PEDESTRIAN WAS HIT, TAKEN TO
THE HOSPITAL.
THANKFULLY WITH
NONLIFE-THREATENING INJURIES.
THAT DRIVER WAS EVALUATED ON
THE SCENE.
THERE'S NO WORD YET THIS
MORNING WHAT CAUSED THAT
DRIVER TO CRASH RIGHT INTO THE
STORE.
>> MONTGOMERY COUNTY PUBLIC
SCHOOL OFFICIALS GEARING UP
FOR POTENTIAL LEGAL BATTLES
AFTER A COUNTY WIDE REVIEW OF
SCHOOL BOUNDARIES.
THE BOARD OF EDUCATION WILL
MEET AGAIN TODAY IN CLOSED
SESSION TO DISCUSS POTENTIAL
LITIGATION RELATED TO THE
EXAMINATION AND ANALYSIS OF
SCHOOL BOUNDARY DATA.
NO LAWSUITS HAVE BEEN FILED
YET BUT SCHOOL OFFICIALS SAY
THEY BELIEVE SOME COMMUNITY
MEMBERS WILL SEEK AN
INJUNCTION FROM A JUDGE WHICH
WOULD LEGALLY PREVENT THE
BOUNDARY ANALYSIS TO CONTINUE.
>> MEMBERS OF THE PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY BOARD OF
EDUCATION POLICY AND
GOVERNANCE COMMITTEE WILL MEET
TONIGHT.
THEY'LL DISCUSS THE SCHOOL
DISTRICT'S UNIVERSAL MEALS
PROGRAM FOR STUDENTS.
THE PROGRAM IS CALLED THE NO
MORE STUDENTS HUNGER AND MEALS
EXPANSION OR THE SHAME ACT.
SCHOOL OFFICIALS SAY THAT WHEN
STUDENTS GO HUNGRY IT'S
DETRIMENTAL TO THEIR EMOTIONAL
PHYSICAL AND MENTAL HEALTH AND
GETTING FED PROPERLY IS JUST
AS IMPORTANT TO THEIR ACADEMIC
SUCCESS.
>> ♪
>> COMING UP ON 7: ZERO FIVE.
LET'S GET BACK TO TUCKER.
WE'LL GET A LITTLE MORE
ANALYSIS ON WHAT'S HAPPENING
OUT THERE.
>> SOMETIMES IT'S NOT ABOUT
HOW MUCH SNOW WE GET IT'S
ABOUT THE TIMING ON THE SNOW
AND THIS MORNING IT'S HITTING
US RIGHT AT PRIME TIME AS
PEOPLE ARE OFF TO WORK AND
SCHOOL SO OBVIOUSLY CAUSING
SOME TROUBLE, SLOWDOWNS
DIFFICULTIES AND SCHOOL
DELAYS.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED
MONTGOMERY COUNTY MADE THE
CALL.
>> I GREW UP IN MARYLAND.
I AM SHOCKED AT THE LEVEL AT
WHICH EVERYBODY'S GETTING
DELAYS AND CANCELLATIONS NOW.
I'LL LEAVE IT AT THAT.
>> OKAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF THERE WAS A
SURPRISE POP-UP AT ABOUT
1 O'CLOCK TODAY.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHY I'M
SURPRISED.
IT'S GOING TO TRANSITION
PRETTY QUICKLY TO RAIN AND
IT'S GOING TO BE LIGHT AND THE
SNOW TOTALS ARE GENERALLY LESS
THAN AN INCH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> SO IT JUST BECOMES A
FREE -- A THREE DAY WEEKEND
THEN.
>> I MEAN, LISTEN, IF I WAS A
STUDENT I'M NOT COMPLAINING
I'LL TELL THAT YOU.
>> YUP.
>> HERE WE GO.
66.
STILL SNOWING.
AND THERE CAN -- THAT CAN AND
THERE ARE LIKELY STILL SOME
AREAS GETTING SOME PRETTY GOOD
BURSTS OF SNOW.
ON THE WESTERN SIDE OF THE
BELTWAY PERHAPS NEAR TYSONS
CORNER AND LOOKS LIKE IT'S
MAYBE FLIPPED BACK TO A LITTLE
LIGHT SNOW HERE ON THE
SOUTHEAST SIDE OF THE BELTWAY
OUT INTO PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY WE'RE STILL GETTING
SOME PRETTY GOOD SNOWS OUT
TOWARDS ANNAPOLIS AS WELL.
HOW MUCH SNOW WILL WE RECEIVE
SO FAR?  I SAW A REPORT OF A
MORE THAN A HALF INCH IN
COLUMBIA, WINCHESTER ABOUT AN
INCH OF SNOW.
NOT TERRIBLY IMPRESSIVE
AMOUNTS.
WHERE IT WAS COMING DOWN IT
WAS ENOUGH AS MELANIE
MENTIONED UP IN FREDERICK
STICK ON SOME OF THE ROADS.
THIS IS GOING TO FLIP OVER
PRETTY QUICKLY.
GOING TO CHANGE PRETTY QUICKLY
OVER TO A LIGHT RAIN FOR US.
WE'RE WARMING UP THE
ATMOSPHERE.
SO AT THE ONSET WE'RE TABLE TO
GET THIS SNOW BURST BUT YOU
CAN SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE
OUT TO THE SOUTH AND WEST.
IT'S ALL RAIN.
WE'LL WARM UP THE ATMOSPHERE
OVER THE NEXT COUPLE HOURS AND
EVENTUALLY DAYTIME HIGHS WILL
BE NEAR 40 DEGREES AND MORE
IMPORTANTLY UPSTAIRS AS YOU
GET UP A FEW THOUSAND FEET
TEMPERATURES WILL BE WARM AS
WELL SO THIS WILL BE FALLING
AS JUST A LIGHT RAIN FOR MUCH
OF THE DAY ACROSS THE REGION
AND WE CAN EXPECT THE RAIN
SHOWERS TO CONTINUE INTO
TONIGHT.
SO, AGAIN, THE WORST OF IT FOR
THE MOST PART WILL BE ENDING
HERE IN THE NEXT HOUR OR TWO.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORIES
CONTINUE OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST.
MONTGOMERY HOWARD COUNTY
FREDERICK COUNTY UNDER THAT
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY,
LOUDOUN COUNTY FAUQUIER COUNTY
AND ALONG 81 YOU'RE UNDER THAT
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY UNTIL
1 O'CLOCK THIS AFTERNOON.
TEMPERATURES NOTICE WE'RE
KEEPING THEM ABOVE FREEZING.
THAT IS CRITICAL HERE FOR THE
ROADS.
AND THERE ARE AREAS OR PARTS
OF THE REGION THAT ARE BELOW
32 AT THE MOMENT, GAITHERSBURG
UP TOWARDS FREDERICK AND OUT
ALONG 81.
JUST BE ON THE LOOKOUT.
THERE COULD BE A FEW SLIPPERY
SPOTS.
40 DEGREES AND EVEN IF IT'S
NOT STICKING TO THE ROADWAYS
WE ALL KNOW WHAT WET ROADWAYS
WILL DOIL DO.
I'LL LET ERIN COMMENT ON THAT.
RAIN SHOWERS AFTER THE SNOW
GETS OUT OF HERE OVER THE NEXT
HOUR OR SO.
>> ALL RIGHT TUCK.
A LOOK AT OUR SIX-PACK OF
CAMERAS.
WE'RE JUST SEEING RAIN
EVERYWHERE.
DO YOU SEE ALL THE SLOW MOVING
TRAFFIC AND WET ROADS.
>> I DO.
>> LOOKS LIKE A LOT OF THAT
SNOW HAS MOVED OUT.
EXCEPT THE LEGION BRIDGE.
WE'RE SEEING SOME SNOWY
CONDITIONS ON THE GRASS THERE.
BW PARKWAY OUT BY 197
SOUTHBOUND SIDE IS ALL JAMMED
UP.
WATCH FOR THE POTENTIAL TO
HYDROPLANE.
SLICK CONDITIONS AS WELL.
WE HAD A CRASH 395 MAIN LANES
OUT BY EDSALL ROAD THAT
QUICKLY CLEARED.
HEAVY VOLUME THERE.
66 WESTBOUND SINGLE RIGHT LANE
HAD BEEN GETTING BY AT NUTLEY
STREET.
THEY MOVED THAT HAD CRASH OVER
TO THE LEFT SHOULDER LEFT
LANE.
RUBBERNECK DELAY EASTBOUND.
THERE'S THAT EDSALL ROAD CRASH
THAT MOVED TO THE SHOULDER.
WE'RE SEEING VERY HEAVY VOLUME
THERE.
ABOUT A 30 MINUTE SLOWDOWN UP
TO THE 14TH STREET BRIDGE.
INNER LOOP CRASH IN THE HOV
LANES.
RIGHT LANE BLOCKED OUT BY 7.
WE ALSO HAVE 95 NORTHBOUND
DELAYS IN THOSE MAIN LANES
DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY,
HEAVY VOLUME, SLICK CONDITIONS
THERE.
270 SOUTHBOUND FREDERICK TO
THE BELTWAY VERY SLOW.
YOU CAN SEE SOME OF THE
EARLIER SNOW WE SAW FALLING
HAS DISSIPATED AND TURNED INTO
RAIN.
ROAD SPRAY THE POTENTIAL TO
HYDROPLANE.
ANY QUESTIONS AT ERIN FOX5 D.C..
>> ♪
>> THE U.S. HOUSE SET TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT THIS
WEEK.
THAT VOTE SHOULD TAKE PLACE ON
WEDNESDAY.
AND THE SENATE TRIAL THAT
WOULD FOLLOW IS ALREADY TAKING
SHAPE.
LET'S GET THE LATEST FROM
MAUREEN SHE'S IN THE NEWSROOM
FOLLOWING DEVELOPMENTS ON THE
HEEL.
>> GOOD MORNING STEVE T THE
HOUSE VOTE IS REALLY ACCEPTED
AS A FORGON CONCLUSION THE
PRESIDENT WILL BE IMPEACHED
BUT THE REAL DEBATE IS WHAT
COMES NEXT.
WHAT'S TO HAPPEN UNDER THE
DOME THIS WEEK COULD BE A
DEFINING MOMENT FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND HIS LEGAL TEAM IS
BRACING FOR WHAT WILL ALMOST
SURELY COME NEXT.
>> WE WEREN'T GIVEN A FAIR
TRIAL IN THE HOUSE AT ALL.
NOW IT GOES TO THE SENATE AND
THESE SENATORS, THE PRESIDENT
DESERVES TO BE HEARD.
>> SO WHAT WOULD A SENATE
PRESIDENTIAL TRIAL LOOK LIKE?
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ONE IN TWO
DECADES AFTER THEN PRESIDENT
CLINTON WAS IMPEACHED AND THIS
TIME PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY WANT
TO PULL OUT ALL THE STOPS AND
PUSH FOR LONG TRIAL FULL OF
WITNESSES.
MAYBE EVEN FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN AND HIS
SON HUNTER.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DOESN'T
JUST WANT ACQUITTAL THROUGH
THIS TRIAL HE WANTS
VINDICATION.
HE WANTS PEOPLE TO WATCH THIS
TRIAL, SIX DAYS A WEEK AND
COME OUT AND NOT JUST SAY I
DON'T THINK HE SHOULD BE
REMOVED FROM OFFICE I DON'T
THINK HE DID ANYTHING WRONG.
>> BUT ULTIMATELY IT WILL COME
DOWN WHAT SENATE LEADERS CAN
AGREE UPON AND MAJORITY LEADER
MITCH McCONNELL EXPECTED TO
MEET WITH CHUCK SCHUMER TO
WORK OUT THE GROUND RULES.
SCHUMER HAS ASKED FOR FOUR
WITNESSES INCLUDING ACTING
WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF
MICK MULVANEY AND FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON.
McCONNELL MAY HAVE OTHER
IDEAS IF SOME REPUBLICANS
INCLUDING LINDSEY GRAHAM WANT
TO WRAP THIS UP QUICKLY.
>> WELL, I'D TELL THE
PRESIDENT SOMEBODY'S RED TO
ACQUIT YOU I WOULD SORT OF GET
OUT OF THE WAY.
>> AND AS PART OF THE PROCESS
DEMOCRATS WILL HAVE TO DECIDE
WHO WILL ACT AS THE
IMPEACHMENT MANAGERS
ESPECIALLY THE PROSECUTORS WHO
WILL MAKE THE CASE AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT.
STEVE AND ALLISON, BACK TO
YOU.
>> MAUREEN THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> THERE'S BEEN AN ARREST IN
CONNECTION TO THE DEADLY
SHOOTING AT A JERSEY CITY
KOSHER MARKET.
THIS COMES AFTER A HANDWRITTEN
NOTE LED OFFICIALS 35-YEAR-OLD
AHMED AHADI.
HIS PHONE NUMBER WAS FOUND IN
THE BACK POCKET OF ONE OF THE
SOURCES INVOLVED IN THE
SHOOTING ALONG WITH A ADDRESS
FOR HIS PAWNSHOP.
DAVID ANDERSON AND FRANCINE
GRAHAM KILLED FOUR PEOPLE
DURING A SHOOTING SPREE BEFORE
BEING KILLED IN A SHOOTOUT
WITH POLICE.
ANTISEMITISM WAS LIKE A MOTIVE
BUT IT'S BEING INVESTIGATED AS
AN AN ACTS OF DOMESTIC
TERRORISM.
>>> IN NEW ZEALAND A MINUTE OF
SILENCE WAS HELD AT THE MOMENT
THAT A VOLCANO ERUPTED ONE
WEEK AGO KILLING 18 PEOPLE.
TWO BODIES HAVE YET TO BE
RECOVERED FROM WHITE ISLAND.
ONE BODY IS BELIEVED TO BE IN
THE WATER AROUND THE ISLAND.
THE OTHERS LOCATION IS
UNKNOWN.
LAND AND S SEA SURGES
UNSUCCESSFUL.
MOST OF THE 47 PEOPLE ON THE
ISLAND AT THE TIME IT ERUPTED
WERE TOURISTS INCLUDING
SEVERAL AMERICANS.
>> THIS YEAR'S ARMY/NAVY
FOOTBALL GAME STIRRING UP
CONTROVERSY.
MILITARY LEADERS ARE
INVESTIGATING SERVICE ACADEMY
STUDENTS WHO FLASHED HAND
SIGNS ON NATIONAL TV PROMOTING
WHITE SUPREMACY.
THEY WERE SEEN HOLDING THE
SIGNS ASSOCIATED WITH WHITE
POWER AT THE GAME IN
PHILADELPHIA, A GAME IN WHICH
THE PRESIDENT ATTENDED.
PEOPLE ON SOCIAL MEDIA POINT
OUT THAT THIS COULD ALSO BE
THE CIRCLE GAME WHEN SOMEONE
MAKES A CIRCLE WITH THEIR
FINGERS TRYING TO CONVINCE
SOMEONE ELSE TO LOOK AND IF
THEY DO SO THAT PERSON GETS A
PUNCH IN THE SHOULDER.
THAT'S HOW IT WAS BACK IN THE
DAY.
REGARDLESS MILITARY OFFICIALS
FROM BOTH THE NAVAL ACADEMY
AND WEST POINT SAY
INTERLOOKING INTO IT.
>>> HALLMARK CHANNEL TRENDING.
CAME UNDER FIRE AFTER PULLING
AN AD FEATURING A SAME-SEX
COUPLE.
AND THEN PUTTING IT BACK ON.
WHAT THE COMPANY IS NOW
SAYING.
>> PLUS BOB HAS SOME COMMUTER
NEWS IN MARYLAND.
BOB, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD
MORNING, ALLISON AND STEVE.
YES, HIT THE BRAKES, FOLKS.
PLANS TO BRING TOLL LANES TO
THE BELTWAY AND I-270 HERE IN
MARYLAND, WELL, THEY'RE PRETTY
MUCH UP IN THE AIR THIS
MORNING.
WE'LL EXPLAIN WHY WHEN FOX5
NEWS MORNING ROUNDS THE BEND.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
(Military Mom)
Love you, miss you guys!
(Military Mom's Family)
Love you!
♪
(Joy Ofodu)
We got this!
♪
(Kids)
Wow! Santa was here!
(Military Mom's Husband)
Whoa.
How did this happen?
(Military Mom)
I think I know.
(Military Mom's Husband)
Merry Christmas honey.
(Military Mom)
Merry Christmas!
(Kids)
Look, it's snowing.
♪
OK, network inspection.
OK.
Connected to WiFi,
protected from threats.
Thermostat -
connected, protected.
Speaker, space vacuum...
Connected, protected. Shh.
Eh, this is not
connected or protected.
But, that's a family heirloom.
And, it's a family
security breach. It's gotta go.
With Xfinity xFi, if it's
connected, it's protected.
Pull the truck around.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
Internet for $39.99 a month
for 12 months.
Plus, ask about enhanced
network security
for all your
connected devices.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
>> ♪
>> MELANIE, GOOD MORNING.
WHAT ARE YOU AND WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
>> Reporter: WE'RE BACK IN
FREDERICK COUNTY.
WE'RE ON ROUTE 109.
IT LOOKS SO PRETTY OUT HERE.
WE REALLY HAVE NOT HAD A LOT
OF WIND SO IT'S THAT KIND OF
SNOW THAT JUST GETS ALONG THE
TREE BRANCHES, COATS THE EDGES
AND SITS THERE AND REALLY JUST
MAKES SUCH A WONDERFUL WINTER
SILHOUETTE.
ON THE ROADS OF COURSE NOT SO
WONDERFUL.
WE'RE SEEING THEY ARE MOSTLY
WET, PERHAPS IN SOME OF THE
SUBURBS IF YOUR STREETS HAVE
NOT BEEN TREATED YOU MIGHT
HAVE BEEN A LITTLE BIT OF SNOW
AND SLUSH THIS MORNING.
WE DID SEE THAT IN PARTS IN
THE RESIDENTIAL AREAS.
IT'S CAUSED A LOT OF SLOWDOWNS
THIS MORNING ON THE ROADS AS
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO KIND OF
GET THEIR SNOW FEET I WOULD
SAY BACK UNDERNEATH THEM SINCE
THIS IS REALLY THE FIRST TIME
WE'VE HAD TO SIGNIFICANTLY
DEAL WITH ALL OF THIS.
FREDERICK COUNTY SCHOOLS, THEY
JUST ANNOUNCED THAT THEY ARE
CLOSED.
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO FREDERICK
CITY GOVERNMENT WAS ON LIBERAL
LEAVE.
WE'LL KEEP CHECKING BACK TO
SEE IF THAT SITUATION HAS
CHANGED AS WELL BUT RELATIVELY
DRY OUT HERE RIGHT NOW, JUST A
LOT OF ROAD SPRAY BUT WE DO
HEAR FROM OUR WEATHER FOLKS
CAN HE COULD BE EXPECTING
ANOTHER BAND COMING THROUGH.
WE'LL BE ON IT WHEN IT DOES.
>> MEL THANKS SO MUCH.
>> SPEAKING OF THAT NEXT BAND
COMING THROUGH LET'S GET
DETAILS FROM TUCKER.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, STEVE.
FOR THE MOST PART THE WINTRY
PART OF THIS STORM SYSTEM
GOING TO WRAP UP HERE PRETTY
QUICKLY HERE IN THE NEXT HOUR
OR TWO.
SNOW TOTALS, NOT TERRIBLY
IMPRESSIVE BUT ENOUGH AS YOU
SAW IN THAT LIVE SHOT WITH MEL
TO COAT THE GROUND IN SOME
SPOTS.
WINCHESTER ABOUT AN INCH UP IN
COLUMBIA .6, HALF INCH IN
LEESBURG.
IF YOU WANT TO SEND MOW YOUR
SNOW TOTALS PO PLEASE THEM SEND
THEM IN.
A BOX OF FRUIT LOOPS.
STORM TRACKER RADAR.
LOTS HAPPENING HERE.
PURPLES INDICATING WHERE THE
SNOW IS STILL COMING DOWN.
POSSIBLE WE HAVE A NICE LITTLE
SNOW BAND HERE IN THE NORTHERN
PART OF D.C.
AND THEN SOME LIGHT SNOW
SHOWERS OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST.
IT'S MIXING HERE JUST TO THE
SOUTH AND EAST OUT TOWARDS
ANNAPOLIS NOW WE'RE GETTING A
MIX BUT THIS WILL BE THE THEME
AS WE SEE THIS QUICK BURST OF
WINTER EARLY THIS MORNING
TRANSITION AND CHANGE OVER TO
ALL RAIN IN THE NEXT FEW
HOURS.
AGAIN, WE'RE WARMING UP THE
ATMOSPHERE SEVERAL THOUSAND
FEET UP AND AS THAT PROCESS
OCCURS, THIS WILL CHANGE OVER
TO ALL RAIN FOR EVERYBODY
LATER THIS MORNING AND FOR
MUCH OF THE AFTERNOON.
BIG PICTURE, YOU CAN SEE THAT
WARMER AIR, A WARM FRONT
PUSHING IN FROM THE SOUTH AND
WEST AND THINGS WILL GRADUALLY
START TO AGAIN TAPER OFF HERE.
THE RAIN WE'RE EXPECTING LATER
THIS MORNING AND THIS
AFTERNOON SHOULD BE ON THE
LIGHT SIDE.
DAYTIME HIGHS WILL BE ABOUT 40 E
PLENTY WARM THAT ANY LIGHT
SNOWS WE'RE GETTING OUT THERE
SHOULD MELT BUT RIGHT NOW 35
IN WASHINGTON.
NOTICE NORTH AND WEST YOU GUYS
ARE REALLY FLIRTING WITH THAT
FREEZING MARK, GAITHERSBURG,
FREDERICK OUT IN THE
MOUNTAINS, WINCHESTER
32 DEGREES SO IT'S OFF TOWARDS
THE NORTH AND WEST WHERE YOU
COULD ENCOUNTER A SLICK SPOT
OF ICE ON SOME OF THE ROADS.
THE REST OF US ARE ABOVE
FREEZING WHICH IS GREAT NEWS.
I THINK THINGS WILL JUST BE
WET AS YOU SEE THAT SNOW
COMING DOWN.
40 THIS AFTERNOON.
50 TOMORROW.
AGAIN, WE WARM IT UP LATER
TODAY SO ANY SNOW YOU GET NOW
SHOULD CHANGE TO RAIN IN THE
NEXT COUPLE HOURS AND THEN
LIGHT RAIN SHOWERS TOMORROW.
QUIET THE REST OF THE WEEK IF
YOU'RE GETTING OUT THERE AND
TRAVELING.
I KNOW WE'RE GETTING VERY
CLOSE TO CHRISTMAS.
ERIN, HOW ARE THE ROADS.
>> 7:18 AND WE HAVE OUR FAIR
SHARE OF PROBLEMS ON THE ROADS
WITH THIS WINTRY MIX COMING
DOWN.
INCLUDING CONSTRUCTION AS WELL
BAY BRIDGE WESTBOUND SIDE OF
THINGS AS YOU HEAD FROM THE
EASTERN SHORE TOWARD
ANNAPOLIS, THE WESTBOUND RIGHT
LANE IS STILL TAKEN OUT.
MILES OF BACKED UP TRAFFIC.
WATCH OUT FOR SLOW CONDITIONS.
OUTER LOOP DOWN TO 8 MILES PER
HOUR 95 OVER TO 270 VERY SLICK
CONDITIONS POTENTIAL THE
HYDROPLANE AS WELL AS THE
POTENTIAL FOR SLICK SPOTS
ESPECIALLY BRIDGES OVERPASSES
ON AND OFF RAMPS THAT TEND TO
FREEZE FIRST.
270 VERY SLOW AS WELL
FREDERICK DOWN TO THE BELTWAY.
LOOK AT THAT.
WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF SLOW
MOVING TRAFFIC.
YOU CAN SEE THE SNOW IN THE
GRASSY AREAS MORE OF A RAINY
MIX ON THE ROADS THEMSELVES.
66 WESTBOUND LEFT LANE BLOCKED
AT NUTLEY BY AN EARLIER CRASH
TAKING OUT SEVERAL LANES.
BACKED UP WELL BEFORE THE
BELTWAY.
INNER LOOP JAMS FROM THE
SPRINGFIELD INTERCHANGE
THROUGH 66.
SEEING A LOT OF SLOW MOVING
TRAFFIC EVERYWHERE FROM THESE
WET SLICK CONDITIONS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> 7:19.
HAPPENING TODAY MARYLAND
GOVERNOR LARRY HOGAN'S
$9 BILLION PLAN TO WIDEN AND
ADD NEW TOLL LANES TO REDUCE
TRAFFIC ON I-270 IS HITTING
MORE ROAD BLOCKS.
>> IT'S A TROUBLED PLAN THAT
KEEPS GETTING MORE
CONTROVERSIAL.
FOX5's BOB BARNARD OUT IN
THE ELEMENTS LI LIVE IN BETHESDA
WITH US WITH THE VERY LATEST.
>> Reporter: THE PLAN IS YES
TO WIDEN THE BELTWAY HERE AND
270, ADD SOME TOLL LANES TO
EASE CONGESTION WHICH RIGHT
NOW EVEN THOUGH THE SNOW HAS
TURNED TO RAIN THE ROADS ARE
NOT FROZEN AND SO FAR SO GOOD.
BUT THIS IS A CHRONIC ISSUE.
IT'S GOING TO BE WORSE IN THE
FUTURE.
AND SO WHAT THE GOVERNOR WANTS
TO DO IS ADD THESE TOLL LANES.
WIDEN THE BELTWAY AND 270.
BUT THE DEMOCRATIC COMPTROLLER
OF MARYLAND PETER FRANCHOT IS
SAYING HOLD ON.
WE AND WANT THE ENVIRONMENTAL
IMPACT STUDIES DONE BEFORE THE
MARYLAND DEPARTMENT OF
TRANSPORTATION GOES OUT AND
SEEKS BIDS FROM PRIVATE
COMPANIES TO DO THE WOULD,
WHICH WAS THE PLAN.
THERE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A
MARYLAND BOARD OF PUBLIC WORKS
MEETING ON WEDNESDAY.
IT'S THREE MEMBERS.
THE REPUBLICAN GOVERNOR LARRY
HOGAN, THE DIPLOMATIC
COMPTROLLER MR. FRANCHOT AND
NANCY COX.
YOU NEED TWO OF THREE VOTES.
PETER FRANCHOT IN JUNE SAID
YES.
NOW HE'S SAYING NO ACCORDING
TO THE "WASHINGTON POST."
SO, THE GOVERNOR HAS TAKEN
THAT PUBLIC WORKS MEETING OFF
THE SCHEDULE FOR WEDNESDAY SO
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS GOING
FORWARD.
IN THE MEANTIME, A NUMBER OF
MARYLAND, MONTGOMERY COUNTY
SPECIFICALLY ELECTED
OFFICIALS, THE COUNTY
EXECUTIVE AND MEMBERS OF THE
COUNTY COUNCIL ARE PLANNING A
COMMUNITY RALLY TONIGHT AT THE
SILVER SPRING CIVIC CENTER.
THAT'S SCHEDULED FOR 7 O'CLOCK
TONIGHT.
THEY ARE OPPOSED TO THE
GOVERNOR'S PLANS AS THEY STAND
NOW WHICH WOULD BE TO WIDEN
AND DO THE WORK ON THE BELTWAY
BEFORE 270.
IN JUNE IT WAS ANNOUNCED IT
WOULD BE THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CONFUSING.
THERE ARE A LOT OF HICCUPS IN
THE ROADWAY HERE BUT THAT
COMMUNITY MEETING SET FOR
7 O'CLOCK TONIGHT IN SILVER
SPRING IS GOING FORWARD WHILE
THE BOARD OF PUBLIC WORKS
MEETING WHICH WAS THAT
SCHEDULED FOR WEDNESDAY WHICH
WAS THE REAL WORK TO GET THIS
THING GOING IS ON HOLD, GUYS.
>> BOB, QUICK QUESTION FOR
YOU.
WHERE YOU ARE SPECIFICALLY,
RAIN OR SNOW RIGHT NOW?
>> Reporter: IT'S RAIN MORE
SO.
WE WERE ON AT 6:30.
I'LL LET INDIRA SHOW YOU THE
ROAD HERE.
IT'S TURNED TO RAIN.
EVEN WHEN IT WAS SNOWING IT
WAS NEVER REALLY STICKING ON
THE BELTWAY HERE AND THE ROAD
SURFACES DOWN HERE IN THE
LOWER PART OF THE COUNTY, I
KNOW THEY'VE CLOSED THE
SCHOOLS NOW, DOWN HERE THE
ROADS ARE FINE AND IT IS NOW
RAIN HERE IN BETHESDA BUT YOU
KNOW, YOU GO UP TO DAMASCUS
OUT TO POOLESVILLE, IT COULD
BE A DIFFERENT SITUATION AND
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY SCHOOL
OFFICIALS HERE IN MONTGOMERY
COUNTY HAVE CANCELED CLASSES
FOR THE DAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
APPRECIATE YOU DOUBLE TEAMING
THE STORY, BOB THANKS MUCH.
IT'S 7:22.
>> STILL AHEAD HOLIDAY CHEER
IN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY.
MIKE ON LOCATION IN
WOODBRIDGE.
THAT'S COMING UP FOR YOU.
>> ALSO A LIVE LOOK AT
NATIONAL HARBOR IN MARYLAND.
MORE SNOW TURNING TO RAIN
THERE.
BUT PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
GETTING SOME SNOW IN OTHER
PARTS OF THE COUNTY.
THAT'S KIND OF THE WAY IT IS
RIGHT NOW.
SOME PLACES RAIN, SOME PLACES
SNOW.
YOU GOT IT ALL COVERED RIGHT
HERE THOUGH.
TUCKER HAS GOT YOUR FORECAST
COMING UP NEXT.
>> ♪
Step right up!
Try the all new Tyson
Air Fried Chicken.
With 75% less fat.
It's all pleasure and no guilt.
Plus we air fry it
before you buy it.
It's the best thing to happen
to fried chicken since...
fried chicken.
>> ♪ 7: 25.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO TUCKER WITH
A CHECK ON WHAT'S HAPPENING
OUT THERE.
THERE YOU SEE MORE OF THE ROAD
CONDITIONS.
LOOKS GOOD THERE, TUCK BUT WE
KNOW IN SOME OTHER PLACES IT'S
STILL A LITTLE DISSEE.
>>  DICEY.
>> 35 DEGREES AND THE SNOW IS
CHANGING PRETTY QUICKLY TO A
LIGHT RAIN, A LIGHT DRIZZLE.
AND THAT IS WHAT WE CAN EXPECT
FOR MUCH OF OUR DAY TODAY,
JUST LIGHT RAIN AND DRIZZLE
AROUND LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
TEMPS ARE ONLY GOING UP FROM
HERE.
ANY THREAT WE HAVE AS FAR AS
WINTER WEATHER SHOULD PRETTY
QUICKLY DISSIPATE IN THE NEXT
HOUR OR SO.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE SEEING SOME
RAIN START TO MIX IN WITH THE
SNOW.
BOB MENTIONED IT.
AND AREAS IN PURPLE HERE JUST
OFF TO THE NORTH SIDE OF THE
BELTWAY, EAST SIDE OF THE
BELTWAY, IT'S LIKELY OUT
TOWARDS CROFTON BOWIE AND
ANNAPOLIS, YOU'RE STILL MIXING
WITH SNOW OUT THERE BUT AGAIN,
THE GREEN IS STARTING TO WIN
OUT.
THAT'S THE RAIN IN SOUTHERN
PARTS OF THE BELTWAY HERE AND
IT WILL CERTAINLY TURN INTO A
LIGHT RAIN, CLOUDY, OVERCAST
AND GLOOMY DAY NO DOUBT ABOUT
IT BUT IT WILL NOT BE A SNOWY
AFTERNOON.
40 TODAY.
50 TOMORROW.
MORE SHOWERS TONIGHT INTO
EARLY TOMORROW.
ERIN, YOU CAN JAM IT.
>> UNFORTUNATELY THERE'S LOTS
TO JAM TODAY.
7:26.
AND THAT WINTRY MIX WET COLD
CONDITIONS, 66 WESTBOUND
REALLY HEAVY DELAYS BECAUSE OF
AN EARLIER CRASH BLOCKING THE
LEFT LANE BY NUTLEY.
DELAYS BACK TO INSIDE THE
BELTWAY.
INNER LOOP JAMS COMPLETELY
FROM THE SPRINGFIELD
INTERCHANGE THROUGH 66.
HEAVY EASTBOUND DELAYS
MANASSAS THROUGH THE BELTWAY.
28 NORTHBOUND THERE'S STILL A
CRASH BLOCKING ALL LANES SOUTH
OF 66 IN MANASSAS BETWEEN
MAPLEWOOD DRIVE AND RUGBY
ROAD.
YOU'LL HAVE TO DETOUR AROUND
THAT.
HEAVY NORTHBOUND SLOWDOWNS
THERE.
KEEP IT TO FOX5.
MUCH MORE ON THIS WINTRY
WEATHER AND HOW IT'S IMPACTING
YOUR RIDE THIS MONDAY MORNING
AS WE CONTINUE.
>> ♪
At Hertz, we know
that a change of scenery
shouldn't mean
a change in standards.
That's why
- thanks to you -
we're rated number one
in customer satisfaction
by J.D. Power.
♪
TAKING A LOOK AT A COUPLE THINGS
THERE.
ONE, IF YOU WANT TO SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN REAL TIME, THAT'S A
LOOK AT NATIONAL HARBOR IN
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY LOOKING
AT THE WILSON BRIDGE AND THEN IF
IT WASN'T SO SNOWY, RAINY,
CLOUDY OUT THERE YOU'D BE ABLE
TO SEE PARTS OF NORTHERN
VIRGINIA AND D.C.
WE HAVE WEATHER CONDITIONS OUT
THERE WHICH IS ILLUSTRATED
FURTHER BY THE RADAR ON THE
RIGHT OF THE 15.
ALTHOUGH A LOT OF THAT SNOW IS
STARTING TO WORK ITS WAY OUT OF
HERE RIGHT NOW.
AT LEAST THE IMMEDIATE D.C. AREA
WITH A LOT OF THAT TURNING TO
RAIN.
SO WE'LL GET AN UPDATE FROM
TUCKER COMING UP IN JUST A
COUPLE OF MINUTES MUCH WEATHER
AND TRAFFIC ON THE 5'S AT 7:35.
WE HAVE SCHOOL CLOSINGS IN THE
AREA.
SOME OUT TO THE WEST OF D.C.
SPEAKING OF NORTHERN VIRGINIA
DEPUTY SAYS HE HAS A PLAN TO
RESPOND TO THE DEMOCRATIC LED
LEGISLATION IN VIRGINIA IF
ENACTS GUN CONTROL MEASURES
DURING A BOARD OF SUPERVISORS
MEETING EARLIER THIS MOTT BOARD
UNANIMOUSLY DECLARED THE COUNTY
A SECOND AMENDMENT
CONSTITUTIONAL COUNTY AND THE
SHERIFF VOTE -- VOWED I SHOULD
SAY TO DEPUTY PIES CULPEPER
COUNTY RESIDENTS.
>> IT WILL BE MY INTENT IF
LEGISLATURE DECIDES TO RESTRICT
CERTAIN WEAPONS THAT I FEEL ARE
HARM TO OUR COMMUNITY, I WILL
LOOK TO SWEAR IN THOUSANDS OF
AUXILIARY DEPUTIES IN CULPEPER
OF PEOPLE WHO ARE WILLING TO
PASS A BACKGROUND CHECK, UM,
PROPER SCREENING MUST BE DONE,
BUT, UM, OUR AUXILIARIES ARE
REQUIRED TO WORK AT LEAST EIGHT
HOURS A MONTH IN SERVICE TO OUR
DEPARTMENT.
THAT MAY BE SERVICE ALL AROUND
THE COUNTY FOR OTHER THINGS.
BUT, UM, THERE'S NO LIMIT ON THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE I CAN SWEAR IN
AS A DEPUTY SHERIFF.
>> NUMBER OF COUNTIES IN THE
STATE HAVE PASSED SIMILAR
RESOLUTIONS IN RESPONSE TO
EXPECTED GUN CONTROL LEGISLATION
WHICH GOVERNOR NORTHAM SAYS
DEMOCRATS WILL PUSH FOR SINCE IT
REGAINED CONTROL OF THE VIRGINIA
GENERAL ASSEMBLY.
SO WHAT DOES THIS ALL MEAN?
WHAT IS THE BREAK DOWN FOR FOLKS
IN CULPEPER COUNTY WILL THIS
REVERBERATE IN OTHER PARTS OF
THE STATE AND COMMONWEALTH.
SHERIFF SCOTT JENKINS JOINS US
LIVE THIS MORNING.
WE REACHED OUT TO OTHER COUNTIES
WHO ALREADY PASSED THIS ALLEGES
LAYER IT BUT NO ONE ACCEPTED OUR
INVITATION.
>> THANK YOU FOR INK?  US.
SECOND AMENDMENT CONSTITUTIONAL
COUNTY WHAT IN YOUR EYES DOES
THAT ENTAIL?
>> THAT'S A GESTURE BY OUR
COUNTY BOARD OF SUPERVISE TO LET
EVERYONE KNOW THEY FEEL STRONGLY
ABOUT THE PROPOSED LEGISLATION
GOING TO THE RICHMOND AFTER
FIRST OF THE YEAR AS OVER 70
OTHER COUNTIES IN THE STATE SO
FAR HAVE DONE THE SAME.
>> SO BREAK IT DOWN FOR US IN
REAL TERMS.
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING ON DOING
AND IS IT BASED ON ACTION FROM
THE STATE LEGISLATURE FIRST OR
DO YOU WANT TO BE PRO ACT THINK
OF IN THIS MEASURE?
>> I'M GOING TO WAIT HOPEFULLY
THE MEASURES THEY'RE HOPING TO
APPROVE WON'T ACTUALLY PASS, AND
WON'T BE NECESSARY, BUT IF THEY
DO ENACT THOSE LAWS THAT THEY'RE
PROPOSING, RESTRICTING
EVERYTHING FROM SO-CALLED
ASSAULT WEAPONS TO HIGH CAPACITY
MAGAZINES AND OTHER THINGS LET
ALONE THE RED FLAG LAWS, UM, MY
STANCE WILL BE TO IF NEED BE IF
IT'S PASSED SWEAR IN HUNDREDS OR
EVEN THOUSANDS OF CITIZENS AS
AUXILIARY DEPUTIES.
WE HAVE THOUSANDS OF CONCEALED
CARRY PERMIT HOLDERS IN THE CUN
TEE CURRENT WHO'LL HAVE NO ISSUE
WHATSOEVER AND ENCOURAGE PEOPLE
TO HAVE CONCEALED CARRY PERMITS.
BUT WHAT THEIR INTENT WHAT THEY
HOPE TO ACHIEVE BY THIS
LEGISLATION IT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
THE CLINTON AIR GUN BAN WAS
PROOF OF THAT FOR 10 YEARS.
STATISTICS DON'T BEAR ANYTHING
TO PROVE THAT IT'S GOING TO BE
EFFECTIVE.
SO WHY THEY'RE GOING TO TRY THIS
BILL WHICH IS BASICALLY THE THAT
BAN ON STEROIDS IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> THOSE WHO DON'T AGREE WITH
USHER RIFF WOULD SAY BASED ON
YOUR COMMENT RIGHT THERE THE
CERTAIN WEAPONS HIGH CAPACITY
MAGAZINES THOSE TYPE OF WEAPONS
SOME MIGHT QUESTION WHY THOSE
ARE NECESSARILY FROM FLARING
SOMEONE FROM A LAW ENFORCEMENT
BACKGROUND.
>> WELL, THE FACT THAT THE LAW
ABIDING CITIZENS POSSESS THEM
FOR EVERYTHING FROM SPORT
SHOOTING, HUNTING AND ON THE
USES ARE HOME DEFENSE.
THOSE AREN'T THE PEOPLE WE'RE
HAVING THE PROBLEMS WITH.
CRIMINALS ARE GOING TO OBTAIN
THOSE WEAPONS REGARDLESS OF WHAT
LAWS ARE PASSED, AND IT'S
RIDICULOUS TO THINK THAT IT'S
GOING TO HAVE ANY EFFECT ON THE
ACTUAL CRIME.
THEY LIKE TO SPOUT FIGURES
STATISTICS ON SHOOTING DEATHS
AND CRIME WITH VARIOUS TYPES OF
WEAPONS BUT WHEN YOU REALLY
DRILL DOWN A LOOK AT THE
STATISTICS FOR WHAT THEY ARE,
THEY JUST DON'T BEAR WHAT THEY
SAY THEY WILL.
>> THERE ARE OTHERS WHO MIGHT
SAY THAT YOUR JOB SHERIFF IS TO
ENFORCE THE LAW, NOT MAKE THE
LAW OR MAKE CHANGES TO THE LAWS
OR AS SOME MIGHT EVEN SAY,
CIRCUMVENT THE LAW BY MAKING
CHANGES AND NOT LISTENING TO
WHAT'S HAPPENING DOWN IN
RICHMOND.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND THAT.
>> HE'LL BE CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
I'M NOT CIRCUMVENT THE LAW.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, UNLIKE
SHERIFFS ALL OVER THE
COMMONWEALTH OF UNITED STATES
HAVE SAID THEY WON'T ENFORCE
LAWS THAT ARE PASSED, I HAVE
BEEN FIRST SO FAR I THINK THE
ONLY ONE WHO HAS SAID I WILL NOT
SAY THAT I WON'T ENFORCE LAWS
THAT ARE DULY PASSED.
I SAID WHEN I ORIGINALLY
ANNOUNCED ELECTIONS HAVE
CONSEQUENCES AND THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE GETTING THE RESULT OF THAT
ELECTION I DO HAVE A LEGAL RIGHT
TO SWEAR IN DEPUTIES AND THAT'S
BEEN THE SAME FOR HUNDREDS OF
YEARS HERE IN THE COMMONWEALTH
FOR ANY SHERIFF.
>> OTHERS MIGHT SAY THAT MIGHT
BE OKAY FOR A HANDFUL OF PEOPLE
IF YOU DEPTH TIES HUNDREDS OR
THOUSANDS THAT SOUNDS LIKE A
MILITIA IN THE MAKING.
>> THEY'LL BE PROPERLY AND
SCREENED AND VETTED THEY'RE THE
SAME CITIZENS I CURRENTLY SERVE
AND PUT ME IN OFFICE.
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT DESERVE
EVERYTHING I CAN DO IN MY POWER
TO PROTECT THEM AND PROTECT
THEIR CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS.
IT'S MY DUTY.
>> SHERIFF, WE DO APPRECIATE YOU
JOINING US THIS MORNING.
ONE OFF TOPIC QUESTION SINCE YOU
CAME IN FROM CULPEPER.
HOW ARE THE ROADS.
>> LITTLE ICY WHEN WE GOT CLOSER
INTO D.C.
NOT TOO BAD OVERALL.
>> SHERIFF JENKINS THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US THIS MORNING.
WE APPRECIATE IT THAT WAS.
>> THANK YOU FOR THE
OPPORTUNITY.
>> IT'S 7:35.
LET'S GOOD A LOOK WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
WHERE IS THE SNOW HEADED NOW,
TUCK.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING WE'RE
WATCHING A QUICK TRANSACTION
FROM A SNOWY SEEN A COUPLE HOURS
AGO TO MOSTLY RAIN ACROSS THE
REGION AT THE MOMENT HERE
ALTHOUGH WE'RE STILL SEEING KIND
OF A RAIN/SNOW MIX IN ACROSS THE
IMMEDIATE WASHINGTON AREA.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT IS A VERY COMPLICATED STORM
TRACKER RADAR FOR YOU BUT THE
BOTTOM LINE IS, ANY SNOW YOU'LL
YOU'RE GET AT YOUR HOUSE AT THE
MOMENT SHOULD CHANGE OVER TO
RAIN HERE IN THE NEXT HOUR OR
TWO.
VERY LIGHT STUFF OFF TO THE
NORTH AND WEST NOW, AND IT LOOKS
LIKE THE BULK OF THE ACTIVITY
WORKING THROUGH THE CITY AND
POINTS SOUTH AND AGAIN WE'VE
SEEN THAT KIND OF RAIN/SNOW LINE
RIGHT THROUGH D.C. HERE IN THE
PAST HOUR OR SO.
BIG PICTURE, IT'S GOING TO BE
LIGHT RAIN SHOWERS FOR ALL OF US
LATER THIS AFTERNOON, AS WARMER
AIR IS ABLE TO SURGE IN HERE
FROM THE SOUTH AND WEST.
ANY LIGHT SNOW ACCUMULATION AT
YOUR HOUSE EARLY THIS MORNING
SHOULD MELT OFF AS DAYTIME HIGHS
UP NEAR 40 AND CAN EXPECT LIGHT
RAIN ACROSS THE REGION LATER
TODAY.
REAL QUICK, THAT WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORY CONTINUES NORTH AND
WEST.
ALL OF MONTGOMERY AND HOWARD
COUNTIES, PARTS OF LOUDOUN
COUNTY UNTIL 1:00 O'CLOCK THIS
AFTERNOON, AND AGAIN RAIN SH
SHOWERS SHOULD TAPER OFF HERE,
REAL LIGHT LATER THIS AFTERNOON
SOME JUST SHOWERS AROUND DAYTIME
HIGHS ABOUT 40.
PLENTY MORE ON THE FORECAST
WEEVIL LOOK AT HOW MUCH SNOW WE
PICKED UP IN THE PAST HOUR OR
TWO THE IN JUST A MINUTE.
ERIN G MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
7:36.
KEEPING OUR EYES ON THE ROADS.
[ INAUDIBLE ]
WE'RE HAVING TROUBLE HEARING YOU
RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL STEAL IT FROM YOU AND GIVE
THE OPPORTUNITY TO TALK MORE
BOUT ROADS IN JUST A FEW
MINUTES.
IN THE MEANTIME, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE TOP DESTINATION
PERHAPS FOR THOSE WHO REALLY
WANT TO GET AWAY.
>> OKAY.
THE TOP TOURIST DESTINATION FOR
THE YEAR IS... WE'LL HAVE THAT
ANSWER FOR YOU NEXT.
>> I THINK SOME PLACE WITH HIGH
ALTITUDE AND VERY FAR.
AND NOT WHAT YOU WOULD THINK.
TURNS OUT, TAPPING THE TOP OF
YOUR CAN, YOUR SODA, YOUR BEER
CAN, PREVENT FIZZ FROM GOING
EVERYWHERE DOESN'T WORK AFTER
ALL.
THE SCIENCE BEHIND IT COMING UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TAKE LIVE LOOK AT OXON HILL,
MARYLAND, AS WE TAKE YOU TO THE
BREAK.
LOOKS LIKE SOME WET WEATHER OUT
THERE ON THE ROADS.
FOLKS TAKING IT NICE AND SLOW.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK CONTINUING
TO TRACK THIS WINTER WEATHER ON
A MONDAY.
♪
>>> BACK NOW AT 7:40, COUNTRY
WITH THE WORLD'S HIGHEST PEAKS
HAS BEEN NAMED ONE TRAVEL --
NAMED NUMBER ONE TRAVEL
MAGAZINE'S TOP DESTINATION FOR
2020.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT PAKISTAN.
GRABBING THE TOP MUST SEE SPOT
FOR NEXT YEAR BY LUXURY AND
TRAVEL PUBLICATION TRAVELER.
THE PUBLICATION SITES PAKISTAN'
NATURAL FEATURES SUCH AS HIGH
MOUNTAIN PEAKS.
COUNTRY NEAR AND DEAR TO MY
HEART.
>> ABSOLUTELY GORGEOUS NATURE.
>> YES.
>> GOING TO BE A TOUGH SELL FOR
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
VERY VERY FAR AWAY A LITTLE
PRICEY.
>> MY FATHER SERVED AS A PEACE
CORPS VOLUNTEER THERE IN THE
EARLY '60S THAT'S WHY IT'S NEAR
AND DEAR TO MY HEART.
>> WINDS.
>> Y.
>>> TAPPING THE SIDES OF YOUR
BEER CAN, SODA CAN, YOUR POP
CAN, IF YOU'RE FROM THOSE PARTS
OF THE COUNTRY, TO PREVENT FIZZ
FROM GOING EVERYWHERE A MYTH.
TEAM OF SCIENTISTS TESTED 1,000
CANS OF BEER TO SEE IF THE CAN
TAPPING TRADITION REALLY HELPS
REDUCE AMOUNT OF FIZZY BUBBLES
IN THE DRINK.
GUESS WHAT THEY FOUND OUT?
RESEARCHERS GAVE ONE VOLUNTEER A
CAN THAT HAD BEEN SHAKEN, A
SECOND GROUP CANS LEFT UNTOUCHED
AND THE TAPPING DID NOTHING TO
HELP WITH THE AMOUNT OF FIZZ.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>>> 7:41 RIGHT NOW.
COMING UP NEXT CHANGE OF HEART
FROM THE HALLMARK CHANNEL
FOLLOWING A CONTROVERSIAL
COMMERCIAL.
>> PLUS ON THIS SNOWY MONDAY
MORNING LET'S GET INTO THE
HOLIDAY SPIRIT RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL HEAD DOWN TO PRINCE
WILLIAM COUNTY PART OF OUR
HOLIDAY LOCATION SERIES FOR YOU.
IN THE MEANTIME BEFORE WE GO GO
DISTRICT.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC ON THE 5'S
COMING UP NEXT.
♪
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
>>> IN TODAY'S BUSINESS BEAT
CHANGE OF HEART FROM THE
HALLMARK CHANNEL OVER A
CONTROVERSIAL COMMERCIAL.
FIRST THOUGH A QUICK CHECK OF
THE MARKETS JOINING US FROM THE
FOX BUSINESS NETWORK STUDIO ON A
MONDAY MORNING, TRACEE CARRASCO.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE SEEING FUTURES
POINTING HIGHER.
DOW FUTURES ARE UP BY 43 POINTS.
THIS AFTER THAT PHASE ONE OF THE
TRADE DEAL WITH CHINA WAS
REACHED ON FRIDAY.
WE SAW ALL THREE MAJOR U.S.
AVERAGES UP ON FRIDAY AS WELL
WITH THE S&P 500 AND NASDAQ BOTH
HITTING NEW RECORD HIGHS.
I DO WANT TO MENTION BOEING THIS
IS A STOCK WE'LL BE WATCHING
TODAY.
RIGHT NOW DOWN BY 4% IN THE PRE
MARKET.
REPORTS THAT BOEING MAY
TEMPORARILY SUSPECT OR CUT
PRODUCTION OF THE GROUNDED 737
MAX PLANES.
THAT IS MOVING THE STOCK THIS
MORNING.
SO WATCHING ALL OF THAT RIGHT
NOW.
>> OKAY.
FOR AWHILE WE WERE NOT WATCHING
A COMMERCIAL ON THE HALLMARK
CHANNEL.
NOW WE WILL BE WATCHING IT ONCE
AGAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> WELL, THE HALLMARK CHANNEL IS
REVERSING COURSE AFTER PULLING
ADS FROM SOLE LA THAT IS A
WEDDING PLANNING WEBSITE THAT
FEATURED A SAME SEX COUPLE, TWO
BRIDES KISSING.
THEY INITIALLY PULLED THE AD
AFTER THEY WERE -- CONTACTED BY
A CONSERVATIVE GROUP THAT SAID
THAT THEY DID NOT LIKE THE AD.
SO RATHER THAN GETTING IN THE
MIDDLE OF ANY SORT OF
CONTROVERSY, THEY SIMI PULLED
THE ADS.
HOWEVER THE HALLMARK CHANNEL
FINDING THEMSELVES NOW IN THE
MIDST OF A CONTROVERSY.
BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE
UPSET THAT THEY PULLED ITS THESE
ADS.
THERE WAS A TRENDING TOPIC ON
TWITTER HASH TAG BOYCOTT
HALLMARK CHANNEL.
A NUMBER OF CELEBRITIES
INCLUDING ELLEN DEGENERES AND
OTHER ADVOCACY GROUPS CAME OUT
AND SAID THIS WAS THE WRONG MOVE
THAT IS WHY THE HALLMARK CHANNEL
HAS REVERSED ITS DECISION SAYING
THAT THEY WILL NOT PULL THE ADS.
THEY SAID THAT IT WAS A MISTAKE
THAT THEY DIDN'T MEAN TO CAUSE
ANY HARM OR HURT ANYBODY.
SOLE LA THIS IS THE COMPANY AT
THE CENTER OF THIS.
THEY PUT OUT A TWEET YESTERDAY
THAT SAID ALL KISSES COUPLES AND
MARRIAGES ARE EQUAL CELEBRATIONS
OF LOVE.
OF COURSE, THIS COMES AT A TIME
WHEN THIS IS HALLMARK'S REALLY
BUSY SEASON AS FAR AS THEIR
CHANNEL GOES.
THEY'RE REALLY PUSHING A LOT OF
THOSE HOLIDAY MOVIES.
SO  A LOT OF EYES ON THE NETWORK
RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY.
SEEING WHAT THEY DO.
ALL RIGHTY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, TRACEE
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> THANKS, BYE-BYE.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>>> TUCKER BARNES, GOOD MORNING,
SIR.
>> GOOD MORNING.
LIGHT SNOW ACROSS THE AREA
QUICKLY CHANGING OVER TO RAIN.
IT WILL BE A MOSTLY RAIN EVENT
GOING FORWARD HERE.
BUT OUR SNOW TOTALS THANK YOU
FOR ZENNING THEM IN MARTINSBURG
ONE PENT 7 INCHES.
EYE THAT I GENE TEE IS THE
WINNER OF OUR SWEEP SAKES.
DULLES JUST REPORTING .40 OF AN
INCH OF SNOW.
AGAIN, LIGHT AMOUNTS HERE BUT
YOU KNOW THE TIMING ON IT SUCH
ARRIVING FIVE TO 6:00 THE IN
MORNING HERE CAUSING SOME ISSUES
OUT THERE.
THERE'S YOUR STORM TRACKER RADAR
AND HERE IN NORTHWEST D.C. I
JUST WENT OUTSIDE AND I CAN TELL
YOU THAT THE SNOW THAT WE HAD AN
HOUR AGO IS NOW TRANSITIONED A
VERY CHILLY RAIN OUT THERE.
AND WE CAN EXPECT RAIN SHOWERS
AND/OR SNOW MIXED IN LOOKS LIKE
PARTS OF AREA.
SEE THE PURPLE OUT TO THE EAST.
PARTS OF AREA COULD STILL BE
SEEING SOME SNOW MIXED IN IT
WILL CHANGE TO RAIN FOR ALL OF
US HERE.
MAYBE SLEET FOR A PERIOD OF TIME
AND THEN RAIN FOR EVERYBODY OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
JUST A COOL LIGHT RAIN EXPECTED
LATER THIS AFTERNOON WE DAYTIME
HIGHS ABOUT 40 DEGREES OR SO.
SO MAKE SURE YOU'RE READY AND
EQUIPPED HERE UMBRELLA WISE FOR
RAIN SHOWERS GOING FORWARD.
THERE'S THE SATELLITE/RADAR BIG
PICTURE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE
BACK HERE.
JUST A WARM FRONT AND AGAIN THE
WARM FRONT WILL GRADUALLY BRING
IN WARMER TEMPERATURES NOT JUST
AT THE SURFACE BUT A LOFT.
SO THE COLD POOL OF AREA WILL
GET PUSHED TO THE NORTH AND EAST
WE'LL BE LOOKING AT JUST LIGHT
RAIN AROUND HERE PRETTY MUCH IN
THE NEXT HOUR OR TWO IF YOU'RE
GETTING SNOW YOU SHOULD SEE IT
CHANGING TO ALL RAIN.
35 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
OKAY.
NORTH AND WEST THERE COULD BE A
SLIPPERY SPOT OR TWO.
YOU'RE HITTING THE FREEZING
MARK.
GAITHERSBURG, DULLES, FREDERICK,
MOUNTAINS BELOW FREEZING AT THE
MOMENT.
SO AGAIN THE POSSIBILITY OF SOME
RAIN THAT FREEZES ON CONTACT
HERE.
FREEZING RAIN STILL IN PLAY OFF
TO THE NORTH AND WEST AND THERE
IS WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY OFF
TO THE NORTH AND WEST UNTIL 1:0.
NOTICE FUTURE CAST NOT LOVING
THE IDEA OF MUCH OF ANYTHING
HERE AT NOON JUST SOME CLOUDS.
MAYBE WE'LL GET A FEW LIGHT
SPRINKLES AND SHOWERS THIS
AFTERNOON AT 4:00.
TEMPERATURES ABOUT 40 DEGREES.
PLENTY WARM OUT THERE.
GOT TO GET UP INTO CENTRAL
PENNSYLVANIA TO FIND ANY MORE
WINTER WEATHER WE'LL KEEP
SHOWERS AROUND TONIGHT INTO THE
FIRST PART OF TOMORROW BUT
NOTICE TOMORROW'S HIGH 50.
TOMORROW MORNING WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE ANY PROBLEMS COMMUTE WISE
WITH WINTER WEATHER.
SUN COMES BACK WEDNESDAY,
THURSDAY, FRIDAY GREAT SHOPPING
WEATHER BEFORE WINTER ARRIVES
EARLY.
>> GOOD TO KNOW ONLY SO MANY
DAYS LEFT BEFORE THE CHRISTMAS
HOLIDAY TO SHOP.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> RED LINE SINGLE TRACKING
TRACK PROBLEM AT FRIENDSHIP
BETWEEN FAR RUT AND GLOB
MONTGOMERY.
EXTRA TIME NEEDED.
ASIDE FROM THAT BAY BRIDGE
WESTBOUND DISABLE VEHICLE BLOCKS
THE CENTER LANE THAT'S IN
ADDITION TO THE RIGHT LANE.
IT'S TAKE OUT FOR LONG TERM
CONSTRUCTION.
HEAVY DELAYS FROM THE EASTERN
SHORE TOWARD ANNAPOLIS THIS
MORNING.
WET ROADS AS WELL POLICE EAST
CAPITAL STREET BETWEEN SIXTH AND
SEVENTH IN NORTHEAST.
YOU CAN SEE ALL OF THAT RED
AROUND THAT AREA WITH WET
CONDITIONS AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
SLICK SPOTS A LOT OF SLOW
TRAFFIC THIS CRASH STILL BLOCKS
THE LEFT LANE LEFT SHOULDER 66
WESTBOUND BY NUTLEY.
DELAYS BACK TO INSIDE THE
BELTWAY.
LOOK AT THAT INNER LOOP JAMMED
BACK TO THE SPRINGFIELD
INTERCHANGE.
VERY SLOW MOVING TRAFFIC 66
EASTBOUND WET SPOTS WITH
POTENTIAL FOR ICY CONDITIONS.
TAKE IT SLOW.
BACK TO YOU.
>>> BITTERSWEET WIN ON THE
FOOTBALL FIELD IN CONNECTICUT.
SEVEN YEARS TO THE DAY SINCE THE
SANDY HOOK SCHOOL SHOOTING
NEWTOWN HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL
TEAM WON THE STATE TITLE IN
DRAMATIC FASHION WINNING OH AND
A FINAL PLAY TOUCHDOWN PASS.
THE FIRST STATE CHAMPIONSHIP FOR
THE TOWN SINCE 1992 AND IT GETS
BETTER.
THE BROTHER OF ONE OF THE
YOUNGSTERS WHO WAS KILLED ONE OF
THE PLAYERS ON THE FIELD FOR
NEWTOWN.
>>> WOW.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>>> 7:50 ON THIS LITTLE BIT
DREARY MONDAY MORNING.
LET'S GET INTO THE HOLIDAY
SPIRIT, SHALL WE?  THERE ARE
PLENTY OFNESS TIFF THINGS TO DO
IN THE D.C. REGION.
TODAY WE THOUGHT WE'D TAKE A
LITTLE HOLIDAY ROAD TRIP.
>> SO MIKE THOMAS DID JUST THAT.
HE'S LIVE IN PRINCE WILLIAM
COUNTY.
FIVE HOLIDAY THINGS TO DO THERE.
MIKE, I KNOW YOU HAD YOUR EYE ON
THE WEATHER THE WHOLE DRIVE DOWN
THERE TO WOODBRIDGE.
WHAT DID YOU FIND ON THE WAY
DOWN THERE, FIRST OF ALL?
>> Reporter: A LOT OF RAIN ON
THE WAY DOWN HERE, STEVE AND
ALLISON.
WE'RE HERE IN PRINCE WILLIAM
COUNTY, YES, SCHOOLS ARE CLOSED
THIS MORNING BECAUSE OF ALL THE
SNOW YOU SEE BEHIND US.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M KIDDING AROUND.
THEY REALLILY BE CLOSED THOUGH.
THE WEATHER IT COULD BE BETTER
OUT THERE THIS MORNING BUT WE
KNOW IT'S NOT GOING TO STOP THE
HOLIDAY SHOPPERS AND FOLKS THAT
WANT TO GET OUT AND ABOUT FIND
SOMETHING TO DO THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
SO THAT'S WHY WE HAVE COME DOWN
TO THE POTOMAC CENTER HERE AT
PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY.
LOOK.
HOLIDAYS POUR AND US.
THIS IS ANNE-MARIE THE DIRECTOR
OF TOURISM HERE IN PRINCE
WILLIAM COUNTY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> ARE YOU READY?  YOU ARE
DRESSED TO IMPRESS, I WILL TELL
YOU THAT.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
>> YOU ARE READY FOR THE HOLIDAY
SEASON.
WHAT DO FOLKS HAVE TO LOOK
FORWARD TO SAY HERE IN PRINCE
WILL 81 COULD COUNTY IN
PARTICULAR IF THEY WANT TO GET
OUT AND ABOUT AND GET STUFF DONE
FOR THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> CERTAINLY.
YOU CANNOT MISS THE POTOMAC
MILLS MALL AND THE SHOPPING THAT
IS HAPPENING OVER THERE.
HERE POTOMAC TOWN CENTER AS
WELL.
WE ALSO HAVE TAX MILL CENTER WHO
HAS A BEE STORE I THINK PEOPLE
WOULD REALLY LOVE.
>> A BEE STORE?
>> YES.
>> OH.
>> YOU CAN LEARN ABOUT BEES.
YOU CAN PURCHASE, YOU KNOW,
WAXED CANDLES AND THINGS LIKE
THAT.
THEN WE ALSO HAVE THE PRINCE
WILLIAM HIGHS CENTER.
THE TOWN OF ACT QUON WHICH HAS
SUCH QUAINT LOCALLY OWNED SHOPS.
>> WE'VE DONE ZIP TRIPS THERE.
>> YOU HAVE.
>> BEAUTIFUL TOWN.
SO MUCH TO DO.
>> AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST OUR
HISTORIC CENTERS ARE OUR
HISTORIC SITES WHICH HAVE THE
MOST FANTASTIC HISTORY.
WE HAVE WEEKEND ACTIVITIES
HAPPENING RIGHT THIS COMING
WEEKEND AT RAH PENNSAUKEN LODGE
WHICH IS A FABULOUS HISTORIC
SITE RIGHT ON THE POTOMAC RIVER.
IN FACT RIGHT ACROSS FROM THERE
IS THE BOARDWALK WHICH IS A
FANTASTIC NEW BOARDWALK WE HAVE
YOU CAN WALK ON WATER.
>> OH.
>> YES.
>> OF COURSE OUR FIRST HIKES
WHICH ARE FANTASTIC FOR NEW
YEAR'S DAY.
SO VISIT PCW.COM/WEEKEND AND YOU
CAN FIND OUT EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO DO HERE.
>> EXCELLENT.
THERE'S SO MUCH GOING ON HERE IN
PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY.
YOU MENTIONED THE HISTORIC
SOCIETY.
WE HAVE HAVE SOME FOLKS HERE
FROM THE HISTORIC PRESERVATION
SOCIETY OF PRINCE WILLIAM CO
COUNTY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> SANTA, HOW ARE YOU THIS
MORNING.
>> A GIFT FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
>> A GIFT FOR ME THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON I DIDN'T BRING ANYTHING
FOR YOU.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> MAYBE ALL THESE SHOPS AROUND
HERE MAYBE I CAN PICK YOU UP
SOMETHING HERE BEFORE THE
MORNING IS OUT.
YOU GUYS LOOK FANTASTIC THIS
MORNING.
PLEASE INTRODUCE YOURSELF TO
EVERYBODY AT HOME.
>> WELL I'M SANTA CLAUS.
>> YOU'RE SANTA CLAUS.
>> I'M PAGE GIVENS BACKUS.
>> AND TELL US ABOUT THE PERIOD.
SANTA, I GOT TO ADMIT YOU LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE DRESSED LIKE THE
AMERICAN FLAG THIS MORNING.
>> I AM.
>> WHAT'S ABOUT THIS PIECE HERE?
>> WELL, IN 1862, THE BATTLE OF
FREDERICKSBURG WAS FOUGHT IN
DECEMBER.
>> UM-HMM.
>> AND ILLUSTRATE THOMAS NEST
AST DECIDED TO MAKE SANTA A
PROPAGANDA PIECE FOR THE UNION
ARMY.
>> OH.
>> SO HE PUT HIM IN RED, WHITE
AND BLUE.
I CAN ACTUALLY SHOW I WAS
PICTURE.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
>> THERE'S SOMETHING YOU JUST
DON'T THINK MUCH ABOUT.
>> THERE'S A PICTURE OF HIM
ACTUALLY GIVING GIFTS TO UNION
SOLDIERS OUTSIDE OF
FREDERICKSBURG.
>> FOR ALL THE FOLK AT HOME.
>> YEAH.
CHRISTMAS GOES BACK.
OR SANTA GOES BACK TO THE CIVIL
WAR.
>> THIS IS THOMAS NAST'S FIRST
ILLUSTRATION OF SANTA CLAUS AND
HE WILL DO A NUMBER THROUGHOUT
HIS LIFE.
THE PICTURE ON THE BACK IS
PROBABLY HIS MOST FAMOUS IMAGE
OF SANTA CLAUS.
>> OH YEAH.
>> IF YOU OR I IN THE 19th
CENTURY OR EARLY 20th CENTURY
WERE TALKING ABOUT SANTA, ABOUT
MYSELF, THIS WOULD BE THE IMAGE
THAT WOULD BE IN OUR HEADS.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> THAT WILL BE THE SAME.
IT WILL NOT CHANGE UNTIL 1931
WHEN THE COCA-COLA BOTTLING
COMPANY DECIDES TO TRADEMARK THE
IMAGE OF SANTA CLAUS.
>> THAT WE ALL KNOW AND LOVE
TODAY.
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US HERE THIS MORNING.
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
WE'RE NOT OUT OF TIME IN PRINCE
WILLIAM COUNTY MUCH MORE COMING
UP ALL MORNING LONG.
JOIN AS OUR HOLIDAY SERIES
CONTINUES.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT 8:00 O'CLOCK.
MUCH MORE COMING UP.
>> DREARY WEAR IT'S THE HOL
HOLIDAYS.
THANKS, MIKE.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> BUT WE ARE KEEPING AN EYE ON
THINGS OUT THERE.
>> GUYS, YEAH, MOSTLY JUST RAIN
NOW.
REALLY WANT TO EMPHASIZE.
A LITTLE SNOW MIXED GOING
FORWARD MOSTLY A RAINY COLD DAY.
I STEPPED OUTSIDE AND WOW IT
FEELS EVERY BIT OF, YOU KNOW,
WINTER WEATHER OUT THERE.
WITH A COOL TEMPS.
35 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
LIGHT RAIN BEING REPORTED WINDS
OUT OF THE EAST NORTHEAST AT
FIVE.
THERE'S STORM TRACKER RADAR THAT
WAS FILLED WITH SNOW A FEW HOURS
AGO NOW WE'RE SEEING THAT QUICK
CHANGE OVER TO RAIN AND GOING
FORWARD HERE FOR THE MOST PART
IS JUST GOING TO BE A WET DAY.
IT'S NOT GOING TO RAIN ALL DAY
BUT TAKE THE UMBRELLA.
WE'LL HAVE ON AGAIN OFF AGAIN
SHOWERS THROUGHOUT OUR MONDAY
HERE AND IT'S GOING TO BE CHILLY
AFTERNOON DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT
40.
BIG PICTURE ABOUT 24 HOURS WITH
CLOUDY SKIES AND SOME RAIN
SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST BEFORE
THINGS WILL START TO IMPROVE
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
SO KEEP THE UMBRELLA LANDY HERE.
40 THIS AFTERNOON.
WE'RE DONE FOR THE MOST PART
WITH WINTER WEATHER THAT WE HAD
AROUND HERE EARLIER THIS
MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
MORE ON THE FORECAST COMING
RIGHT UP.
ERIN, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
7:56 RIGHT NOW.
A LOT OF PROBLEMS ON THE ROADS
AND RAILS.
TRACK PROBLEM ON THE RED LINE
THE A FRIENDSHIP SINGLE TR TRACG
BETWEEN GLENMONT AND FARRAGUT
NORTH.
CAUTION THERE.
THEN EARLIER DISABLE VEHICLE
CLEARED ON THE BAY BRIDGE ON
THAT WESTBOUND SIDE.
CONSTRUCTION STILL OUT THERE AND
IT'S PARKED UP WITH A LOT OF
RAINY CONDITIONS.
POLICE ACTIVITY EAST CAPITAL
STREET CLOSED BETWEEN SIXTH AND
SEVENTH STREET IN NORTHEAST.
WATCH OUT FOR THAT ONE.
66 WESTBOUND THAT CRASH OUT BY
NUTLEY STILL BLOCKS THE LEFT
SHOULDER LEFT LANE HEAVY FROM
THE SPRING INTERCHANGE THROUGH
66.
28 NORTHBOUND LEFT LANE GETS BY
AT MAPLE WOOD DRIVES.
MASSIVE DELAYS TOWARDS 66.
66 EAST A CRASH BY NUTLEY
STREET.
LOTS GOING ON AS WELL 66
EASTBOUND BY SUDLEY.
BACK TO YOU.
>> KEEP IT TO FOX5.
MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR
8:00 O'CLOCK HOUR.
INCLUDING WHY HARVEY WEINSTEIN
SAYS HE'S A FORGOTTEN MAN WEEKS
BEFORE HE'S DUE TO STAND TRIAL
FOR RAPE.
>>> PLUS THE NEW MISS WORLD
IS -- AND WHY HER FELLOW
CONTESTANT IS GETTING A WHOLE
LOT OF PRAISE THIS MORNING.
>> WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON THE
WEATHER AS WELL OUT THERE AS WE
DO HAVE THE SNOW CHANGING TO
RAIN IN A LOT OF PLACES BUT AS
YOU CAN SEE RIGHT THERE STILL
SOME SNOW ON THE GROUND.
SO WE'LL CONTINUE TO TRACK THAT
WITH TUCKER COMING UP IN THE
8:00 O'CLOCK HOUR.
UPDATE FOR YOU RIGHT OFF THE TOP
IN JUST A COUPLE OF MINUTES.
♪
♪♪
(VO)
The flock blindly
falls into formation.
But this season, a more
thrilling journey is calling.
Defy the laws of human nature.
At the
Season of Audi Sales Event.
Ernest Hemingway wrote The Old
Man and the Sea at 52 .
Satchel Paige was still
dominating batters at 59.
Celia Cruz was still winning
Grammys at 77.
John Wheeler illuminated our
ideas of the universe at 70.
And Roger Crouch was 56 when
he first went into space.
Your Best is Yet to Come.
♪
>>> 8:00 O'CLOCK.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT FREDERICK
COUNTY RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE DRIVING THROUGH THAT AREA
MELANIE ALNWICK HAS BEEN OUT
SINCE VERY EARLY THIS MORNING
TRYING TO HIT AS MANY
COMMUNITIES AS WE CAN.
SO WE HAVE CREWS ALL OVER THE
PLACE AS WE KEEP AN EYE ON
WHAT'S HAPPENING OUTSIDE.
SOME PLACES LIKE FREDERICK
COUNTY STILL SOME SNOW THIS
MORNING.
>> OTHER PLACES LIKE D.C. --
>> GONE.
>> WINTRY MIX OF RAIN.
>> YES.
>> COLD RAIN HERE.
>> COLD RAIN FOR EVERYBODY IN
THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS F
YOU'RE STILL GETTING LIGHT
SNOWS, GET READY FOR IT TO
CHANGE TO RAIN.
TAKE THE UMBRELLA AND WET
ROADWAYS ARE SLOW THE COMMUTE
AND MOST PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
SCHOOL TODAY NOT A GREAT MORNING
FOR IT WE'LL LOOK AT HOW MUCH
SNOW WE GOT AND WHAT WE CAN
EXPECT GOING FORWARD FROM HERE
IN JUST A MINUTE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY SLICK SPOTS OUT
THERE RAIN COMBINED WITH SNOW
FROM EARLIER.
66 WESTBOUND HAS BEEN A BIG
PROBLEM AREA WITH A CRASH BY
NUTLEY STREET BLOCKING THE LEFT
LANE.
WE ALSO HAVE EASTBOUND CRASH BY
SUDLEY ROAD.
YOU SEE ALL THAT RED ON THE MAP.
PEOPLE ARE REDUCING THEIR SPEEDS
AS THEY SHOULD SEARCH FOR SLICK
SPOTS BRIDGES, OVERPASSES, ON
AND OFF-RAMPS.
>> LET'S GET BACK TO AN AREA
THAT HAS SOME SNOW RIGHT NOW AND
THAT'S WHERE MELANIE ALNWICK IS
AND HAS BEEN.
LET'S CHECK IN WITH MEL.
>> GOOD MORNING.
GOOD GOOD MORNING, MEL.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GUYS.
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE HIT A DRY SLOT
HERE LISTENING TO TUCK KIT
SOUNDS LIKE IT WILL BE THAT WAY
FOR THE REST OF THE MORNING, BUT
THE RESULTS OF THE STORM THAT
CAME THROUGH HERE YOU CAN SEE
PEOPLE ARE GETTING OUT THIS
MORNING AND FIGURING OUT OKAY,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO CLEAR OFF
MY WINDSHIELD, MY DRIVEWAY MIGHT
BE A LITTLE SLIPPERY WE'RE GOING
THROUGH SOME OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD
STREETS NOW.
MOSTLY WET NOW THAT THE CITY
CREWS HAVE COME THROUGH AND
TREATED BUT THE SIDEWALKS WE'RE
SEEING SOME OF THEM ARE WET BUT
SLUSH COVERED BRIDGES,
OVERPASSES THOSE SORTS OF THINGS
THEY ARE GOING TO BE A LITTLE
TRICKIER.
THEY ARE GOING TO FREEZE FIRST
THE SCHOOLS WE WENT BY SAME KIND
OF SITUATION.
SO YOU CAN UNDERSTAND WHY THEY
WANTED TO BE VERY CAREFUL WITH
THE TRAVEL CONDITIONS FOR THE
STUDENTS TODAY.
THERE IS A SNOW EMERGENCY PLAN
IN EFFECT IN FREDERICK COUNTY SO
THE STATE ROADS, NO PARKING.
YOU MUST HAVE YOUR ALL WEATHER
TIRES OR YOUR SNOW TIRES EVEN
THOUGH YOU REALLY DON'T NEEDON'D
THE SNOW EMERGENCY PLAN.
AND ALSO, CITY OF FREDERICK HAS
LIBERAL LEAVE IN EFFECT FOR
EMPLOYEES.
THEY'RE SAYING, YOU KNOW, SOME
CITY SERVICES MAY BE IMPACTED IF
A LOT OF PEOPLE DECIDE TO CALL
OUT ESPECIALLY NOW WITH
FREDERICK COUNTY SCHOOLS CLOSED
THAT MEANS THE KIDS WILL BE HOME
TODAY.
NO SCHOOL MAN BUILDING SNOW
HERE, THOUGH.
I WOULD SAY MAYBE AN INCH IN
SOME PLACES AND IT'S DEFINITELY
KIND OF WET SNOW AND YOU WON'T
BE ABLE TO DO MUCH WITH IT
EXCEPT DEAL WITH THE SLUSH.
FORTUNATELY THE PAVEMENT
TEMPERATURES HOVERING RIGHT
AROUND FREEZING SO THAT'S BEEN
HELPING OUT AS WELL.
SO KIDS ARE GOING TO GET LITTLE
EXTRA SNOW DAY PARENTS AND MAYBE
A LITTLE BIT OF EXTRA HEADACHE
AS THEY HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THEY'RE GOING TO DO BEFORE THE
WINTER BREAK COMES NEXT WEEK BUT
LOOKS KIND OF PRETTY OUT HERE,
GUYS.
AND THE TRAFFIC IS STACKING UP
JUST BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE KIND OF
SLOWING DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
BUT IT'S REALLY NOT THAT
HAZARDOUS WHEN IT COMES TO
TRAVEL CONDITIONS ON THE ROAD.
>> THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
MEL, THANKS SO MUCH.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> 8:03 RIGHT NOW.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE
MORNING'S OTHER TOP STORIES ON A
MONDAY.
IMPORTANT VOTE TO DETERMINE
WHETHER MARYLAND WILL ADD TOLL
LANES TO THE CAPITAL BELTWAY AND
I270 WILL NOT TAKE PLACE THIS
WEEK AFTER ALL.
GOVERNOR LARRY HOGAN CANCELED
THIS WEEK'S MEETING OF THE BOARD
OF PUBLIC WORKS.
THE WASHINGTON POST REPORTING
THE BOARD WAS EXPECTED TO VOTE
ON WEDNESDAY ON RECENT CHANGES
THAT THE GOVERNOR PROPOSED TO
THE TOLL LANE PROJECT.
NOW THE STATE CONTROLLER SITS ON
THE BOARD AND LAST WEEK HE
ANNOUNCED HE OPPOSES THE CHA
CHANGES.
>> ON CAPTAIN TOLL HILL A VOTE
ON IMPEACHMENT EXPECTED LATER
THIS WEEK.
HOUSE JUDICIARY APPROVED TWO
ARTICLES OF IMPEACH MANY AGAINST
THE PRESIDENT.
THE CHARGES EXPECTED TO EASILY
PASS IN THE DEMOCRATIC
CONTROLLED HOUSE BUT ONCE IN THE
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER MITCH
MCCONNELL SEES ZERO CHANCE THE
PRESIDENT WOULD BE REMOVED FROM
OFFICE BUT HE DOES EXPECT THE
TRIAL WILL TAKE MACE IN JANUARY.
THIS YEAR'S ARMY-NAVY FOOTBALL
GAME STIRRING UP CONTROVERSY OFF
THE FIELD.
MILITARY LEADERS SAY THEY'RE NOW
INVESTIGATING SERVICE ACADEMY
STUDENTS WHO NABBED HAND SIGNS
APPEARING TO PROMOTE WHITE
SUPREMACY DURING A BROADCAST OF
THE GAME IN PHILADELPHIA.
SPECIFICALLY, TWO WEST POINT
CADETS AND ONE NAVAL MIDSHIPMEN
SEEING FLASHING THAT SIGN DURING
THE PRE-GAME CELEBRATION AIRED
BY ESPN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS AT THE GAME
IN PHILADELPHIA ON SATURDAY.
IN PEOPLE ON SOCIAL MEDIA
DOWNPLAYING THE CONNECTION TO
WHITE POWER AND SAY IT'S THE
SO-CALLED CIRCLE GAME WHEN
SOMEBODY MAKES A CIRCLE WITH
THEIR FINGERS, IN ATTEMPT TO GET
SOMEONE TO LOOK AT IT.
>>> A BOND WILL BE HELD FOR A
MAN WHO KIDNAPPED A WOMAN FROM
HER HOME AND FORCED HER TO GET
INTO HER CAR AND WITHDRAW MONEY.
THIS HAPPENED LAST WEDNESDAY IN
WALDORF.
INVESTIGATORS SAY CHRISTOPHER
BROWN HAD JUST BROKEN INTO THE
WOMAN'S HOME WHEN SHE SUDDENLY
ARRIVED HOME.
MANY OFFICIALS THERE SAY THAT
BROWN EVENTUALLY DROPPED THE
WOMAN OFF IN ACCOKEEK SCHENN WAS
ABLE TO CALL FOR HELP.
>>> AND IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY, NO
WORD WHAT CAUSED THIS CHAOTIC
AND FRIGHTENING SCENE.
SUV CRASH THE RIGHT INTO THE
FRONT OF A SHELL GAS STATION ON
FREDERICK ROAD IN GERMANTOWN.
A PEDESTRIAN WAS HIT, TAKEN TO
THE HOSPITAL.
THANKFULLY WITH NON-LIFE
THREATENING INJURIES THAT DRIVE
WAS EVALUATED AT THE SCENE.
♪
>>> 8:05.
WHAT STARTED AS A SNOW DAY
QUICKLY TURNING INTO A RAIN DAY.
>> THAT'S A GREAT CALL.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE SEEING
FOR THE MOST PART WE'RE DONE
WITH THE SNOW EVENT.
THERE MIGHT BE A BIT OF A MIX OR
MIGHT BE HEARING SLEET PELLETS
BUT FOR THE MOST PART RAIN HERE
GOING FORWARD.
>> OKAY.
>> SO ANY ANOTHER WAVE WOULD BE
PERHAPS A MIX BUT NO MORE SNOW
IN YOUR PREDICTION?
>> YEAH.
CERTAINLY NOT EXPECTING ANY
ADDITIONAL ACCUMULATION THAT'S
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING.
>> OKAY.
>> I'LL LET ERIN TELL YOU ABOUT
THE ROADWAYS.
FROM WHAT I'VE BEEN HEARING FOR
THE MOST PART THEY'RE JUST WET.
STORM TRACKER RADAR.
THE PURPLE YOU SEE THE NORTHEAST
SIDE OF THE BELTWAY UP TOWARDS
LAUREL AND COLUMN YOUS OUT
TOWARDS ANNAPOLIS CROFTON AND
BOWIE YOU'RE GETTING WINTRY MIX.
LET ME KNOW.
I'M SEEING MORE AND MORE GREEN
ON THE MAP EVEN PINK SHADES
STARTING TO DEVELOP OUT TO THE
WEST.
THAT'S THE POTENTIAL FOR LITTLE
FREEZING RAIN OR SLEET.
AGAIN HERE I THINK THE NEXT HOUR
OR TWO WILL BE DONE WITH THE
SNOWFLAKES MAYBE A LITTLE SLEET
OR IN SPOTS WHERE THE
TEMPERATURES RIGHT AROUND
FREEZING.
POTENTIAL FOR SOME LIGHT
FREEZING RAIN.
AND THEN BIG PICTURE IT'S JUST
GOING TO BE A CLOUDY CHILLY
AFTERNOON HIGH TEMPERATURES
ABOUT 40 WITH SOME ON AGAIN OFF
AGAIN LIGHT RAIN SHOWERS.
SO AGAIN THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE
A MAJOR WINTER STORM FOR US AND
THINGS LOOK IMPROVING FROM HERE.
QUICKLY THE WEATHER ADVISORY
CONTINUES OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST NOW INCLUDES ALL OF
MONTGOMERY AND HOWARD COUNTIES.
PARTS OF LOUDOUN COUNTY,
FREDERICK COUNTY UNDER THAT
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY I'VE
SEEN ACCUMULATIONS HALF INCH TO
ABOUT AN INCH ACROSS THE AREA.
THANK YOU EVERYONE SENDING IN
YOUR PICTURES AND YOUR SNOW
TOTALS.
TUCKER FOX5.
SEND ME YOUR THOUGHTS.
I'LL HAVE MORE ON THE FORECAST
IN A SECOND.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANKS TUCK.
HERE'S ERIN WITH THE IMPACT ON
THE ROADS.
>> 8:06.
SLICK CONDITIONS SLOWS SLOWING
US DOWN AROUND THE DMV.
CRASH ON 395 NORTHBOUND RIGHT
LANE BLOCKED AT WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD.
WE'RE SEEING OVER 45 MINUTE SLOW
DOWN.
FROM EDSALL ROAD TO ACROSS THE
14th STREET BRIDGE.
WESTBOUND CRASH ON 66 STILL
BLOCKING THE LEFT SHOULDER LEFT
LANE.
OUT BY NUTLEY STREET AND DELAYS
EXTEND BACK INSIDE THE BELTWAY.
GW PARKWAY IS HEAVY INNER LOOP
COMPLETELY JAMMED FROM THE
SPRINGFIELD INTERCHANGE THROUGH
66.
EXTRA CAUTION NEEDED WE'RE SLOW
OVER THE LEGION BRIDGE WATCH OUT
FOR SLICK SPOTS.
BRIDGES, OVER PASSES, ON AND
OFF-RAMPS.
270 SLOW IN CLARK BURG PRETTY
SNOWY CONDITIONS ON THE GRASS.
THE ROADS ARE DRIED UP ENOUGH
BUT THEY ARE WET.
WATCH OUT FOR POTENTIAL TO HAVE
SLOW SPOTS AND SLICK AREAS.
REDUCE THOSE SPEEDS RIGHT NOW
SEEING VERY LIGHT SOL YUM UNTIL
YOU GET CLOSER TO THE BELTWAY.
MARYLAND DRIVE ON THE OUTER LOOP
STILL UNDER 10 MILES AN HOUR
AVERAGE VERY CROWDED IN SLICK
CONDITIONS FROM 95 OVER TO THE
SPUR WITH OVER A 45 MINUTE
DELAY.
BW PARKWAY IS SLOW IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS AND 95 SOUTHBOUND
SLOWS FROM THEISM CC DOWN
THROUGH THE INNER LOOP.
HEAVY VOLUME ON 295 NORTHBOUND
PASSED MALCOLM X AND THE INNER
LOOP THROUGH PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY.
VERY SLOW AS WELL.
BACK TO YOU.
>> A MINUTE OF SILENCE HELD IN
NEW ZEALAND TODAY AT THE MOMENT
THE VOLCANO ERUPTED ONE WEEK AGO
KILLING 18 PEOPLE.
TWO BODIES STILL HAVE TO BE
ROUGHED FROM THE ISLAND ONE
BELIEVED TO BE IN THE WATERS
AROUND THE ISLAND THE OTHERS
LOCATION STILL UNKNOWN.
MOST OF THE 47 PEOPLE WHO WERE
ON THE ISLAND AT THE TIME THAT
THE VOLCANO ERUPTED WERE
TOURISTS INCLUDING SELF
AMERICANS.
>>> SOMBER CEREMONY IN NEW YORK
CITY LAST NIGHT AS A VIGIL WAS
HELD TO REMEMBER A BON NARD
UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDERED
DURING AN ALLEGED ROBBERY.
18-YEAR-OLD TESSA MAJORS FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
SHE WAS STABBED TO DEATH LAST
WEDNESDAY IN A PARK IN UPPER
MANHATTAN.
A 13-YEAR-OLD BOY IS NOW UNDER
ARREST.
IN TEXAS, A DESPERATE SEARCH IS
UNDERWAY FOR A MISSING MOTHER
AND HER NEWBORN BABY.
HEIDI BRUSARD WAS LAST SEEN WITH
HER TWO WEEK OLD BABY GIRL AFTER
DROPPING HER SON OFF TO SCHOOL
IN AUSTIN ON THURSDAY.
NOW, POLICE BELIEVE SHE RETURNED
HOME WITH THE BABY BEFORE THEY
BOTH DISAPPEARED.
HER CAR AND ALL OF HER
BELONGINGS STILL AT THE HOUSE.
HER BOYFRIEND AND INFANT'S
FATHER REPORTED THEM MISSING
AFTER GETTING A CALL TO PICK UP
THEIR SON FROM SCHOOL THAT
AFTERNOON.
>> DID HE SAY GRACED HOLLYWOOD
MOGUL HARVEY WEINSTEIN SPEAKING
ABOUT HIS LEGACY IN THE FILM
INDUSTRY.
>> HIS COMMENTS LEFT MANY PEOPLE
FEELING HE'S WAY OUT OF TOUCH.
WISDOM MARTIN JOINS US NOW FROM
THE FOX5 DEN WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, WIS.
>> GOOD MORNING, ALLISON AND
STEVE.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH THE NEW
YORK POST, HARVEY WEINSTEIN WELL
HE SPOKE ABOUT WHAT HE'S BEEN
GOING THROUGH SPEAKING FROM A
NEW YORK HOSPITAL WHERE HE
UNDERWENT SPINAL SURGERY FOR AN
INJURY HE SAID HE SUSTAINED IN A
CAR ACCIDENT BACK IN AUGUST.
NOW WEINSTEIN SAYS HE SHOULD BE
REMEMBERED FOR DOING MORE
PROFESSIONALLY FOR WOMEN THAN
ANYONE IN HISTORY AND NOT FOR
THE RAPE AND SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST HIM.
WINE CITY REFUSED TO SPEAK ABOUT
ANY OF THE ALLEGATIONS AND SAID
HE ONLY AGREED TO THE INTERVIEW
TO PROVE THAT HE HASN'T BEEN
EXAGGERATING ABOUT HIS INJURIES.
WEINSTEIN TOLD THE POST QUOTE I
FEEL LIKE THE FORGOTTEN MAN.
I MADE MORE MOVIES, DIRECTED BY
WOMEN AND ABOUT WOMEN THAN ANY
FILM MAKER AND I'M TALKING ABOUT
30 YEARS AGO I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT NOW WHEN IT'S VOGUE.
I DID IT FIRST.
I PIONEERED IT ALL.
IT ALL GOT EVISCERATED BECAUSE
OF WHAT HAPPENED.
MY WORK HAS BEEN FORGOTTEN.
WEINSTEIN WAS PHOTOGRAPHED USING
A WALKER DURING A COURT
APPEARANCE IN MANHATTAN LAST
WEEK.
SOME ACCUSED OF HIM OF USING IT
TO GARNER SYMPATHY SINCE HE WAS
SPOTTED SHOPPING AT A TARGET A
FEW DAYS LATER WITHOUT THAT
WALKER.
HE WAS DISCHARGED FROM THE
HOSPITAL YESTERDAY.
ALLISON, STEVE.
>> NOBODY DISPUTING HARVEY
WEINSTEIN MADE A LOT OF MOVIES
IN HIS DAY.
PERHAPS HE SHOULD HAVE LEFT IT
AT THAT.
>> YEAH.
PROBABLY NOT THE DIRECTION YOU
WANT TO GO IN WHEN YOU'RE FACING
SOMETHING AS SERIOUS AS THIS.
>> ABSOLUTELY, WIS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
>>> STILL AHEAD, MEANING TO THE
TERM BLIND DATE.
IF YOU USE DATING APPS YOU COULD
BE SEEING A PROFILE WRITTEN  BYA
GHOST WRITER AND NOT EVEN KNOW
IT BUT, IF IT HELPS YOU FIND
LOVE, DOES IT REALLY MATTER.
>> LY PROLY NOT UNLESS YOU
STICKLER FOR DETAILS LIKE TRUTH
AND HONESTY.
SHOP AND DRIVE IT'S A DANGEROUS
TREND.
PEOPLE TRYING TO DO THEIR
HOLIDAY SHOPPING ONLINE BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
APPARENTLY THAT'S A THING.
IT'S TROUBLING.
A NUMBER OF DRIVERS SAY THEY
HAVE DONE IT.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
TAKING YOU TO BREAK WITH A LIVE
LOOK AT WHAT'S GOING ON IN OUR
AREA.
YOU SEE DRIVING CONDITIONS ON
THE TOP RIGHT THERE.
ROADS ARE OKAY.
A LITTLE WET.
NORTHWEST D.C. ON THE BOTTOM AND
THEN THAT RADAR ON YOUR LEFT.
TUCK SAYS IT'S ALL GOING TO TURN
OVER TO A COLD RAIN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
>> BACK NOW 8:14.
ON A MONDAY.
MISS JAMAICA THE NEWEST MISS
WORLD SHE'S HAPPY.
THE 23-YEAR-OLD IS A GRADUATE OF
FLORIDA STATE UNIVERSITY.
>> THAT WASN'T EVEN HER.
>> WAIT FOR IT.
>> OKAY.
>> MISS FRANCE CAME IN SECOND
PLACE.
MISS INDIA IN THIRD PLACE.
MISS JAMAICA'S WITHIN MISS USA,
MISS TEEN USA, MISS AMERICA,
MISS UNIVERSE AND MISS WORLD ARE
ALL AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMEN.
>> OKAY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THIS IS THE OTHER MOMENT FROM
THE COMPETITION.
PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT EVEN
THOUGH SHE DID NOT WITHIN, MISS
NYSIER YA COULDN'T HOLD BACK HER
EXCITEMENT FOR MISS JAMAICA.
TWITTER LOOK AT THAT.
TWITTER PRAISED MISS NIGERIA FOR
BEING SO SUPPORTIVE OF HER
FELLOW CONTESTANT.
>> I HOPE THEY'RE REALLY
FRIENDS.
STEP BACK A LITTLE BIT.
THIS IS MY MOMENT.
I'M TRYING TO BE NICE AND PROPER
HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> KEEP IT UNDER CONTROL.
>> YOU KNOW HOW EXCITED I AM FOR
MISS WORLD, CONGRATULATIONS BUT
THE MISS UNIVERSE, I CAN'T DO
BECAUSE WE CAN'T PROVE THAT
THERE'S NOT MORE BEAUTIFUL
SOMEWHERE IN THE UNIVERSE.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> SOMEWHERE --
>> MISS WORLD IS MORE DEFI
DEFINITIVE.
>> THE CONTESTANT FROM VENUS IS
REALLY MAD.
>> BE CAREFULLY WITH MISS
UNIVERSE.
>> HAVING OUR PAGEANTS FOR
MILLENNIUMS.
>> WE CAN DO MISS WORLD.
CAN'T DO MISS UNIVERSE.
WE DID A LITTLE --
>> MISS UNIVERSE AS FAR AS WE
KNOW.
>> EXACTLY.
>> YES.
>> HEY, THE SNOW IS PRETTY MUCH
FLIPPED OVER TO RAIN FOR MOST
EVERYBODY HERE.
THERE MAY BE STILL SNOWFLAKES
MIXING IN WHERE YOU SEE THE
PURPLE OUT TOWARDS BALTIMORE
ANNAPOLIS MAYBE STILL GETTING A
LITTLE MIX LOOKS LIKE LITTLE
POCKET TRYING TO REDEVELOP WEST
OF HAGERSTOWN THAT'S GOING TO BE
ABOUT IT, AND REALLY THE CONCERN
HERE GOING FORWARD IS JUST A
CHILLY RAIN ACROSS THE REGION
WITH DAY HEIM HIGHS ABOUT
40 DEGREES.
THE EXCEPTION IS GOING TO BE YOU
GUYS NORTH AND WEST WHERE THE
RAIN TO BRIEFLY FALL AS PERIOD
OF SLEET OR FREEZING RAIN AS
TEMPERATURES ARE RIGHT AROUND
FREEZING.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU HERE.
ALL OCCASIONS ARE THE ATMOSPHERE
WILL WARM PRETTY QUICK FOR THE
MOST PART FOR MUCH OF THE DAY
HERE THIS SHOULD JUST BE LIGHT
RAIN AS TEMPERATURES CLIMB INTO
THE UPPER 30S TO ABOUT 40.
BIG PICTURE WARM FRONT THIS
MORNING.
THEN AREA OF LOW PRESSURE BACK
NO WESTERN PARTS OF KENTUCKY
WILL START TO ROW HE WILL INTO
THE AREA THAT WILL BRING US
CLOUDS THIS AFTERNOON.
35 HERE IN WASHINGTON.
36 LEONARDTOWN.
37 QUANTICO.
WE'RE IN THE CLEAR WHERE WE'RE
ABOVE FREEZING NORTH AND WEST
GAITHERSBURG, HAGERSTOWN,
WINCHESTER, ALL AT THE FREEZING
MARK.
SO THERE COULD BE AN ICY SPOT OR
TWO TO THE NORTH AND WEST
PROCEED WITH CAUTION HERE
OBVIOUSLY AS YOU HIT THE
SIDEWALKS AND ROADWAYS LATER
THIS MORNING.
40 DEGREES TODAY.
WINTER WEATHER TRANSITIONING
CHANGING AS WE SPEAK TO RAIN,
AND WE'LL HAVE LIGHT RAIN SHOWER
ACTIVITY AROUND HERE THIS
AFTERNOON TON NIGHT.
DAYTIME HIGHS TOMORROW 50.
TOMORROW MORNING LICENSE JUST
PLAIN RAIN SHOWERS.
MUCH BETTER BY WEDNESDAY,
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY.
BACK TO SUNSHINE.
>> 8:17.
WE HAVE HAD BIG PROBLEMS ON THE
ROADS THIS MORNING.
METRO UPDATE THERE'S A TRACK
PROBLEM REPORTED AT FRIENDSHIP
HEIGHTS IMPACTING THE RED LINE
WE DO HAVE THE D.C. FIRE
DEPARTMENT OUT THERE PETE
PIRINGER LETTING US KNOW THEY'RE
INVESTIGATING ON SCENE RIGHT NOW
CAUSING SINGLE TRACKING AND
DELAYS ON THE RED LINE.
BETWEEN GLENMONT AND FARRAGUT
NORTH SOME TRAINS OPERATING
BETWEEN FRIAND SHIP HIGHS AND
VAN NESS.
270 NORTHBOUND EARLIER CRASH
CLEARED AFTER 1,212th ONE
AFTER 370.
SLICK CONDITIONS OUT THERE.
YOU CAN SEE THE SNOW ON THE
GRASS THERE.
WET CONDITIONS COLD CONDITIONS.
WATCH FOR THE POTENTIAL FOR ICE
OUT THERE.
MARYLAND DRIVE OUTER LOOP
REMAINS VERY SLOW AND CROWDED
KNIFE OVER TO THE 270 SPUR.
9 MILES AN HOUR AVERAGE.
ABOUT 45 MINUTE DELAY.
WE'RE ALSO SEEING DELAYS ON 395
NORTHBOUND WITH A CRASH BLOCKING
THE RIGHT SHOULDER RIGHT LANE.
ABOUT 45 MINUTE SLOW DOWN THERE
FROM EDSALL ROAD OVER TO THE
14th STREET BRIDGE.
FREEWAY IS HEAVY AND 295
NORTHBOUND IS PARKED AS WELL.
SO LOTS OF PROBLEMS ON THE ROADS
THIS MORNING.
GUYS, AND SPEAKING OF ROADS, ARE
YOU GUILTY OF SHOPPING WHILE
DRIVING?  WELL, ACCORDING TO NEW
STUDY BY ROOT INSURANCE TWO AND
FIVE AMERICANS ADMIT TO SHOPPING
ON THEIR PHONE WHILE AT THE
WHEEL.
THAT IS A 4% INCREASE FROM LAST
YEAR.
49% OF MEN ADMITTED TO SHOPPING
WHILE DRIVING COMPARED TO 30 FOR
WOMEN.
BROWS, CHECK AN ORDER STATUS,
SEARCH FOR DEALS AND ACTUALLY
COMPLETE A PURCHASE THAT'S VERY
DANGEROUS, I WOULD ADVISE
WAITING TILL YOU'RE HOME SAFELY
AND NOT BEHIND THE WHEEL.
>> TWO OUT OF FIVE SOUNDS LIKE
AN EXTREMELY HIGH NUMBER.
>> PEOPLE DO STUFF ON THEIR
PHONES AND HOPPING IS ONE OF
THINGS ESPECIALLY THIS TIME OF
YEAR.
SO I KNOW IT'S TERRIBLE.
DO END DO IT.
>> JUSTIFY WHILE THEY'RE IN
DELAYS STUCK ON THE BELTWAY THAT
IS THE WORST THING YOU CAN DO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I MEAN IF YOU DID THAT SAME
POLL WHO CHECKS THEIR E-MAILS.
>> RIGHT.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?  THE
SHOPPING COULD BE AN E-MAIL
MAIL.
>> I DO A LITTLE SCROLL.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED AT ALL BY
THOSE NUMBERS.
DO END DO IT.
>> SHOPPING BY BROWSING AND
LOOKING AT A WEB PAGE IF THAT'S
CONSTITUTES SHOPPING PERHAPS THE
NUMBER IS AS POP OPPOSED TO PUT
YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION IN.
>> LOOKING AROUND TRAFFIC WITH
THE DMV TODAY WITH THIS LITTLE
WINTRY MIX IT'S REALLY CROWDED
AND ICY THE WORST TIME NOT THAT
THERE'S EVERY GOOD TIME.
>> I HOPE WE DEBT TO POINT WE'RE
USED TO OUR DEVICES AND YOU GET
BOARD YOU'RE SIT TAG LIGHT AND
THE FIRST THING YOU DO NOT LOOK
AT YOUR DEVICE.
I HOPE WE GET TO THAT POINT.
>> THAT'S A PHONE ADDICTION I
THINK THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
SO NEW.
I HOPE THE TIDE GOES BACK.
I THINK IT LEADS TO A LOT OF BAD
ACCIDENTS.
>> IT WORSE ME FOR TEEN DRIVERS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BE SAFE OUT THERE, YA'LL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SPEAKING OF THE HOLIDAYS NOT
SHOPPING BUT THE DELIVERY IT'S
PROBLEM IN AT LOVE PLACES WITH
PORCH PIRATES.
IF THAT HAPPENS IN MICHIGAN THE
PORCH PIRATES WILL FACE FELONY
CHARGES.
COULD RANGE FROM A YEAR IN JAIL
AND UP TO FIVE YEARS IN PRISON
FOR REPEAT OFFENDERS.
NEARLY ONE IN FIVE AMERICANS HAS
BEEN A VICTIM OF A PORCH PIRATE
OR AT LEAST KNOWS SOMEONE WHO
HAS BEEN.
>> I THINK THE RULES ALREADY IN
PLACE FOR LIKE IF YOU STEAL
SOMEONE'S MALE, RIGHT?  ALMOST
LIKE THE TRENDS CATCHING UP WITH
ALL THIS OTHER ONLINE SHOPPING
WE'RE DOING NOW, TOO.
>> STRENGTHEN THE PENALTIES.
RUINS A LOT OF CHRISTMASES.
>>> THEY SAY WHAT'S OLD IS NEW
AGAIN.
STILL AHEAD ONE ITEM EXPECTED TO
MAKE A BIG COME BACK IN THE NEW
YEAR.
>> FIRST GETTING INTO THE
HOLIDAY SPIRIT IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
MIKE THOMAS IS ON LOCATION.
OH LOOK AT THAT.
SOUNDS ANGELIC.
♪
>> IT IS ANGELIC.
GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
GOOD MORNING, STEVE.
LIVE IN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY
THE NEW DOMINION CORAL LEASE ARE
SERENADING US WITH THE SOUNDS OF
THE HOLIDAYS.
WE'RE GOING TO MEET THE GROUP
TALK TO THEIR DIRECTOR AND TELL
YOU HOW YOU CAN SEE THEM LIVE
COMING UP IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
GUYS, BACK TO YOU.
♪
>> STILL TRACKING THE WEATHER
OUT THERE,.
TO THERE'S A LOOK AT NATIONAL
HARBOR.
IT'S JUST DREARY IN THE AREA
RIGHT NOW.
MOST OF THE KNOW LAS MOVED ON
FROM THE IMMEDIATE D.C. AREA.
BUT IT'S STILL RAINY, IT'S
MESSY.
THE ROADS ARE NOT GOOD.
A LOT OF ROAD SPRAY WHERE
THERE'S NOT SNOW.
A LOT GOING ON FOR TUCKER TO GET
THROUGH BUT HE'LL BRING US THE
UPDATE COMING UP IN A FEW
MINUTES WITH WEATHER ON THE 5'S.
Z3MRHZ Z16FZ
Y3MRHY Y16FY
At Hertz, we know
that a change of scenery
shouldn't mean
a change in standards.
That's why
- thanks to you -
we're rated number one
in customer satisfaction
by J.D. Power.
(bell rings)
- So, what are you in for?
- Well, according to
this discipline slip,
I was allegedly talking
during quiet time again.
But, there were no witnesses
except the teacher's pet.
- Oh, really?
- Her testimony
shouldn't be admissible.
So, I'm here to
appeal the decision.
(door opens)
- [Tuition Monster] Oh.
(whistling)
- [Narrator] Tame
the Tuition Monster.
- Well, I'll see you in
law school, kid. (laughs)
- [Narrator] Contribute
by December 31st
and receive a Virginia
state tax deduction.
- [Narrator] Contribute
by DecZ3MGGZ Z16FZ
Y3MGGY Y16FY
>>> BACK NOW 8:23.
MANY PEOPLE HAVE HOLIDAY
TRADITIONINGS BUT THIS ONE
REALLY TAKES THE CAKE.
OKAY.
A MICHIGAN FAMILY IS PASSED DOWN
THE SAME OLD FRUIT CAKE FOR FIVE
GENERATIONS.
>> IMPRESSIVE.
>> IN FACT IT'S 171 YEARS OLD.
>> THE ACTUAL CAKE?
>> IT WAS FIRST BAKED IN 1848.
>> WOW!
>> ALL QUESTIONS ANSWERED I
HOPE.
THE CAKE HAS BEEN STORED IN AN
ANTIQUE GLASS DISH GUINNESS
RECORD WORDS DOESN'T HAVE AN
ENTRY FOR THE OLDEST FRUIT CAKE
BUT IT SHOULD.
IT DOES HAVE ONE FOR CAKE IN
GENERAL IT GOES TO 4100 CAKE
FOUND IN EGYPT SHOULDN'T TOMB.
>> THE WORST PART OF THIS
PICTURE.
>> DON'T YOU SAY ANYTHING ABOUT
A FRUIT CAKE.
>> LOOK BY HER NAILS IN THE
BOTTOM SOMEBODY TRIED THAT AT
SOME POINT.
>> STOP IT.
>> AND THEN OPTED TO NOT EAT ANY
MORE.
>> STEVE, HOW IN THE WORLD DO
YOU KNOW THAT?
>> BECAUSE THERE'S A --
>> YOU DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA ABOUT
HOW THAT DENT GOT IN THE -- I'M
JUST GOING TO CALL IT.
>> OBVIOUSLY SOMEBODY TOOK
SOMTHING OUT OF IT.
>> IT'S NOT OBVIOUS.
SOMETHING COULD HAVE HAPPENED IN
THE BAKING.
>> YOU HAVE UNIFORM EDGES AND
OFF PIECE MISSING.
>> IF YOU WERE A DETECTIVE OF
THE FRUIT CAKE IT DOES APPEAR
THAT'S A PLUS CYBILL SCENARIO.
>> IT IS A PLUS CYBILL SCENARIO.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> DID YOU NOTICE THERE WAS AN
OLD TIME ME PHOTO IN THE CORNER.
MUST HAVE BEEN THE PERSON WHO
BAKED IT.
>> RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU LIKE
FRUIT CAKE.
>> NEVER HAD.
>> ONE OUT OF FOUR LIKES FRUIT
CAKE.
DO THEY FREEZE THAT?  LEAVE IT
SITTING OUT --
>> ANTIQUE CASE.
>> IT'S A PLATE, AL.
>> OKAY.
>> AFTER I GET INTO THE EGGNOG
I'LL EAT ANYTHING.
>> I LIKE A GOOD EGGNOG.
>> GIVE IT TO ME.
EVERYTHING EXCEPT MINCE MEAT
PIE.
>> 35, RAINING HERE IN D.C.
NORTHWEST D.C. JUST RAIN NOW.
WINDS OUT OF THE EAST NORTHEAST
AT FIVE.
WE GOT HALF INCH IN SOME SPOTS
AN INCH.
IT'S ALL WRAPPING UP HERE AND
JUST A RAINY AND CHILLY
AFTERNOON.
HIGH TEMPERATURES ABOUT 40.
I'LL HAVE MORE ON THE WEATHER
COMING UP.
RAIN FROM HERE ON OUT.
>> BW PARKWAY CRASH BLOCKING THE
LANE AT 50.
DELAYS ON 50 THE BELTWAY AND 295
SOUTHBOUND.
THIS WINTRY MIX CAUSING BIG
PROBLEMS ON THE ROADS.
TAKE CLOSER LOOK AROUND THE DMV
NEXT, GUYS.
>> UP AT 8:30 THE MOST CARING
CITY IN AMERICA.
IS IT IN VIRGINIA.
>> GHOST WRITERS BEING HIRED TO
MAKE POTENTIAL LOVE CONNECTIONS
ON DATING APPS.
SO IF YOU FIND LOVE DOES IT
REALLY MATTER?  THE PERSON YOU
THINK YOU'RE TALKING TO ISN'T
THE ONE SENDING THE MESSAGES.
>> THAT'S A STICKY ONE.
♪
>>> 8:29.
YEAH, WE ARE IN IT.
IT'S THE HOLIDAYS.
I HOPE YOU'RE FEELING GOOD.
I KNOW THIS WEATHER IS A BIT OF
A PAIN FOR YOU IN FACT WE'RE
LOOKING AT OUR TOWER CAM UP TOP
LOOKING AT THE STREETS DOWN
BELOW.
SLOW GOING BUT LOOK IT'S
HOLIDAYS.
HOPE YOU ARE SQUEEZING SOME JOY
OUT ON THIS MONDAY MORNING.
IT IS COMING UP ON 8:30 RIGHT
NOW.
AND IF YOU USE DATING APPS, YOU
COULD BE SEEING A PROFILE
WRITTEN BY A GHOST WRITER AND
NOT REALLY KNOW IT.
>> IF IT HELPS YOU FIND LOVE
DOES IT MATTER.
>> ACCORDING TO ONE COMPANY
NOPE, DOESN'T.
MAUREEN IS HERE TO BREAK IT ALL
DOWN FOR US, MO.
>> THIS IS INTERESTING.
THE IDEA CERTAINLY GIVES NEW
MEANING TO THE TERM BLIND DATE,
RIGHT?  THE COMPANY IS CALLED
VIDA DATING HIRES GHOST WRITERS
TO GET DATES FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
IT OUT SOURCES ITS CLIENT DATING
LIVES AND THIS MORNING THE
COMPANY FOUNDER IS DEFENDING
THIS IDEA.
IT WAS POSTED AS A ONE OF A KIND
WRITING OPPORTUNITY ON
CRAIGSLIST.
A COMPANY CALLED V.
IDA DATING HIRING GHOST WRITERS
TO GET DATES FOR THEIR CLIENTS.
OKAY MATCH, OKAY CUPID, TINDER
AND BUMBLE.
FIRST STEP TO APPLY, A TIME TEST
OF FLIRTING SKILLS FOR JOB AS A
CLOSER.
SOMEONE WHO WOULD CRAFT CHARMING
PROFILES CREATIVE ICE BREAKERS
AND HANDLE ALL THE BACK AND
FORTH MESSAGES FOR A CLIENT.
>> WE WILL ULTIMATELY SEARCH FOR
YOUR MATCHES, FIND THE ONES THAT
ARE REALLY CHECK ALL YOUR BOXES,
SEND ENGAGING MESSAGES AND SET
UP YOUR DATES.
>> THE FOUNDER SCOTT GOT THE
IDEA AFTER HE SUCCESSFULLY HIRED
SOMEONE ON CRAIGSLIST TO HANDLE
HIS ONLINE DATING.
>> THERE'S NOTHING ILLEGAL ABOUT
SOMEONE WRITING FOR SOMEONE
ELSE.
PEOPLE DON'T EVEN WRITE THEIR
OWN BOOKS A LOT OF TIMES THESE
DAYS.
THEY PUT THEIR NAME ON.
>> HE FOUND IT SO SUCCESSFUL HE
MODELED A BUSINESS AFTER IT.
HIRING WRITERRING TO HANDLE YOUR
LOVE LIVE.
KHLOE ROSE WAS ONE OF THEM.
>> AS A CLOSER AS ONE OF THE
GHOST WRITERS I HAD NO CONTACT
WITH THE CLIENT THAT IS I WAS
PRETENDING TO BE.
SO I HAD NO WAY OF KNOWING IF
THEY WERE CREEPY OR DANGEROUS OR
ANYTHING OR MARRIED.
>> SHE SAYS WHAT STARTED OFF AS
AN ENTERTAINING WAY TO MAKE
MONEY QUICKLY BECAME
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> EVERY DAY GETTING NEW TINDER
MESSAGES FROM WOMEN AND HAVING
TO PRETEND TO BE THIS MAN AND
HAVING TO MISREPRESENT MYSELF,
UM, WAS VERY TROUBLING.
>> VALDEZ QUESTIONS WHY SHE
STUCK WITH IT FOR SEVERAL MONTHS
IF THAT WAS THE CASE.
AND WONDERING IF SHE DID IT
SIMPLY TO WRITE THE EXPO SAY SHE
LATER PUBLISHED IN QZ MAGAZINE.
>> IT'S KIND OF STRANGE THAT SHE
WORKED FOR US.
SHE DIDN'T JUST WORK TWO DAYS.
SHE WORKED SEVERAL MONTHS AS
LONG AS SHE DID IT SHE SO ANTI
EVERYTHING.
>> KHLOE SAYS HER DISS COMFORT
GREW OVER HOW THEY WERE
INSTRUCTED TO INTERACT WHILE
POSING AS MALE CLIENTS.
>> WE HAD TO FOLLOW RULES
ACCORDING TO, YOU KNOW, HOW TO
BE THE ALPHA MALE AND HOW TO BE,
UM, UNAPOLOGETIC ONLINE BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT WOMEN WANT.
>> WE WERE ABLE TO OBTAIN COPIES
OF THE MANUALS WRITTEN FOR
EMPLOYEES BY VALDEZ.
HOW TO MASTER THE ATTITUDE OF
THE ALCOHOLIC MAGNET SENT TO
VIDASS WRITERS HE OFFERS THESE
TIPS.
THE ALPHA MALE IS THE SELECTOR
HE CHOOSES, HE IS NOT CHOSEN.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE TECHNICALLY
ASKING FOR HER APPROVAL, THE
TRICK IS TO MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
SHE'S ASKING FOR YOURS.
>> NEVER COMPLEMENTS HER WITHOUT
A QUALIFICATION.
TELL HER YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED
IN HER IF LET HER IN ON WHAT YOU
WANT IN A WOMAN AND MAKE HER
EXPLAIN TO YOU WHY SHE FITS YOUR
CRITERIA.
THE DATING SCENE IN MODERN
DATING CHANGES EXTREMELY FAST
WHAT WORKED TWO YEARS AGO WON'T
WORK AS WELL TODAY.
VALDEZ TOLD US THEY'RE
PUBLISHING NEW MANUALS WITH
LEVELS EMPHASIS ON THE ALPHA
MAIL.
WHILE MAINTAINING VIDA'S
INTEGRITY.
>> TO ANYONE WHO QUESTIONS THE
ETHICS OF WHAT WE DO, UM, YOU
KNOW, MY RESPONSE IS THEY'VE
NEVER SEEN IT.
THEY'VE NEVER SEEN THE WAY THAT
WE REALLY KIND OF ENCAPSULATE
OUR CLIENTS PERSONAS IF ANY WHAT
THAT MANY CASES MORE ACCURATE
THAN WHAT THEY WERE DOING BEFORE
THEY HIRED US.
>> THE MORAL GRAY AREA FOR ME IS
VERY CLEAR.
YOU'RE TRICKING THEM INTO GOING
ON A DATE WITH A COMPLETE
STRANGER.
>> NEW DATA MAT FORMS BRINGING
NEW MEANING TO THE IDEA OF A
BLIND DATE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO SEEMS A LITTLE WEIRD BUT WE
WERE JUST DISCUSSING THIS IS NOT
REALLY NEW.
I MEAN THINK ABOUT THE ROMANCE
NOVELS.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHEN YOU'RE TELLING --
>> THAT'S NOT WRIT TONE ONE
PERSON SPECIFICALLY THOUGH.
>> BUT YOU CAN MAYBE MAKE THE
LEAP THIS IS NOT UNHEARD OF
IDEA.
>> HERE'S THE THING.
IF YOU'RE PAYING FOR THE SER
SERVICE, YOU'RE GOING GET WHAT
YOU PAY FOR.
>> EXACTLY.
>> BUT I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA OF
THE PERSONAL MESSAGES BACK AND
FORTH.
I WON'T WANT SOMEBODY TO
MISREPRESENT ME IN THAT WAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> IF YOU DO IT AS LONG AS IF
YOU MEET SOMEBODY AND YOU'RE
FORTHCOMING ABOUT IT SAY I
DIDN'T WRITE THOSE MESSAGES.
>> THAT WOULD DISS CAL IF I YOU
RIGHT AWAY FOR ME.
>> YOU'RE DONE.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> IF YOU DIDN'T OWN UP TO THAT.
>> YOU'RE AN EVEN BIGGER CREEP.
>> WHY WOULD YOU EVER OWN UP TO
IT.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING TO OWN UP
TO IT.
IF THEY DID HOW ARE THEY GOING
TO -- THEY'RE NOT DOING IT.
I JUST FEEL LIKE --
>> KEEP SECRETS RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE WITH THE RELATIONSHIP.
>> NO, EVEN BEFORE.
>> OKAY.
>> THEY'RE WRITING SOMEBODY ELSE
IS WRITING THEM.
>> RELATIONSHIPS AND BUILT ON
LIES.
>> IT'S NOT THE PERSON YOU THINK
YOU'RE GETTING AND IT'S UNFAIR.
>> IT IS.
>> THE GUY HAS A SUCCESSFUL
BUSINESS.
>> RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> ON THAT OH ME JOE.
>> LET'S GET TO TUCKER.
>> NATIONAL HARBOR CLOUDY SKIES.
MOSTLY JUST RAIN FOR EVERYBODY
AT THIS HOUR.
THERE'S STILL MIGHT BE A FEW
SNOWFLAKES MIXED IN NORTH AND
WEST, AND IT'S POSSIBLE ACROSS
NORTHEAST D.C., WHERE YOU SEE
THE PURPLE THERE MIGHT BE A FEW
SNOWFLAKES MIXED IN BUT
GENERALLY RAIN SHOWERS.
LITTLE POCKET HERE UP TOWARDS
HAGERSTOWN MIGHT BE PRODUCING A
LITTLE SNOW.
>> WHAT CAN WE EXPECT TODAY?
CHILLY RAIN.
DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT 40 DEGREES.
OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST THERE
ARE A FEW SPOTS THAT ARE STILL
HANGING AROUND THE FREEZING MARK
SO SOME OF THAT RAIN NOW FALLING
COULD FREEZE ON THE SURFACE JUST
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
BE CAREFUL THE SIDEWALKS.
THE ROADS WILL BE PRETTY GOOD AS
TEMPERATURES WERE NICE AND MILD
YESTERDAY.
BUT BIG PICTURE, WE'LL HAVE ON
AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN SHOWERS
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
CLOUDS AROUND TAKE THE UMBRELLA
DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT 40 DEGREES.
CHILLY RAIN EXPECTED LATER THIS
AFTERNOON AND WE'LL KEEP THE
RAIN SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST
LATER TONIGHT.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
CONTINUES.
NOW ALL IN MONTGOMERY AND HOWARD
COUNTIES.
WE SAW HALF INCH TO A AN INCH OF
SNOW OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
KEEP THE WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
IN EFFECT FOR A COUPLE MORE
HOURS AS THE LAST OF THE SNOW
TAPERING YOU HAVE.
38 DEGREES AT 1:00 P.M.
AND AGAIN JUST SHOWERS FROM HERE
ON OUT.
WITH DAYTIME HIGHS WELL ABOVE
FREEZING SO THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
STILL GOING TO BE A CHILLY DAY
BUT WE'LL GET IT WELL ABOVE THE
FREEZING MARK AND KEEP IT JUST
RAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT' A QUICK LOOK AT WEATHER
I'LL SHOW YOU SNOW TOTALS.
YOU'LL WANT TO SEE THEM BEFORE
YOU GO COMING UP IN JUST A
MINUTE.
ERIN.
>> 8:36 TUCK.
ROADS HAVE BEEN A MESS WITH THIS
WINTRY MIX.
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE CRASH AT
408.
SOME VERY HEAVY DELAYS BACK INTO
BRISTOL TOWARD UPPER MARLBORO.
BW PARKWAY SOUTHBOUND RIGHT LANE
BLOCKED THIS MORNING BY A CRASH
AT 50 DELAYS INTO RIVERDALE
PARK.
WE DO HAVE 50 DELAYS 202295.
KENILWORTH SLOW NEW YORK AVENUE
SLOW AS WELL.
270 NORTHBOUND A CRASH AFTER
370.
YOU CAN SEE THAT SNOW OUT THERE
IN THE CENTER MEDIAN AND TO THE
SIDES WET CONDITIONS ON THE ROAD
WATCH OUT FOR SLICK SPOTS AND
THE POTENTIAL FOR BLACK ICE.
OUTER LOOP DOWN TO 7 MILES AN
HOUR AVERAGE.
95 OVER TO THE 270 SPUR OVER AN
HOUR DELAY.
BW PARKWAY SLOW IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS FOR THE POTENTIAL FOR
SLICK SPOTS.
DELAYS 395 NORTHBOUND WITH A
CRASH BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE
RIGHT SHOULDER AT WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD.
OVER HALF HOUR DELAY EDSALL ROAD
TO THE 14th STREET BRIDGE A
LOT OF SLOW TRAFFIC ON
SECONDARIES.
295 STACKS FROM THE BELTWAY
PASSED MALCOLM X.
BACK TO YOU.
>> THEY SAY WHAT'S OLD IS NEW
AGAIN, RIGHT?  SO UP NEXT, THE
ITEM THAT'S EXPECTED TO MAKE A
BIG COME BACK IN THE NEW YEAR.
OH LET IT BE BELL BOTTOMS.
>> YOU GET THEM IF YOU LIKE.
>> MORE WEATHER AND TRAFFIC
COMING UP AS WE GET THROUGH A
RAINY AND DREARY MONDAY MORNING.
CAN BARELY EVEN SEE THE CAPITOL
DOME.
IT'S 8:37.
STAY WITH US.
MORE OF FOX5 MORNING UP NEXT.
♪
Some of the biggest
breakthroughs in health,
Have been tools
that let doctors see things
they couldn't before.
Now CVS Health has a tool,
that shows
doctors what drugs cost.
So they can choose
affordable options.
It's also available
to out pharmacists.
Managing health costs.
Another visionary idea,
from CVS Health.
Where health is everything.
8:40.
WHAT'S OLD IS NEW AGAIN.
TRADITIONAL ANTENNAS THEY ARE
LIVE AND WELL.
WHATEVER THAT PROGRAMMING IS.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A PREDICTION
FROM PROFESSIONAL SERVICES
COMPANY DEE LGBT.
IN 2020 THE COMPANY FOUND THE
NUMBER OF TV WATCHERS USING
ANTENNA WILL BE 50% MORE THAN
CABLE, INTERNET TV AND DIRECT
BROADCAST SATELLITE COMBINED.
SO GET READY.
ALL RIGHT.
THE MOST CARING CITY IN AMERICA
HAPPENS TO BE IN THE
COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA.
THE PERSONAL FINANCE WEBSITE
WALLET HUB RELEASED ITS REPORT
ON THE MOST CARING CITIES IN
AMERICA.
BASED ON ACTS OF KINDNESS LIKE
CHARITABLE GIVING.
VIRGINIA BEACH CAME IN NUMBER
ONE FOLLOWED BY MADISON,
WISCONSIN, PITTSBURGH, STEVE,
NUMBER THREE.
CHESAPEAKE, VIRGINIA, AT NUMBER
EIGHT.
WASHINGTON, D.C. NOT TOO BAD.
>> NUMBER 18.
>> YOU DON'T REALLY CARE ABOUT
PITTSBURGH OR YOU'D PUT THE H ON
THE END OF IT.
>> GREAT TO SEE --
>> PITTSBURGH ERS ARE SERIOUS
ABOUT IT.
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD WE'RE SINGING
OUR WAY THROUGH THE HOLIDAY
SEASON.
WE'LL CHAT WITH SOME CAROL
LOWERS IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA AS
THE GROUP CELEBRATES IT'S 24th
HOLIDAY SEASON IN PRINCE WILLIAM
COUNTY.
♪
cohe
mpetition
and we broke through.
You've tried retinol,
but you have never tried one
like this.
Olay's Retinol24 complex
hydrates
better than the #1 retinol.
Visibly smoother brighter skin
in just 24 hours.
A skin upgrade?
Crushed it.
New Olay Retinol24.
Face Anything.
Olay.
Now available with retinol serum
and retinol eye cream.
♪
>> COMING UP ON 8:45 WHICH MEANS
WE'RE JUST ABOUT 15 MINUTES AWAY
FROM GOOD DAY D.C.
HOW ABOUT THOSE TWO GUYS
TOGETHER?  WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
TO HEAR WHAT THEY HAVE TO SAY?
WELL, BECAUSE WE HAVE KEVIN
MCCARTHY HE HAS THE OPPORTUNITY
TO TALK TO PEOPLE LIKE JAMIE
FOXX AND MICHAEL B. JORDAN
TOGETHER.
NEW FILM CALLED JUST MERCY.
KEVIN ASKED JAMIE FOXX IF HE'S
ONE OF THE MYSTERY CONTESTANTS
ON THE MASKED SINGER.
FIND OUT WHAT HE HAD TO SAY
COMING UP ON GOOD DAY.
>> I BET HE'S GOING TO SAY HE'S
NOT BUT IT'S A TRICK.
>> I ASKED HIS DAUGHTER IF JAMIE
FOXX WAS.
>> YEAH.
>> HIS DAUGHTER IS GOING TO BE
IN THE LIVE EDITION OF GOOD
TIMES.
IT'S AIRING NEXT WEEK.
>> SHE'S GETTING A LOT OF GOOD
OPPORTUNITIES LATELY BUT CORRINE
SAID -- WHAT DID SHE SAY.
>> SHE DID NOT THINK SO BUT SHE
ALSO SAID THAT HE SOMETIMES
DISAPPEARS FOR EXTENDED AMOUNTS
OF TIME SO IT WOULD NOT SURPRISE
HER IF HE WAS AWAY FROM PEOPLE
FOR AWHILE.
>> RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
WE'LL FIND OUT THE IF YOU UNTIL
SYSTEM COMING UP THIS WEEK.
>> SHE DIDN'T THINK SO.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> HELLO.
>> STEVE, I GOT TO KNOW NOW.
I GOT TO KNOW.
>> YOU GOT TO WATCH ON
WEDNESDAY, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I HAVE ANSWERS TO THIS QUESTION
FOR YOU.
HOW MUCH SNOW DID WE GET?
ANYTHING FROM A COVERING ON THE
GRASSY AREAS TO BIGGER SNOW
TOTALS.
DULLES .40 OF AN INCH.
GERMANTOWN MARYLAND ABOUT AN
INCH.
MARTINSBURG SEEMS TO BE OUR
WINNER 1.7 INCHES OF SNOW.
AND AS FAR AS WINTER WEATHER, I
THINK WE'RE PRETTY MUCH DONE
WITH IT YOU MIGHT BE GETTING FEW
FLAKES MIXING IN THE RADAR
REALLY STARTING TO SHOW A LOT OF
RAIN ACROSS THE AREA IT WILL BE
A CHILLY DAY AND A RAINY DAY
WITH AGAIN I THINK MOST OF THE
WINTER WEATHER GONE IF YOU'RE
ACROSS NORTHERN MARYLAND,
HAGERSTOWN, THURMONT THINKING OF
YOU GUYS.
PERHAPS FREDERICK AND OUT ALONG
81 IT'S POSSIBLE YOU CAN GET A
FEW MORE FLAKES AND MAYBE IT
WILL MIX WITH SLEET PELLETS OR
POTENTIALLY LITTLE FREEZING RAIN
HERE BEFORE THINGS REALLY WARM
UP BUT FOR THE MOST OF US A
PLANE RAIN AND DAYTIME HIGHS
ABOUT 40 DEGREES IT WILL REMAIN
A VERY CHILLY AFTERNOON.
BIG PICTURE IT'S A WARM FRONT
COMING IN.
PROCESS WE CALL OVERRUNNING
EARLY THIS MORNING, BUT LARGE
SCALE HERE WE HAVE AN AREA OF
LOW PRESSURE BACK INTO WESTERN
KENTUCKY THAT WILL CONTINUE TO
PUSH THIS MOISTURE AND THE CLOUD
COVER AND THE COOL CONDITIONS ON
TOP OF US LATER THIS AFTERNOON
SO WE'RE NO GOING TO WARM IT UP
A WHOLE LOT.
BUT I JUST REALLY WANT TO
EMPHASIZE AGAIN AS FAR AS WINTER
WEATHER WE'RE DONE WITH THE
BIGGEST THREAT OF IT THE
EXCEPTION BEING NORTHTH WEST
TEMPERATURES A LITTLE MORE
MARGINAL.
YOU COULD HAVE POTENTIAL AL
LITTLE FREEZING RAIN ALTHOUGH I
DON'T HAVE REPORTS OF IT AT THE
MOMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
32 THAT'S THE WINNING NUMBER OUT
ALONG 81 AND AGAIN ANYPLACE YOU
SEE 32 DEGREES POTENTIAL FOR
LITTLE ICING.
GAITHERSBURG 32.
34 IN FREDERICK YOU'RE UP IN THE
PAST HOUR.
35 HERE IN WASHINGTON AND
ANNAPOLIS 35.
36 IN LEONARDTOWN MOST OF THE
REGION A CHILLY RAIN THIS
AFTERNOON AND WE'LL KEEP THE
THREAT OF SHOWERS AROUND TON
TONIGHT.
LISTEN IT'S NOT GOING TO RAIN
ALL DAY.
WE BELIEVE GET SOME BREAKS HERE
BUT WE'LL KEEP THE CLOUDS AROUND
ALL DAY.
40 TODAY.
TOMORROW MORNING WE'RE GOING TO
WAKE UP WITH JUST RAIN SHOWERS.
NOTICE YOUR DAYTIME HIGH
TOMORROW IS 50.
KEEP IT ON THE WARMER SIDE
TOMORROW AFTERNOON AND THEN BACK
INTO SUNSHINE, WEDNESDAY,
THURSDAY, FRIDAY WINTER GETS
HERE, GUYS, SATURDAY.
YEAH.
>> IT ALREADY FEELS LIKE WINTER
IS HERE.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> RIGHT NOW 8:47.
TUCK, THE WINTRY MIX NOT DOING
THE ROADS ANY FAVORS THIS AMONG
MORNING.
RAIL PROBLEMS.
START TO GO CLEAR UP OUTSIDE
FRIENDSHIP HEIGHTS THAT EARLIER
TRACK PROBLEM NO LONGER SINGLE
TRACKING ON THE RED LINE JUST
RESIDUAL DELAYS IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS SURROUNDING THAT
AREA.
AS WE FORWARD THINGS ALONG
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE THERE'S A
CRASH AT 408.
SOME DELAYS WERE BACK TO BRISTOL
BUT IT LOOK LIKE IT'S START TO
GO CLEAR UP A BIT.
SOUTHBOUND BW PARKWAY RIGHT LANE
BLOCK ON THE RAM TOM 50'S.
RAMPS, BRIDGES OVERPASSES ON AND
OFF-RAMPS TEND TO FREEZE FIRST.
LOOKS LIKE THE SOUTHBOUND
CONGESTION DISSIPATED ON 270.
YOU CAN SEE THAT SLUSH AND SNOW
TO THE CENTER MEDIAN TO THE
GRASS THERE USE CAUTION.
WATCH OUT FOR SLICK SPOTS.
IT'S WET BECAUSE OF THE WINTRY
MIX OF RIN AND SNOW.
OUTER LOOP A PARKING LOT THIS
MORNING UNDER 10 MILES AN HOUR
AVERAGE.
HEAVY VOLUME WET CONDITIONS AND
STILL UP FOR AN HOUR DELAY 95 TO
THE SPUR.
BW PARKWAY HEAVY IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS.
AND 66 STILL DEALING WITH A LOT
OF VOLUME BY NUTLEY MUCH THAT'S
WHAT WE HAVE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> 8:48.
ON THIS MONDAY MORNING, LET'S
GET INTO THE HOLIDAY SPIRIT, AND
WHAT BETTER WAY TO DO THAT IS
WITH SOME HOLIDAY TUNES.
MIKE THOMAS IS LIVE ON LOCATION
IN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY WITH
THE NEW DOMINION CAROLERS.
>> ALLISON, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT I HAVE JUST LEARN THIS
MORNING.
CAROL LEASE.
>> CHORALEIRS.
WE'RE SPREAD THE CHRISTMAS CHEER
AND WE'RE LEARNING NEW TERMS
HERE IN PRINCE WILLIAM COUNTY
THIS MORNING.
I AM WITH CATHERINE NELSON
TRACEE THE FOUNDING DIRECTOR OF
THE NEW DOUGH MILLION CAROL
LEASE.
THANK EVERYBODY FORGET UM EARLY
AND JOINING US THIS MORNING.
IT'S NOT CHRISTMAS WITHOUT SOME
CAROLS BUT YOU ALL DO MUCH MORE
THAN THAT.
TELL US BOUGH AL ABOUT THE NEW
DOMINION CAROLERS AND WHAT
YOU'RE ALL ABOUT.
>> WE PRACTICE MOST OF THE YEAR.
WE GIVE TWO MAIN CONCERTS.
HOLIDAY CONCERT IN DECEMBER, AND
A SPRING CONCERT IN MAY USUALLY.
WE DO A LOT OF OUT REACH GIGS TO
NURSING HOMES, CHRISTMAS TREE
LIGHTINGS, UM, BOYS AND GIRLS
CLUB CHRISTMAS PARTY.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT SPREADING GOOD
CLEAR CHEER.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> NO MATTER WHAT THE SEASON.
>> THROUGH THE COMMUNITY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
>> YOU'VE DONE 24 YEARS, IS THAT
CORRECT.
>> YES.
>> WHAT ARE SOME OF THE
HIGHLIGHTS OVER THE 24 YEARS
WOULD YOU SAY BECAUSE YOU'VE
BEEN THERE FOR ALL OF THEM.
>> YES, I'VE BEEN THERE.
EVERY YEAR IS DIFFERENT.
SINGING AT THE PENITENTIARY IN
LEWES TOWN, PENNSYLVANIA, WAS
INTERESTING.
SINGING IN --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SINKING AT STRATHMORE IN
MARYLAND IT WAS A LOT OF FUN.
WE HAVE BEEN BEEN ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
>> YOU'RE A TEACHING WHICH ARE
RUSS.
WHAT EXACTLY IS THAT.
>> WE'RE A COMMUNITY CHORUS THAT
DOES NOT AUDITION IN ORDER FOR
PEOPLE TO JOIN.
WE HAVE MENTORS IN EVERY
SECTION.
WE HAVE SECTION LEADERS.
WE PROVIDE RECORDINGS FOR PEOPLE
TO LEARN THEIR PARTS.
>> UM-HMM.
>> WE TAKE THE NOVA STUDENTS
FROM THE WOODBRIDGE CAMPUS WHO
WANT TO GET CREDIT FOR ENSEMBLE,
AND THEY CAN -- COME AND SING
WITH US SO WE ARE THE --
>> IF I WAS THE POP IN, DO, RE,
SO, FA, LA, TI, DO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I'M IN ALREADY EVERYBODY.
FOR FOLKS WHO MIGHT WANT TO COME
OUT AND CATCH A CONCERT OR GET
INVOLVED WHERE CAN THEY FIND OUT
MORE INFORMATION.
>> GO TO OUR WEBSITE WWW NEW
DOMINION CORAL LEARS.ORG AND ALL
SORTS OF INFORMATION THERE.
PICTURES AND APPLICATION FORMS
AND THAT SORT OF THING.
>> EXCELLENT.
I CAN'T LET YOU GO AND WILL YOU
PLEASE KING US A LITTLE
CHRISTMAS TUNE HERE THIS MORNING
WE WILL THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
I'LL LET YOU TAKE AWAY.
THIS IS THE NEW DOMINION C
CHORALIERS HERE THIS MORNING.
♪ JINGLE, BELL, JINGLE BELL,
JINGLE ROCK, JINGLE SWING AND
JINGLE RINKS ♪
♪
♪ JINGLE BELL ROCK ♪
THIS IS THE PART RIGHT HERE.
♪
THANK YOU MIKE.
KEEPING US IN THE HOLIDAY SP
SPIRIT.
WE SHALL DO SO THROUGHOUT THE
REST OF THE MONTH.
ALSO COMING UP LATER THIS MONTH
THE WAIT ALMOST OVER NOW.
LATEST STAR WARS INSTALLMENT
HITTING THEATERS LATER THIS
WEEK.
TON NIGHT KEVIN WILL BE ONE OF
THE FIRST PEOPLE IN THE WORLD
DARE I SAY IN THE UNIVERSE, IN
THE GALAXY.
>> WHAT?
>> TO SEE IT.
HE'S LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
WE'LL CHAT WITH HIM NEXT.
>> HE'S SO LUCKY.
♪
TIME FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA MCC
MCCARTHY.
LET'S HEAD OUT TO LOS ANGELES
IT'S A BIG WIN FOR KEV.
STAR WARS WEEK.
HE'S OUT ON HOLLYWOOD BOULEVARD.
HAS A PLACE TO HIMSELF.
EARLY IN THE MORNING.
HOW EXC EXCITED ARE YOU, KEV?
>> GOOD MORNING TO YOU STEVE.
I'M VERY EX EXCITED.
WHAT'S BORE EXCITING THAT'S THE
PREMIER.
THAT IS THE ACTUAL RED CARPET
MUCH THAT'S THE CHINESE THEATER.
THAT'S THE KODAK THEATER.
DOLBY THEATER WHERE WE PROCEDURE
TONIGHT.
I'LL BE ON THAT CARPET LATER ON
THIS EVENING FOR STAR WARS THE
RISE OF SKY WALKER.
JUST SAYING THAT OUT OF MY MOUTH
DOES NOT SOUND REAL TO ME.
IT'S CRAZY.
BUT YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE
INTERVIEW I DID WITH JOHN BOYEGA
WHO PLAYS FIN A BIG PART OF
FRANCHISE SINCE EPISODE SEVEN
AND EIGHT AND NOW EPISODE NINE
RISE OF SKY WALKER I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU KNOW THIS STORY STORY OUT
THERE FOR AWHILE NOW.
HE HAD A SCRIPT FOR EPISODE NINE
RISE OF SKY WALKER HE BROUGHT
HOME AND HIS CLEANING PERSON
FOUND THE SCRIPT AND APPARENTLY
PUT IT ON E-BAY AND DISNEY WAS
ABLE TO FIND THE SCRIPT BEFORE
IT GOT SOLD TO THE WRONG PERSON.
I WANTED TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
THIS BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS HEARD
THE SCRIPTS WERE ALWAYS SECURE
AND YOU COULDN'T BRING THEM
HOME.
I WANTED TO FIND OUT WHAT EX
EXACTLY HAPPENED WITH JOHN
BOYEGA AND HIS EPISODE NINE
SCRIPT.
WATCH THIS.
>> I KNOW YOU'VE ALREADY TALKED
ABOUT THE SCRIPT STORY A SILL I
DON'T KNOW TIMES MUCH IT'S AN
AMAZING STORY, BUT I DO HAVE A
GENUINE QUESTION ABOUT IT.
>> WHEN I FIRST STARTED READING
ABOUT STAR WARS AND JJ I WAS
ALWAYS TOLD THAT JJ WAS VERY
SECURE ABOUT THE SCRIPTS AND
HONESTLY HE WOULDN'T LET PEOPLE
LEAVE WITH THEM.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DID IT GET TO YOUR HOUSE
LIKE WAS THAT -- ARE YOU ALLOWED
TO TAKE IT HOME.
>> THE PRACTICALITY OF HAVING TO
LEARN LINES FOR A MOVIE THAT'S
OVER TWO HOURS AND NOT BEING
ABLE TO TAKE IT HOME WAS
ABSOLUTELY DUMB.
SO I THINK LUCAS REALIZED, MAYBE
THE ACTORS WOULD BE BETTER
ACTORS IF THEY HAD A SCRIPT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT SEEMS REASONABLE.
IT SEEMS REASONABLE.
TAKE THE SCRIPT HOME.
BUT I WAS MOVING.
I WAS MOVING APARTMENTS AND
WHILE LIKE GETTING TO THE LAST
LEG OF SHOOTING SOMETHING SO I
WAS, YOU KNOW, THERE WERE ALL
SORTS OF LAYERS AND DETAILS TO
THIS THE MASSES DON'T KNOW,
BUT --
>> WHAT'S CRAZY I'M WONDERING
WHERE THEIR COPIES MADE?  HOW DO
WE EVEN -- IT'S A CRAZY STORY.
>> I THINK IF THAT WERE COPIES
MADE, WE WOULD HAVE FOUND OUT.
WE WOULD HAVE FOUND OUT BY NOW.
THEY MANAGED TO GET AT IT PRETTY
SOON.
FAITHFULLY IT WAS LOST IN A MORE
SECURITY A CLEANER CAME IN AT
THIS TIME.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE YOUR
FURNITURE AS WELL?  I GOT TO
EXPLAIN MY LEASE DEAL TO YOU.
>> LET'S LOOK AT YOUR MORTGAGE.
CREDIT CARD STATEMENTS.
>> SCRIPT IS BACK.
WHAT HAPPENED AFTER THAT ALL
WENT DOWN?  DID YOU GET TALKED
TO?
>> DID JJ WE'RE ADULTS.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT WAS THE CONVERSATION
HIKE WITH JJ WHEN HE FOUND OUT.
>> JJ WAS ACTUALLY COOL ABOUT
IT.
WE WERE JUST LIKE AS LONG AS WE
GOT IT BACK THAT'S THE PRIORITY.
WHAT HAPPENED?  WHEN THEY FOUND
OUT THEY WERE LIKE HMM, ACTUALLY
WHILE I WAS WORKING ON STAR WARS
MY ACCOMMODATION I WAS IN THE
STATE BECAUSE I WAS MOVING FROM
PLACE TO PLACE.
EVERYONE KIND OF FIGURED THAT I
WAS LIKE, YOU KNOW, STRESSED OUT
WITH THE MOVE WHILE, YOU KNOW,
FILMING.
I FELT LIKE THERE WAS A NICE BIT
OF EMPATHY.
I DIDN'T EVEN GET AN OFFICIAL
CALL.
>> JJ IS RIGHT DOWNSTAIRS.
>> NO, NOT FROM JJ.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE SCARED OF
JJ.
>> HE'S TOO NICE.
>> HOW DID FIN CHANGE YOU?  YOU
THINK ABOUT SOMEONE IT PLAY FOR
THREE MASSIVE FILMS.
>> WHAT'S FUNNY ABOUT THAT, I
THINK I CHANGED FIN.
>> CAN YOU ELABORATE ON THAT?
>> AS IN THE CHARACTER CAN'T
REALLY CHANGE ME BECAUSE I
CREATE HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> I LITERALLY THINK HIM UP.
WHATEVER CHANGES HAPPEN WITH ME
I ADD TO THE CHARACTER.
SO THE CHARACTER IS MORE THE
EXPRESSION AND GETS MORE THE
INFLUENCE THAN ME BEING
INFLUENCED BY THE CHARACTER.
>> WHAT'S AN AS SPEC OF JOHN ON
SCREEN THAT I'D SEE?
>> HE'S JUST SOMEONE I KNOW
AFTER WATCHING IT YESTERDAY,
HE'S MUCH MORE GROWN UP.
YEAH, WE SIGNED ON TO THE FILM
AT 23 AND NOW I'M 27.
THERE'S BAN TRANSITION OF GROWTH
JJ WAS SAYING IT TOO.
WE WATCH IT IN THE EDIT.
FORCE AWAKENS YOU WERE BABIES
MUCH WATCHING IN YOU NINE WE SEE
HOW YOU'VE GROWN AND THE
CONFIDENCE WE GET IN REAL LIFE
ACTUALLY INFLUENCES THE
CHARACTERS RATHER THAN THE
CHARACTERS INFLUENCING US.
>> JOHN BOYEGA I WILL BE ON THAT
CARPET AT SOME POINT THIS
EVENING.
I WILL NOT BE WITH JOHN.
HE'LL BE WALKING DOWN THE CARPET
DOING INTERVIEWS BECAUSE HE'S
THE STAR OF THE MOVIE.
BUT I WILL BE IN THAT SAME AREA
LATER ON TONIGHT.
I'LL TALK TO YOU GUYS ON GOOD
DAY.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN, JAMIE FOXX
AND JOHN BOYEGA ON GOOD DAY D.C.
STAY TUNE MANY LET US KNOW YOUR
THOUGHTS ON THE NEW STAR WARS IN
IF YOU'RE EXCITED #GOODDAYDC.
>> KEV, THANKS VERY MUCH.ANKS V.
>> I WANT TO SAY -- I THINK I
ARRIVE AT 5:30 ASSUMING THE
MOVIE IS AT 7:00.
I'VE NOT CHECKED THE TIMING YET
TO BE HONEST.
>> VERY COOL.
>> I'M TWO NERVOUS.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU ON GOOD DAY.
I KNOW YOU'RE EXCITED ABOUT IT.
>> NEWS IS NON-STOP SPEAKING OF
GOOD DAY.
GOOD DAY AT 9A STARTS RIGHT NOW.
LET'S JUST ROLE INTO IT.
♪
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, A MONDAY
MORNIN