CHRISSY ON TO DWITER AND YOU
SEE HIM WALKING OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL NANDIPATI HAND WITH
HIS TWO DAUGHTERS.
EARLIER IN THE DAY A STATEMENT
FROM NEWMAN'S TEAM SAYING
"TRUE TO HIS JOVIAL NATURE HE
HAS BEEN JOKE AROUND WITH
STAFF, FRIENDS AND FAMILY
WHILE SPENDING TIME PLAYING
WITH HIS TWO DAUGHTERS" RIGHT
NOW NO DETAILS ON HIS INJURIES
RELEASED AND THE TEAM NOT
ANNOUNCED WHO WILL DRIVE HIS
CAR AT LAS VEGAS RACE THIS
WEEKEND GUYS AND A LOT OF
PEOPLE CARING THIS TO THE
WRECK FROM DALE ERP HART.
19 YEARS AGO.
THAT UNFORTUNATELY ENDED
TRAUMATICALLY FROM FOR HIM AN
THE SAFETY NASCAR ASSURED
THESE DRIVERS INSIDE CARS ON
THE RACETRACK SAVING RYAN
NEWMAN AS LIFE.
>>  I WAS STILL EXPECTING A
CANE OR SOMETHING.
>>  NO IT IS ACTUALLY SOYN
CREDIBLE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT HOW THE CRASH
HAPPENED THEY TALK ABOUT HOW
THAT DRAFTING THE BUMPING AND
BLOCKING IT'S SOMETHING THEY
DO ALL THE TIME.
AND IT'S JUST SUCH A DELICATE
MANEUVER THAT ONE THING IT CAN
LEAD TO YOU VICTORY OR WHAT
THEY SAW THERE THERE.
>>  SO CLOSE TO THE FINISH
LINE FIVRPISHING FIRST BUT AT
LEAST HE'S ALIVE AND WELL.
>>  THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
MARINA.
>>  LET'S TURN OUR ATTENTION
TO THE WEATHER.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> CHECK OUT BLOSSOMS.
>> WOW.
>>  SO PRETTY OUT THERE.
>>  THIS IS NEER NATIONAL
HARBOR WARM WEATHER IS MAKING
THEM START TO BLOOEM.
>>  ALREADY.
>>  FEBRUARY 19TH, GUYS, THOSE
WHAT LOOK LIKE CHERRY MONTHS
OMZ I DON'T THINK THEY'RE OUR
TIDAL BASIN CHERRY MONTHS OMZ
CLOSE ENOUGH.
>>  UT, OH APRIL 1ST BIG
WEEKEND FOR THAT.
WE MAY HAVE TO MOVE IT UP THIS
YEAR.
>> THAT'S TRUE IF WE CONTINUE
AT THIS PACE WE WOULD BE
TALKING ABOUT A VERY EARLY
BLOOM FOR THE CHERRY BLOSSOMS.
BUT MOTHER NATURE ALWAYS WITH
A FEW TRICKS AND MARCH LOOKS
LIKE IT COULD START CHILLY,
GUYS, I'M JUST SAYING THAT.
OF COURSE, JANUARY AND
FEBRUARY SO MILD YOU TIMELY
GET TO MARCH EGG SERVE READY
FOR SPRING AND IT WILL BE
COLD.
THAT'S NOT A LOCK BUT
SOMETHING SHOWING UP IN THE
MODELS IN NOT SO DISTANT
FUTURE.
LOOK AT THE SUNSHINE ON
BUILDING TOPS IN NORTHWEST
D.C..
THAT'S BECAUSE IT TURNED INTO
A NICE AFTERNOON.
IT TOOK ALL DAY.
BUT THE CLOUD COVER KLOLY
GIVING WAY TO SUNSHINE.
50 IN THE DISTRICT.
STILL IN THE 40s ALONG 1.
48LE GAITHERSBURG AND 52
BALTIMORE AND 53 FRED
FREDERICKSBURG AND 53 CUL
CULPEPER.
YES IT'S BEEN BREEZY AND WIND
GUSTS ARE OVER 20 MILES AN
HOUR IN RESPONSIBLE SPOTS.
THAT HAS CERTAINLY KEPT THINGS
FEELING COOL DESPITE SUNSHINE.
CLOUD COVER LINE SLOWLY GIVING
WAY NORTH AND WEST AND HERE IN
THE METRO.
SOUTHERN MARYLAND AND SOUTH
EASTERN VIRGINIA STILL
STRUGGLING AND I THINK THEY'LL
CLEAR OUT TONIGHT.
TEMPERATURES FALL FAST AS
COLDER AIR FILTERS THROUGH AND
45 BY 7 P.M. AND 42 BY 9 P.M.
AND WE SHOULD FALL BELOW
FREEZING THERE BY 11:00.
IT WILL BE COLD HER TONIGHT WE
FALL CLOSE TO FREEZING IN
WASHINGTON AND OUTSIDE THE
BELTWAY WE COULD SEE 0s.
A QUICK BLAST OF COLD AND
WORKWEEK.
NICE WARM-UP INTO THE WEEKEND
AND DETAILS AHEAD, BLAKE,
ANGIE, OVER TO YOU.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
CAITLIN, POLICE CONTINUE TO
GUARD A HOME IN SOUTHERN
MARYLAND WHERE THE SON OF
PRINCE GEORGE COUNTY HOMICIDE
SERGEANT WAS SHOT AND KILLED
LAST NIGHT.
17-YEAR-OLD BRADLEYAL EP BROWN
WAS FOUND IN THE DRIVEWAY BY A
NEIGHBOR.
>> THIS POINT INVESTIGATORS DO
NO BELIEVE THE TEEN'S MURDERER
IS CORRECTED TO HIS FATHER'S
WORK.
PAUL WAGNER JOINS US LIVE FROM
THE SCENE IN CHARLES COUNTY
WITH MORE ON THE STORY.  HI,
PAUL.
>> Reporter: HEY, THERE ANKLE
YES, I MAKE, I'M ON WAREHOUSE
LANDING ROAD OFF BUSY ROUTE
210 INDIANA HIGHWAY IN THE
CHARLES COUNTY JUST BEFORE:00
LAST NIGHT THIS TEENAGER WAS
FOUND IN THE DRIVE WAY OF HIS
HOME JUST BEHIND ME YOU CAN
SEE THOSE UNMARKED CRUISERS
THERE THAT ARE BLOCKING THE
ROAD NOT ALLOWING ANYBODY TO
GO UP TO THE HOUSE AT THIS
POINT.
THIS IS A VERY TOUGH TIME FOR
THE PRINCE GEORGE COUNTY
POLICE COMMUNITY.  NOT ONLY IS
THIS DETECTIVE INCREDIBLY
WELL-KNOWN BUT HE HAS TWO SONS
ON THE POLICE FORCE AS WELL
AND BRADLEY BROWN THE TEENITH
FP AIRJ KILLED WAS IN THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE PROGRAM AT
NORTH POINT HIGH SCHOOL.
WE'LL SHOW YOU A PHOTO OF THAT
TEEN.
BROWN WAS A SENIOR ON TRACK TO
GRADUATE THIS COMING SPRING
FROM NORTH POINT WHERE HE RAN
CROSS COUNTRY.
HE WAS ALSO ACTIVE IN SCOUTING
AND ENTER EARNED ENOUGH
CREDITS TO BE EAGLE SCOUT.
HIS TRACK COACH SAID THE TEEN
ALWAYS HAD A SMILE ON HIS FACE
AND WOULD BOUNCE IF ONE GROUP
AT SCHOOL TO ANOTHER.
NEIGHBORS HERE ON WAREHOUSE
LANDING ROAD SAY BRADLEY WAS A
FRIENDLY KID ALWAYS WILLING TO
HELP.
FIRST ARRIVING DEPUTIES FOUND
THE TEEN WITH NO PULSE IN THE
DRIVE WAY AND A SMITH AND
WESSON 9mm PISTOL NEARBY.
AT THIS POINT, THE CHARLES
COUNTY SCHAEFER OFFICE IS NOT
SAYING MUCH ABOUT THIS CASE
OTHER THAN THEY'RE SAYING IT'S
NOT COME TO AND NO
AINVESTIGATES BEEN MADE.
THEY DO REPORT THAT THERE WERE
MULTIPLE SHOTS HEARD BY
NEIGHBORS NEAR THIS COMMUNITY.
BLAKE, ANGIE.
>> YEAH I'M CURIOUS DID THEY
ELABORATE OR SAY ANYTHING MORE
ABOUT THE PICTURE TOLL FOUND
AND YOU MENTIONED SHOTS FIRED
ANY OTHER SUSPICIOUS ACTIVITY
REPORTED BEFORE AND AFTER BY
THOSE THAT LIVE AROUND THERE?
>>> YEAH, AS FAR AS THE PISTOL
IS CONCERNED POLICE ARE NOT
SAYING ANYTHING ABOUT THAT AT
THIS POINT.
WE DO KNOW THAT THEY CHECKED
-- HE THEY HAD A SERIAL NUMBER
FOR THE PISTOL AND THEY TRIED
TO TRACE IT AT HAD THIS POINT
AND IT'S UNCLEAR WHO OWNS THAT
PISTOL AND WHY IT WAS THERE.
AT THIS POINT, IT'S UNCLEAR
WHETHER OR NOT THAT MAY HAVE
BEEN USED IN THE SHOOTING AND
THE NEIGHBORS HERE ON
WAREHOUSE LANDING TOLD ME THAT
THEY HAVE NOT SEEN ANY UNUSUAL
ACTIVITY HERE AND THAT THIS IS
JUST A COMPLETE SHOCK ON THIS
ROADWAY TONIGHT.
>>  YEAH, REAL SAD STORY.
PAUL, THANK YOU.
>>  IT'S DAY TWO OF JURY
DELIBERATIONS IN HARVEY
WEINSTEIN SEXUAL ASSAULT CASE.
THEY ASKED TO SEE EVIDENCE
INVOLVING HALEY.
SHE SAID SHE WAS FORCED TO
HAVE SEX WITH WEINSTEIN.
JURORS ASKED TO SEE EMAILS
WEINSTEIN SENT TO OTHER PEOPLE
REGARDING HALEY.
>>  DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ARE PREPARING TO
ROLL THE THE DICE IN LAS VEGAS
TONIGHT AND ALL EYES WILL BE
ON MIKE BLOOMBERG AND BERNIE
SANDERS.
HE WILL FACE OFF AGAINST FIVE
OF DEMOCRATIC RIVALS, BL
BLOOMBURG WILL FACE TOUGH
QUESTIONING REGARDING HIS
POSSESSIONS AND COMMENTS ON
EVERYTHING FROM FARMERS TO
STOP AND FRISK POLICING.
THIS WILL BE THE FINAL DEBATE
BEFORE THE NEVADA CAUCUSES ON
SATURDAY.
>>  ROB LAGOYAVICH IS HOME IN
CHICAGO AND SPEAKING OUT AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP COMMUTED HIS
SENTENCE FOR POLITICAL
CORRUPTION.
HE WAS SENTENCED TO 14 YEARS
AND SERVED 8 FOR TRYING TO
SELL THE SENATE SEAT VACATED
BY BARACK OBAMA.
>>  HE DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
HE'S A REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT.
I WAS A DEMOCRATIC GOVERNOR
AND DOING THIS DOES NOTHING TO
HELP HIS POLITICS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SURPRISE A MAN
WHO IS TOUGH AND OUT SPOKEN.
BUT HE ALSO HAS A KIND HEART.
>>  YESTERDAY THE PRESIDENT
GRANTED CLEMENCY TO A TOTAL OF
11 PEOPLE.
>>  NOW TO CAUGHT ON CAMERA
MOMENTS AN ELDERLY MAN FIGHTS
OFF A WOULD-BE ROBERT OUTSIDE
THIS GROCERY STORM OF THE
77-YEAR-OLD MAN WAS USING AN
AT BHXT THAT SUSPECT
APPROACHES HIM.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK HERE.
THEY START PUSHING A LITTLE
BIT.
THEY SQUARE UP LIKE BOXING
STYLE ALMOST HERE IT COMES.
OH, GOSH, HERE THEY GO.
>>  OH, MY GOODNESS.
>>  IT'S LIKE BOX SDMRING LIKE
WE'RE IN THE RING RIGHT
OUTSIDE A GROCERY STORE.
>>  THE SENIOR JOB WARDS OFF
THE MUGGER OH, HE EVEN SAID
COME HERE, COME ON, COME ON.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
WOW.
♪
>>  AMAZING CARRY ON.
>>  LOOK AT THAT EXTRAORDINARY
SIGHT A PATIENT PLAYING HER
VIOLIN AS SURGEONS IN LONDON
REMOVED A TUMOR FROM HER BR
BRAIN.
SHE'S UNDERGOING BRAIN SURGERY
TO KEEP HER ALERT AND MAKE
SURE HAPPENED MOVEMENT AND
COORDINATION WERE NOT DAMAGED
DURING THE OPERATION THEY
ASKED THE 53-YEAR-OLD TO PLAY
THE VIOLIN SHE PRAISED THE
SURGEONS WHO IS A MUSIC LOVER.
>>  A WOMAN VACUUMING THE
SIDEWALK.
BEFORE YOU JUDGE THE WOMAN HAS
A PRETTY GOOD EXPLANATION.
SHE WAS CLEANING UP GLASS
AFTER A DRUNK DRIVER CRASHED
INTO HER CAR AND DIDN'T WANT
ANYONE STEPPING ON THE BROKEN
GLASS AND GETTING HURT.
HER CAR WAS TOTALED AND GO
FUND ME PAGE IS SET UP TO HELP
HER BUY A NEW VEHICLE.
>>  THINGS AREN'T ALWAYS WHAT
THEY SEEM WHEN YOU THINK WHAT
IS THAT WEIRDO DOING.
>>  UNION WORKERS EMPLOYED BY
SAFE WAY SAY THEY WILL BE OFF
THE JOB SOON IF A NEW COURT IS
NOT WORKED OUT.
TODAY THEY WERE PROTESTING
OUTSIDE A SAFE WAY IN SOUTH
WEST.
MARCH 5 IS A KEY DATE IN ALL
THIS WHEN THE LOCAL 400 GROUP
SAID IT WILL VOTE ON AWHETHER
TO STRIKE.
TENTATIVE AGREEMENT BETWEEN
UNION AND GIVRNLT WILL BE IN
TWO WEEKS.
>>  OAR LIPING TOON COOL
CELEBRATING ONE OF THE STATE'S
MOST IMPORTANT REASONS FOR A
START TO A NEW DAY.
HE WAS OUT THERE THIS MORNING
NEAR 26 AND MILITARY ROAD LIKE
HE'S BEEN DOING THE LAST THREE
YEARS.
ST. ALEEK IS A TRAINED CHEF
HAVE I'M OWN YAP SINCE THIS
JOB HE CONSIDERS HIMSELF A
PUBLIC SERVANT.
>>  WHOEVER COMES TO YOU YOU
HAVE TO ACCEPT HIM AND RECEIVE
HIM WITH WARM MIND YOU KNOW
BECAUSE OF THEM I'M HERE.
BECAUSE OF THE CHILDREN I'M
HERE.
>>  YEAH THEY DO SAY YOU CAN
CHANGE THE WORLD WITH A SMILE
AND IMAGINE HOW MANY DAYS HE'S
CHANGED AAND HOW MANY PEOPLE
HE UP LIFTED MR. Z WON AT WORD
AFTER BEATING OUT 70 OTHER
CROSSING GUARDS AGAINST
VIRGINIA STIFF COMPETITION.
SO --
>>  I CAN SEE THIS AS POST
RETIREMENT JOB FOR YOU WITH
ALL THE COSTUME.
>> IT WOULD BE FEW LIKE
HALLOWEEN CROSSING THE STREET
EVERY DAY.
>> HEY, GUYS GOT TO UPDATE FOR
YOU.
JUST IN NUMBERS FOR THIS Y
YEAR'S NEWS BASH 40,000 AND
COUNTING GOING TO BREAST
CANCER "FOX5" FAMILIAR FACES
JOINING PACKED CROWD AT THE
PEARL STREET HOUSE JOINING TO
HELP BREAST CANCER GROUPS IN
THE REAM DON'T.
WHAT A NIGHT AT THE WAR OF IF
FAM TURNING UP FOR THE STEP
SISTERS.
THE MONEY RAISED WILL GO TO
THAT ORGANIZATION'S CRISIS
FUND WHICH HELPS PATIENTS COST
COST OF EVERYTHING FROM
PRESENT AND MORTGAGE TO
GROSSYES AND MEDICINE.
SO, A REALLY BIG NIGHT.
WHAT A NIGHT AT THE WAR OF,
WOW.
>> THERE'S NOT A LOT OF
OPPORTUNITIES FOR ALL THE
STATIONS TO COME TOGETHER AND
SAY THIS IS A CAUSE WE ALL
BELIEVE IN AND WORTH HIGH
HEIGHT SDMRING AND WE PUT
EVERYTHING ASIDE.
>>  WE PUT ALL OUR DIFFERENCE
ASIDE.
>> STILL TO COME A YOUNG GIRL
IN LOUDOUN COUNTY IS USING
CRAYONS TO TEACH APP IMPORTANT
LESSON OF DIVERSITY FOR OTHER
STUDENTS AND SHE'S STILL IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
>> AND PHONE CATCHES FIRE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A FLIGHT CAUSING
PANIC AND EMERGENCY LANDING.
WE'LL EXPLAIN HOW THIS ALL
HAPPENED.
>>  AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
OT TRAFFIC AROUND THE DMV AS
RUSH HOUR RAMPS UP.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
BEFORE YOU GET LOOSE AND START
TO LOSE YOUR MIND♪
♪
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
McKissack and McKissack
is the nation's oldest
black-owned design
and construction firm.
Before Mike, we were desperate.
There were not a lot
of opportunities for
black-owned businesses
to compete.
Mike saw that and he leveled
the playing field for
black-owned businesses.
Over the years, we have
heard a lot of talk.
But Mike came in, and he
actually did something about it.
And that's how Mike will get
it done as president.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> A BRITISH AIRLINE FLIGHT
WAS FORCED TO LAND WHEN A
CELLPHONE SPARKED A FIRE ON
BOARD FORTSING IT TO LAND IN
BERMUDA.
BRITISH AIRWAYS SAYS THE CELL
HOPE TO FELL INTO A FULLY
REKLIPD SEAT.
>>  I TRIED TO RETRIEVE IT
MYSELF IS THE ISSUE.
IT BROKE THE LITHIUM BATTERY
AND THERE WAS FLAMES AND SMOKE
COMING FROM THE CHAIR.
I THINK THE SMOKE WAS PRETTY
MUCH CONTAINED AND STRAIGHT
AWAY THE STUD AR GRABBED WHAT
LAKDZ LUKE A FIRE EXTINGUISHER
OUT OF THE BACK.
I DIDN'T THINK THAT WAS TOO
GOOD.
>>  CAN YOU PAGE IN30 FEET UP
IN THE AIR AND YOU START A
FIRE IN YOUR SEAT.
AFTER FIREFIGHTERS INSPEINGTSD
THE PLANE THE JOURNEY DID
CONTINUE TO TAMPA AND ARRIVED
A FEW HOURS LATE.
>>  THAT'S FRIGHT EPING.
>> A STUDENT IN LOUDOUN IS
MAKING A HUGE IMPACT ON HER
COMMUNITY AND ONLY IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
ELLEN WITNESSARD STARTED MORE
THAT PEACH PROJECT AFTER TIRED
OF HER FRIENDS AND CLASSMATES
REFERRING TO PEACH COY ON AS
SKIN COLOR CRAYON.
SHE'S HOPING TO RAISE
AWARENESS BY HANDED OUT
MULTI-CULTURAL EXTRA ON.
THE 9 THE-YEAR-OLD STOPPED TO
SHARE WHAT IT MEANS TO HER.
>>  IT MAKES ME FEEL GOOD
BECAUSE NOW EVERYONE KNOWS
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE SKIN
COLOR BESIDES A PEACH CRAYON.
>>  WHAT DO YOU HOPE THIS DO
DO IN THE FUTURE.
I KNOW YOU'RE NINE WHAT DO YOU
HOPE TO DO TEN YEARS DOWN THE
ROAD SGLUXT M, WHAT I WANT TO
BE WHEN I GROW UP IS ASTR
ASTRONAUT, SCIENTIST AND AC
ACTOR.
>>  YOU'RE GOING TO BE ALL
THAT.
>>  YES.
>>  HOW DO YOU THINK YOU'LL
MAKE SURE EVERYBODY KNOWS
ABOUT MORE THAN PEACH.
>>  I'M GOING TO MAKE -- I
HOPE THAT MORE THAN PEACH
KEEPS ON RUNNING THROUGHOUT
THE YEARS.
>>  YEAH.
>> AND IT MAY NOT BE LIKE H
HUGE, HUGE AS THE YEARS PASS
BY BUT AT LEAST THEN MAYBE
EVERYONE WOULD KNOW ABOUT MORE
THAN PEACH AND KNOW THAT
THERE'S MORE THAN ONE SKIN
COLOR AND ALL THE CLASSES AND
WHAT HAVE MULTI-CULTURAL EXTRA
YONZ AND MARKERS AND STUFF.
>> HOW ADORABLE IS SHE.
HOW ADORE SABL SHE.
>>  YOU CAN DONATE TO THE
PROJECT AND REQUEST
MULTI-CULTURAL EXTRA YONZ AND
YOUR CLASS AT MORE THAN
PEACH.com.
>>  NOW TO RESIDENT SCIENTIST.
>>  CAITLIN IT'S KNOT NICE TO
SEE THEY MADE A BIG FOUSH MAKE
SURE LITTLE YOU GIRLS
UNDERSTAND THERE'S MA'AM AND
SCIENCE PROGRAMS OUT THERE FOR
THEM.
>> HUGE STEM PROGRAMS.
TO MUCH MIND NOW.
WE DEPOSIT HAVE TWHAT I WAS
YOUNG YOU.
>> NO, I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
LIKE IT.
IT IS WONDERFUL.
EACH THOUGH I DID GRADUATE
WITH A SCIENCE DEGREE IT WAS
ALWAYS A STRUGGLE, MA'AM AND
SCIENCE WELL ARE NOT EASY.
I WOULD NOT WANT TO GO BACK.
I'M HAPPY FOR HER.
THAT'S A WONDERFUL PROJECT AND
LOOK AT THAT LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
WE H WHAT A WONDERFUL DAY
AGAIN.
ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL ONE IN THE
YAIBD.
SUNSHINE CAME OUT AFTER
MORNING CLOUD COVER FELT NICE
TO SEE THAT.
WE'RE TURN COLDER OVERNIGHT AS
WE GET A QUICK NRAINGT OUT OF
ARCTIC AND THAT MEANS LOW
NORMAL TEMPERATURES THE LAST
COUPLE DAYS.
FLURRIES COULD COME NOT
SOUTHERN COUNTY THIS AFTERNOON
AND EVENING AND THIS WOULD BE
A MINOR THING IF IT HAPPENS.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE MODEL IN A
MINUTE.
IT GETS CLOSE.
IT MAY NOT BE CLOSE ENOUGH.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S GETTING COLD
THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS WARMING
UP AS WE HEAD TO THE WEEKEND.
CURRENT TEMPERATURES OUTSIDE
RIGHT NOW NICE 53 WASHINGTON
AND 52 RICH MOPPED AND 55 NEW
YORK AND BOSTON AND COLDER
BACK NORTH AND WEST AND 39
PITTSBURGH AND 39 COLUMBUS AND
39 CHICAGO.
THE JET STREAM DIPS STARTING
TONIGHT WE'LL SHOW YOU LOW
TEMPERATURES 20s AND 30s AND
PROBABLY STRUGGLE TO GET FAR
ABOVE 40 FOR TOMORROW AND SAME
THING FOR FRIDAY.
FRIDAY MORNING WILL BE COLDNER
20s.
DAYTIME HIGHs 30s TO MAYBE 40s
IN SOUTH CENTRAL VIRGINIA.
FEELING LIKE WINTER AND
FEBRUARY WE DID THIS LAST WEEK
AND WE'LL DO IT TOMORROW AND
FIRDAY IT'S SHORT LIVED.
LATE DAY FLURRIES AND FRIDAY,
SUNSHINE, BRIGHT, BRIGHT,
SUNSHINE AND BEAUTIFUL APE
BRISK.
KEEPING A CLOSE EYE ON THE
SYSTEM SOUTH AND WEST.
SO ARCTIC HIGH PRESSURE TO THE
NORTH WILL STEP TRESS
EVERYTHING OUT OF THE AREA.
RALEIGH, THROUGH NORFOLK AND
CHARLOTTESVILLE TO SEE
FLURRIES, SOUTHERN MARYLAND,
LOWER EASTERN SHORE, YES, 5:30
TOMORROW.
WE'RE ON THE EDGE OF
PRECIPITATION.
THAT'S WHY WE KEEP FLURRIES IN
THE FORECAST.
BY IN LARGE THIS IS A SYSTEM
STAYING SOUTH AND WE'LL MOVE
OFFSHORE EARLY FRIDAY.
ACTUALLY, SNOW FOR PLACES LIKE
NORTHERN -- NORM CAROLINA AND
UP TO SOUTHEASTERN VIRGINIA
COUPLE INCHES RALEIGH,
CHARLOTTE.
NOR POKE ANOTHER SWING AND
MISS.
THAT'S A LOOK AT THE NEXT
COUPLE DAYS STILL AHEAD.
>> IT'S YOUR BIRTH DAY.
>>  IT'S ALL ABOUT --
>>  GO MAMA, GO MAMA.
>>  YOU LIKE IT DON'T YOU.
>>  IS IT REAL?
>> THIS WEEK ON OH, MY GOLF
ANGIE GOFF SHOW.
WE HAD A FEW SUBPOENAS FOR HER
TOO.
>> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL SHE'S SO
GREAT THEY'RE ALWAYS LIKE
SHE'S TO BEAUTIFUL SHE'S SO
GREAT THEY'RE NOT LYING RIGHT.
>> WHAT'S YOUR SECRET WHAT DO
YOU DO TO KEEP IT FLAWLESS.
>> DOESN'T CLEAN YOUR SKIN
LIKE PONDS.
>>  WE HAVE A SITUATION♪
♪
BOY THAT ESCALATED QUICKLY.
>>  WHAT DO YOU THINK MAMA
CHIN.
>> I THINK IT WAS WONDERFUL.
>>  THERE'S MY DAD.
>>  YOU CAN SEND ME A PICTURE
THIS.
>> YOU TAPED THIS MONDAY
MORNING.
>>  YES.
>>  THIS IS HOW ANGIE STARTS
YOUR WORKWEEK WE'RE DOING IT
WRONG.
>>  IT'S 10:00 SOMEWHERE.
>> THE REST OF THE PARTY
UNIQUE GIFT IDEAS TO GET
SOMEONE SPECIAL OPEN SOWED 37
ON THE OH, MY GOFF SHOW AS
WELL AS APPLE POD CAST.
MAMA CHIN SAID THIS WAS THE
BEST DAY OF HER LIFE.
HE SAW MY DAD AT THE END FRAME
THE PHOTO OF HER AND CHASE IT
PUT IT IN THE HOUSE LIKE HE'S
A FAMILY MEMBER WITH OPEN A
ARMS.
BUT, YEAH.
>>  THAT'S VERY CUTE.
>>  SHE DOESN'T TAKE 20s.
SHE ONLY WROTE 20 FOR BIRTH
DAY AND IT'S 100 DOLLAR BILL.
>>  MY SISTER GAVE HER BILLS
AND LIKE DOES THIS COUNSELED.
>> STILL TO COME CASINOS.
LOT MORE TO WALK N.
>> STILL TO COME.
BURGER KING IS ATING CAMPAIGN
FOR FAMOUS WHOER ARE HEAD
SCRATCH AIR LITTLE BIT.
WHY THE FAST FOOD SDMRVR THE
WHOLE TEAM BACK IN TOWN.
>>  MARINA MARRACO WITH A LOOK
AT WHAT IS TRENDING.
>>  HOPEFULLY ON HAVE A OKAY
YOU DEPOSIT EAT FAST FOOD.
IF YOU DID A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
GROSSED OUT ABOUT THE VIDEO
BURGER KING TRYING TO SHOW
THEIR I DON'T KNOW I WANT TO
SEE THE PICTURE I HAVE NOT
SEEN IT BUT I WANT TO REACT
THEY SHOW BASICALLY HOW THEIR
BIG MAC.
>>  THAT'S THE WHOER.
>>  WHOER.
>>  OH,
>>  PEACH FUZZ.
>>  THERE YOU GO.
>>  I'LL LET YOU REACT.
>>  LOOKS LIKE PRO DMUS MY
FRIDGE.
>>  THE WHOER IS TURNING MOLDY
AND THE THE REASON I BROUGHT
UP THE BIG SMACK BECAUSE TO
COMPARE ITSELF TO COMPETITOR
MCDONALD'S BIG MACK WHICH
NEVER DISSINT GRATES.
>>  NO PRESERVATIVES.
>>  AS A CONSUMER DO YOU
REALLY WANT TO SEE HOW IT GOES
BAD.
>>  NO.
>>  I DON'T -- I FEEL LIKE
IMAGES ARE POWERFUL AND THEY
STICK WITH YOU.
TO THIS DAY THIS IS WHY MY
HUSBAND DOESN'T EAT MAYO
MAYONNAISE.
>>  TOUCHING AND SEEING IT.
I DON'T HE KNOW THIS WILL WORK
FOR THEM YOU.
>> MAY START THINKING ABOUT
MOLD EVERY TIME YOU OPEN.
>>  IT LOOKED LIKE A COTTON
BOWL GROW AROUND THE BURGER.
>>  SOMETIMES I THINK AS A
JUICY CHAR BROYLD CAMPAIGN BUT
I THINK THEY WEPT WRONG HERE.
>>  BURGER KING HOME OF THE
WHOER.
>> I THINK MORE BIG MACKS WILL
BE BEING COLD.
>>  WE'LL MOVE ON IT'S A BIG
TALKER OWN SOCIAL MEDIA TODAY
SUBWAY SOCIAL CLUB IN NEW YORK
FOLKS TALKING TO STRAI
STRAIVRPINGZER ON TRAINSL
OKING FOR THOSE PEOPLE I'M
OPEN TO A CONVERSATION COME
TALK TO ME.
>>FY KNOW THE TRAIN PEOPLE I'M
LOOKING A LONG TIME FOR PINS.
RAIDING THE NEWSPAPER.
>>  YOU GET THAT AABOUT NEW
NEW YORKERS.
>>  MIP IS GET OUT OF THE WAY
YOU'RE ON THE WRONG SIDE OF
THE SIDEWALK.
>>  STILL TO COME A MAJOR.
>>  CHANGING REQUIREMENTS FOR
SPORTS AND ACTIVITIES.
GET OUT YOUR PHONES IT'S
SUBJECT OF "FOX5" UP IS IT A
POLL TODAY.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> NOW A LOOK AT SOME OF THE
TOP STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING 1
IS 3th SUSPECT IS IN CUSTODY
FOR STABBING DEATH OF TESSA
MAJOR IN NEW YORK CITY AND THE
IS 4-YEAR-OLD TURNED HIMSELF
INTO AUTHORITIES.
HE AND A 14 HAD-YEAR-OLD BOY
ARRESTED SATURDAY APPEARED IN
COURT TODAY AND PLEADED NOT
GUILTY.
MAJOR HAVE CHARLOTTESVILLE
STUDYING AT BARNARD COLLEGE.
>>  REDUCED WORKLOAD REMOTELY.
APP INVESTIGATION TO WHAT
CAUSED THAT FALSE ALARM IS
UNDERWAY.
>>  GOOD NEWS FOR RED SKIPS
FANS.
VETERAN RUNNING BACK ADRIAN
PETER SOP WILL RETURN NEXT
SEASON.
SHE EXERCISED 2020 CLUB OPTION
ON PETERSON'S CONTRACT A MOVE
WIDELY EXPECTED.
HE TURNS 35 IN MARCH AND WAS
RED SKIP LEADING RUSHER LAST
SEASON WITH 900 YARDS AND FIVE
TOUCHDOWNS.
HE'S CURRENTLY RANKEDIVE IFTH
ON NFL CAREER RUSHING LIST
STILL GOING STRONG.
>>  THE REDSKINS HAD FIVE
TOUCHDOWNS.
>>  THAT'S A LOW BLOW.
>>  SPORTS AND EXTRACU
EXTRACURRICULARS ARE A CORNER
STONE OF HIGH SCHOOL LIFE.
SCHOOL DISTRICT HAVE MINIMUM
GPA TO PARTICIPATE.
SOME MEMBERS OF MONTGOMERY
COUNTY SCHOOL BOARD WANT TO
GET RID OF THAT FOR SOME
STUDENTS.
IKE EJIOCKH IS LIVE FROM
BETHESDA.
IKE, THIS PROPOSAL EXEMPTS
FRESHMEN FROM 2.0 GPA
THRESHOLD.
THERE WILL SOME STUDENTS THAT
ACTUALLY G COULD BENEFIT BY
BEING INCLUDED IN
EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES AND
SPORTS PROGRAMS.
THEY'RE HERE SAYING INCLUSION
OF EVERYONE WILL DO BETTER FOR
THE SCHOOL SYSTEM AS A WHOLE.
EVEN THEY CITE THE SUDDENY BY
SAYING IT WILL DO POSITIVES
SUCH AS INCREASE THE
GRADUATION RATES FOR STUDENTS
AND IT WILL RAISE THEIRSELF
ESTATE AND EQUIPPED THEM WITH
LIFE SKILLS THEY NEED BOEJ
POST SCHOOL.
>>  THEY WEREN'T THE BEST
STUDENTS BUT REALLY THRIVED IN
SPORTS.
>>  I SPOKE TO SEVERAL PARENTS
AND ADMINISTRATOR FROM OTHER
SCHOOLS.
THEY FEEL SPORTS AND
ACTIVITIES THEY'RE SAYING
THERE SHOULD BE A REWARD NOT A
PRIVILEGE.
THEY'RE SAYING THAT THIS
ACTUALLY SENDS THE WRONG
MESSAGE TO STUDENTS BY SAYING
YOU KNOW WHAT, COOL IS NOT
THAT IMPORTANT JUST COME IN
HERE AND HAVE A GOOD TIME.
CLEAR CLEARLY BOTH SIDES OF
HIS OFFENSE HERE.
AND THIS IS JUST A
PROPOSITION.
WE'LL OFFICIALLY PRESENT THE
BOARD IN THE NEXT FEW MONTHS
AND PUBLIC HAS A CHANCE TO
COME IN AND VOICE CONCERNS.
AND IN EFFECT FORTHE 202 IT IT
1 SCHOOL YEAR.
>>  WRUVR STAND ON IT
DISCUSSION WORTH HAVING.
>>.
>>  TAW A LOOK.
>>  93% SAY YES.
>>  KEEP IN MIND WE JUST PUTLE
POLLS UP BEFORE THE NEWSCAST.
>>.
>>  WE'LL CHECK BACK N ALL
RIGHT.
STILL TO COME, IT'S OFFICIAL
MRAIK.
>> GO-GO MUSIC THAT IS RIGHT
TEAR IT UP MO IN THE STUDIO.
THE MUSIC IS GETTING
RECOGNITION IT SDEVBS IN
NATION'S CAPITOL.
WE'RE GOING LIVE TO THE BILL
SIGNING AND CELEBRATION.
>>  AND LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
ALONG THE BELTWAY NEAR GREEN
BELT MARYLAND AS WE GO TO
BREAK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Here's one you guys will like.
Show me Making It.
Oh! I got one.
The Best of Amy Poehler.
Amy, maybe we could
use the Voice Remote
to search for something
that you're not in.
Show me Parks and Rec.
From Netflix to
Prime Video to live TV,
Xfinity lets you
find your favorites
with the Emmy award-winning
X1 Voice Remote.
Show me The Best of
Amy Poehler, again.
This time around...
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
for $79.99 a month
for two years.
Plus, for a limited time,
get $100 pre-paid card.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
>> JUST ABOUT EVERY STREET
FESTIVAL, CITY, CELEBRATION OR
WALKING DOWN THE STREET IN THE
DISTRICT YOU'RE LIKELY TO HEAR
GO, GO MUSIC.
>>  IT'S SOUNDS EVER CITY
TODAY BECAME THE OFFICIAL
MUSIC OF D.C., GWEN GWEN JOINS
US LIVE IN SOUTHWEST WITH ALL
THE EXCITEMENT.
>>  YOU HAVE A GO GO HAT.
>>  THIS IS AA MAJOR
DEPARTMENT.
>>  TIME TO GET DOWN.
>>♪
♪
>>  AND IT'S A PACKED HOUSE
HERE.
>>  RIGHT NOW THE MAYOR IS
ACTUALLY SPEAKING AND
ADDRESSING EVERYONE HERE.
THIS PLACE IS JUST PACKED WALL
TO WALL WITH PEOPLE FROM D.C.
WHO REALLY HAVE SUCH A PASSION
FOR GO GO MUSIC AS BECOMES THE
OFFICIAL MUSIC OF CITY.
WITH ME NOW IS SOMEONE WHO
FEELS THE SAME WAY.
THIS IS  VALJEAN THOMAS.
YOU'RE A LONG-TIME D.C.
RESIDENT FOR LIFE WHY IS THIS
IMPORTANT.
>>  GO GO MUSIC HAS BECOME
PART OF CULTURE.
IT'S VERY POINTED TO ME.
YOU CANNOT HELP WHEN YOU HEAR
THE BEAT YOU WANT TO GET UP
AND DANCE.
AND THEN AFTER HEARING THE
MUSIC I NOTICED THAT A LOT OF
ARTISTS THAT ARE NOT FROM THIS
AREA ARE SAMPLING GO GO MUSIC.
DO GO MUSIC IS A CULTURE AND
I'M GLAD D.C. IS FINALLY BEING
RECOGNIZED FOR THE MUSIC WE
ARE PRODUCING IN THIS AREA.
>>  YOU'RE SOMEONE WHO IS BORN
AND RACED IN D.C. AND IT'S
BEEN PART OF YOUR LIFE FOR SO
LONG.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THIS MESSAGE
SENDS TO THE YOUNG PEOPLE.
>>  I THINK THAT IF THEY HAVE
A DREAM AND THEY BELIEVE IN
MUSIC BECAUSE I CAN REMEMBER
HOW MY BROTHER STARTED WITH
RARE ESSENCE.
AND HE WANTED THE MUSIC AND HE
GOT HIS GUYS TOGETHER AND
BUDDIES AND THEY WOULD
PRACTICE MUSIC AND IT WAS
SOMETHING FOR THEM TO GO AND
SOME PLACE FOR THEM TO DO IT
AND IT WAS JUST LIKE -- IT WAS
FUN TO SEE ALL THESE YOUNG
PEOPLE CREATE MUSIC THAT HAS
THIS STRONG BEAT.
I JUST LOVE GO GO AND JUST TO
SEE IT ON BET MY GOD THAT WAS
WOULDN'T FUVRM I ALMOST --
WELL DI CRY TO SHE THEM AND MY
BROTHER JAMES FUNCTIONLE ON
THERE AND ALL THESE PEOPLE
COME TOGETHER TO REALIZE NOW
THAT GO GO MUSIC IS PART OF
D.C..
IT IS D.C.
>> YOU'RE DEFINITELY RIGHT AND
TODAY IT BECOMES OVERRULELY
PART OF D.C..
THANK YOU FOR SPEAKING WITH
US.
DEFINITELY ALL OF THESE PEOPLE
ARE HERE BECAUSE THEY CARE
ABOUT.
IT I'M TELL YOU I HEARD SOME
OF IT EARLIER I CANNOT STAND
STILL.
BACK TO YOU.
>>  WELL, SHE'S SUPPOSED IT UP
PERFECT LIMIT WE'RE AIR HER
CLIP FOR THE REST OF THE NI
NIGHT.
>>  I KNOW BECAUSE REALLY MORE
THAN A GENRE IT'S A GROOVE AND
FEELING AND IT'S A FEELING OF
THE CITY AND IT REPRESENTS SO
MUCH MORE.
>>  THERE ARE NOT MANY CITIES
IN THE WORLD THAT CAN LAY
CLAIM TO A SPECIFIC TYPE OF ME
SUTION.
>>  JAZZ, NEW ORLEANS,
NASHVILLE, COMMUNITY, THERE
ARE NOT A LOT OF CITIES THAT
CAN SAY THEY HAVE THEIR OWN
MUSIC.
>>  AUTOPSYEN COMING RAPPER
POP SMOKE WAS SHOT AT HIS
HOLLYWOOD HOME.
THERE'S A LOT OF QUESTIONS
SURROUNDING HAD HIS DEATH THIS
WAS TOP TREPINGD STORY IN
D.C..
IF YOU HAVE NOT HEARD OF HIM A
LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE AND TMZ
WILL JOIN BUS IT COMING UP.
>> POPULAR LADIES SONG TAKE ON
ME HUT A HISTORIC MILESTONE IN
THE INDUSTRY.
AND THIS VIDEO IS SO COOL.
>> I MEAN THIS JUST TAKES ME
BACK TO WATCHING VH-1 POPUP
VIDEO ON REPEAT AS A ADD LESS
SGLENLT REMEMBER WHEN WE
WATCHED MUSIC VISITIOS.
>>  I WAS WATCHING MTV COOLER.
>> I WAS WATCHING VH-1.
>> I WAS WALKING WHAT.
>>  FUSE.
>>  SGLUS DID YOU EVER WATCH
THAT.
>>  MY CABLE DEPOSIT DO THAT
HIGH.
>> VH-1 I WAS PROBABLY
WATCHING WITH MY PAEVRNLTS
POPUP VIDEO.
I DO MISS THE MUSIC VIDEOS.
WE'LL HAVE THE FORECAST AS
WELL AND QUICK DAY AND QUICK
BLAST OF COLD AIR AND FOLLOWED
BY A COOL WEEKEND.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.
>> FORGET E-ZPass THERE'S AN
ANY APP IN THE D.C. REGION.
>>  MORE ON THAT AND WHAT
THEY'RE WORK ON, HI, SARAH.
>>  BRAND NEW APP THAT CAN
MAKE YOU RIDE A LITTLE
SMOOTHER AT LEAST WHEN IT
COMES TO PAYING TOLLS.
WE WILL SHOW YOU HOW THAT
WORKS.
>> AND DO YOU REMEMBER CUPID
HERE A LOCAL CAT THAT IS
REALLY LUCKY TO BE ALIVE AFTER
HIT BY AN ARROW.
WE HAVE AN A BIG UPDATE ON THE
CAT'S RECOVERY PROCESS AND HOW
HIS STORY IS HELPING DOZENS OF
OTHER SHELTER APP MALLS IN
NEED.
>> AND PLUS, WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS THE MOST POPULAR DISNEY
RIDE.
I NEW LIST IS WRAVRPINGING
BEST OF THE BEST AND NUMBER
ONE SPOT MAY NOT BE WHAT YOU
EXPECT, GUYS.
>>  IT'S A SMALL WORLD WHAT I
WOULD THINK MAYBE NOSTALGIA.
>> HOW MANY TIMES YOU HAVE
BEEN THERE.
>>  IS HE AN EXPERT.
>>  I DON'T HAVE KIDS.
>>  WE ALWAYS DO IT'S A SMALL
WORLD FOR NOSTALGIA BUT
BIGGEST IS SPACE MOUNTAIN OR
ONE OF THOSE.
>>  IT'S POPULAR.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU AT "FOX5".
>>  SURE.
>> AHA MUSIC VIDEO.
IN 2020 TAKE ON ME JUST
REACHED 1 BILLION VIEWS ON
uTUBE♪
♪
IT'S RARE FOR PRE1990 TRACKS
TO HIT THAT MILESTONE.
TAKES FIST FOR EUROPEAN ACT.
THE SONG WAS ORIGINALLY
RELEASED IN 194 AND IT WAS"
CHRONIC PENCIL SKETCH
ANIMATION IN THE MUSIC VIDEO
THAT MADE IT FAME US.  GROUND
BREAKING.
AND PAULA ABDUL DID DANCING
WITH THE CAR SGLOON I MISSED
THAT.
>> AND LAST NIGHT WAS 40th
EDITION OF NATIONAL BRIT
AWARDS.
>>  SINGER, LOUIS CAPALDI TOOK
HOME BEST NEW ARTIST AND SONG
OF THE YEAR FOR SOMEONE YOU
LOVED AND BILLY EILISH BEAT
OUT ARIANA GRAND YEAH FOR
FEMALE ARTIST.
♪
>>  AND THE WINER IS.
>>  HERE AT "FOX5" IT'S NO
PSYCH RECEIPT I'M NOT A BIG
BILLY EI LIMIT SH FAN.
>>  SHE WROTE IT AND IT'S
GOOD.
>>  EI LIMIT SH MADE LIVE
DEBUT WITH THAT SONG AND IT'S
ON FACE TO BECOME FIRST UK
CHART TOPPER.
>>  I LIKED WHAT I HEARD.
>>  I THINK HER VOICE MATCHES
THAT MOVIE.
>> IT'S LIKE A MUCH SLOWER,
SADDER VERSION OF ADELE SKY
FALL.
>>  WE HAVE TO MENTION LIZZO
OWEP LOOK.
THIS DRESS IS INSPIRED BY
LUCHINO I CAN NEVER SAY THOSE
FANCY NAMES IT HAD A BAR CODE,
NUTRITION LABEL AND PRICE TAG
OF TA CENTS ON IT AND HAD A
JEWEL ENCRUSTED CHOCOLATE BAR.
>>  AND I KNOW THIS WRAPPED
DOES A LOT OF CHEEK QUESTION
AND NOVELTY TYPE THINGS.
I USED TO HAVE A FRENCH FRIED
HOPE TO COVER.
>>  THIS IS LEAST OUT THERE
THINGS I'VE SEEN LIDDO.
>>  RAPPER POP SMOKE WAS SHOT
IN WHAT AAPPEARS A HOME UP
VACATION.
THERE'S A LOT OF QUESTIONS
SURROUNDING THE UP AND COMING
RAPPER'S DEATH.
TMZ ALL OVER THIS STORY.
LAUREN LAROSEA FIRST.
>>  FOR THOSE OF US WHO DON'T
KNOW WHO HE IS.
HOW WELL
♪ IS HE IN LOS ANGELES.
>> SUPER WELL KNOWN POP SMOKE
IS ARTIST FROM BROOKYLN NEW
YORK, 20 O. SUPER YOUNG.
RELEASE AID SONG LAST SUMMER
WELCOME TO THE PARTY.
IT WAS HUGE, NIKKI MINAJ
REMIXED THE SONG.
HIS PROJECT HIT NUMBER 7 ON
BILLBOARD CHART TUESDAY.
SO HE WAS A AN UP AND COMING
ART AIST.
TRAVIS SCOTT, HAD A LOT OF
POTENTIAL.
THIS IS VERY, VERY SAD BECAUSE
HE HAD SO MUCH POTENTIAL H HE
WAS HOME AT AIR BNB THEY WERE
RENTING IN HOLLYWOOD HILLS AND
AROUND 4:30 THERE WERE FOUR
HELP WEARING HOODIES AND MASKS
THAT BROKE INTO HIS HOME AND
FIRED MULTIPLE SHOT KILLING
POP SMOKE AND HE WAS RUSHED TO
SINAI.
SUSPECTS WERE NOT CAUGHT AND
IT'S UP CLEAR FOR NOW WHAT THE
FILLING INFORM GRAY AREA WAS.
DID HE♪
SHOOTERS.
THERE WAS AN ALARM IN THE H
HOLE.
THE ALARM WAS NOT SET WHEN
THEY GOT UP TO LOCK THE DOORS
RIGHT BEFORE THE MEN ENTERED
HOME.
>>  THIS IS AIR BNB BUT HE WAS
RENTING IT.
>> YES.
>>  THEY MAY V NOT HAVE BEEN
TARGETING HIM.
>>  THERE'S SO MANY QUESTIONS
THERE AND I DON'T WANT TO SAY
ANYTHING THAT PEOPLE WOULD
TAKE AS US CON FIRPING
ANYTHING BECAUSE WE DON'T KNOW
THE ANSWERS TO THAT QUESTION.
THE WAY IT SEEMS BECAUSE
THERE'S MULTIPLE PEOPLE IN THE
HOME AND HE WAS THE ONLY ONE
HIT IS THAT HE MAY HAVE BEEN
TARGETEDED BUT AGAIN, WE
WEREN'T -- WE WERE NOT INSIDE
THE HOME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
THERE IS SURVEILLANCE FOOTAGE
HOWEVER NOT SURE HOW MUCH OF
IT IT CAUGHT.
IT SOOEMZ HE WAS TARGETED.
HE RECEIVED A GIFT TO THE HOME
PRIOR TO THIS FROM MARY THE
JEAN COMPANY HE POSTED THE
ADDRESS ACCIDENTALLY ON THE
GIFT ON HIS SOCIAL MEDIA.
PEOPLE WERE SAYING THEY COULD
USE THE ADDRESS AND GET TO HIM
FROM THAT.
THIS HAS NOT ABOUT CONFIRMED
BEN THE REPORTS IT'S
SOMETHING WE IN THE HAVE
HAPPENED, PHOTOS OF THE YOU'LL
GIFT ON HAWZ AS WELL.
>> SAD NEWS FOR HE, HIS
NATIONAL ANTHEM I AND FRIENDS.
>>  TMZ AIRS AT:30 ON "FOX5"
AFTER "LIKE IT OR NOT".
IT'S A GOOD REMINDER, I KNOW
YOU'RE BAD AS LOCKING DOORS AT
AIR BNB WE'RE ALL KIND OF
COMING.
>>  A FALSE SENSE OF SECURE
TIVRMENT WE WANT TO OPEN THAT
DOOR.
LET'S DO.
IT YES.
LET'S SEE THE SIGN.
♪
I SAW THE SMOOIN SIGN♪
>> KLOINGTEST SHOT YOU CAN
POSSIBLY GET I CAN ALMOST READ
THE LICENSE PLATE.
>>  I CAN SEE INTO THE CAR
STOP TEXTING.
>> VERY IN DEPTH LOOK AT YOUR
COMMUTE.
>>  CAR, BY CAR.
>> WESTBOUND RAMP OF THE --
>> RIGHT?
>> THIS IS THE REALITY.
>>  THINGS ARE SLOWING DOWN
YOU CAN'T COMPLAIN ABOUT THE
WEATHER, RIGHT, CAITLIN.
>>  SURE THERE'S ALWAYS
SOMETHING AND IT'S NOT TO
GUESS THAT GUY BACK ON US AND
DESPITE THE CLOUDY START.
IT GETS COILED GUESS YOU CAN
COMPLAIN ABOUT THAT.
WHAT YOU CANNOT COMPLAIN ABOUT
IS DURATION EVER THE COLD.
IT'S A QUICK HIT ONCE AGAIN.
BLAST OF COLD COMING IN
TONIGHT AND IT'S GONE SATURDAY
AFTERNOON.  THE WEEKEND IS
LOOKING FAB AWE LUS.
53.
NICE COMFORTABLE AFTERNOON.
ANOTHER ONE IN FEBRUARY.
51 IN ANNAPOLIS AND 52 BILLION
MORE AND 48 GAITHERSBURG AND
45 WHIP CHESTER AND 3 CUL
CULPEPER.
BREEZE TODAY THAT FRONTAL
SYSTEM THAT HAD CLOUDS
IRRELEVANTLY THIS MORNING AND
WINDS GUSTS AND WE'LL BE LESS
BREEZY AS WE GO INTO THE
OVERNIGHT HOURS.
SLOWLY ERODING NORTHWEST TO
SOUTHEAST.
THAT'S WHY WE SAW NICE DRIVE
HOME.
TURNING COLDER, OVERNIGHT
TONIGHT WE STARTED THE DAY
THIS MORNING ABOUT THE LOW 40s
THAT'S A TEN DEGREE JOB AND
WE'LL SEE UPPER 20s OUTSIDE
THE BELTWAY.
THIS LOW PRESSURE JUST SOUTH,
HIGH PRESSURE IS BUILDING IN
SQUEEZE PLAY KEEPING THE
MOISTURE SOUTH OF WASHINGTON.
THERE WILL BE A POCKET OF SNOW
COLD ENOUGH FOR NORTH CAROLINA
VIRGINIA BORDER.
RAIN FURTHER DOWN TO SOUTH AND
EAST.
PRIMARILY LOOKING AT DRY DAY.
WITH HIGH PRESSURE WHIPPING
OUT.
WE WILL GET ALL THE CLOUD
COVER ASSOCIATEDED WITH THE
STORM SYSTEM AND PROBABLY
WON'T GET ANYTHING BEYOND A
FEW FLURRIES SOUTH.
NOTABLY KOHLER AND 40 IN
WASHINGTON AND SOME OF US
DON'T CLIMB OUT OF 30s.
HERE'S FUTURE CAST.
NOT A LOFT CLOUD COVER AROUND
TOMORROW.  RAIN AND SNOW
SHOWERS FUTURE CAST IS DIM D
DINISHING AFFECT OF NICK INS
IRON SHORE SEEING FLURRIES.
>>  AND FLURRIES TO NORTH
SUBURBS AND IN BETWEEN THAT
MUCH.
I'LL SAY FLURRIES ARE POSSIBLE
TOMORROW EVENING.
SNOW SHOWERS GETTING INTO
EXTREME SOUTHERN MARYLAND.
>>  5 SATURDAY AND 55 SUNDAY
AND ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL.
ANOTHER FEBRUARY WEEKEND.
LOOKS GREAT.
INTO NEXT WEEK ONCE AGAIN
CHANCE OF RAIN SHOWERS.
NO SNOW OR COLD ON THAT 7 DAY.
NEXT WEEK IS THE LAST WEEK OF
FEBRUARY, GUYS.
THAT'S YOUR 7 DAY.
MAKE OVER TO YOU.
>>  CAITLIN, ALL RIGHT ARE,
FEBRUARY IS IS ALMOST OVER.
>> STUL TO KORJS 9 TO 5 ONE OF
DOLLY PARTON'S MOST FEMALE US
SONGS AND IRISH ORK STRAY
PLAYED IT WITH A NICE TWIST
EYE
to bring this country together
to finally make progress
for the American people.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
S >> A PRINCE WILLIAMON THAT
CANNOT PLY AN A PUPPY THAT
CAN'T WALK ARE TURNING SOCIAL
MEDIA INTO A SENSATION.
THE DOG IS NAMED LONDY AND
PIGEON HER MAN AND THEY'RE
ROOMMATES AT THE MIA
FOUNDATION IN MILL HILTON, NEW
YORK, AND PEOPLE ARE MAKING
DONATIONS FOR SPECIAL NEEDS
AND BIRTH DEFECTS.
>>  I DIDN'T KNOW THESE NON
PROFITS EXISTED.
>>  WE SHOULD GIVE ALL OUR
MONEY TO THEM.
>>  SOUP AREA DOORABLE.
>>
.
>>  DID YOU SEE THE TYPEWRITER
AN ORCHESTRA PERFORMED DOLLY
PARTON 9  TO 5.
DID YOU KNOW SHE USED HER LONG
NAILS TO MAKE THE TYPEWRITER
SONG.
THE ORCHESTRA DECIDED TO US A
TYPEWRITER AND THAT'S WHAT
HE'S DOING NOW.
>>  THEY DEPOSIT HAVE DOLLY'S
NAILS.
>>  IT'S HARD TO DO SHE PLAYED
GUITAR WITH THEM TOO.
>>  THEY CAN BE SEEN TYPE AGO
WAY IN PERFECT TIME DURING
THAT PERFORMANCE.
>>  ANYTHING THAT MAKES NOISE
CAN BE AN INSTRUMENT.
THAT'S CREATIVE.
>>  INSTEAD OF RUNNING OF THE
BULLS IT WAS RUNNING OF THE
DASH HOUNDS IN WISCONSIN.
33 DOGS TRIED TO TAKE PLACE IN
A RACE.
IT HAPPENS ANNUALLY AND A
RECORD NUMBER OF DOGS.
>>  THEY'RE SO LOW TO THE
GROUND THOSE WEEPER DOGS.
>> BETTER ON THE ICE THAN MOST
PEOPLE.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US AT
.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 5:00.
THE SEARCH FOR A SUSPECT AFTER
THE SON OF A LOCAL POLICE
OFFICER IS KILLED OUTSIDE OF HIS
OWN HOME.
WHAT WE'RE LEARNING ABOUT THE
YOUNG VICTIM.
>>> PLUS, A REMARKABLE RECOVERY
FOR NASCAR DRIVER RYAN NEWMAN AS
HE WALKS OUT OF THE HOSPITAL
JUST 2 DAYS AFTER THIS HORRIFIC
CRASH AT DAYTONA 500.
>> WHY LOCAL SCHOOL DISTRICT
WANTS TO GET RID OF GPA
REQUIREMENTS FOR SOME STUDENT
ATHLETES.
YOUR NEWS STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> OFF THE TOP OF THE FIVE AND
DEVELOPING RIGHT NOW WHO KILLED
THE TEENAGE SON OF A LOCAL
POLICE DETECTIVE?  THAT'S WHAT