ABROAD, IT IS UNLIKELY THAT YOU
HAVE THE CORONAVIRUS.
WHAT YOU PROBABLY HAVE IS THE
FLU.
AND YOU'RE PROBABLY PASSING
ALONG THE FLU.
WE SPOKE WITH DR. DAVID WHEELER
HERE AT INOVA HOSPITAL, HE IS
THE INFECTION DISEASES DOCTOR
PHYSICIAN AND HE SAYS THAT THERE
ARE MANY LEGITIMATE CONCERNS
ABOUT THE CORONAVIRUS, BUT THERE
ARE MANY NOT SO LEGITIMATE
CONCERNS ABOUT THE CORONAVIRUS.
THIS MORNING, THE CDC CONFIRMING
THAT THERE ARE NOW 13 CASES IN
OUR AREA T13TH, SOMEONE WHO CAME
FROM CHINA.
ALSO, HE SAYS THAT WE DON'T HAVE
ANY RECOGNIZED CASES OF
CORONAVIRUS IN OUR AREA OR
ANYWHERE NEAR THE MID ATLANTIC.
SO OUR GOAL, OF COURSE, IS TO
SEPARATE FACT FROM FIX AND MAKE
SURE THAT FOLKS ARE NOT HAVING
UNNECESSARY CONCERNS AND PLACING
THEMES SELVES AND OTHERS IN
DANGER AS YOU ALL MENTIONED.
OBVIOUSLY CORONAVIRUS CONCERNS
ARE PROMPTING PEOPLE TO FLOOD
EMERGENCY ROOMS ACROSS THE AREA,
PEOPLE WHO ULTIMATELY DO NOT
HAVE CORONAVIRUS, WHAT IS
HAPPENING IS MORE PEOPLE ARE
REPORTEDLY CONTRACTING THE FLU
DUE TO CONTINUE FLUX OF PEOPLE
COMING TO THE ER CONCERNED ABOUT
HAVING THE VIRUS WHICH IS
ULTIMATELY UNLIKELY UNLESS
YOU'VE TRAVELED ABROAD.
BLAKE.
>> TO BE CAREER THERE ARE NO
CONFIRMED CORONAVIRUS CASES
ANYWHERE IN OUR AREA.
BUT TISHA, IF PEOPLE ARE
CONCERNED THEY DO HAVE THE
VIRUS, OTHER THAN JUST SHOWING
UP TO THEIR LOCAL EMERGENCY
ROOM, WHAT SHOULD THEY BE DOING?
>> Reporter: BEFORE YOU SHOW UP,
PICK UP THE PHONE AND CALL YOUR
PHYSICIAN.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A PRIMARY CARE
DOCTOR, PICK UP THE PHONE AND
CALL YOUR DOCTOR FIRST AND THEN
FOLLOW THOSE MEDICAL
INSTRUCTIONS.
BLAKE.
>> ALL RIGHT, TISHA LEWIS LIVE
FOR US.
THANK YOU, TISHA.
>>> HERE LOCALLY THE CORONAVIRUS
IS AFFECTING A GLOBAL CHRISTIAN
SCHOOL IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
THE COLLEGIATE ACADEMY HAS
SEVERAL CAMPUSES INCLUDING IN
FAIRFAX, SPRINGFIELD, HAMMONTON
ROADS, AND TWO IN CHINA.
WE SPOKE WITH THE SUPERINTENDENT
WHO SKYPED ONE OF HIS STUDENTS
STUCK IN CHINA UNTIL THE HEALTH
CRISIS IS OVER.
>> YOU CAN'T GO OUTSIDE,
CORRECT?
>> NOW WE CAN GO OUT AND EVERY
FAMILY, THEY HAVE LESS TIME --
TWICE A MEEK, MY PARENTS THEY
BOUGHT A LOT OF FOOD, SNACKS.
>> OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S IMPORTANT.
>> THE ACADEMY RECENTLY STARTED
THE WUHAN RELIEF PROJECT TO
RAISE MONEY TO PURCHASE
PROTECTIVE GEAR FOR HOSPITAL
WORKERS TRYING TO CONTAIN THE
VIRUS.
SO FAR THEY'VE RAISED NEARLY
$20,000.
>>> LET'S TURN OUR ATTENTION TO
THE WEATHER.
RAINY START TO THE DAY.
THIS IS VIDEO FROM EARLIER TODAY
IN ANNAPOLIS, MARYLAND.pLOOKS A
>> I KNOW.
>> CAITLIN ROTH.
>> IT DOES.
>> CAITLIN ROTH JOINS US NOW.
CAITLIN WHEN I WAS DRIVING IN,
THE RAIN SEEMS TO HAVE
DISSIPATED FOR A WHILE.
>> YES.
SO THAT SIGNALS A DRY BREAK.
SO WE GET A LITTLE BIT OF A
REPRIEVE UNTIL PROBABLY THIS
TIME TOMORROW.
>> OKAY.
>> SO WEDNESDAY, IF YOU HAVE
THINGS YOU WANT TO DO OUTSIDE
TOMORROW, YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN
LUCK BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO
ACTUALLY BE DRY.
YES, THE RAIN HAS PRETTY MUCH
ENDED AREA WIDE, STILL VERY WET
OUT THERE.
A STOKING START TO OUR TUESDAY,
THE MORNING COMMUTE WAS WET.
EVENING COMMUTE LOOKS LIKE IT
WILL BE DRIER.
SO SHOWERS NOW WELL OFF THE
TOWARDS OUR SOUTH AND EAST AS
ONE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE WHO
HAVE HAD OFF SHORE.
A COUPLE SHOWERS OVER WEST
VIRGINIA BUT I THINK THAT WILL
DISSIPATE AND LOOKING AT DRY
CONDITIONS THE REST OF THE
NIGHT.
INTERESTING A LITTLE WARMER
TODAY DESPITE THE FACT THAT WE
HAD THAT BOUNDARY PUSH OFF TO
THE EAST AND NORTHERLY WINDS ARE
PUSHING IN SOME DRY AIR.
THAT NORTHERLY WIND HAS ALLOWED
OUR TEMPERATURES TO JUMP UP.
57 DEGREES CLOUDY SKIES IN THE
DISTRICT.
STILL PRETTY OVERCAST NOT
EXPECTING THAT TO CHANGE, 52 IN
ANNAPOLIS, 55 IN LEONARDTOWN, 52
IN QUANTICO, 54 IN MANASSAS,
LITTLE COLDER ACROSS THE
MOUNTAINS WHERE THEY ARE STILL
IN THE 40S.
IF YOU HAVE PLANS TONIGHT,
YOU'RE IN LUCK.
IT'S NOT RAINING SO THAT'S A
ISSUE.
TEMPERATURES ARE ON THE MILDER
SIDE AS WE'LL BE IN THE 50S
THROUGH 7:00 P.M. BY 9:00
O'CLOCK RIGHT AROUND 50 DEGREES,
SLIPPING INTO THE 40S BY 11:00
O'CLOCK TONIGHT.
IT WILL GET COLDER OVERNIGHT SO
WE'LL START OFF IN THE 30S AND
LOW 40S FOR YOUR WEDNESDAY.
AND THAT'S WITH WEAK HIGH
PRESSURE OVERHEAD.
SO ACTUALLY, WEDNESDAY, TOMORROW
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
IT'S DRY FOR THE MORNING
COMMUTE, AND WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
ANY ISSUES UNTIL THIS SYSTEM
THAT'S GATHERING STRENGTH IN THE
SOUTH STARTS TO APPROACH.
THAT WARM FRONT WILL PUSH IN
DURING THE LATE AFTERNOON AND
EVENING HOURS.
SEVERE WEATHER AND HEAVY RAIN
ACROSS THE SOUTHEASTERN STATES
BY THE NOON HOUR SHOWERS INTO
THE TENNESSEE AND OHIO VALLEY AS
WELL AS PROBABLY SOUTHERN
VIRGINIA.
THAT MIX STAYS WELL OFF TOWARDS
OUR NORTH.
SO A DRY BREAK UNTIL LATE
TOMORROW.
I WOULD SAY PROBABLY THIS TIME,
BETWEEN 4:00 AND 6:00 P.M. WE'LL
START TO SEE SHOWERS IN PARTS OF
OUR AREA.
I'LL SHOW YOU FUTURECAST WALK
YOU THROUGH THE REST OF THE WEEK
COMING UP IN JUST A BUCK.
BLAKE AND ANGIE BACK OVER TO
YOU.
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>> THE LATEST IN THE HARVEY
WEINSTEIN TRIAL.
THEY DIDN'T CALL HIM TO THE
STAND.
WEINSTEIN'S ATTORNEY TOLD THE
JUDGE THAT THEY HAD NOT PROVEN
THEIR CASE SO WEINSTEIN WOULD
NOT TESTIFY.
CLOSING ARGUMENTS SET FOR
THURSDAY.
>>> BREAKING NEWS FROM HERE IN
DC, A FEDERAL PROSECUTOR
INVOLVED UNTIL THE SENTENCING
PHASE OF ROGER STONE'S CASE HAS
ABRUPTLY RESIGNED.
THAT COMES AFTER THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT SAID IT WOULD REQUEST
A MORE LENIENT SENTENCE FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S LONG TIME
FRIEND.
PROSECUTOR AARON ZELENSKY ASKED
THE JUDGE TO SENTENCE HIM TO
SEVEN TO NINE YEARS FOR
OBSTRUCTING CONGRESS AND WITNESS
TAMPERING BUT THE WHITE HOUSE
CALLED IT TOO ASH AND ASKED THE
DEPARTMENT TO REDUCE IT.
ZELENSKY RESIGNED HOURS AFTER
THE WHITE HOUSE MADE ITS
REQUEST.
>>> RIGHT NOW IN CAPITOL HILL,
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT AND REFORM
COMMITTEES MARKING UP A BILL TO
MAKE THE DISTRICT THE COUNTRY'S
51ST STATE.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME SINCE 1993
THAT THE HOUSE HAS CONSIDERED
THE MEASURE.
EARLIER TODAY DC DELEGATE
ELEANOR HOLMES-NORTON MADE THE
CASE FOR STATE HOOD.
>> POLLS SHOW THAT MOST
AMERICANS THINK THE RESIDENTS OF
THE NATION'S CAPITOL HAVE THE
SAME RIGHTS THEY ENJOY.
EVEN SOME MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
MAY NOT KNOW THAT THE DISTRICT
RANKS FIRST IN THE NATION IN
FEDERAL TAXES PAID TO SUPPORT
THE NATIONAL GOVERNMENT, MAKING
THE RESIDENTS OF THE NATION'S
CAPITOL THE ONLY FULL TAX PAYING
AMERICANS NOT TREATED AS EQUAL
CITIZENS.
>> REPUBLICANS DON'T SUPPORT THE
MOVE.
THEY SAY THE FOUNDING FATHERS
PROVIDED A MECHANISM TO CREATE A
NEW STATE.
>> IN ORDER FOR THE DISTRICT TO
BECOME THE 51ST STATE CONGRESS
NEEDS TO PASS AND THE STATES
NEED TO RATIFY AN AMENDMENT TO
THE CONSTITUTION.
HOWEVER, A GALLUP POLL --
>> EVEN IF THE HOUSE VOTES FOR
DC STATE HOOD THE MEASURE IS NOT
EXPECTED TO PASS THE REPUBLICAN
CONTROLLED SENATE.
>>> VOTING IN THE NEW HAMPSHIRE
PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY IS
UNDERWAY.
POLLS OPENED EARLY THIS MORNING
AMID POOR WEATHER CONDITIONS BUT
THE SNOW AND RAIN IN SOME PARTS
OF THE STATE HAS NOT STOPPED
LONG LINES OF VOTERS FROM
SHOWING UP TO THE POLLS.
BERNIE SANDERS HAS BEEN LEADING
IN NEW HAMPSHIRE AHEAD OF
TODAY'S VOTE.
WE KNOW THAT JOE BIDEN, WHO HAS
FALLEN OUT OF FRONT RUNNER
STATUS WILL LEAVE THE STATE
BEFORE THE RESULTS ARE ANNOUNCED
TONIGHT.
HE'S PLANNING A RALLY IN SOUTH
CAROLINA INSTEAD.
SO GET THIS.
A CHICKEN, CHICKEN, HAS NOW BEEN
REUNITED WITH ITS OWNER, THIS
AFTER STRUTTING ITS STUFF INTO
AN ELIZABETH WARREN CAMPAIGN
OFFICE IN NORTH CAROLINA.
STAFFERS SENDING A CALLOUT FOR
THE OWNER ON TWITTER, AND THEN
AN HOUR AND A HALF LATER, FAMILY
SHOWED UP TO GET BACK THEIR HEN.
IN THE SMALL TIME SHE WAS THERE,
THE HEN ACTUALLY LAID AN EGG.
>> SOME SORT OF METAPHOR THERE
BUT --
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, I'M NOT GOING TO GUESS
IT.
>>> AN ON BOARD CAMERA, THIS IS
THE VIDEO WE SHOWED YOU AT THE
TOP OF THE SHOW, SHOWS A
SHOCKING MOMENT A SCHOOL BUS
FULL OF KIDS HITS A CAR, FLIPS
OVER AND YOU SEE THE KIDS GO
FLYING, THIS HAPPENED BACK IN
DECEMBER IN OHIO.
POLICE JUST RELEASED THE VIDEO.
A CAR RAN A RED LIGHT AND HIT
THE BUS, AND THEN YOU CAN SEE
THE STUDENTS GO FLYING INTO THE
AIR.
LOOK AT THAT.
AND WHAT WE'RE SEEING IS THE BUS
ACTUALLY FLIP ON ITS SIDE AND
THAT'S WHY ALL THE KIDS.
WILL AT THIS KID HANGING ON TO
THE SEAT SO HE DOESN'T FLY AND
HIT THE WINDOW.
25 KIDS WERE ON BOARD AT THE
TIME OF THE CRASH.
THE DRIVER AND EIGHT KIDS WERE
TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL BUT
AMAZINGLY, ANGIE, EVERYOE IS
GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> THAT IS JUST SUCH A
FRIGHTENING SCENE.
IT ALMOST LOOKS LIKE GRAVE
PARTICULARS YOU KNOW, WHEN WE
SEE THESE SPACE CHUTES AND THE
ASTRONAUTS, THAT'S WHAT IT WAS
LIKE BECAUSE THEY WERE UP ON THE
CEILING.
>> AND THERE'S BEEN A PUSH TO
PUT MORE SEAT BELTS ON BUSES AND
THIS IS AN EXAMPLE OF WHY.
>> YEP.
>> BUT WE HAVE A LOT MORE
ACTUALLY CAUGHT ON CAMERA TOO WE
WANT TO SHOW YOU AT THAT TIME.
JUST THIS VIDEO ALONE IS ENOUGH
TO MAKE SOME OF YOU QUEASY, A
LITTLE SEASICK, FOOTAGE FROM A
BOAT TRYING TO MAKE ITS WAY
THROUGH THE ENGLISH CHANNEL AND
THROUGH ROUGH WATERS.
NOW A STORM WE TALKED ABOUT
YESTERDAY, STORM CIERA HIT THE
UK OVER THE WEEKEND, IT HAD
WINDS UP TO 90 MILES PER HOUR
CAUSING SOME SEVERE DAMAGE AND
FLOODING AND FOR MAKING SOME
PRETTY ROUGH TRIPS OUT IN THE
SEAS.
>> THE JIG IS UP FOR SERIAL
GROCERY STORE THIEF CAUGHT ON ON
CAMERA GOING THROUGH THE STORE
ON CHRISTMAS DAY, GOT A BIG BAG
WITH HIM.
POLICE SAY HE WAS LIVING ABOVE
THE STORE IN THE RAFTER AND
SNEAKING DOWN TO GET FOOD AND
CIGARETTES FOR WEEKS.
THE THIEF IS ACCUSED OF STEALING
AN EXPENSIVE WHEEL OF CHEESE
PRICED AT CLOSE TO $400.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHEN THEY
NOTICED, RIGHT?  WHERE DURING
THAT $400 WHEEL OF CHEESE GO,
LET'S LOOK AT THE TAPE.
STORE EMPLOYEES IN AUBURN
WASHINGTON HAD THEIR SUSPICIONS.
THEY APPARENTLY HEARD SOMETHING
IN THE RAFTERS WHEN THEY HEARD
SOMETHING RECENTLY BUT IT WASN'T
UNTIL THEY SAW THE TAPE THAT IT
WAS DONE FIRMED.
>>> MY GOODNESS.
SEVERAL GAMES OF GOLF WENT DOWN
IN FLAMES BECAUSE OF A FIRE ON
THE 7TH HOLE OF THIS GOLF
COURSE.
THIS HAPPENED IN A PATCHY JUNK
SHUNNING NEAR PHOENIX.
THE PLAYERS USING THIS GOLF CART
WERE ABLE TO GET AWAY FROM THE
FLAMES.
NOBODY WAS HURT IN ALL OF THIS.
NO WORD ON WHAT ACTUALLY SPARKED
THE FLAMES BUT THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T SEE EVERY DAY.
>>> THE HOUSE VOTED
OVERWHELMINGLY TODAY TO BUILD A
WOMEN'S HISTORY MUSEUM ON THE
MALL.
THE BIPARTISAN MEASURE WOULD
ESTABLISH A MUSEUM WITHIN THE
SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION.
NO WORD ON WHERE EXACTLY ALONG
THE MALL IT WOULD BE BUILT.
EFFORTS TO ESTABLISH SUCH A
WOMEN'S HISTORY MUSEUM GO ALL
THE WAY BACK TO 1998.
SINCE IT PASSED THE HOUSE TODAY
IT NOW GOES TO THE SENATE FOR A
VOTE.
♪
>>> STILL TO COME, WHERE'S THE
LOVE?  THE LOCAL SCHOOL IS
GETTING RID OF VALENTINE'S DAY
AND REBRANDING IT FRIENDSHIP
DAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S COMING UP.
AND TRENDING, PLUS SKELETAL
REMAINS FOUND UNDER A HOME AND
ARC I DON'T BELIEVE VISITS HOPE
IT COULD BE PART OF AN HISTORIC
DISCOVERY.
>> AND A LOOK AT HOW TRAFFIC IS
MOVING ALONG ON WHAT IS THIS,
TUESDAY, JUST TUESDAY.
OH, MY GOD A STANDSTILL.
>> LOOK AT 395.
>> STAY IN YOUR HOUSE RIGHT NOW,
STICK AROUND, FIVE AT 4:00 WILL
BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
♪
BACK AFTER THIS.
♪♪
MIKE: Anyone hear the slogan,
'Mike Will Get It Done?'
OK, let me tell
you what the 'it' is.
As Mayor,
I expanded healthcare coverage.
As President,
I'll build on Obamacare
because healthcare is a right.
I created nearly
500,000 jobs in New York City.
As President,
I'll build an economy
that delivers good jobs
with higher wages.
I'll take on the gun lobby
and save lives.
And I will stop Trump's assault
on women's reproductive rights.
I've got a record
of doing things.
I've got the resources
to take on this fight.
As mayor,
I held myself
accountable for results.
As President,
I'll offer common sense plans
and I will get it done.
So let's stay on the offensive,
and let's win.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
♪
>> NOW TO A STARTLING DISCOVERY
IN GEORGETOWN.
>> YES, HUMAN SKELETAL REMAINS
WERE FOUND IN THIS BASEMENT OF A
HOUSE ON Q STREET.
THIS HAPPENED JUST A FEW DAYS
AGO.
>> YEAH, AND THAT IS WHERE WE
FIND OUR GARY MCGRADY WITH MORE
ON WHO THE BONES MIGHT BELONG
TO.
GARY, I UNDERSTAND YOU KNOCKED
ON THE DOOR TODAY AND THEY SAID,
COME ON IN, WE'LL SHOW YOU WHERE
WE FOUND THEM.
>> REPORTER: YEAH, WELL, THEY
DID.
LET'S SET THAT STAGE FOR YOU.
THIS HOUSE RIGHT HERE, 3300
BLOCK OF Q DOWN IN GEORGETOWN,
COMPLETELY UNDER RENOVATION FROM
THE BASEMENT ALL THE WAY UP TO
THE SECOND FLOOR, THIRD FLOOR IF
YOU COUNT THE BASEMENT.
SO THE WORKERS ARE IN THERE.
SO JOSE SAID COME ON IN AND
WE'LL LET YOU GO DOWN INTO THE
BASEMENT.
SO WE HAVE THESE PICTURES HERE
OF DOWN UNDER THERE, AND THE DC
ARCHEOLOGISTS CAME OUT.
THIS WAS A WEEK AGO THEY FOUND
SOME HUMAN SKELETONS, HUMAN
BONES DOWN THERE, THEY KNOW
THEY'RE HUMAN BONES.
AND THE BIG QUESTION IS, DO
THESE BONES POTENTIALLY BELONG
TO YARO, IN, AMMUT.
HE WAS A FORMER SLAVE AND WAS A
LITTLE BIT OF A CELEBRITY.
HE GAINED HIS FREEDOM.
LITTLE BIT OF A CELEBRITY IN
GEORGETOWN BACK IN THE 1800S AND
HE DID HAVE PROPERTY IN THE
AREA.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT IN JUST A
SECOND.
BUT THE POTENTIAL THAT THESE
BONES COULD BE HIS VERY
FASCINATING.
WE WENT TO THE PUBLIC LIBRARY TO
THE PEABODY ROOM THAT'S WHERE WE
FOUND JERRY McCOY, BIT OF AN
PER, HE HAD THOUGHTS ON WHY
THESE MAY BE YARO'S BONES.
>> FOR ME IT WOULD BE VERY
EMOTIONAL BECAUSE HE HAS BECOME
SORT OF A SPIRIT HISTORIC FIGURE
TO ME OVER THE 20 YEARS THAT
I'VE BEEN HERE AND AN
ARCHEOLOGICAL DIG WAS DONE BACK
IN 2001 BY THE DC ARC I DON'T
BELIEVEY BUILDING.
A BUILDING THAT JAYRO OPENED AT
ONE TIME WAS TORN DOWN TO BE
REDEVELOPED.
IT WAS KNOWN HE WAS BURIED
ACCORDING TO HISTORICAL RECORDS
ON THE PROPERTY WITH HIS BODY
FACING MECCA.
>> Reporter: RIGHT BEHIND THIS
PROPERTY, JAYRO ACTUALLY OWNED
PROPERTY IN GEORGETOWN.
NOW, THEY THINK THAT THIS
POTENTIALLY COULD BE MAYBE
JAYRO'S BONES, BECAUSE THE
THOUGHT IS, HE WAS BURIED ON HIS
OWN PROPERTY RIGHT BEHIND THIS
HOUSE IN THE -- IN 18 23 IS WHEN
JAYRO DIED.
SO -- BUT, YOU KNOW, BELIEVE IT
OR NOT, IT'S NOT UNCOMMON FOR
THESE HOMEOWNERS HERE IN
GEORGETOWN, ESPECIALLY RIGHT
HERE ON Q STREET, TO FIND
REMAINS RIGHT ACROSS THE STREET
FROM US IS THE PARK THAT WAS THE
OLD PRESBYTERIAN BURIAL GROUND
BACK IN THE 1800S.
AND THEN WE ALSO HAVE OTHER
PLACES.
BECAUSE BACK THEN, I MEAN, THE
LAND OWNERS, THEY WOULD JUST BE
BURIED ON THEIR OWN PROPERTY.
SO, AGAIN, NOT UNCOMMON.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A WHILE FOR
THESE BONES TO GO -- THEY'RE
WITH THE DC ARCHEOLOGISTS NOW.
THEY'LL BE TESTED.
IT WILL TAKE A WHILE.
THEY'LL GO THROUGH A DNA STUDY
TO DETERMINE WHETHER OR NOT
THESE COULD BE THE BONES OF
JAYRO, THE FORMER SLAVE THAT WAS
AGAIN SO PROMINENT IN THE
HISTORY OF GEORGETOWN SO SO MANY
YEARS AGO.
QUITE AN INTERESTING STORY.
COMING UP AT 5:00 AND 6:00
ANGIE, WE'LL TAKE YOU INSIDE, I
WAS INSIDE, WE KIND OF WENT
THROUGH THE BASEMENT TO SHOW YOU
EXACTLY WHERE THESE BONES WERE
FOUND.
ANGIE.
>> IT IS ABSOLUTELY FASCINATING
AND WE WILL BE WATCHING FOR THAT
AND IF IT DOES TURN OUT THAT
THIS DNA DOES DETERMINE THAT IT
WAS, INDEED, HIM, I MEAN WHAT A
REMARKABLE DISCOVERY.
THANKS, GARY.
>>> A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE NOW ON
THIS RAINY TUESDAY.
NATIONAL HARBOR BEHIND YOU,
CAITLIN.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT WHAT I'M SEEING BEHIND
YOU IS A BREAK IN THE CLOUDS.
>> I KNOW.
LOOK A LITTLE BIT OF BLUE OUT
THERE.
YOU COULD SEE WITH GARY YOU SAW
A LITTLE BIT OF SUN COMING ON
HIS FAME SO A CELEBRATION.
>> SO WE HAVE, WHAT, A 12-HOUR
WINDOW?
>> WE HAVE --
>> A GOOD WHILE?
>> NO, PROBABLY A 24-HOUR DRY
WINDOW.
SUN WILL BE LINTED OBVIOUSLY
IT'S GOING DOWN IN ABOUT AN HOUR
AND A HALF.
BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO BE RAINING
TOMORROW MORNING SO THAT'S
GREAT.
SO WE DO HAVE A DRY BREAK AND
YOU CAN SEE SEE A TINY BIT OF
SUNSHINE PEEKING THROUGH THE
CLOUD COVER ACROSS NATIONAL
HARBOR SO A NICE REPRIEVE FROM
THE WET WEATHER THE PAST COUPLE
DAYS.
IT IS A BREAK BUT A BRIEF BREAK.
SHOWERS RETURN THIS TIME
TOMORROW EVENING THROUGH THE
NIGHT THURSDAY MORNING, AND THEN
FINALLY PUSHING OUT LATE
THURSDAY AFTERNOON.
AND BEHIND THAT, A REAL COLD
SNAP.
SOMETHING WE HAVEN'T DONE MUCH
OF THIS WINTER, ARCTIC AIR
FRIDAY AND SATURDAY.
SO WE'LL GET THE SUNSHINE BACK,
BUT IT WILL BE COLD.
57 DEGREES OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW IN
REAGAN, NOT TOO COLD, 53 AT
DULLES AND BWI EVEN REPORTING A
LITTLE BIT OF SUNSHINE THERE, 54
DEGREES, SO AS WE CLEAR OUT
NORTHERLY WINDS HAVE DRIED US
OUT BUT WE'VE SEEN A LITTLE BIT
OF A BOOST IN OUR TEMPERATURES.
STORM TRACKER RADAR IS QUIET AT
THE MOMENT AND FUTURECAST
SHOWING JUST SOME PARTIAL
CLEARING THROUGH TONIGHT.
SO THAT WILL HELP US DRY OUT A
LITTLE BIT.
NOT A SOGGY COMMUTE TOMORROW
MORNING WITH EVEN THE HINT OF
SUNSHINE TO START OFF ON
WEDNESDAY, SO THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
MOST OF THE DAY IS DRY, YOU CAN
STEP OUT ON YOUR LUNCH BREAK AND
EVEN BY THE TIME THE KIDS GET
HOME AT 4:00 O'CLOCK, OKAY IN
THE METRO THOUGH SHOWERS HAVE
ALREADY STARTED TO FILL IN
ACROSS 81.
PROBABLY BETWEEN FIVE AND SIX WE
SEE OUR FIRST SHOWERS LOCALLY.
THINGS LOOK SCATTERED TOMORROW
NIGHT, I WOULDN'T SAY A
CONSISTENT HEAVY RAIN BUT
SHOWERS AROUND IN THE EVENING
AND THEN MORE SHOWERS FOR THE
THURSDAY MORNING COMMUTE BEFORE
WE'RE DONE.
40 DEGREES TONIGHT, DRY
CONDITIONS WITH HIGH PRESSURE
GIVING US JUST ENOUGH CLEARING
WE OULD HIT THE FREEZING MARK
FAR NORTH AND WEST SO A LITTLE
CHILLIER TO START AND HIGH
TEMPERATURES TOMORROW WILL BE
CHILLIER.
AGAIN A MOSTLY CLOUDY ONE, 49
FOR THE HIGH TEMPERATURE IN DC.
TEMPERATURE TREND CONTINUES TO
BE ALL OVER THE PLACE.
WE FALL TOMORROW IN THE 40S.
WE SPIKE ON THURSDAY INTO THE
60S.
THAT'S A BIG PUSH OUT AHEAD OF A
COLD FRONT WHICH WILL DELIVER
THAT ARCTIC AIR.
42 ON FRIDAY, JUST 36 FOR A HIGH
TEMPERATURE ON SATURDAY.
THAT IS COLD, BUT IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE IT WILL LAST TOO LONG.
THE WEEKEND SHOWS UP IN YOUR
SEVEN DAY.
I'LL HAVE THAT STILL AHEAD.
ANGIE?
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>>> DULLES ONE OF SEVERAL
AIRPORTS NATIONWIDE HOPING TO
HELP PASSENGERS KILL TIME BY
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
A NEW VIDEO GAME LOUNGE IS
STARTING UP NEXT WEEK AND
FEATURES NINTENDO GAMES THAT CAN
EITHER BE PLAYED WITH HAND HELD
DEVICES OR ON TV SCREENS.
SOME GAMES FEATURED WILL BE
MARIO CART, AT THE TIME TRUSS, I
TETRUS AND THE LEGEND OF ZELDA.
THE CARTRIDGE WAS PRETTY.
YOU CAN FIND IT ON CONCOURSE B
THROUGH THE END OF MARCH.
I NOW HAVE A NEW PLACE TO GO FOR
PLAY DATES WITH THE KIDS.
>> OUR PRODUCER HAD NO IDEA THIS
WOULD TURN INTO ANGIE'S NINTENDO
REVIEW.
>> NOTHING BEATS CALIFORNIA
DREAMS, REMEMBER THAT GAME?  THE
GIRL THAT WOULD ROLLER SKATE AND
SLIP ON THE BANANA PEEL.
>> I MISSED THAT.
>> OUT LIKE A LIGHT.
>>> STILL TO COME.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
STILL TO COME, DESPERATE TIMES
CALL FOR DESPERATE MEASURES.
AN AUSTRALIAN COUPLE CARNE TABID
ON A CRUISE SHIP DUE TO THE
CORONAVIRUS DECIDED TO MAKE THE
BEST OF THEIR SITUATION.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE HOW
THEY GOT DELIVERY ON A
QUARANTINED CRUISE SHIP COMING
UP NEXT.
>>> WE DO WANT TO TAKE A LIVE
LOOK THOUGH, WE'RE FOLLOWING
TRAFFIC AS WELL, WE KNOW 395 IN
VIRGINIA HORRIBLE BUT TAKING A
LIVE LOOK AT THE WOODROW WILSON
BRIDGE HERE PRETTY FREE FLOWING,
NOT TOO CONGESTED YET.
WE'LL BE BACK AFTER THIS.
STAY WITH US.
♪
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
.
>>> TIME FOR A LOOK AT WHAT'S
TRENDING WITH MARINA MARRACO.
>> SO WE'RE A COUPLE DAYS AWAY
FROM VALENTINE'S DAY AND IT'S
NOT FOR ADULTS.
APPARENTLY THE SCHOOL HAVING A
DISCUSSION ABOUT THE BIG DAY
BECAUSE ONE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
VIRGINIA IS REPLACING CANDY
HEARTS AND VALENTINE'S DAY CARDS
WITH FRIENDSHIP DAY.
STUDENTS ARE STILL ENCOURAGED TO
WEAR RED AND PINK AND EXCHANGE
FRIENDSHIP CARDS AND TREATS IF
THEY WANT TO BUT THE TERM
VALENTINE'S DAY WILL NOT BE
USED.
IN THE PAST OTHER ELEMENTARY
SCHOOLS HAVE DONE SOMETHING
SIMILAR.
THEY SAY FRIENDSHIP PARTY FALLS
MORE IN LINE WITH WHAT THEY'RE
TRYING TO PROMOTE AT THE SCHOOLS
AND NOT TRYING TO FOSTER
ROMANTIC LOVE.
>> I LOVE IT.
I KNOW YOU THINK I'M TOO PC
WHICH NO ONE EVER SAYS EXCEPT
MARINA, BUT I THINK THIS IS
GREAT.
WHY SHOULD THEY BE TRYING TO
FOSTER LOVE.
>> WHY?
>> PEOPLE GET PICKED ON, IT
BECOMES A BIG THING IN SCHOOL
THAT IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE.
LET'S PROMOTE FRIENDSHIP AND
LIKING ONE ANOTHER.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY WE
HAVE TO SEXUAL EYES VALENTINE'S
DAY.
WHY CAN'T IT BE ABOUT LOVING
YOUR FRIENDS, LOVING YOUR
PARENTS.
>> WILL YOU BE MY VALENTINE
MARINA.
>> ABSOLUTELY, ANYDAY.
>> YOU CAN BE MY FRIEND, YOU'LL
BE MY VALENTINE.
FRIENDSHIP DAY SHOULD BE EVERY
DAY LIKE EARTH DAY AND THAT'S
WHAT THEY PROMOTE COMMUNITY AND
FRIENDSHIP.
YOU DON'T NEED A PARTY SET ASIDE
FOR THAT, THAT'S WHAT FRIENDSHIP
BRACELETS ARE FOR.
>> I JUST THINK BY TELLING THEM
THAT VALENTINE'S DAY'S NEGATIVE,
THEN YOU HAVE A NEGATIVE
CONNOTATION.
>> THEY'RE NOT SAYING IT'S
NEGATIVE, YOU JUST DON'T NEED A
LOVE CULTURE IN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
>> YOU SHOULD BE PROMOTING LOVE.
>> NO.
OH MY GOSH.
>> HAVEN'T YOU EVER HEARD THE
SAYING ALL THE WORLD NEEDS LOVE
IS.
>> HOW DID WE TURN INTO FLOWER
CHILDREN.
>>> TOPIC NUMBER TWO.
>> YOU WON'T BE GETTING IN I
WINE BECAUSE ONE COUPLE THEIR
QUARANTINE OFF THE COAST OF
JAPAN BECAUSE OF THE CORONAVIRUS
HAD WINE DELIVERED TO THEIR
CABIN VIA DRONE.
THESE GUYS ARE THE MOST ENGENIUS
PEOPLE IN THE WORLD.
THE NAKED WINE CLUB LEARNED THEY
WERE GOING TO BE STUCK ON THE
SHIP SO MUCH TO THEIR DELIGHT
THE NAKED WINE CLUB SENT THEM
TWO BOTTLES OF PINOT FOYER, THE
JAPANESE COST GUARD WAS LIKE
WHAT IS HAPPENING OVER OUR BOAT.
AND THESE GUYS WERE HAVING A
PARTY, DRINKING SOME WINE.
NONE FOR YOU BLAKE.
>> YES, YES, EXACTLY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AERIAL, MY FAVORITE.
>> THAT'S THE BEST I CAN DO.
>> LEAVE IT TO THE AUSSIES TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET ALCOHOL
WHILE QUARANTINED ON A CRUISE
SHIP.
>> I'LL GET YOU ONE FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> THANK YOU.
BUT HOW MUCH DID THIS COST THEM
DO YOU KNOW.
>> I THIS HE THIS PUT OUT AN SOS
ON SOCIAL MEDIA LIKE LISTEN
WE'RE IN THIS CABIN DOING
NOTHING AND THEY WERE LIKE WE
GOT YOU.
KIND OF A FREE BEE.
>>> STILL TO COME A SCHOOL
THREAT CRACKDOWN, WHAT PROMPTED
A MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE TO
SEND OUT A WARNING TO BOTH
PARENTS AND STUDENTS.
ALMOST 700 KIDS CALLED OUT OF
SCHOOL TODAY BECAUSE OF THIS,
AND NOW THE SCHOOL DISTRICT IS
COMING OUT WITH A STATEMENT OF
THEIR OWN.
>> OKAY.
♪
♪♪
>>> A LOOK AT SOME OF THE OTHER
TOP STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING ON
THIS TUESDAY.
FIRST UP NO WORD YET ON THE
CAUSE OF A DEADLY HOUSE FIRE IN
SOUTHEAST THAT HAPPENED AROUND
5:00 A.M. IN THE 600 BLOCK OF
DARRINGTON STREET.
DC FIRE SAYS INCLUDEERED
CONDITIONS INSIDE THE HOMEMADE
IT DIFFICULT TO RESCUE A WOMAN
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
TWO OTHERS HEARD A SMOKE ALARM
AND MADE IT OUT SAFELY.
>>> A MARYLAND MAN ARRESTED FOR
REPORTEDLY THREATENING TO BURN
DOWN A FAMILY MEMBER'S HOME.
THIS HAPPENED IN CUMBERLAND
YESTERDAY.
THIS MAN, MICHAEL SHIPLEY JR.
DOUSEED A HOME ON SPRINGDALE
STREET WITH GASOLINE AND IS
ACCUSED OF MAKING THREATS
THROUGH SOCIAL MEDIA TO BURN THE
HOME WITH HIS ESTRANGED FAMILY
INSIDE OF IT.
SHIPLEY IS CHARGED WITH ARSON,
THREAT -- WITH AN ARSON THREAT
AND RECKLESS ENDANGERMENT.
>>> HOW MUCH PROGRESS HAS BEEN
MADE ON A ROAD DIET ON SEMINARY
ROAD IN ALEXANDRIA.
INITIAL DATA FROM A REPORT SHOWS
COMMUTERS ARE ONLY IN TRAFFIC 30
SECONDS TO A MINUTE LONGER THAN
THEY WERE BEFORE.
LANES WERE REDUCED LATE LAST
YEAR TO IMPROVE SAFETY FOR
PEDESTRIANS AND CYCLISTS.
COUNSEL LEADERS PLAN TO HEAR
THAT REPORT AND GET FEEDBACK
TONIGHT.
>>> TWO CONTROVERSIAL BILLS ARE
UNDER CONSIDERATION THIS
AFTERNOON IN THE MARYLAND
GENERAL ASSEMBLY TO RESTRICT LAW
ENFORCEMENT'S ABILITY TO CONDUCT
IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT.
POLICE FROM AT LEAST THREE
COUNTIES OPPOSE THE SAYING THEY
ARE SANCTUARY STATUS.
THEY SAY THEY WANT TO CUT TIES
WITH IMMIGRATION AND CUSTOMS
ENFORCEMENT BECAUSE THEY DON'T
AGREE WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
IMMIGRATION POLICIES.
THIS LEADS US TO OUR FOX5
INSTAPOLL TODAY.
SHOULD ALL OF MARYLAND BECOME A
SANCTUARY STATE FOR UNDOCUMENTED
IMMIGRANTS?  YOU CAN VOTE RIGHT
NOW ON FOX5 DC'S APP OR ON
FOX5DC.COM.
SHOULD ALL OF MARYLAND BECOME A
SANCTUARY STATE.
RIGHT NOW THE OVERWHELMING
MAJORITY OF YOU SAY NO.
>>> SHOCKING NEW DETAILS ABOUT
WHAT PROMPTED MONTGOMERY COUNTY
POLICE TO SEND OUT A WARNING
SINCE THE START OF THE YEAR,
COUNTY POLICE AND PUBLIC SCHOOL
LEADERS SAY THERE'S BEEN AN
UPTICK IN SOCIAL MEDIA THREATS
AND THREATS MADE IN PERSON BY
STUDENTS.
BUT IN THE MOST RECENT CASE IN
MONTGOMERY BLAIR HIGH SCHOOL THE
CONCERN OVER A THREAT CAUSED
MORE THAN 700 STUDENTS TO STAY
HOME YESTERDAY.
FOX5'S STEPHANIE RAMIREZ IS LIVE
IN SILVER SPRING WITH MORE ON
THIS STORY.
HI, STEPHANIE.
> HEY, GOOD EVENING.
SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT CLOSE TO
700 STUDENTS HERE.
POLICE TELL US, THOUGH, AND WANT
TO MAKE CLEAR, THE THREAT WAS
FOUND TO BE NOT CREDIBL.
A PARENT HAD SAW THIS AND
REPORTED TO THE SCHOOL ON
SUNDAY.
THE POST HAD TO DO WITH A
STUDENT VOICING RUSH STRAYINGS
OVER BULLYING.
AND NOW, THOUGH, EVEN THOUGH IT
WAS FOUND NOT CREDIBLE ON
MONDAY, THE FEARS STILL PROMPTED
SOME 700 STUDENTS TO STAY HOME
FROM CLASS OUT OF CONCERN.
AND IF WE'RE TALKING ABOUT 3,000
STUDENTS HERE, THAT'S CLOSE TO A
QUARTER OF THE ENTIRE SCHOOL
BODY.
SO THIS IS A MAJOR POINT OF
CONCERN, A BIG DEAL FOR
MONTGOMERY COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
AND POLICE AND IT'S A MAJOR
DISRUPTION, TOO.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
SAY THIS IS ALSO NOT THE FIRST
TIME.
MCPS TOLD ME THAT THEY HAD A
THREAT INVESTIGATION OVER AT
QUINCE ORCHARD HIGH SCHOOL
PROMPTING SIMILAR RESPONSES
THERE.
POLICE TELL ME THEY'VE ALSO
INVESTIGATED MORE THAN 20
THREATS AT MIDDLE SCHOOLS AND
HIGH SCHOOLS, ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTY, SINCE THE START OF THE
SCHOOL YEAR.
THE MONTGOMERY BLAIR CASE HERE,
A APPARENT SHARED ONE OF THE TWO
POSTS WITH US AND I'M TOLD THE
STUDENT HAD POSTED TO AN APP
CALLED TELL ON THEM WHERE YOU
CAN POST ANONYMOUSLY.
SOMEONE THEN SHARED THE POST TO
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A PRIVATE
INSTAGRAM GROUP CALLED BLARE
CONFESSIONS.
POLICE WERE STILL ABLE TO TRACK
DOWN THE STUDENT RESPONSIBLE,
AND I'M TOLD THAT STUDENT DID
ADMIT TO MAKING THAT POST.
ANGIE?
>> AND ALONG THOSE LINES,
STEPHANIE, BECAUSE WE DO KNOW
MOST OF THESE THREATS ARE
HAPPENING JUST LIKE WHAT YOU
SHOWED US THERE, THEY'RE
HAPPENING ON SOCIAL MEDIA AND ON
ALL THESE PLATFORMS FOR
EVERYBODY TO SEE.
WHAT DID POLICE HAVE TO SAY
ABOUT THAT IN THEIR TWOORNG THE
SCHOOL COMMUNITY?
>> Reporter: YEAH, ANGIE, EVEN
TICK TOCK IS ONE OF THE APPS
THAT THEY SAID THAT THESE
STUDENTS ARE USING.
SO REALLY THE POLICE AND THE
SCHOOL COMMUNITY ARE TELLING
PARENTS TO PLEASE OF A
CONVERSATION WITH THE STUDENTS
ABOUT PROPER SOCIAL MEDIA
ETIQUETTE AND ARE WARNING
STUDENTS YOU CAN FACE CRIMINAL
CHARGES FOR THESE THREATS MADE
WHETHER IT'S JOKING OR DONE ON
PURPOSE IT WILL BE INVESTIGATED
THE SAME.
>> SO HAVE THEY MADE ANY ARRESTS
SINCE ALL OF THIS.
BECAUSE YOU MENTIONED IN ONE
CASE THEY WERE ABLE TO PINPOINT
WHO MADE THAT PARTICULAR POST.
>> REPORTER: YEAH, AND THAT IS
VERY IMPORTANT TO POLICE AS
WELL.
THEY TELL US THEY HAVE MADE
ARRESTS, BUT IN TERMS OF THE
OVERALL NUMBER, THEY SAY THAT'S
REALLY NOT A CLEAR PICTURE
BECAUSE IN SOME OF THESE CASES
YOU HAVE JUVENILES AND IF
THEY'RE CHARGED WE'RE MOST
LIKELY NOT GOING TO HEAR ABOUT
IT BECAUSE THEY ARE JUVENILES.
ANOTHER THING THEY MENTIONED IS
SOMETIMES THE SCHOOL SYSTEM WILL
INVESTIGATE TO DETERMINE IF
OTHER NEEDS OR OTHER ISSUES ARE
INVOLVED HERE LIKE MAYBE SOME
MORE MENTAL HEALTH NEEDS THAT
THE STUDENT NEEDS HELP WITH.
I CAN TELL YOU, WITH THE CASE
HERE, THE STUDENT ADMITTED TO
CREATING THAT POST, BUT WE'VE
BEEN TOLD NO CHARGES YET AS THE
SCHOOL SYSTEM CONTINUES TO
INVESTIGATE.
GUYS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
STEPHANIE RAMIREZ FOR US.
THANKS SO MUCH.
>>> STILL TO COME, YOU PROBABLY
SAW THIS ALL OVER SOCIAL MEDIA.
IT'S CALLED THE BROOM CHALLENGE.
>> YEAH.
>> ANGIE'S BEEN REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT ONLY THAT,
BEEN'S TEXTING ME ABOUT IT.
ARE WE TRYING IT?
>> WELL OUR MORNING CREW
ACTUALLY PUT THIS BROOM
CHALLENGE TO THE TEST.
>> OKAY
>> THE RESULTS COMING UP.
>>> AND WE DO WANT TO KEEP AN
EYE ON TRAFFIC.
TAKE A LOOK RIGHT HERE.
SMOOTH SAILING AND NOTHING TO
REPORT AT THIS TIME AS FAR AS
INCIDENTS AND ACCIDENTS.
WE'RE BACK AFTER THIS.
STAY WITH US.
♪
OBAMA: He's been a leader
throughout the country for the
past twelve years,
Mr. Michael Bloomberg is here.
VO: Leadership in action.
Mayor Bloomberg and
President Obama worked together
in the fight for gun safety
laws,
to improve education, and to
develop innovative ways to help
teens gain the skills needed to
find good jobs.
OBAMA: At a time
when Washington is divided in
old ideological battles he shows
us what can be achieved when
we bring people together
to seek pragmatic solutions.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
♪♪
[clapping]
You're up next. Good luck.
From the moment a child comes
to Children's
National Hospital,
and well after
they've returned home,
we will always
be by their side.
Children's
National Hospital.
Grow Up Stronger.
♪
>> SO HAVE YOU SEEN THE LATEST
SOCIAL MEDIA CHALLENGE?  IT'S
CALLED THE BROOMSTICK CHALLENGE.
IT WAS ALL OVER EVERY PLATFORM
YESTERDAY BECAUSE ACCORDING TO
THIS URBAN LEGEND ON
FEBRUARY 10TH PLANETS ALIGN IN A
WAY THAT AFFECT A GRAVE TOUCHILY
PULL WHICH ALLOWS THE BROOM TO
STAND UP ON ITS OWN.
MANY SCIENTISTS SAY IT'S ALL
ABOUT BALANCE AND YOU CAN MAKE A
BROOM STAND ON ITS OWN ANY DAY
OF THE YEAR.
EARLIER THIS MORNING, FOX5
MORNING, THE TEAM THERE, PUT IT
TO THE TEST WITH TUCKER.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> HERE WE GO.
SO WE'VE GOT MY BROOM AND I'M
JUST GOING TO JUST PLACE IT
RIGHT HERE AND JUST DO A LITTLE
TOUCH TO IT AND --
>> WHAT?
>> WOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IS IT ROTATIONAL PULL?
>> YES.
>> ON YOUR FIRST TRY, TOO.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT ELSE I CAN DO,
HUH?
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> COME ON GUYS.
>> YOU'RE A WAR LOCK.
>> AMAZING.
>> SHOW US SOMETHING ELSE.
>> OKAY.
>> DO ANOTHER TRICK.
THIS IS THE MOST AMAZING BROOM
EVER.
COME ON NOW.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME RIGHT NOW?
>> THIS IS THE CRAZIEST GRAVE
TOUCHILY PULL EVER.
>>.
>> I'VE GOT SKILLS MAN, WHAT CAN
I TELL YOU.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE.
>> IT'S STUCK IN THERE.
>> IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT
THE SCIENCE.
>> WAS THAT MIKE THOMAS IN
THERE?
>> YES.
>> THAT IS SO HILARIOUS.
ONE OF THOSE MOVES WAS ALMOST
LIKE THAT, IN THE MICHAEL
JACKSON WHEN HE DOES THE MOON
WALK AND PEOPLE HAVE ATTEMPTED
THAT AND FALL FLAT ON THEIR FACE
BUT THAT WAS ACTUALLY PRETTY
BRILLIANT.
TUCKER NEEDS TO BE SHOWING
EVERYBODY THE TRICK YOU KNOW.
>> COMING UP WE SHOW RIHANNA
DROPPING HINTS ABOUT HER ALBUM,
BUT CAITLIN THAT'S YOUR FIANCEE
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE RELATED TO THIS GUY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WHY IS HE GETTING THE
HARD SCIENCE LIKE THAT AND WE'RE
STUCK WITH A RAIN FORECAST FOR
4:00 O'CLOCK?  WHERE IS YOUR
BROOM?  LET'S GET TO THE GOOD
SCIENCE.
>> WELL, I NEED A HELPER LIKE
MIKE THOMAS WHO I FEEL LIKE I
MIGHT ALSO BE MARRYING BUT THEY
DON'T SEEM TO DO ANYTHING
WITHOUT EACH OTHER, THAT GREEN
SUIT.
LET'S SEE IF THAT SHOWS UP AT
THE WEDDING GUY, THAT WAS
SOMETHING.
RIGHT ANGIE?  LIKE A WHOLE SUIT
OF IT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THERE FOR IT.
>> WHO WOULDN'T WANT THAT, IT
WORKS OUT WHEN YOU'RE TRYING TO
DO A TRICK.
BY THE WAY I HADN'T HEARD OF
THIS UNTIL I SAW IT THIS
MORNING, SO THAT SHOWS YOU HOW
OUT OF THE LOOP I AM, BUSY
FOCUSING ON THE FORECAST I
GUESS.
WE HAVE A LOOK AT THE FULL SEVEN
DAY COMING UP WHEN FOX5 RETURNS.
♪
FOX5 RETURNS.
♪♪
OK, network inspection.
OK.
Connected to WiFi,
protected from threats.
Thermostat -
connected, protected.
Speaker, space vacuum...
Connected, protected. Shh.
Eh, this is not
connected or protected.
But, that's a family heirloom.
And, it's a family security
breach. It's gotta go.
With Xfinity xFi, if it's
connected, it's protected.
Pull the truck around.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Get started with
Xfinity Internet for
$39.99 a month
for 12 months.
Plus, ask about enhanced
network security
for all your
connected devices.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
>>> FOX5 IS GATHERING NEW
DETAILS ON A MURDER MYSTERY.
>> SARAH SIMMONS IS IN THE NEWS
ROOM NOW WITH MORE ON THAT AND
WHAT ELSE THEY'RE WORKING ON.
HI SARAH.
>> HI GUYS, ALL NEW AT 5:00
WORLD WAR II HIGH SCHOOL GRADS
COG IN SOUTHWEST VIRGINIA OVER
THE WEEKEND AND HOW DID THEY
WIND UP DEAD?  FOX5 TALKS WITH
THEIR FAMILIES.
PLUS A BIG PUSH FOR PROPER PLANE
ETIQUETTE.
WHAT ONE AIRLINE IS DOING TO
CRACK DOWN ON BAD BEHAVIOR FROM
PASSENGERS.
AND SHOW A LOT OF LOVE AND A
LITTLE HATE.
WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU ABOUT
THE WILD VALENTINE'S DAY
PROMOTION AT A LOCAL CAT CAFE
HELPING FIRE RELIEF FUNDS AND
THROWING SHADE AT YOUR X AT THE
SAME TIME.
SEEMS TO BE THE POPULAR THING ON
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> JUST IN THE NEWS ROOM,
BREAKING NEWS, JUSSIE SMOLLETT
THE EMPIRE ACTOR HAS BEEN
APPARENTLY INDICTED BY A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR, THAT IS COMING FROM
OUR CHICAGO FOX STATION AND I
KNOW YOU GUYS ARE WORKING BEHIND
THE SEASONS.
>> YEAH, WE'LL HAVE MORE COMING
UP.
>> TO GET CLARITY ON WHAT'S
GOING ON IN CHICAGO.
THANK YOU.
>>> DON'T LET THAT GAP ACTUALLY
BE A GAP.
>> BE INTENTIONAL WITH YOUR TIME
BETWEEN JOBS SAYS JENNIFER A
WORKING MOM OF THREE.
THE AUTHOR OF RING MASTER WORK
LIFE AND KEEPING IT ALL TOGETHER
SHARED TIPS FOR REENTERING THE
WORK FORCE ON MY OH MY GOFF
SHOW.
>> THE FINANCIAL IMPLICATIONS
ARE ENORMOUS.
IF YOU TAKE APPROXIMATELY ONE TO
TWO YEARS OUT OF THE WORK FORCE,
YOU CAN EXPECT A TEN TO 20% CUT
IN YOUR SALARY.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THINGS LIKE
DAY CARE ON AVERAGE, INFANT CARE
IN THE DISTRICT COSTS ABOUT
24,000 SO YOU NEED THE
FLEXIBILITY BUT YOU ALSO NEED TO
EARN.
>> THE ONE THING I HEAR FROM MY
GIRLFRIENDS IS LIKE, WHY AM I
GOING TO GO BACK TO WORK WHEN
EVERY PEN COUNTRY I MAKE GOES TO
DAY CARE.
>> IT'S ABOUT STAYING IN THE
GAME.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO TAKE THE
PURPOSEFUL TIMEOUT, IF YOU WORK
FOR A NONPROFIT IN DEVELOPMENT,
YOU'RE A FUNDRAISER, DON'T JUST
CHAIR THE PRESCHOOL CHAIR, GO
AND VOLUNTEER AT THE RED CROSS
CHAPTER, EXPAND YOUR NETWORK
THAT WAY.
IF YOU'RE AN ATTORNEY AND TAKING
A COUPLE YEARS OFF, MAKE SURE
YOU KEEP THE CONTINUING
EDUCATION CREDITS UP.
IMAGINE FUTURE YOU HAS A RESUME
AND WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> YOU CAN WATCH THE FULL
INTERVIEW BY SUBSCRIBING TO THE
OH MY GOFF PODCAST OR APPLE
PODCAST.
THE REALITY ITS SO FEW PEOPLE
ARE INDEPENDENTLY WEALTHY THAT
WHEN THEY DO TAKE TIME OFF WORK
THAT THEY CAN JUST, YOU KNOW, BE
OFF WORK FOREVER.
>> RIGHT.
>> AT ONE POINT YOU DO HAVE TO
GET BACK IN THAT GAME AND SHE'S
SAYING, LOOK, ENJOY THE TIME OFF
FOR WHATEVER REASON, BUT HAVE A
PLAN STILL IN PLACE.
>> IT IS IMPORTANT TO, YEAH,
KEEP YOUR SKILLS GOING, KEEP
YOURSELF MARKETABLE DURING THAT
TIME FOR WHEN YOU DO WANT TO
RETURN TO THE WORK FORCE.
>>> RIHANNA DROPPED A HINT ABOUT
HER HIGHLY ANTICIPATED NINTH
ALBUM.
WHEN ASKED ABOUT HER VALENTINE'S
DAY PLANS IN A RECENT INTERVIEW
SHE SAID SHE'S SPENDING THE DAY
IN THE STUDIO.
WHEN PRESSED FURTHER THE SINGER
ADMITTED SHE'S WORKING WITH
PHARRELL.
SHE PROMISED FANS THAT HER NINTH
ALBUM WOULD BE RELEASED LAST
YEAR.
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
IT'S RUE MORED TO HAVE A HEAVY
REGGAE INFLUENCE.
NO WORD YET ON A RELEASE DATE.
>> IT WOULD BE NICE.
WE'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR THAT.
>> SHE'S BEEN TEASING FANS TOO
>>> FOR BRAD PITT AND JENNIFER
ANISTON, LISTEN, YOU'RE OUT OF
LUCK.
THE CORDIAL XS REPORTEDLY HUNG
OUT AT AN OSCARS AFTER PARTY.
OKAY?  THIS IS AN OLDER PICTURE.
WITH GENERAL CONGRATULATING
BRAD.
IS THAT THE SAME WAY?  BRAD ON
HIS BEST SUPPORTING ACTOR WIN
ALAS THERE WAS NO SEVERAL
BETWEEN THEM.
THEY CONGRATULATED EACH OTHER
AFTER THE SAGA WARDS, THAT
SPARKED RUMORS BUT THOSE WHO MAY
WANT THEM TO GET BACK TOGETHER,
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO BE LEFT WAITING RIGHT?  DID
SHE SAY SOMETHING?  LIKE SHE --
SHE'S NOT DOING IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT FOLLOWING IT AS CLOSELY.
>> I DON'T WANT IT TO HAPPEN.
I JUST DON'T.
>> OKAY.
>> I DON'T.
YOU KNOW, HIM AND THE REST OF
AMERICA GAVE UP ON HER WHEN HE
LEFT ON HER.
>> SHE'S BECOMING THE MEGHAN
MARKLE OF THE UNITED STATES
WHERE WE ARE JUST LOOKING AT HER
EVERY MOVE WONDERING WHAT'S
GOING ON READING INTO IT.
LEAVE HER ALONE.
>> SHE'S GOING TO LEAVE US AND
MOVE TOENING GLAND HAPPY
BIRTHDAY JENNIFER ANISTON.
51 YEARS OLD, SHE LOOKS AMAZING
AND YEAH IT'S HER BIRTHDAY.
>>> LOOKS LIKE THE ROCK'S
DAUGHTER IS GETTING INTO THE
FAMILY BUSINESS T WWE ANNOUNCED
DWAYNE THE ROCK JOHNSON'S
TEEN-AGE DAUGHTER SIMONE HAS
BEEN TRAINING TO BECOME A WWE
SUPER STAR, THE 18 YEAR OLD, IF
SHE MAKES IT ALL THE WAY TO THE
RING, SHE WOULD BE A FOURTH
GENERATION PRO WRESTLER
FOLLOWING IN THE FOOTSTEPS OF
HER WRESTLING CHAMP TURNED DAD
AND GRANDFATHER ROCKY JOHNSON
AND GREAT GRANDFATHER PETER
MAVIA.
>>> JANET FANS RHYTHM NATION GET
READY, JANET JACKSON HEADED ON
THE ROAD THIS SUMMER, COMING TO
DC.
THE 53 YEAR OLD ANNOUNCED HER
BLACK DIAMOND WORLD TOUR WHICH
WILL BE MAKING A STOP AT THE
CAPITAL ONE ARENA ON JULY 7TH.
TICKET PRE SALE BEGAN THIS
MORNING.
THE SHOW WILL FEATURE NEW MUSIC
FROM HER UPCOMING ALBUM ALONG
WITH A SPECIAL PERFORMANCE OF
HER 1989 RECORD RHYTHM NATION
1814.
JACKSON SAYS THE INSPIRATION FOR
THE BLACK DIAMOND TOUR, THAT
NAME ACTUALLY CAME FROM HER
INNER STRENGTH FOLLOWING HER
SPLIT FROM HER EX-HUSBAND
SAYING, QUOTE, BLACK DIAMONDS
ARE THE TOUGHEST OF ALL THE
DIAMONDS, THE HARDEST TO CUT.
GOOD FOR HER.
THIS IS GOING TO BE GOOD.
IT'S GOING TO BE GOOD.
>>> LET'S TAKE A LIVE LOOK
OUTSIDE.
WHAT DO WE HAVE?  THE CAPITOL
BUILDING.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE GETTING A I BRIEF BREAK
FROM THE RAIN.
>> NOTHING TOO EXCITING CAITLIN.
>> NO, I KNOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE SPRING IS POPPING
UP HERE AS THE RAIN ENDS.
IT'S NOT TOO EXCITING.
BUT I GUESS THE FACT THAT IT'S
NOT RAINING MIGHT BE HELPFUL IF
YOU HAVE THINGS TO DO THIS
EVENING OR MOST OF THE DAY
TOMORROW.
WE ARE GOING TO ENJOY A DRY
BREAKMENT SHOWERS DON'T FILL IN
UNTIL PROBABLY THIS TIME
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW, SATELLITE AND
RADAR STILL A LOT OF CLOUD
COVER, A COUPLE OF SPRINKLES OFF
TO OUR WEST BUT THE FRONTAL
BOUNDARY RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL THE
RAIN YESTERDAY AND TODAY, MOST
OF THAT NOW OFFSHORE AT LEAST
NEAR US.
IT'S STILL KIND OF STUCK TO OUR
SOUTH AND EAST AND HUNG UP BACK
ACROSS THE SOUTHERN STATES AND
ACTUALLY ALL THIS MOISTURE
STRETCHING FROM DALLAS THROUGH
MEMPHIS AND TOWARDS ATLANTA IS
GOING TO BE THE NEXT PLAYER IN
THE GAME AS WE'VE GOT ANOTHER
ROUND OF LOW PRESSURE THAT'S
GOING TO KIND OF ROLL UP ON THAT
BOUNDARY AND IMPACT US BY
TOMORROW.
HERE'S YOUR TEMPERATURES RIGHT
NOW, GOT A NICE BOOST OF SOME
MILD WEATHER HERE AS WE CLEARED
OUT, 57 IN DC, 51 IN ANNAPOLIS,
54 IN BALTIMORE, 52 IN
FREDERICK, 51 MARTINSBURG, AND
46 IN WINCHESTER.
THAT WARM AIR KIND OF HUGGING
THE MID ATLANTIC HERE, IT'S 61
IN RICHMOND, 70 IN RALEIGH AND
68 IN CAPE HATTERAS BUT THAT
COLD AIR RIGHT BEHIND THE
MOUNTAINS SO EVEN UP IN NEW YORK
IT'S ONLY 47 BUT 37 IN
PITTSBURGH AS WELL AS COLUMBUS,
33 IN CHICAGO, FEELING WINTERY
THERE.
FOR THE REST OF TONIGHT, NO
RAIN.
MAYBE A FEW SPRINKLES OUT WEST
AS YOU CAN SEE IN WEST VIRGINIA
BUT OTHERWISE TEMPERATURES RIGHT
AROUND 50 DEGREES.
AFTER 9:00 O'CLOCK WE FALL INTO
THE 40S, 48 BY 11:00 O'CLOCK.
HERE'S TOMORROW FUTURECAST.
GOING OPTIMISTIC STARTING OFF
WITH SUNSHINE FOR YOUR
WEDNESDAY.
IT WILL AT LEAST BE DRY FOR THE
DRIVE IN.
ANY SUNSHINE WE HAVE IN THE
MORNING I THINK WILL BE LIMITED
AS CLOUDS WILL RACE IN AHEAD OF
OUR NEXT SYSTEM WHICH BY 3:00
O'CLOCK IS SPREADING SHOWERS TO
CENTRAL VIRGINIA ALONG THE I81
CORRIDOR.
THAT FILLS IN SO THAT BY 6:00
O'CLOCK FOR THE EVENING COMMUTE
WE'VE GOT MORE RAIN SHOWERS
TOMORROW.
BUT WE AT LEAST GET ONE COMMUTE
IN WITHOUT ANY WET WEATHER.
LOOKS LIKE SHOWERS ARE PRETTY
SCATTERED THROUGH THE NIGHT
TOMORROW AND INTO THURSDAY
MORNING BUT THURSDAY MORNING
WILL BE THE FINAL ROUND OF WHAT
HAS BEEN A RAINY WEEK.
SO THIS COULD EVEN LAST UNTIL
THE MIDDLE PART OF THE DAY.
WE'VE GOT THIS SYSTEM THAT WILL
BE UP OVER US THURSDAY MORNING.
BUT AS WE GET INTO THE
AFTERNOON, THAT SHOULD PUSH OFF
THE NEW ENGLAND COASTLINE, HIGH
PRESSURE MOVES IN.
NOW, THIS IS ARCTIC HIGH
PRESSURE THAT'S MOVING IN LATE
THURSDAY.
THE COLD AIR WON'T BE FELT UNTIL
FRIDAY.
REALLY THROUGH THE DAY FRIDAY,
AND THEN ONCE IT'S HERE IT WILL
SIT OVER US THROUGH SATURDAY.
IT WILL BE REALLY COLD SATURDAY
MORNING.
TENS AND 20S TO START THE DAY.
WE HAVE NOT REALLY DONE
TEMPERATURES THAT LOW SINCE
DECEMBER, SINCE 2019.
THAT'S AMAZING WE'VE GONE THE
FIRST SIX WEEKS OF THE YEAR HERE
WITHOUT ANY REAL COLD AIR.
IT'S NOT COLD THE NEXT TWO DAYS.
YES, A STEP BACK TOMORROW WITH A
HIGH OF 49, THE STEADIEST RAIN
IS WEDNESDAY NIGHT, EARLY
THURSDAY MORNING.
AS THAT RAIN CLEARS, LIKE I
SAID, THE COLD AIR'S LAGGING.
WE SHOULD HIT 63 ON THURSDAY.
THAT WILL BE A MILD, MILD
AFTERNOON.
KIND OF NICE.
AND THEN AS HIGH PRESSURE BUILDS
IN, TEMPERATURES ARE PLUMMETING,
42 WILL PROBABLY BE AN EARLY
HIGH TEMPERATURE ON FRIDAY.
SATURDAY LOOKS VERY COLD, HIGH
OF JUST 36, BUT WE VERY, VERY
QUICKLY WARM IT UP.
NOTICE IT'S 36 ON SATURDAY BUT
50 BY SUNDAY.
MORE SHOWERS POSSIBLE.
BUT NOT UNTIL NEXT TUESDAY.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN DAY.
BLAKE, OVER TO YOU.
>>> A COLD SATURDAY.
>>> ALL RIGHT, STILL TO COME,
ACCORDING TO THE TRAFFIC SIGNS
IN ONE UTAH TOWN, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE CHICKEN REALLY DID CROSS THE
ROAD.
THE STORY BEHIND THE SIGNS
COMING UP.
♪
SIGNS
COMING UP.
♪♪
MIKE: Anyone hear the slogan,
'Mike Will Get It Done?'
OK, let me tell
you what the 'it' is.
As Mayor,
I expanded healthcare coverage.
As President,
I'll build on Obamacare
because healthcare is a right.
I created nearly
500,000 jobs in New York City.
As President,
I'll build an economy
that delivers good jobs
with higher wages.
I'll take on the gun lobby
and save lives.
And I will stop Trump's assault
on women's reproductive rights.
I've got a record
of doing things.
I've got the resources
to take on this fight.
As mayor,
PRODUCTIVE RIGHTS.
♪.
♪
ffer common sense plans
and I will get it done.
So let's stay on the offensive,
and let's win.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
.
>>> FOR US EAGLES PROJECT.
RYAN INSTALLED CROSSWALK SIGNS
AT BUSY INTERSECTION, LET'S LOOK
AT THEM.
THEY DID PUT THEM ON THE SIGN,
IT'S CAUSING PEOPLE TO SLOW
DOWN, SO HE IS ACCOMPLISHING HIS
GUN CONTROL.
>>.
>>> THE DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC
SAFETY POSTED THESE PICTURES,
THEY SAY IT WAS HONORED TO HELP
WASH THE WEINER MOBILE.
YOU BRING IT TO ITHAT WOULD BE
HARD TO GET THROUGH A CAR WASH,
I CAN IMAGINE.
>>> LET'S GO BACK TO UTAH, THE
BRING YOUNG UNIVERSITY MASCOT IS
KNOWN FOR HIS STUNTS AND DANCE
MOVE, HE CAN ALSO FLY, LOOK AT
THIS.
WHOA.
THAT LOOKS LIKE IT HURT.
IT SHOWS HIM GETTING LAUNCHED
INTO THE AIR, THAT'S NOT A TRAM
POLE LIEN, THE JUST MALE
CHEERLEADERS AND HE SINKS IT.
>> DID HE WIN ANYTHING?
USUALLY YOU WIN A FREE TUITION
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> HE'S THE MASCOT.
>> BUT AT STUDENT.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON THIS
TUESDAY AT 4:00.
>>> NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> AT 5:00, HUNDREDS IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY STAY HOME ADD
A SOCIAL MEDIA THREAT, AND IT'S
JUST THE LATEST IN SERIES OF
ONLINE THREATS.
THE CORONAVIRUS CRISIS DOZENS OF
EVACUEES IN THE U ARE BEING
QUARANTINED.
AND FEAR PUTTING PEOPLE AT RISK
FOR OTHER ILLNESSES.
>>> WHY A LOCAL SCHOOL IS
REPLACING VALENTINE'S DAY WITH
FRIENDSHIP DAY.
YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
♪.
>>> OFF THE TOP AT 5:00, A
MSTERY IN VIRGINIA, A YOUNG
GERMANTOWN COUPLE FOUND DEAD
ALONG A REMOTE HIGHWAY.
>> BODIES DISCOVERED FOLLOWING A
CAR CRASH, NO ONE KNOWS WHY THEY
WERE THERE IN THE FIRST PLACE,
PAUL WAGNER IS LIVE IN
GERMANTOWN WITH THAT STORY.
PAUL?
>>  THAT IS THE BIG MYSTERY, WHY
WAS THIS COUPLE DOWN IN HALIFAX
COUNTY NEAR THE NORTH CAROLINA
BORDER, I SPOKE WITH DIANA
GRIFFIN'S FATHER, HE WAS AT THE
SCENE, I SPOKE TO HIM BY PHONE
AS HE WAS DRIVING BACK.
I ALSO SPOKE WITH HER AUNT WHO
LIVES NORTH CAROLINA, THE PEOPLE
HAVE NO FRIENDS IN HALIFAX OR
CONNECTIONS TO HALIFAX COUNTY
AND THEY DON'T CARE WHY THEY
WERE THERE.
STATE POLICE DON'T KNOW EITHER.
THIS IS WHERE THE COUPLE MET IN
GERMANTOWN, THAT'S WHY WE'RE
HERE THIS AFTERNOON.