WATCHING, AND KEEP YOUR EYES
OPEN FOR THE 10th SEASON OF
"FEHERTY" COMING UP EARLY NEXT
YEAR.
THANKS A LOT.
TAHO
IT'S BEEN 30 YEARS
SINCE WE BROADCAST THE
AMERICAN CENTURY
CHAMPIONSHIP
TODAY NBC SATURDAY
SPORTS SHOWCASE
TRAVELS TO MAGNIFICENT
LAKE TAHOE
AFTER BRYANT GUMBEL
BROUGHT US ON THE AIR
FOR THE FIRST TIME, SO
MANY THINGS HAVE
TRANSPIRED AND
TRANSFORMED THIS
EVENT.
IT'S A CAN'T-MISS
SHOWCASE
THE FUN HAS REMAINED A
CONSTANT IN THIS 30th
YEAR OF GOLF'S
CELEBRITY EVENT.
A YEAR AGO TONY ROMO
BROKE THROUGH THE
QUARTERBACK TURNED
ANALYST IS BACK
DEFENDING AGAINST THE
LIKES OF NBA SUPERSTAR
STEPH CURRY AND NFL
GREAT AARON RODGERS.
AFTER A ONE-YEAR
ABSENCE DUE TO HIS
CONCERT TOUR JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE IS BACK
TRADING IN THE RED
CARPET, THE STARS ARE
HELPING TO CELEBRATE
THE EVENT'S 30th
ANNIVERSARY.
NBCSN PROUDLY PRESENTS
FIRST ROUND COVERAGE
OF THE AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
AND WE ARE NOW WITH
JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE.
AFTER A ONE-YEAR
HIATUS, THIS IS FOR
BIRDIE AT THE 12th
STEVE SANDS, PETER
JACOBSON
NO
NODA BEGAY, THERE HAS
TO BE A HUGE CROWD
DOWN THERE
>> ENJOYING A
BEAUTIFUL DAY ON THE
SOUTH SIDE OF THE LAKE
AND SEEING SOME SOLID
GOLF
ROMO GOT OFF TO A SLOW
START, ABOUT YOU HE
HAS BROUGHT IT AROUND.
HE IS WORKING UP THE
HILL
STILL HAS A SHOT TO
GET SOME MORE POINTS
ON THE BOARD
>> THIS IS THE BACK
PART OF THE GREEN
WHERE MOST OF THE
GREENS HERE AT
EDGEWOOD SLOPE FROM
BACK TO FRONT.
SO IT'S AN IMPORTANT
THING TO GET THE BALL
HOLE HIGH.
>> YEAH, SPEED IS
GOING TO BE A KEY
POINT HERE
LOOK HOW FAR OUT TO
THE LEFT
HE WILL HAVE SOME GOOD
LEFT TO RIGHT SWING IN
IT, ESPECIALLY AT THE
END.
>> WE GO OVER TO THE
7th HOLE AND WELCOME
IN CHARLIE RYMER
THIS GUY, DELL CURRY.
>> EVERYTHING HAS BEEN
SMOOTH FOR HIM TODAY
BIRDIED THE FIRST
THREE HOLES.
HE HAS HIS HANDS FULL
WITH THIS ONE.
A LOT OF FRINGE TO
DEAL WITH.
IT'S ALSO GOING TO
MOVE A LOT TO HIS
RIGHT.
YEAH, JUST BUM BLD
RIGHT THROUGH THAT
FRINGE
>> FROM ONE CURRY TO
ANOTHER.
DELTO HIS SON STEPH.
>> PULLED HIS TEE SHOT
LONG AND LEFT AND HIT
A NIFTY -- HE HAD A
DIFFICULT DOWNHILL
PITCH SHOT, BUT A
PRETTY NICE SHOT
NOW UNDERNEATH THE
HOLE, A LITTLE RIGHT
TO LEFT.
>> GOOD SAVE RIGHT
THERE.
>> VERY GOOD
NOT JUST SMOOTH ON THE
BASKETBALL COURT,
PETER, IS STEPH.
>> GOOD FROM LONG
RANGE AND CLEARLY GOOD
FROM CLOSE IN AS WELL.
>> NOW TO JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE
NODA, YOU HAVE BEEN
AROUND HIM A FEW
TIMES.
HE LOVES THIS SPORT.
>> HE REALLY LOVES
THIS GAME.
REALLY WORKS ON IT
DILIGENTLY IN TERMS IT
OF EVALUATING HIS
SWING.
HAS HIS SWING
INSTRUCTOR IN THE
GALLERY.
HE TAKES IT VERY
SERIOUSLY, STEVE.
>> THAT HE DOES.
SO SOME ACTION FROM
EARLIER TODAY.
CHARLES BARKLEY ALWAYS
A HUGE STAR WHENEVER
HE COMES HERE.
SAID YESTERDAY, PETER,
HE IS PLAYING AS WELL
AS HE HAS PLAYED IN A
LONG TIME.
HE STARTED AT 10
THE FOURTH SHOT AT 16.
>> NO HITCH ON THAT
DOWNSWING.
WHEN YOU WATCH HIM ON
THE RINGS, THERE IS NO
HIP.
LOOKS LIKE HE HAS BEEN
ABLE TO TAKE IT TO THE
GOLF COURSE.
HE WENT ON TO MAKE
THAT PUTT FOR PAR AND
THEN ONE HOLE AHEAD AT
17 THIS FOR BOGEY.
HOW ABOUT IT, CHARLES?
>> LOOK AT THE FIST
PUMP.
>> OH, CHARLES
CHARLES IN CHARGE AT
HAVING A GREAT TIME.
SPEAKING OF 17, TO THE
TEE AND LARRY THE
CABLE GUY.
>> THE MUCH IMPROVED
LARRY THE CABLE GUY.
WHEN HE FIRST STARTED
PLAYING GOLF HE REALLY
STRUGGLED.
HE IS HITTING MORE AND
MORE SHOTS LIKE THAT
HE PLAYED WELL LAST
YEAR
LOOKS LIKE HE IS ON IT
THIS YEAR AS WELL.
>> HE IS ASKING FOR
THE BOAT
THAT'S ON A DIFFERENT
HOLE IF YOU MAKE A
HOLE IN ONE.
LARRY THE CABLE GUY.
BASEBALL'S VINCE
CARTER
HIS TEE SHOT AT 12.
>> THIS IS SUCH A HARD
HOLE
FORCE CARRY.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HE ALMOST JARS IT.
>> THE NBA SUPERSTAR
WITH A BEAUTIFUL TEE
SHOT THERE AT THE PAR
3 12th
TONY ROMO, THE DEFEND
BE CHAMPION.
BIRDIE AT 10
KIND OF A SLOW START
AFTER THAT BIRDIE AT
10, HE BIRDIED 11.
SO BACK-TO-BACK
BIRDIES FOR ROMO
HE HAS CLIMBED ON TO
THE FIRST PAGE OF THE
LEADERBOARD.
WE HAVE THE MODIFIED
STABLEFORD SCORING
SYSTEM
10 POINTS FOR THE
DOUBLE EAGLE, EIGHT
FOR THE HOLE IN ONE,
ON DOWN THE LINE
THE ONLY TIME YOU GET
HURT, A DOUBLE-BOGEY
MINUS TWO.
IT PROMOTES AGGRESSIVE
PLAY.
>> YEAH, THE PAR 5s
ARE REACHABLE.
YOU CAN PICK UP POINTS
BY JUST MAKING PAR
SO POSITION IN THE
FAIRWAY IS KEY
>> AND WE TALKED ABOUT
THAT FIRST PAGE ON THE
LEADERBOARD.
TAKE A LOOK AT WHO IS
LEADING RIGHT NOW.
AND YOU KNOW THE SIDE
BETS BETWEEN THE
CURRYS
DELO
DELL OFF TO A FABULOUS
START.
DEREK LOW PLAYING
WELL, 17 POINTS.
REDSKINS QUARTERBACK
CASE KEENUM PLAYING
WELL AS WELL
JOE PAVELSKI MADE A
FEW PUTTS DOWN THE
STRETCH.
SO LOTS OF GOOD
SCORING RIGHT NOW AS
WE GO BACK TO DELL
CURRY AND SEE IF HE
CAN MAKE HIS PAR AT
THE 7th.
>> AND THIS IS REALLY
WHERE WE'RE GOING TO
SEE WHO IS GOING TO
WIN AND LOSE
THESE FOUR OR
FIVE-FOOTERS HAVE SO
MUCH BREAK
SO NO POINTS RIGHT
THERE FOR A BOGEY FOR
DELL.
>> DELL WILL REMAIN AT
18 POINTS.
ONE POINT AHEAD OF
DEREK LOWE, WHO IS
SITTING THERE AT 17,
BUT HE HAS A COUPLE OF
HOLES AHEAD OF DELL
CURRY TO PLAY.
SO AS WE WELCOME YOU
INTO SOUTH LAKE TAHOE,
GOOD TO BE WITH YOU.
30-YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF
THIS AMERICAN CENTURY
CHAMPIONSHIP
HOW IS THIS
CHAMPIONSHIP IMPROVED
IN THREE DECADES
>> I USED TO WATCH
THIS TOURNAMENT WHEN I
WASN'T WORKING WITH
YOU HERE BECAUSE I
LOVE TO WATCH MY
HEROES, MY ATHLETIC
HEROES DO WHAT I DO
INSIDE THE ROPES,
WORKING ON THEIR GAME,
TRYING TO MAKE THE
SHORT PUTTS FOR PAR
AND BIRDIES.
TO SEE THE STRAIN ON
THEIR FACE
WHEN THEY ARE ON THE
BASKETBALL FIELD OR
FOOTBALL FIELD, THEY
KNOW WHAT THEY ARE
DOING.
OUT HERE SOMETIMES
THAT'S IN QUESTION
THIS EVENT IS
INCREDIBLE
YOU CAN FEEL IT IN THE
ATMOSPHERE
THE INTENSITY, THE
LOVE, AND THE FUN.
WE SEE KIDS REALLY
START LOOKING AT
PLAYING THE GAME RIGHT
HERE
THEY COME OUT TO WATCH
STEPH CURRY AND ROMO
AND THEY THINK, HEY,
IF THESE GUYS PLAY
GOLF, I WANT TO DO IT,
TOO.
>> YOU PLAYED ON THE
PGA TOUR FOR ABOUT
THREE DECADES.
WON AT THE HIGHEST
LEVEL.
WHAT DOES A WEEK LIKE
THIS MEAN?
>> WHEN YOU SEE STEPH
CURRY AND JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE AND THESE
GUYS THAT WE KNOW AND
LOVE FROM OUTSIDE OF
THE GAME OF GOLF THEY
LOVE TO LEARN.
AND WHENEVER WE ARE ON
THE RANGE BEFORE THE
ROUND OR AFTER THE
ROUND THEY ARE ALWAYS
ASKING, HOW DO I HIT A
LITTLE MORE SPIN, MAKE
THE BALL HOOK WITH A 5
IRON ON 8 IRON
WHAT'S FUN FOR ME AS A
GOLF PRO IS TO GO
OUTSIDE TO THE RANGE
AND TALK TO THESE
PLAYERS AND HELP THEM
WITH THEIR GAME
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO
LEARN IT
THEY ARE SO TALENTED
THEY ABSORB IT LIKE A
SPONGE
SO THAT'S THE ONE
THING.
THEY WANT TO LEARN
THEY KNOW HOW TO
PERFORM AT THE HIGHEST
LEVEL AND THEY WANT TO
BE THE BEST THEY CAN
BE.
>> AND THEY LOVE THIS
SPORT.
SO DOES THIS MAN
HOCKEY STAR MIKE
MODANO, A SOLHSTANLEY
CHAMPION AT THE 14th
WE GO DOWN TO HEATHER
COX.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
JOINED BY TRAVIS
KELCE, TIGHT END OF
THE KANSAS CITY
CHIEFS, PLAYING IN
THIS TOURNAMENT FOR
THE FIRST TIME, CAME
IN LAST NIGHT AND
CRUSHED IT WINNING
CELEBRITY CKARAOKE.
A WAITING LIST A MILE
LONG TO GET INTO THIS
TOURNAMENT
WHAT HAVE BEEN YOUR
IMPRESSIONS SO FAR
>> IT'S A BLAST.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
JUST THE SUPPORT THEY
GET OUT HERE IN TAHOE
IS ABSOLUTELY
UNBELIEVABLE AND THEN
ALL I CAN SAY IS THANK
YOU TOO EVERYONE AT
NBC AND AMERICAN
CENTURY FOR LETTING ME
BE A PART OF IT.
>> THE CHIEFS AN ODDS
ON FAVORITE TO WIN THE
SUPER BOWL
WHAT IS YOUR PRIMARY
FOCUS IN THE OFFSEASON
TO MAKE SURE YOU DO
EVERYTHING YOU CAN TO
REACH THOSE GOALS?
>> JUST ENJOYING
MYSELF
I WILL BE LOCKED AND
LOADED AND THINKING
ABOUT FOOTBALL
NON-STOP WHEN I AM
THERE.
WE WERE THIS CLOSE
LAST YEAR FROM GETTING
A TRIP TO THE SUPER
BOWL
THAT IS MOTIVATION TO
GET THERE THIS YEAR
AND WITH THAT BEING
SAID, YOU KNOW,
CUTTING IT LOOSE WHILE
I'M NOT IN SEASON SO
THAT DURING THE SEASON
I CAN USE MY FOCUS FOR
IT.
>> WE SAW YOU DO THAT
LAST NIGHT
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOUR
QUARTERBACK, PATRICK
MAHOMES.
CERTAINLY TOOK THE
LEAGUE BY STORM LAST
YEAR, GETTING MVP.
LOVED WATCHING THE
CHEMISTRY BETWEEN THE
TWO OF YOU
WHAT KIND OF ADVICE
HAVE YOU GIVEN HIM TO
KEEP THAT CHEMISTRY
AND KEEP THAT MOJO
GOING?
>> I THINK JUST KEEP
COMING TO WORK EVERY
DAY, READY TO GO TO
WORK
I MEAN, IT'S A BIG
THING IN COACH ANDY
REID'S SCHEME IS THAT,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DURING THE WEEK WE ARE
GOING TO HAVE TO GO TO
WORK, WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO PUT IN A LOT
OF EFFORT IN TERMS OF
STUDYING AS WELL
GETTING OUR
FUNDAMENTALS AND
TIMING RIGHT AT LEAST
ON THE OFFENSIVE SIDE
OF THE BALL.
SO IT'S JUST ONE OF
THOSE THINGS THAT IT'S
A NON-STOP ROUTINE
ANDEST TO KEEP GETTING
BETTER EVERY SINGLE
WEEK
A LOT OF GUYS WHAT
THEY ARE COG IN KANSAS
CITY
SO I THINK COMING TO
WORK IS PRETTY FUN.
>> IT CERTAINLY SHOWS.
WE WILL GLET YOU GET
BACK TO THE FUN AT 17.
ONE OF THE BEST HOLES
ON THE COURSE.
>> ALL RIGHT
THIS IS ONE OF THE
BEST SCENES OF THE
WEEKEND.
TRAVIS, HAVE SOME FUN.
>> JIMMY, LAST NIGHT
WE WERE THERE FOR
KARAOKE.
JOURNEY'S "DON'T STOP
BELI
BELIEVIN'," CRUSHED
IT.
>> WHEN I JOINED NBC
SPORTS 20 YEARS AGO,
ONE OF THE FIRST
THINGS THEY DID IS
GIVE ME ONE OF THOSE
HATS
I THOUGHT IT WAS
PRETTY COOL BACK THEN.
THAT IS OLD SCHOOL
YOU KNOW, YOU
SUSPECT -- THAT'S
KINDA LIKE AN OLD HAT
--
>> HE GOT UP ON STAGE
AND STARTED SINGING
JOURNEY.
STEVE PERRY HAS THE
HIGH REGISTER.
I WAS SURPRISED
TRAVIS, HE WENT UP
PRETTY HIGH FOR A BIG
DUDE
YOU WOULD THINK HE
WOULD HAVE A FAIRLY
LOW VOICE, BUT HE
NAILED IT.
>> SO MUCH IS MADE OF,
YOU KNOW, THIS
TOURNAMENT, BUT WHEN
WE TALK ABOUT THIS
TOURNAMENT, WE TALK
ABOUT THIS HOLE.
YOU GOT A LITTLE BIT
OF A GLANCE OF IT
RIGHT NOW.
LOOK AT THAT SHOT.
THERE ARE, YOU KNOW,
HOW DO YOU EVEN
CALCULATE HOW MANY
PEOPLE ATHERE ARE?
WE HAVE SEEN THE
NUMBER OF BOATS GROW
OUT THERE.
THERE IS AN ARMADA OUT
THERE.
GETTING BACK TO ACTUAL
GOLF, 174 YARDS.
HOLE LOCATION IN THE
FRONT, PETER
AND IT COMES UP JUST
SHORT.
A REMINDER THIS WEEK
HERE ON 17, ANY GOLFER
WITH A HOLE IN ONE, $1
MILLION, 500,000 TO
THE GOLFER, 500,000 TO
THE STOWERS INSTITUTE
FOR MEDICAL RESEARCH
ON BEHALF OF AMERICAN
CENTURY.
A GREAT STORY.
WE WILL TELL YOU MORE
ABOUT THAT OVER THE
WEEKEND.
AND OVER THE YEARS
ONLY TWO PEOPLE ABLE
TO JAR IT HERE AT 17
JOE SAKIC IN 2011,
MARSHALL FALK TWO
YEARS BEFORE THAT.
>> HOW MANY TIMES OVER
THE COURSE OF THE NEXT
THREE DAYS WILL YOU
SAY THE PHRASE NOW
BACK TO THE ACTUAL
GOLF
>> ONE OR TWO.
THAT'S A GOOD LOOKING
SWING, DON'T YOU
THINK?
>> YES, IT IS.
I WATCHED HIM A LITTLE
BIT YESTERDAY IN THE
PRO-AM AND WAS VERY
IMPRESSED.
TALKED TO HIM A LITTLE
BIT AS HE WALKED IN.
>> HOW ABOUT IT?
NEVER CEASES TO AMAZE
ME
WE COME HERE AND SEE
THESE GUYS, MANY OF
WHOM HAVE ONLY TAKEN
UP GOLF LATE IN LIFE
AND THEY GET REALLY
GOOD REALLY QUICKLY AS
WE TAKE A LOOK AT
TYLER EIFERT.
>> WHAT'S INTIMIDATING
FOR THE PLAYERS,
JIMMY, IS WHEN YOU
HAVE GOT A CARRY OVER
A BUNKER OR A PENALTY
AREA IN FRONT OF YOU
THAT'S INTIMIDATING TO
AMATEUR GOLFERS.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
LEVEL.
EVERYBODY LIKES TO SEE
THE GREEN GRASS
LEADING RIGHT UP TO
THE FLAG
>> WELL, THE FUN IN
THE SUN IS JUST
GETTING STARTED.
SO GLAD TO HAVE YOU
WITH US HERE ON NBCSN.
DAY ONE OF THE
AMERICAN CENTURY
CHAMPIONSHIP IN YEAR
NUMBER 30 AND THE
CROWD HAS GATHERED
STRONG ON A FRIDAY
AFTERNOON.
UNDER THE SUNSHINE
HERE IN THE VALLEY
HERE IN T
>>> SPEAKING OF TONY
ROMO, AT THE 13th.
14 POINTS.
GOOD SHOT.
>> WELL.
>> HE'S GOT THAT TYPE
OF GOLF SWING, HE
PLAYED IN THREE PGA
TOUR EVENTS IN THE
LAST TWO OR THREE
YEARS.
>> YOU SEE THAT
BEAUTIFUL RIDE RIGHT
THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT IS ON THE LINE
THIS WEEK IF YOU GET A
HOLE-IN-ONE.
AT THE 12th,
MASTERCRAFT WILL BE
GIVING AWAY A BOAT TO
ANY SLEB WHO GETS A
HOLE-IN-ONE.
AN ICONIC X STAR TOW
BOAT VALUED AT NEARLY
$200,000
THAT IS SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> HOW MANY COOLERS
CAN YOU FIT ON THAT
POET
>> LET'S SEE IF LAYRRY
FITZGERALD CAN GET A
BOAT AND BRING IT BACK
TO ARIZONA.
>> THIS GUY IS A
PLAYER.
>> GOOD SHOT.
>> ALWAYS PLAYS AT THE
AT&T AT PEBBLE BEACH
>> FROM ONE PAR 3 TO
ANOTHER.
WE GO TO 17.
>> YEAH, AND IT LOOKS
LIKE A RELATIVELY OPEN
GREEN.
BUT TYLER EIFERT
GIVING THE HOLE A
SCARE.
EIFERT ONE OF TWO
NOTRE DAME TIGHT ENDS
IN THIS GROUP ALONG
WITH KYLE RUDOLPH.
OVER TO 8.
>> ALL RIGHT, CHARLIE,
WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH
ALFONSO RYE BARROW AT
8?
>> HE HIT A VERY POOR
APPROACH, CHIPPED IT
UP TO THIS POINT
THIS TO SAVE HIS PAR
ANYTHING ABOVE THE
HOLE, STEVE, REALLY,
REALLY QUICK.
>> CHARLIE, HE IS THE
HIGHLIGHT AT CELEBRITY
KARAOKE.
LAST NIGHT HE DIDN'T
DO HIS MICHAEL JACKSON
"BILLY JEAN".
>> OR THE BRUNO MARS
VERSION.
>> HE A TALENTED GUY.
>> INCREDIBLY
TALENTED.
>> ALSO SUPER NICE,
TOO, BUT NOT HIS BEST
DAY ON THE GOLF
COURSE.
>> HE CAN POUND IT OFF
THE TEE.
>> HE IS USING AN
UNUSUAL PUTTING GRIP
LOOKS PAINFUL TO ME.
HE CALLS IT THE
ALFONSO.
SAYS HE IS GOING TO
PATENT IT.
>> WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO HIGHLIGHT THAT
LATER ON.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW,
CHARLIE.
HE COULD HAVE A GREAT
WEEK
TONY ROMO FOR BIRDIE
THREE MORE POINTS.
>> SLIDES BY.
>> THESE GREENS CAN BE
TRICKY
IF YOU GET TOO
AGGRESSIVE GOING
DOWNHILL, YOU ARE
GOING TO HAVE THREE,
FOUR, FIVE FEET COMING
BACK.
>> BACK TO THE 8th AND
ONE OF THE CO-LEADERS
DELL CURRY.
>> DROVE IT IN THE
RIGHT ROUGH.
A SQUIRRELY LIE.
WISELY WENT TO THE FAT
PART OF THE GREEN.
A LITTLE BIT OF A LEFT
TO RIGHT IN IT
IT'S ALL ABOUT GETTING
THE SPEED.
THIS ONE WILL ROLL OUT
IF HE HITS IT A LITTLE
TOO FAR.
>> CHARLIE, I WAS OUT
ON THE COURSE
YESTERDAY WATCHING
DELL WITH NBC'S JOHN
MILLER AND TIM
RANDOLPH AND HE DROVE
IT LIKE A MACHINE,
LONG AND BULLET
STRAIGHT EVERY HOLE.
>> YEAH, HE DOESN'T
HAVE THAT HIGH BALL
FLIGHT, SORT OF THAT
MEDIUM-HIGH BORING
TRAJECTORY
I LIKE THAT.
WHEN YOU HIT IT LOW
LIKE THAT, YOUR MISSES
ARE A LITTLE MORE
PLAYABLE, I THINK.
>> TO THE 12th AND RAY
ALLEN, ANOTHER MAN WHO
CAN STROKE IT FROM
BEYOND THE ARC.
>> THIS IS FOR THREE
POINTS
OH
OF COURSE HE MAKES IT
FROM LONG RANGE.
>> LAST YEAR HIS BEST
FINISH IN THIS EVENT A
TIE FOR FIFTH AT 28
POINTS IN THE FINAL
ROUND.
THE MOST OF ANY OF HIS
39 ROUNDS HERE IN HIS
CAREER AT THE AMERICA
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
TO 13 AND JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE.
>> THAT WAS FOR BOGEY.
SO THAT ONE'S GOING TO
HURT A LITTLE BIT.
>> YEAH, THOSE STING.
>> YEAH, YOU'VE GOT TO
STAY AWAY FROM
DOUBLES.
I MEAN, YOU'VE JUST
GOT TO AVOID DROPPING
POINTS IF POSSIBLE.
>> YEAH.
BOGEYS DON'T HURT YOU.
>> NOW ROMO LOOKING AT
THIS
YOU MENTIONED OUR
PRODUCER TOM RANDOLPH.
CONGRATULATIONS.
ALL 30 AMERICA CENTURY
CHAMPIONSHIPS HE HAS
BEEN IN THE TRUCK FOR
NBC.
>> AND IN OUR EARS
.
>> OKAY.
SO IMPORTANT THOSE
PARS, TO GAIN THAT ONE
POINT.
>> THE GREENS HERE AT
EDGEWOOD ARE JUST AS
BEAUTIFUL AS THEY WERE
LAST YEAR, BUT JUST A
LITTLE BIT ON THE
QUICK SIDE WHEN YOU
GET ABOVE THE HOLE
YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP IT
BELOW THE FLAG.
>> FITZGERALD NOW, CAN
HE CONVERT THE BIRDIE
AFTER THE NICE TEE
SHOT
AND HE COMES UP SHORT.
>> AGAIN THAT'S ONE OF
THE TIPS I LEARNED
LONG AGO WHEN I
STARTED THE TOUR
YOU HAVE TO HIT THE
UPHILL PUTTS HARDER
FOR SOME REASON.
IT'S GRAVITY
I CAN'T EXPLAIN THAT,
STEVE, BUT BELIEVE ME
IT'S THERE.
>> ANDRE IGUODALA.
WAS AN NBA CHAMPION
WITH THE WARRIORS, A
FINALS MVP WITH THE
WARRIORS
BUT WAS TRADED IN THE
OFFSEASON AWAY FROM
GOLDEN STATE
NICE PUTT FROM ANDRE,
WHO LIKE ALMOST EVERY
SINGLE PLAYER IN THIS
FIELD, DEARLY LOVES
THE SPORT OF GOLF.
WHAT A DAY WE HAVE IN
STORE FOR YOU HERO
WORLD CHALLENGE AT /*
AT THE AMERICA
CENTURY.
HAPPY 30th BIRTHDAY.
TH
AMERICA CENTURY.
HAPPY 30th BIRTHDAY.
♪
Everything your trip needs,
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
I see what's possible,
instead of what's here.
for everyone you love.
Others see cracked concrete,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
That's why I made
Project Backboard
and a site with GoDaddy.
How will you make your mark?
Make the World You Want
>>> BACK WITH DELL
CURRY IN THE RIGHT
ROUGH AT 9.
>> HE HAS A DECENT
LIE, 120 YARDS
THIS IS NOT GOING TO
HAVE ANY PISPIN ON IT
IF HE LANDS IT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE GREEN,
SHOULD RELEASE TO THE
FLAG
GOT TO GET UP MAYBE A
TOUCH.
YEAH, NICE PLAY FROM
THAT LIE.
>> REALLY NICE PLAY.
FINAL HOLE OF THE DAY
FOR DELL
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING, BUT I LIKE
IT
>> THAT'S FANTASTIC
FROM MR. CURRY
LARRY FITZGERALD AT
>> THESE ARE TOUGH
THESE CHIPS.
OH
LIKE I SAID, THEY ARE
TOUGH DOWNHILL CHIPS
NOT THAT TOUGH
LARRY FITZGERALD
LET'S GO TO 14 AND
JUSTIN TIMBERLAKE.
>> HAVING A LITTLE BIT
OF A PROBLEM HERE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
JUST HOW HE IS GOING
TO GET THE CLUBFACE ON
THAT BALL.
IS GOING TO HAVE
STANCE ISSUES.
AND IT'S NOT THE
GREATEST LIE, PETER.
SO IT'S GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE BIT OF
CREATIVITY HERE FOR
J.T. TO GET THIS ONE
ON THE SURFACE.
>> THIS IS WHERE HE
HAS ONE FOOT IN, ONE
FOOT OUT
SO HE REALLY NEEDS TO
JUST STABILIZE HIS
LOWER BODY AND USE THE
UPPER BODY ROTATION OF
HIS SHOULDERS TO BRING
THE CLUB BACK ONTO THE
BALL AS MUCH AS HE
CAN.
>> JUST CAUGHT THE TOP
HALF OF THE BALL
WAS LUCKY IT GOT OUT
OF THE BUNKER.
IN THE INTERMEDIATE
CUT, HE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET THE CLUB UNDER
IT
>> FROM THE QUIET AT
14 TO THE NOISE AT 17,
JIMMY.
>> YEAH, LET ME TELL
YOU SOMETHING.
THIS GUY, DOUG
PEDERSON, ONLY IN HIS
THIRD YEAR, BUT ADORES
THIS EVENT
OF COURSE, THE HEAD
COACH OF THE EAGLES, A
COUPLE YEARS BACK A
SUPER BOWL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> WHAT A SWING.
>> YEAH, HE CAN PLAY
>> BACK TO 14.
>> THE DEFENDING
CHAMPION.
>> NO EXCUSES NOT TO
GET THIS ONE
15 FEET.
PERFECT LIE.
OFF A PERFECT DRIVE.
>> AND THOSE ARE THE
SHOTS LAST YEAR, NODA,
AS YOU SAW, THAT
HELPED HIM TO WIN THE
TOURNAMENT
HE REALLY WAS DIALED
IN WITH HIS WEDGE PLAY
LAST YEAR.
BEEN WORKING HARD ON
HIS GAME WITH HIS
COACH CHRIS O'CONNELL
IN DALLAS.
>> SEE-SAWING BACK TO
17.
>> WE TALK ABOUT THE
FIRST DAY HERE
THAT'S MATT NAGY,
COACH OF THE BEARS,
PLAYING ALONGSIDE
PEDERSON AND THE COACH
OF THE SAINTS, SEAN
PAYTON
LOVE TO BE A FLY ON
THE WALL BETWEEN THESE
THREE GUYS
LOOK AT THAT SHOT
RIGHT THERE.
I AM SMOOR TURE THERE S
PLENTY OF FRIENDLY
CONVERSATION HERE.
ONE OF THE THINGS YOU
KNOW IS THAT DURING
THE SEASON IF ANY OF
THESE GUYS SHOULD
ENCOUNTER EACH OTHER,
YOU KNOW THEY ARE
TALKING FOOTBALL
BUT YOU KNOW THEY ARE
ALSO TALKING SOME
GOLF
>> AND OUR THOUGHTS
WITH ALL THE PEOPLE
DOWN IN NEW ORLEANS
WHERE SEAN PAYTON
COACHES.
RAIN AND THE STORMS
DOWN THERE WREAKING
HAVOC ON THAT CITY
ONCE AGAIN
THAT'S GOING TO PLAY
NICELY
>> RUNNING RIGHT TO
THE CUP.
>> HE'LL HAVE A GOOD
LOOK FOR A BIRDIE,
WILL SEAN PAYTON
ALWAYS AN ADVANTAGE
HERE
LET'S GO OVER TO THE
9th.
>> AND HERE IS DELL
CURR
CURRY'S TURN FOR
BIRDIE.
>> IT LOOKS PRETTY
STRAIGHT
KEEP IN MIND THE LAKE
IS TO HIS LEFT AND
PETER, AS WE ALL KNOW,
WATER LIKES TO ROLL
DOWNHILL AND SO DO
GOLF BALLS
>> ALL RIGHT
LET'S GO BACK TO 17,
THE TEE, THE BEST SPOT
ON THE GOLF COURSE
THAT'S WHERE WE FIND
HEATHER COBS.
>> JOINED BY COACH
PEDERSON AND COACH
PEYTON
LAST YEAR WE TALKED
YOU HAD A FRIENDLY
WAGER ON THE OUTCOME
IN FACT YOU'VE GOT TO
WEAR HOME GREENS IN
NEW ORLEANS BECAUSE
YOU BEAT COACH PEYTON
IN GOLF.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THIS YEAR?
>> A PLAYER OF CHOICE
JERSEY AND A BALL FROM
THE OPPOSING TEAM.
IF I WIN, I GET TO
PICK A PLAYER FROM THE
SAINTS
IF HE WINS, HE GETS TO
PICK A PLAYER FROM THE
EAGLES
A SIGNED JERSEY,
SIGNED BALL, MAYBE DO
IT FOR CHARITY.
>> MUCH MORE
CIVILIZED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
LET HIM WEAR HOME
GREENS IN THE HOME
CITY
YOU GOT THE WIN,
RIGHT?
>> I TOOK A LOT OF
FLAK FROM THE FANS
IT WAS PART OF THE
DEAL.
>> YOU BOTH HAVE WON
SUPER BOWLS.
KNOWN AS OFFENSIVE
GURUS, COMPETITIVE ON
THE GRIDIRON
HOW COMPETITIVE DO YOU
GET OUT HERE FOR GOLF?
>> HERE IS THE THING
WE HAVE A LITTLE NFC
COACHES, SO MATT NAGY,
COACH P, MYSELF ARE
PLAYING 3 AFC COACHES
TODAY.
WE ARE PULLING FOR
EACH OTHER TODAY
FRANK REICH.
WHO ELSE DO WE HAVE?
ANTHONY LYNN AND MIKE
VRABEL
THEY CHALLENGE US.
WE WANT TO PLAY OUR
BEST AND AS A GROUP
YOU WANT TO PLAY WELL.
>> TONS OF NFL
GREATNESS OUT HERE
SO FUN TO SEE.
COACH PEDERSON, LET'S
TALK A LITTLE SHOP
WHAT IS THAT ONE TOP
PRIORITY IN THE
OFFSEASON YOU ARE
THINKING OF TO GET THE
JOB DONE NEXT YEAR
>> THE BIGGEST THING
WAS GET OUR
QUARTERBACK HEALTHY,
NUMBER ONE
THAT WAS THE BIGGEST
CHALLENGE AND WE DID
THAT
BY THE END OF OTAs WE
FELT COMFORTABLE WHERE
CARSON IS AT
WE ARE LOOKING GOOD
GOING INTO TRAINING
CAMP AND HAVE TO PUT
THINGS TOGETHER ONE
DAY AT A TIME.
>> LOOKING GOOD.
GREAT SHOTS ON 17.
ENJOY.
>> THANK YOU
>> STEVE.
>> ALL RIGHT
HEATHER, THANK YOU
A MOMENT AGO ALFONSO
RYE BAUR
RIBEIRO ON THE 9th.
>> IT'S UP THE FOREARM
BY KUCHAR.
>> THERE YOU GO.
THERE IS CARLTON
>> NOW DELL CURRY FOR
PAR AND 20 POINTS.
BEST ROUND EVER IN
THIS FORMAT BY 7 AT 13
POINTS, DID IT FOUR
TIMES.
THIS IS HIS FOURTH
TIME PLAYING IN THIS
FORMAT, AND DELL CURRY
SHOULD BE SMILING AND
DANCING ALONGSIDE
ALFONSO.
WHAT A DAY FOR CURRY
PLAYING WITH JADE
BILAS AS WELL.
AND THE BASKETBALL
STAR
TAKE A PICTURE OF THE
LEADERBOARD, DELL.
YOU ARE ON TOP OF IT
MIGHT NOT LAST FOR THE
ENTIRE WEEKEND, BUT
YOU NEVER KNOW
♪ ["Stuck in the Middle
with You" by Stealers Wheel] ♪
♪  ♪
♪ Well I don't know why
I came here tonight ♪
♪ I got the feeling that
something ain't right ♪
♪ I'm so scared in case
I fall off my chair ♪
You can't always
choose how you travel
But now, you can choose
a little extra comfort
♪ Jokers to the right, here I am
stuck in the middle with you ♪
I see what's possible,
instead of what's here.
Others see cracked concrete,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
That's why I made
Project Backboard
and a site with GoDaddy.
How will you make your mark?
Make the World You Want
There's no set path.
No way you have to be.
So why not do what
you've been dreaming of?
♪♪
You've got the power.
We've got the tools.
Make a website with GoDaddy and
put what you want out there.
>>> HERE IN SOUTH LAKE
TAHOE ON THE STRIP,
HARRAH'S AND HARVEY'S
LAKE HOTEL AND CASINO
THE OFFICIAL HOST
HOTELS OF THE AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
MULTIPLE FIVE STAR
DINING OPTION WAS A
VIEW AS WELL AS
OPPORTUNITIES TO RELAX
AND UNWIND
IN ADDITION TO DINING
AND RELAXATION,
HARRAH'S AND HARVEY'S
OFFER AN ABUNDANCE OF
EXCITEMENT WITH A
CHANCE TO HIT IT BIG
AT MANY GAMING TABLES
THROUGHOUT THE
PROPERTIES
WHETHER IT'S GAMING,
FINE DINING OR A DAY
AT THE SPA, HARRAH'S
AND HARVEY'S FULFILL
YOUR NEEDS HERE IN
BEAUTIFUL SOUTH LAKE
TAHOE.
AND YOU CAN SEE THE
HOTELS AND CASINOS
FROM THE GOLF COURSE,
ESPECIALLY AT THE 14th
WHERE STEPH IS.
>> A LITTLE UPHILL
RIGHT TO LEFTER.
THAT WILL BE THE
SECOND STRAIGHT HOLE
HE HAD A LITTLE BIT OF
STRUGGLE
DROPPED TWO POINTS ON
THE LAST HOLE.
>> THESE GREENS HERE
AT EDGEWOOD TAHOE,
NODA, THEY ARE A REAL
DEFENSE HERE AT THE
GOLF COURSE, THEY ARE
TOUGH TO READ, TOUGH
TO PUTT.
THERE IS A LOT OF
SLOPE ON THEM.
>> AND ALONG WITH
THAT, PETER, IF YOU
GET GOING IN THE WRONG
DIRECTION THEY CAN GET
IN YOUR HEAD
CLASSIC WEST COAST
WE HAVE SEEN AT PEBBLE
BEACH AND SOME OF THE
WEST COAST VENUES HOW
BUMPY THEY CAN GET AT
TIMES ON THE PGA TOUR.
>> SPEAKING OF THE PGA
TOUR, TONY ROMO HAS
PLAYED AT PGA TOUR
EVENTS
TRIED TO QUALIFY FOR
THE U.S. OPEN.
HOW MUCH CAN THAT HELP
HIM THIS WEEK?
>> IT HELPS HIM
TREMENDOUSLY BECAUSE
HE KNOWS HE IS PLAYING
WITH THE BEST PLAYERS
IN THE WORLD
Y
HE NOW COMES OUT HERE
AND HE FEELS LIKE HE
CAN BRING SOMETHING
FROM THE TOUR HERE
WITH THE EXPERIENCE.
MAKING A PUTT LIKE
THAT
HE KNOWS THAT'S WHAT
YOU NEED TO DO TO WIN.
>> THERE HE IS
>> REMEMBER, THE MORE
HOLES YOU HAVE LEFT,
THE BETTER YOU ARE IN
THIS FORMAT.
TO 17.
>> SEAN PAYTON, STEVE,
FOR BIRDIE
THIS WOULD BE HIS
FIRST OF THE DAY
AFTER THAT NICE TEE
SHOT
HERE ON THE PAR 3.
A LITTLE FRISKY THERE.
MEANWHILE, SEAN PAYTON
PLAYED HIS COLLEGE
FOOTBALL AT EASTERN
ILLINOIS, QUARTERBACK
THERE, SAME SCHOOL AS
TONY ROMO.
WE TELL YOU THAT COACH
PEDERSON MISSED HIS
BIRDIE PUTT AS WELL.
>> LET'S SEE IF JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE CAN POUR IN
A PAR AT 14.
>> DELICATE PUTT HERE.
GOING TO DRIFT A
LITTLE BIT AWAY FROM
HIM.
>> THAT'S HUGE THERE
A GREAT UP AND DOWN.
>> GOT A BAD BREAK OFF
THE TEE TO PUT IT IN
THAT BUNKER.
WALKED AWAY WITH ONE
POINT.
THAT'S BOT TO GIVE HIM
A LIFT
>> AS WE GO TO THE 7th
AND PAPA ROCKET HE
TOLD US YESTERDAY IN
THE PRO-AM
HE IS NOW A
GRANDFATHER, SO HE'D
LIKE TO BE CALLED PAPA
ROCKET
TWINS WERE BORN
RECENTLY.
>> PAPA ROCKET
A HECK OF A SHOT THERE
BY PAPA ROCKET.
>> PAPA ROCKET.
>> A BROUD -
>> SOUNDS LIKE HE IS
GOING TO HAVE A
PIETE PIZZA
LINE COMING OUT.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID
YESTERDAY.
CALL ME PAPA ROCKET, I
AM NOW A GRANDFATHER
OF TWINS
HERE IS JACK WAGNER
FOR BIRDIE
AT THE 6th
OH, YEAH
>> TWO-TIME CHAMPION
HERE AT THE AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> ONE OF ONLY TWO
GUYS IN PLAY IN ALL 30
ALONG WITH JIM
McMAHON.
>> TIED FOR THE LEAD.
>> YEAH, JACK PLAYING
VERY WELL.
>> LAST NIGHT IN
CELEBRITY KARAOKE, UP
AGAIN, KILLED IT
DID A GREAT JOB.
>> AMAZING
HE IS AN INCREDIBLY
TALENTED GUY.
>> AND PETER, YOU
TALKED ABOUT ROMO
MAKING SOME OF THOSE
SWING CHANGES.
TRYING TO PEEL A
LITTLE FADE HERE
NEEDS JUST A BIT MORE.
>> YEAH, IT'S FINE
LEFT SIDE OF THE
FAIRWAY.
>> YEAH, NODA, THIS IS
NOT A HOLE YOU NEED TO
BOMB DRIVE IT.
IT'S NARROW UP THERE
PROBABLY 25 YARDS FROM
DRIP LINE TO DRIP
LINE
YOU SEE IT'S 392
YARDS.
YOU JUST KICK
SOMETHING UP OVER THE
HILL
IT'S A BLIND TEE SHOT.
>> ONE OF THE
NARROWEST LANDING
AREAS ON THE GOLF
COURSE
I WAS TALKING TO
JUSTIN A COUPLE HOLES
AGO AND HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT HOW MUCH MORE
EXHAUSTED HE GETS
AFTER THESE LONG WORLD
TOURS THAT HE DOES
HE GOES, I CAN'T DO
WHAT I USED TO DO AT
28 IN THE 38
I GO, WAIT UNTIL YOU
ARE 48
>> SHOULD HAOLE UP AND
BE FINE.
YEAH
>> AND STEFAN IN HIS
OWN RIGHT TOOK A
TEN-DAY TOUR OF CHINA
ABOUT A WEEK AFTER THE
NBA FINALS
HE IS STILL TRYING TO
GET HIS WITS ABOUT
HIM.
BUT SAID HE HAS PUT A
LITTLE BIT OF TIME
INTO PREPARATION FOR
THIS WEEK.
CERTAINLY WANTED TO
COME OUT AND HAVE A
GOOD SHOWING
STRUGGLED A LITTLE BIT
WITH THESE LAST TWO
TEE SHOTS.
13th HOLE, LOST IT TO
THE RIGHT.
AND AGAIN AT 14.
SO SEE IF HE CAN GET
IT TOGETHER.
>> BEAUTIFUL SWING
RIGHT THERE.
>> HE HAS A BEAUTIFUL
ACTION
>> ALL RIGHT
WELL, LET'S GO TO
CHARLIE RYMER.
>> ALL RIGHT, STEVE.
I'M WITH THE LEADER
DELL CURRY
WE HAVE A LEADERBOARD
HERE BEHIND US
HE CAN'T TAKE HIS EYES
OFF HIS NAME AT THE
TOP.
DELL, I WAS WITH YOUR
SON STEPH WARMING UP
THIS MORNING ON THE
PRACTICE TEE AND WORD
CAME YOU BIRDIED THE
FIRST THREE HOLES.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
FOLKS.
HE WAS NERVOUS
YOU GOT A STANDING BET
EVERY YEAR HERE.
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
>> THE LAST COUPLE OF
YEARS IT'S LOSER JUMPS
IN THE LAKE.
HE SPOTTED ME SOME
POINTS SO I WAS ABLE
TO GET HIM
IT'S ONE AND ONE
WE WILL DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT THIS YEAR.
I HAVE A FEELING HE IS
GOING TO TAKE MY
POINTS AWAY.
WE WILL HAVE TO PLAY
STRAIGHT UP.
HE CAN GET ON A ROLL
AND GET GOING.
>> ANY HINTS ON WHAT
THAT SOMETHING
DIFFERENT IS THIS
YEAR
>> WE DON'T KNOW
US AND OUR CADDIES
WILL PUT OUR HEADS
TOGETHER TONIGHT AT
DINNER.
>> TWO SONS IN THE
NBA.
DOING PRETTY WELL FOR
THEMSELVES
ALSO TWO GOLFERS
GOLF HAS BEEN GREAT
FOR YOUR FAMILY.
YOUR FAMILY HAS BEEN
GREAT FOR GOLF
FOR PARENTS OUT THERE
THAT ARE WATCHING THIS
RIGHT NOW AND
CONSIDERING GETTING
THEIR KIDS IN GOLF,
TELL ME HOW BENEFICIAL
IT'S BEEN FOR YOU GUYS
AND THE RECOMMENDATION
YOU HAVE FOR PARENTS
THAT ARE THINKING
ABOUT JUMPING IN.
>> IT'S BEEN REALLY
GREAT FOR OUR FAMILY
ONE, IT GIVES US A
CHANCE TO GET OUT.
WHEN DAD SAYS I WANT
TO PLAY GOLF WITH THE
FELLAS, THE WIVES
CAN'T SAY ANYTHING
IT'S TIME TO WALK THE
COURSE AND TALK.
CELLPHONES ARE AWAY.
YOU CAN MAKE A LITTLE
FRIENDLY WAGER THERE
IT'S A GREAT CHANCE
FOR US TO BE
COMPETITIVE, TO GET
FATHER AND SON TIMES
AND JUST GET AWAY FROM
THE PEOPLE AND
CELLPHONES AND HAVE
FUN.
>> GREAT PLAYING HERE
TODAY.
YOUR BEST ROUND EVER
IN THE AMERICAN
CENTURY.
I AM HOPING THIS
WEEKEND WE MIGHT SEE A
LITTLE FATHER SON
ACTION BREAK OUT HERE.
WOULD BE A LOT OF FUN
TO WATCH
>> THAT WOULD BE SOME
TYPE OF SHOW OVER THE
WEEKEND HERE IN SOUTH
LAKE TAHOE
SPEAKING OF A SHOW, TO
THE 17th.
>> AND A GUY WHO YOU
ARE A BIG FAN OF,
STEVE.
T.J. OSHIE
HOCKEY PLAYER FOR TEAM
USA.
THROUGH THE YEARS, A
CERTAIN TEAM IN THE
NATION'S CAPITAL,
RIGHT?
>> STANLEY CUP
CHAMPION A COUPLE
YEARS AGO.
THAT COLLAR BONE
HE BROKE THAT COLLAR
BONE IN THE PLAYOFFS
AGAINST CAROLINA
SAYS HE IS FEELING
MUCH, MUCH BETTER NOW.
>> THAT'S A GOOD GOLF
SWING RIGHT THERE.
>> WE SEE A LOT OF
HOCKEY PLAYERS, PETER,
WHO GOT THAT GOOD
MOVE
I WONDER IF IT HAS
ANYTHING TO DO WITH,
YOU KNOW, THAT SIMILAR
MOTION
>> IT DEFINITELY DOES,
JIMMY.
THAT SLAPSHOT MOTION
WORKS WELL ON THE GOLF
COURSE BECAUSE IT
DEVELOPS A LOT OF
SPEED.
>> T.J.'S BROTHER
TAYLOR ON THE BAG WITH
HIM ONCE AGAIN HERE IN
TAHOE.
NICE TO SEE T.J.
HEALTHY AGAIN.
WE GO TO TIMBERLAKE AT
THE 15th.
>> LOOKING
CONSERVATIVE OFF THE
TEE, LEFT HIM 153.
HE MIGHT JUST LIKE
THIS ONE.
>> YEAH, HOW ABOUT
LOVE IT?
WHAT A SHOT.
REALLY GOOD SHOT THERE
FROM JUSTIN.
GOOD TO SEE HIM BACK
IN THIS EVENT.
HAD THAT CONCERT TOUR
GET IN THE WAY LAST
YEAR, SO HE COULDN'T
MAKE IT HERE TO
EDGEWOOD
>> ROMO TAKING A
LITTLE WALK UP TO SEE
WHERE THE HOLE IS CUT.
>> WE ARE LOOKING BACK
ON THE FAIRWAY FROM
THE GREEN, NODA.
YOU CAN SEE HOW TIGHT
THAT FAIRWAY IS AT 15.
>> ANOTHER HOCKEY
PLAYER, JOE PAVELSKI
LOOK AT THAT, PETER.
THAT IS GORGEOUS.
>> YEAH, I LOVE THE
WAY HE MOVES THROUGH
THE BALL
THERE IS NOT A LOT OF
EXTRA MOTION
THE CLUB GOES STRAIGHT
UP THE LINE AND THEN
IT'S A ROTATION
THROUGH.
I REMEMBER LAST YEAR
HE PLAYED SO WELL,
TIED FOR THIRD
I DIDN'T SEE HIM HIT A
LOT OF FOUL BALLS.
>> BACK AT 15.
>> TONY LOOKING AT
THIS ONE
IT'S GOING TO BE
ALMOST THE IDENTICAL
SHOT HE HAD ON THE
PREVIOUS ONE
IT WAS 106
MIGHT NEED TO TAKE A
LITTLE BIT OFF OF THIS
ONE.
THE WIND IS SLIGHTLY
HELPING.
>> WHAT A SHOT
BOY, HE LOOKS DIALED
IN THESE LAST FIVE,
SIX HOLES.
>> WELL, HE HAS
IMPLEMENTED ONE OF THE
STRATEGIES I THOUGHT A
LOT OF THE LONGER
HITTERS HAVE
IMPLEMENTED AT THIS
ALTITUDE
HE PUT FOUR WEDGES IN
HIS BAG SO HE DOESN'T
GET CAUGHT IN BETWEEN
CLUBS AS OFTEN
STEPH'S PERFECT DRIVE
UP HERE.
ONLY 77 YARDS LEFT
MIGHT HAVE TROUBLE
SPINNING IT FROM THIS
CLOSE.
GOT TO MAKE SURE HE
CLIPS IT JUST RIGHT.
>> SOUNDED GOOD.
OH, HOW ABOUT IT
OH, TOOK A PEEK.
HOW ABOUT THOSE THREE
SHOTS?
REALLY GOOD.
KIND OF LIKE WE ARE
WATCHING THE TOUR.
>> AMAZING
>> THAT TOOK A LOOK,
DIDN'T IT?
>> YES, IT DID
RIGHT OVER THE RIGHT
EDGE
HE
IT GOT A BOUNCE OFF
THE FRINGE, NODA, AND
KICKED FORWARD
TOOK ALL THE SPIN OFF
WITH THE BOUNCE.
AND IT JUST TOOK A
PEEK
ROLLING ABOUT THE
SPEED OF A PUTT.
CAUGHT THE EDGE.
>> YEAH.
>> THESE GUYS AREN'T
JUST GREAT IN THEIR
REGULAR PROFESSIONS.
THEY CAN GET IT DONE
ON THE GOLF COURSE AS
WELL AS EVIDENCED
RIGHT THERE FROM
STEPH.
>>> BACK ON THE GREEN
WITH THIS STAR-STUDDED
GROUPING, AND TONY
ROMO STARING THIS
DOWN.
>> TAKING QUITE A BIT
OF TIME GIVING THE 36
# TO WALKAROUND TO SEE
THE ANGLES
THAT'S IMPORTANT HERE.
SOMETIMES ONE LOOK
FROM ONE SIDE CAN BE A
LITTLE DECEPTIVE
BUT HE CERTAINLY IS
TAKING IT ALL IN.
>> YEAH, THERE IS A
LOT OF LITTLE HIDDEN
HUMPS AND BUMPS HERE
I NOTICED THAT IN THE
PRO-AM YESTERDAY
A LOT OF EIGHT AND
TEN-FOOTERS YOU THINK
ARE GOING TO WIGGLE
RIGHT AND THEY JUST
WIGGLE A LITTLE LEFT.
>> THIS SHOULD BREAK
BACK SLIGHTLY TOWARDS
THE LAKE
THE LAKE IS TO TONY'S
RIGHT.
>> OH, WOW, HOW ABOUT
IT
HEY, HE'S BACK.
>> YES, HE IS, BACK ON
TOP OF THE
LEADERBOARD.
A PUM OF PAR 3s
REMAINING -- A COUPLE
OF PAR 5s REMAINING.
>> TWO EARLY BOGEYS
AND A DOUBLE IN THE
FIRST FIVE HOLES
BUT HE HAS GOT IT
TOGETHER
HE IS 3 UNDER ON HIS
CARD ON THE BACK NINE.
HE HAS PICKED UP.
>> ANOTHER GREAT LOOK
FOR BIRDIE
J.T.'S BALL SLIGHTLY
FURTHER TOWARDS THE
FALL LINE, SO THERE IS
GOING TO BE A LITTLE
LESS BREAK IN THIS
THIS IS PRETTY
STRAIGHT OVERALL
MIGHT GO LEFT TO RIGHT
EARLY AND HOLD THE
LINE AT THE END.
>> SEE IF JUSTIN CAN
FOLLOW THE LEADER
ROMO'S PICKED UP 11
POINTS ON FIVE HOLES
ON THE BACK NINE SO
FAR.
>> FOR MOST OF THE
DAY, JUSTIN'S SPEED
CONTROL HAS BEEN
PRETTY GOOD, SO HE
SHOULD BE ABLE TO
MATCH THE SPEED UP
>> THERE IT IS
THAT WIGGLE TO THE
LEFT THAT YOU DON'T
EXPECT.
>> THAT ONE
ACTUALLY -- I DIDN'T
THINK THERE WAS THAT
MUCH WIGGLE TO THE
LEFT BECAUSE IT'S
BREAKING UP AWAY FROM
THE LAKE AND UP
TOWARDS THE MOUNTAIN,
WHICH USUALLY TAKES
SOME OF THE HEAT OFF
OF IT.
>> WELL, YOU MENTIONED
EARLIER THAT TAPOA AT
PEBBLE BEACH AND
TORREY PINES, HERE AT
EDGEWOOD IT CAN BE A
BIT OF A CRAPSHOOT
WHEN YOU ARE PUTTING
YOU HAVE TO FORGET IT.
YOU CAN GET A CRAZY
BOUNCE OR A CRAZY
ROLL
YOU JUST HAVE TO
FORGET IT.
OVER AT 7, JACK
WAGNER
TEE SHOT ON THE
BUNKER
HERE IS HIS THIRD AT
THE PAR 3.
>> STEVE, HE STARTED
THE WEEK PLAYING A
PRACTICE ROUND WITH
MARDY FISH
IN THE FIRST ROUND
HERE HE WAS 7 UNDER
THROUGH THE FIRST 11
HOLES.
MARTY SAID THAT HE
PLAYS A LOT OF GOLF
WITH HIM AT BEL-AIR,
BUT HE HAS NEVER SEEN
HIM PLAY LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH, HE SAID, HE
TOLD ME LAST NIGHT HE
SHOT 66.
HE HADN'T SHOT A ROUND
LIKE THAT IN YEARS.
>> T.J. OSHIE NOW FOR
BIRDIE HERE AT THE PAR
3.
YEP.
ABSOLUTELY
WASHINGTON CAPTAIN
STAR
STEVE.
>> LOVE SEEING HIM
MAKE BIRDIES.
>> OF COURSE YOU DO.
STEPH NOW.
>> ONLY ROMO WAS ABLE
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
THE TERRIFIC SECOND
SHOTS HERE AT 15.
>> I THINK HE
ABSOLUTELY GOT FOOLED
BY TIMBERLAKE'S PUTT
AND PUT IT OUT THERE
JUST A LITTLE BIT TOO
FAR RIGHT.
>> THAT'S PART OF THE
EXPERIENCE, NODA
YOU SEE A PUTT TAKE A
FUNNY WIGGLE, YOU HAVE
TO FORGET IT
STICK WITH YOUR
ORIGINAL READ.
>> AND THIS IS THE
FORMER NHL STAR MIKE
MODANO AT THE PAR 5s
HE WAS IT TELLING ME
EARLY YOUR HE HAS
TAKEN THE DRIVER OUT
OF HIS BAG AND PUT ONE
MORE WEDGE IN.
HE IS SO LONG.
JUST HITTING IT SO
STRAIGHT THIS WEEK
HAVING A GREAT WEEK.
AND HERE IS ANOTHER
ONE OF THE LEADERS,
DEREK LOWE ON 17
LOWE WITH 19 POINTS.
>> YEAH, HE IS MY DARK
HORSE FOR WEEK
I TALKED TO HIM
EARLIER AND HE SAID HE
IS PLAYING WELL.
>> LIKES THIS HOLE
WON THE CLOSEST TO THE
HOLE LAST YEAR
17'11"
THIS GUY LOVES HIS
GOLF
HE PLAYS A LOT OF
GOLF.
>> I HAVE PLAYED WITH
HIM DOWN IN SOUTH
FLORIDA.
HE CAN'T GET ENOUGH.
>> AND TREVOR
HOFFMANN
THE GREAT RELIEVER
JUST SNEAKS OVER THE
EDGE OF THE BUNKER
THERE.
SO HOFFMANN WILL HAVE
THE UPHILL PUTT.
THE THREE IS GOING TO
GET INVOLVED -- WHAT
IS HE DOING HERE
JUST AN AUTOGRAPH.
>> I WAS WAITING FOR A
DEEP THREE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S
GREAT HERE IS HOW
CREATIVE THE FANS GET
WITH THE AUTOGRAPHS.
THEY ARE TAPING THE
SHARPIE, YOU KNOW, TO
THE BALL
HERE IS MIKE MODANO.
RIGHT NOW MODANO WITH
15 POINTS FOR EAGLE IN
THE EARLY WALK,
INDICATIVE OF EITHER
SOMETHING REALLY GOOD
OR SOMETHING NOT SO
GOOD
AND IT WAS THE LATTER
FOR MODANO
NHL HALL OF FAMER.
AND THAT IS REALLY
GOING TO HURT FOR
MODANO
ON IN TWO, AND THE
PAR.
BACK AT THE TEE, HERE
IS AARON RODGERS
>> TEE SHOT.
THAT BIG PINE IN THE
MIDDLE TO THE BASE OF
THE IT, ABOUT 205
YARDS AWAY
>> AND IF YOU GET IT
BY THAT, JIMMY, IT
RUNS STRAIGHT DOWNHILL
AND THE FAIRWAY IS
PRETTY WIDE.
>> YEAH, IT'S AN
ABSOLUTE DART.
THERE IS USUALLY A
LITTLE BIT OF A BACKUP
HERE
LOOK AT THAT GALLERY
OKAY
SO YOU HAVE A GRAMMY
WINNER, AN NBA
CHAMPION, YOU GOT AN
NFL GREAT.
AND HERE IS JORDY
NELSON
LEFT-HANDER.
>> JIMMY, I CAN
RELATE
EARLY IN MY CAREER
WHEN YOU ARE PLAYING
ON THE TOUR AND UP
WALKS NICKLAUS AND
TREVINO AND WATSON
YOU ARE LIKE, OH, NO.
>> KIND OF HOW I FEEL
WHEN YOU WALK UP ON A
GOLF COURSE, PETER.
>> A.J. HAWK
HE IS NOT GETTING
CHEATED.
>> SMOKE ON THE WATER.
>> THESE GUYS ARE
HAVING A REALLY,
REALLY GOOD TIME
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE
OTHER GREAT THINGS
ABOUT THIS HOLE IS
THAT IT'S ALSO WHERE
THERE IS A BIG
SELECTION.
LOOK, THERE ARE A
MILLION THINGS TO DO
HERE AT THE LAKE
NOTICE SHE IS WEARING
A WET SUIT BECAUSE
THAT WATER IS CHILI.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
TONY ROMO BY 1 OVER
DELL CURRY
RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
>>> BACK AT THE 17th
HOLE
DEREK LOW, THIS FOR
BIRDIE
IF IT GOES IT WOULD BE
FOR THE TIMING THE
LEAD
SO DEREK LOWE, 22
POINTS, BEATER.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, HE
IS MY DARK HORSE.
>> NOT SO DARK AT THIS
POINT.
>> NO, RIGHT ON TOP.
>> OVER TO 7 NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT
ONE OF OUR HOCKEY
ANNOUNCERS, KATHRYN
TAPPEN HERE ON NBCSN
AND NBC SPORTS.
>> NICE SWING.
>> PLAYING HERE THE
LAST FEW YEARS
ONE OF THE GREAT
HIGHLIGHTS OF THE
ENTIRE WEEK COMES ON
THURSDAY NIGHT
CELEBRITY KARAOKE WITH
RASCAL FLATTS ON
STAGE.
LOOK AT THIS FROM
KATHERYN AND JEREMY
ROENICK.
♪
♪ COME ON FATSO JUST
BUST A MOVE ♪
♪ YWHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANT BABY
YOU GOT IT ♪
♪ JUST BUST A MOVE ♪
♪ YOU WANT IT, YOU GO
IT ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANT, BABY
YOU GOT IT ♪
♪ WE ARE ON A MISSION
AND YOU'RE WISHING
SOMEONE COULD CURE THE
LONELY CONDITION ♪
>> I MEAN, JEREMY
ROENICK, LEAH McCUE,
MIKE JONES, IT'S TIME
TO STEP UP WITH THE
HOCKEY COVERAGE
BECAUSE THOSE TWO
JAMMED IT LAST NIGHT.
>> HEY, HOW ABOUT OUR
HOCKEY GUYS CHANNELING
YOUNG MC
>> IT'S FANTASTIC.
I HOPE JONSEY IS
WATCHING THIS.
HE NEEDS TO START
SINGING.
>> I'M NOT SURE
AMERICA IS READY FOR
THAT, OR CANADA FOR
THAT PURPOSE.
>> THE MOST IMPRESSIVE
THING, JIMMY, RASCAL
FLATTS AS THE HOUSE
BAND
THAT WAS JOE DON
ROONEY PLAYING GUITAR.
>> LOVE SEEING THE
FACE OF JOE DON WITH
THE GUYS UP THERE
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
>> JEREMY IS KIND OF A
PSEUDO SINGER.
THIS MAN CAN ACTUALLY
SING, AND HE WAS
FABULOUS LAST NIGHT.
HE PICKS UP THE
ELECTRIC GUITAR EVERY
YEAR, KNOCKS OUT A
SONG WITH THE BAND
STILL GROOVING.
>> YEAH, HE IS STILL
GROOVING.
>> HE IS
I LOVE IT.
>> GUYS, WHAT'S GOING
ON, BLAKE SHELTON IS
PLAYING TONIGHT AT THE
HARVEY'S OUTDOOR
ARENA, ABOUT 200 YARDS
WHERE WE ARE STANDING.
A SOUND CHECK RIGHT
NOW.
A NICE VIBE HERE.
>> YOU WILL BE THERE
TONIGHT?
>> MY GOODNESS, BLAKE
SHELTON IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> I BET YOU THIS GOES
IN BECAUSE OF THAT.
>> IT'S LIKE THE
SVENGALI'S TUNE FOR
JEREMY ROENICK
BLAKE SHELTON PLAYING
IN THE DISTANCE.
>> I CAN HEAR HIM
RIGHT NOW.
SOLID PAR FOR JACK
A GOOD DRIVE UP THE
LEFT-HAND SIDE
82 YARDS, BUT AN
AWKWARD LIE.
A LITTLE BIT OF A BAD
BREAK.
>> THAT'S 20 POINTS
FOR JACK
JUST TWO POINTS BACK
OF DEREK LOWE.
THERE HE IS.
HE IS PICKING UP THE
ELECTRIC GUITAR AND
THE ELECTRIC PUTTER AS
WELL
WE TALKED ABOUT HIM
PLAYING IN ALL 30.
HE WON IN 2006 AND
'11.
THE BEST FINISH BY THE
OTHER MAN WHO PLAYED
IN ALL 30 AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIPS
JIM McMAHON, THE
QUARTERBACK FROM THE
NFL.
IN 1992, HE FINISHED
IN 14th.
ALWAYS ENTERTAINING TO
WATCH THE FUN-LOVING
JIM McMAHON.
AND JACK
MULTI-TALENTED MAN ON
THE FIRST PAGE OF THE
LEADERBOARD.
WE SEND YOU BACK DOWN
TO HEATHER AT 17.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
JOINED BY KYLE LOWRY,
NOW NBA CHAMPION
HOISTED THE TROPHY IN
JUNE
WHAT'S YOUR LIFE BEEN
LIKE SINCE THAT
MOMENT
>> A WHIRLWIND BUT
IT'S BEEN FUN.
ONE OF THEM THINGS
WHERE YOU ENJOY EVERY
MOMENT
A SITUATION LIKE THIS,
IT'S MORE OF A
WHIRLWIND.
YOU GET TO HANG OUT
AND PLAY GOLF AND
HEADA
HANG OUT.
>> BIG NEWS IN RECENT
WEEKS, KAWHI LEONARD
HEADING TO THE
CLIPPERS.
>> HE HAD AN
OPPORTUNITY TO PLAY
WHERE HE WANTED TO
PLAY
HE WANTED TO PLAY WITH
THE CLIPPERS
I AM HAPPY FOR HIM
WE HAVE A SMALL
FRATERNITY
YOU ALWAYS SUPPORT
YOUR BROTHERS'
DECISIONS.
>> YOU HAD A 4-2 WIN
OVER THE WAR ARIORS IN
THE FINALS
STEPH CURRY IN THE
FIELD.
I KNOW YOU ARE
COMPETITIVE ON THE
BASKETBALL COURT, BUT
HOW COMPETITIVE OUT
HERE
>> HIS GAME IS WAY
BETTER THAN MINE
THERE IS NO
COMPETITION WITH THAT
ONE.
>> YOU WILL TAKE THE
CHAMPIONSHIP TROPHY
ANY DAY?
>> ANY DAY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS
ENJOY IT.
>> BACK TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU
KYLE'S SECOND
APPEARANCE AT THIS
EVENT, TIED FOR 74th A
YEAR AGO
NOW TO 16.
>> AND OVER AT 16,
STEVE, AFTER THAT
GREAT DRIVE BY AARON
RODGERS HERE ON THE
PAR 5 DOWNHILL TO THAT
HOURGLASS-SHAPED
GREEN.
SO RODGERS IS GOING TO
HAVE A LOOK AT AN
EAGLE.
>> OVER TO 14 NOW.
PATRICK PETERSON
TREMENDOUS PLAYER IN
THE NFL.
>> WOW, RIGHT AT IT.
>> YEAH.
PATRICK PETERSON, FOUR
HOLES REMAINING,
ALREADY HAS 19 POINTS.
>> AND HE'S GOT TWO
REACHABLE PAR 5s
We're related
to them?
We're Portuguese?
I thought we
were Hungarian.
Can you tell me
that story again?
Behind every question
is a story waiting
to be discovered.
This holiday, start the
journey with a DNA kit
from Ancestry.
I see what's possible,
instead of what's here.
This holiday, start the
journey with a DNA kit
Others see cracked concrete,
rundown courts.
I see a way to bring pride
back to communities.
That's why I made
Project Backboard
and a site with GoDaddy.
How will you make your mark?
Make the World You Want
There's no set path.
No way you have to be.
So why not do what
you've been dreaming of?
♪♪
You've got the power.
We've got the tools.
Make a website with GoDaddy and
put what you want out there.
>>> LOOK AT THAT
SETTING.
JUST REMARKABLE.
HERE IS DYLAN DREYER
ON THE 7th
DOING THE WEATHER ON
"THE TODAY SHOW" WITH
AL ROKER.
>> IT'S EASY DOING THE
WEATHER HERE IN SOUTH
LAKE TAHOE
IT'S PERFECT EVERY
DAY.
>> DYLAN LOVES GOLF.
SHE WAS TERRIFIC LAST
NIGHT SINGING BILLY
JOEL'S "WE START THE
FIRE."
ABSOLUTELY TERRIFIC.
GET THERE.
>> OH, YEAH!
DYLAN SENDING IT HOME.
>> DYLAN WAS AT THE
OPEN CHAMPIONSHIP LAST
YEAR AT CARNOUSTIE
WITH US.
HUNG OUT WITH US ALL
WEEK
SHE HAS REALLY FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH THE GAME.
>> REALLY DIGS THE
GAME
GREAT TO SEE HER
ENJOYING HERSELF AT
HER FIRST AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> AARON RODGERS A
GOOD PLAYER, BUT NO
BIRDIES TODAY.
>> OH.
>> AND HE JUST MADE
HIS LIFE AN AWFUL LOT
NOR COMPLICATED WITH
THAT PUTT.
TALKING TO HIMSELF
15th APPEARANCE HERE
BEST WAS EIGHTH IN
HERE IS KYLE LOWRY
WE HEARD HIM TALKING
TO HEATHER BEFORE.
WHAT A CHAMPIONSHIP
SERIES HE HAD IN THE
CLINCHER
26 POINTS, 10 ASSISTS,
7 REBOUNDS
>> WAS THAT A HAZLE
ROCKET
>> COULD HAVE BEEN
I DON'T KNOW.
>> A.J. HAWK
YEAH, FOR BOGEY, I
BELIEVE.
>> DID YOU JUST DROP A
HASSLE TOF
>> YEAH, WHY NOT
THAT IS TREMENDOUS.
>> I CAN'T SAY I
ORIGINATED THAT.
>> IT'S SO GOOD.
>> HAVE YOU EVER HIT
ONE?
>> PLEASE, YOU PLAYED
GOLF WITH ME, PETER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK WE ALL
HAVE.
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY,
YOU KNOW
I HAVE SEEN A PLAYER
OR TWO ON THE PGA TOUR
ACCOMPLISH THAT.
>> OF COURSE
OF COURSE.
>> LOOK AT THAT CROWD,
JIMMY.
SO BIG.
>> OF COURSE, THIS IS
AT THE CROSSROADS OF
THIS CROSS
RODGERS WITH FOUR
POINTS FOR HIS FIRST
BIRDIE OF THE DAY.
HE GETS IT TO GO
SO AARON RODGERS PICKS
UP THREE POINTS THERE.
HIS FIRST BIRDIE
AND WE HEAD BACK OUT
TO THE FAIRWAY
I THINK THEY ARE A
LITTLE BIT
LIGHTHEARTED WITH THAT
CONGRATULATIONS.
TONY ROMO OUT IN THE
FAIRWAY, CONSIDERING
WHAT HE HAS GOT LEFT,
NOTAH.
>> YEAH, HIT JUST A
BEAUTIFUL DRIVE.
UNFORTUNATE IT DIDN'T
END UP IN THE FAIRWAY.
HAD A NICE LITTLE CUT
ACTION ON IT AND JUST
CAUGHT THIS HIGHER CUT
OF ROUGH HERE.
SO GOING TO HAVE TO
GET A LITTLE BIT STEEP
ON THIS ONE, JIMMY, IF
HE WANTS TO GET THE
FULL CARRY OUT OF IT
>> OF COURSE,
EVERYBODY OBVIOUS,
OBVIOUSLY ASSOCIATES
ROMO WITH FOOTBALL,
BUT IT'S INTERESTING
BECAUSE HE GREW UP IN
A GOLF FAMILY.
HIS MOM ACTUALLY RAN
THE DESK AT THE BROWNS
LAKE GOLF CLUB IN
BURLINGTON, WISCONSIN.
AND SO EVERY DAY SHE
WOULD DRIVE HIM AND
BEFORE SCHOOL TONY
WOULD GET OUT THERE,
HIT A FEW BALLS.
WHEN HE WAS DONE, HEAD
ON OFF TO SCHOOL
GREW UP WITH THE GAME.
>> YOU CAN TELL HE HAS
A NICE FLUID ACTION.
TRIED TO SWEEP THIS IN
LEFT TO RIGHT.
JUST RIGHT OF THE
FLAG
HE HAS TO HOLD UP JUST
A BIT.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO
HOLD THERE, BUT STILL.
ONE UNDER FOR HIS
ROUND.
SIX BIRDIES, A DOUBLE,
AND A BOGEY.
21 POINTS.
THAT'S A PRETTY BIG
TEE SHOT FROM STEPH
CURRY, NOTAH
JUST 146 LEFT, IS THAT
RIGHT?
>> I IMAGINE THAT ROMO
AND STEPH HAVE THE
SAME CLUB HEAD SPEECH,
BUT STEPH CURRY'S
LAUNCH IS HIGHER
AT THIS ALTITUDE AN
EXTRA 10 OR 12 YARDS
CARRY.
THAT'S THE REASON HE
ONLY HAS 146 YARDS
LEFT.
>> GOING TO HAVE TO
SWEEP THIS AROUND
RIGHT TO LEFT.
AND HE HAD THE RIGHT
PART RIGHT
MAYBE NOT THE DISTANCE
SO GOOD.
SO STEPH CURRY, WE ARE
NOT FAR FROM THE BAY
AREA
THIS GUY IS JUST SO
POPULAR EVERYWHERE HE
GOES, BUT ESPECIALLY
HERE
HUGE CROWD HERE AT
E
LAKE TAHOE
FIRST ROUND OF THE
AMERICAN CENTURY
BACK AFTER THIS.
>>> A LITTLE BIT
EARLIER AT THE 18th,
MARK MULDER, WHO WON
THIS CHAMPIONSHIP
THREE YEARS IN A ROW
BEFORE ROMO, TOOK IT
FROM HIM LAST YEAR
>> THE SOUND OF THE
CLUB STRIKE FROM HIM,
IT'S JUST SO GOOD,
PETER.
>> YEAH, HE'S GOT THAT
TYPE OF GAME
HE IS PLAYING ON TOUR.
HE PLAYED IN THE
SAFEWAY OPEN THIS
SEASON, LAST FALL.
HE MISSED THE CUT, BUT
HE COMPETED WELL.
>> DEREK LOWE'S THIRD
AT THE PAR 5
OKAY
>> LET'S GO BACK A
COUPLE HOMES.
>> WELL, NOTAH,
COMPLICATED THINGS A
LITTLE BIT FOR HIMSELF
THERE, DIDN'T HE
>> HE SURE DID
BUT THIS IS THE TYPE
OF SHOTS IN THIS
PARTICULAR EVENT THAT
SEPARATE THE UPPER
TIER PLAYERS FROM THE
LOWER TIER PLAYERS
STEPH'S BEEN AROUND
THE GAME, GREW UP
AROUND THE GAME.
SO HE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO GET THIS UP IN THE
AIR.
JUST GOT TO HIT A SPOT
THOUGH.
>> HE HAS TO HOIST
THIS WAY UP TOP TO GET
IT CLOSE
THAT IS SO GOOD.
>> I'VE GOT TO THINK,
NOTAH, THAT THE WAY HE
SHOOTS HIS THREE POINT
SHOTS FROM DEEP, HE
ALWAYS GETS AS MUCH
ALTITUDE AND AS MUCH
ARC.
I THINK THAT'S GOT TO
HELP HIM ON SHOTS LIKE
THAT.
>> YEAH, HE IS A ABLE
TO VISUALIZE AND HIS
HANDS PAY ATTENTION.
>> LOOKS LIKE HE IS
LAUGHING AT HIMSELF A
LITTLE BIT ABOUT THAT.
I AM NOT SURE HE
EXPECTED THAT.
>> I DON'T THINK HE
THOUGHT HE COULD LEAVE
IT SHORT OF THE HOLE.
>> I CERTAINLY DIDN'T.
PRETTY GOOD SHOT RIGHT
THERE.
FOURTH SHOT FOR
TIMBERLAKE WITH EIGHT
POINTS
>> YEAH, AND COULD USE
SOMETHING GOOD TO
HAPPEN TO HIM.
A BIT OF A TOUGH
STRETCH THE LAST FOUR
HOLES.
GOTTEN A LOT OF LOFT
SO HE IS GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE SURE HE
CARRIES IT AT LEAST
40% OF THE WAY IF HE
WANTS TO GET IT TO RUN
OUT.
>> THAT'S A PRETTY
GOOD SHOT RIGHT THERE.
HOW ABOUT THIS
>> WELL DONE
>> ALL RIGHT
SO THAT SHOULD BE A
PAR FOR TIMBERLAKE
AND HE'LL PICK UP A
POINT THERE.
>> PAR ON THIS HOLE IS
LIKE A BOGEY ALMOST.
PAR 4 1/2.
>> YEAH, 16 AND 18,
NOTAH, THEY ARE PAR
4s.
>> YEAH, THEY ARE
REALLY, I MEAN, THEY
ARE HOLES THAT YOU CAN
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF.
BUT I THINK THE
BIGGEST OFFENSE FACTOR
HERE, PETER, IS THE
TREES.
I MEAN, IF SOME OF
THESE PLAYERS HAVE A
TENDENCY TO GET A
LITTLE WAYWARD OFF THE
TEE AND IT CAN CAUSE
SOME PROBLEMS,
ESPECIALLY ON THE
SCORING HOLES LIKE 16
AND 18.
>> PETER, HOW WOULD
YOU CHARACTERIZE THIS
HOLE LOCATION IN TERMS
OF DIFFICULTY?
>> EASY.
THERE IS NOTHING IN
FRONT OF THE GREEN
YOU HAVE GOT ABOUT A
10 TO 12-YARD GAP TO
BE ABLE TO RUN THE
BALL IN.
SO IF YOU ARE IN THE
FAIRWAY OR IN THE
ROUGH, YOU CAN STILL
CHASE IT IN.
SO THIS IS PROBABLY
ONE OF THE EASIER HOLE
LOCATIONS THAT THESE
PLAYERS ARE GOING TO
SEE THIS WEEK.
>> AND TO MAKEABLE
LOOK FOR ROMO HERE
DOWN THE HILL.
>> AND THAT WILL COME
UP SHORT FOR TONY
ROMO
SO SHOULD BE ABLE TO
NEGOTIATE THIS FOR
BIRDIE
ALTHOUGH WE DID SEE A
SIMILAR MISS JUST A
FEW MOMENTS AGO FROM
MIKE MODANO.
MEANWHILE, OVER AT 17,
DEREK LOWE, WHO FOR
THE TIME BEING IS THE
TOURNAMENT LEADER OF
THIS FOR BIRDIE.
>> DEREK TAPS IN FOR
PAR AT THE 18th AND
FINISHES WITH 23
POINTS, CURRENTLY IN
THE LEAD
BUT REMEMBER ROMO
STILL HAS A BIRDIE
PUTT AT 16 AND THEN A
COUPLE OF HOLES TO
PLAY AFTER THAT.
>> NOW STEPH AFTER
THAT BEAUTIFUL FLAP
SHOT, NOTAH.
>> YEAH, THIS IS A
POSTAGE STAMP HERE
BEAUTIFUL BACKDROP
SEE IF HE CAN CONVERT
THIS GREAT UP AND
DOWN
>> MISREAD OR A LITTLE
YANK
>> I THINK A LITTLE
BIT OF A MISREAD
THERE.
YOU KIND OF HAVE TO
RESPECT THE LEAK TO
HIS RIGHT.
I THINK HE THOUGHT IT
WAS GOING TO TAKE A
LITTLE BIT OF BREAK
OUT OF IT.
>> AS YOU SAY,
DISAPPOINTING,
ESPECIALLY SOMEBODY OF
THAT LENGTH.
100, WHAT DID WE SAY,
46 YARDS IN?
NOW 18.
>> MULDER.
OH, HE WANTED THOSE
FIVE POINTS.
>> THAT WAS A GREAT
SECOND SHOT HE PLAYED
IN THERE
HE'LL HAVE TO SETTLE
THE BIRDIE
OKAY
MAKES THAT
MULDER, WHO SAID HE
HAS BEEN PLAYING
BETTER THIS YEAR THAN
HE WAS GOING INTO LAST
YEAR WHEN HE WAS A
THREE-TIME DEFENDING
CHAMPION, WILL BEGIN
WITH 19 POINTS AND HAS
SOME WORK TO DO OVER
THE WEEKEND TO CATCH
UP TO THIS MAN.
>> AND TONY ROMO,
STEVE, IN WITH A
BIRDIE NOW
5 UNDER ON THE BACK
NINE
AND 17 POINTS AFTER
THE TURN
SO ROMO WITH THE LEAD.
WE MOVE OVER TO THE
9th HOLE
>> AND JACK WAGNER
FROM JUST BEYOND THE
PUTTING SURFACE.
>> ONE OF THOSE TRICKY
DOWNHILL PUTTS, BUT
JUST HAVE TO WATCH THE
SPEED.
THAT'S WELL JUDGED
THERE.
JUST DIDN'T GET THE
BREAK.
BUT HE SHOULD HAVE NO
PROBLEM WITH THIS.
STRAIGHT BACK UP THE
HILL FOR HIS PAR
>> AND AARON RODGERS,
ALWAYS A FAVORITE
HERE, PETER, AT 17
USUALLY ENGAGES WITH
THE CROWD.
PLAYING PARTICULARLY
WELL TODAY, BUT NOT
HAPPY.
CLEARLY, SOMEBODY
YELLING IN THE MIDDLE
OF HIS SWING.
>> HE STARED AT ONE OF
THE BOATS.
>> IT'S PRETTY CROWDED
OUT THERE.
LOOKS LIKE A LONG
ISLAND EXPRESSWAY IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE
SUMMER.
>> TALKING ABOUT
COOLERS, HOW MANY
COOLERS PER BOAT ON
THE AVERAGE, JIMMY
TAKE A GUESS.
>> NOT SO SURE
>> OKAY.
THIS IS WHAT PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR.
TIMBERLAKE, HE HAS A
PRETTY GOOD STROKE,
I'D SAY, HERE.
SEE WHAT HE CAN DO
>> BIG BASKETBALL GUY,
HAS A STAKE IN THE
MEMPHIS GRIZZLIES, HIS
HOMETOWN.
>> THE OTHER GUY I
THINK PEOPLE WOULD
LIKE TO SEE SHOOT.
>> THAT ONE?
>> YEAH, THAT ONE.
THAT GUY COULD PLAY A
LITTLE BIT.
>> EVER SEEN ANYBODY
WITH A BETTER STROKE
FROM BEYOND THE ARC
THAN STEPH CURRY
>> YEAH, ONE GUY, I
WOULD SAY, AND HE IS
IN THE FIELD.
>> RAY ALLEN
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, WE
ARE SPLITTING HAIRS
HERE.
>> OH, MAN.
>> DON'T DISCOUNT
STEPH'S DAD.
DELL WAS PRETTY GOOD
FROM LONG RANGE, TOO.
>> HE REALLY WAS
IT'S JUST SO
EFFORTLESS FOR HIM
YOU KNOW
BY THE WAY, ALL
RIGHT --
>> YOU NOTICE ROMO IS
NOT DOING IT.
>> UH-OH
>> ALL RIGHT
LET'S HEAD BACK OUT
OVER TO THE 9th HOLE.
>> ROMO STAYING IN HIS
OWN LANE WITH THE
FOOTBALL IN HIS HAND.
>> GOOD IDEA.
>> JACK WAGNER NOW
OKAY
JACK WILL FINISH WITH
IT'S A GOOD NUMBER IN
THE CASINO AND HERE ON
THE GOLF COURSE.
JACK WAGNER A TWO-TIME
CHAMPION IN 2006 AND
PART OF THE
FESTIVITIES HERE IN
YEAR NUMBER 30
HE HAS TAKEN PLACE IN
ALL 30 OF THEM
WHAT A DAY HERE ON THE
LAKE
>>> ALL RIGHT.
SO BACK AT 17 NOW.
AS MUCH AS THEY COME
FOR THE GOLF, THERE
ARE A MORE THAN A FEW
INTERESTED PARTIES TO
SEE THAT
AND THAT'S FAMILIAR.
TIMBERLAKE.
>> SO YOU ARE SAYING
STEPH'S BETTER
THREE-POINT SHOOTER
THAN TIMBERLAKE?
>> REPLAY THAT
YOU KNOW, STEVE ASKED
BEFORE ABOUT WHO IS A
BETTER SHOOTER
THE FACT OF THE MATTER
HIS SHOOTING
PERCENTAGE FROM BEYOND
THE ARC IS 0.436 WHILE
RAY ALLEN'S WAS 0.400.
THIS KID IS WEARING A
CURRY JERSEY AND HAT
AND GETTING ADVICE
FROM STEPHON HOW TO
SHOOT.
THEN HE GETS NOT ONLY
TO SHOOT WITH STEPH
AND J.T., BUT HOW
ABOUT AN AUTOGRAPH
FROM BOTH OF THEM?
AND I WOULD SAY, AND
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
THIS A MOMENT AGO, YOU
HOPE HIS PARENTS HAVE
GOT THIS ON VIDEO
SOMEWHERE.
BUT YOU KNOW THAT
EVERYBODY HAS THIS ON
VIDEO.
WHAT A MOMENT.
BACK AT 16
THIS IS LARRY
FITZGERALD
THIS GUY'S BEEN
PLAYING GOLF FOR FIVE
YEARS.
AND HE IS A 6
HANDICAP, WHICH IS
CRAZY.
SPEAKING OF CRAZY, HOW
ABOUT THAT PUTT FROM
THE NFL GREAT
RECEIVER
JUST SUCH A TERRIFIC
ATHLETE.
YEAH, THAT IS A PRETTY
GOOD UP AND DOWN
MEANWHILE, BACK AT 17,
NOT MUCH HAS CHANGED
CURRY IS NOW MAKING
THEM SITTING DOWN.
OF COURSE HE IS.
WHAT'S NEXT?
BLINDFOLDED?
CAN YOU IMAGINE,
STEVE, PETER, WHAT
THAT HOUSEHOLD MUST
HAVE BEEN LIKE GROWING
UP
DELL CURRY, STEPH
CURRY, WHAT WERE THE
GAMES LIKE IN THAT
DRIVEWAY
>> THREE NBA PLAYERS,
A COLLEGIATE
VOLLEYBALL PLAYER WITH
A SISTER
JUST AN AMAZING
ATHLETIC FAMILY.
IMAGINE GETTING OUT IN
THE DRIVEWAY AT THE
CURRY HOUSE.
>> HOW ABOUT WATCHING
THE BLAZERS AND THE
WARRIORS PLAYOFF GAME
IN THE WESTERN
CONFERENCE
CHAMPIONSHIP, WATCHING
MOM AND DAD, ONE
WEARING A BLAZER
JERSEY, THE OTHER
WEARING A WARRIORS
JERSEY, PULLING FOR
SETH AND STEPH
IT'S CRAZY.
>> A TOUGH SPOT FOR
MOM AND DAD THERE.
>> HOW DO YOU FIGURE
THAT OUT
I THINK THEY FIGURED
IT PERFECTLY.
>> YEAH.
>> ROMO A LITTLE BIT
LONG
THAT'S A MISSED
OPPORTUNITY FOR HIM.
>> THAT'S ANOTHER
THING, JIMMY
THE CURRY FAMILY, THEY
DON'T MAKE MISTAKES.
THEY ARE AMAZING AT
EVERYTHING THEY DO
IT'S FANTASTIC
>> IT'S GREAT
PARENTING.
>> VERY NICE PEOPLE.
>> THEY REALLY ARE
SO KIND.
THEY ARE JUST GOOD,
GOOD PEOPLE.
IT'S GREAT.
>> ALWAYS SO GOOD WITH
THE FANS HERE, DELL
CURRY.
YOU KNOW, OVER THE
YEARS, HIS SON AS
WELL
WE TALK ABOUT THIS A
LOT.
SOME OF THESE GUYS,
PARTICULARLY TWO OF
THE GUYS IN THIS
CROWD, YOU CAN'T BE
MUCH OF A BIGGER
CELEBRITY THAN THESE
GUYS ARE
AND THEY DO A PRETTY
GOOD JOB OF HANDLING
IT
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
SHOT IF IT WILL STAY
MIGHT BE A LITTLE BIT
SPEEDY COMING DOWN THE
HILL
NO
BUT HE LIKES IT.
>> I THINK HE LIKED
IT
>> IS HE IMITATING
STEPH?
>> NOW STEPH
HE PLAYED HIGH SCHOOL
GOLF ALSO.
AND I THINK HIS DAD
WHO IS OUT THERE
WATCHING, THERE IS
DELL, PROBABLY WANTS
TO JUST TAKE A MEASURE
OF WHAT THIS BET IS
GOING TO BE LIKE AND
WHAT HE HAS IN FRONT
OF HIM
PROUD DAD.
>> WELL, STEPH PLAYED
IN TWO KORN FERRY
TOURNAMENTS, AND I
THINK HE HAD THE
BIGGEST GALLERY ON HIS
EXEMPTION, WHICH IS A
GOOD THING FOR THE
TOURNAMENTS.
IT RAISES THE
AWARENESS.
BRINGS LOCAL FLAVOR
OUT.
OH, HE NUTTED THAT
>> THAT'S LONG
GOING TO BE
DISAPPOINTED WITH
THAT
SPENT A GOOD DEAL OF
TIME HERE ON THE 17th
HOLE
ALL RIGHT.
SO A CROWDED DAY,
ANOTHER ONE HERE ON
THE PAR 3 17th ON A
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL
DAY IN LAKE TAHOE.
THE MARQUEE GROUP
HEADING TO THE GREEN
AT 17, AND WE WILL BE
RIGHT BACK TO CATCH UP
WITH THEM AFTER THIS
Ever since I was little,
I'd open the fridge and see a
world of possibilities.
Finding ways to bring
people together.
That's a revolutionary act.
This feeling of home is why I'm
launching shophomemade
with GoDaddy.
What's your idea?
Make the world you want.
>>> WHILE WE WERE
AWAY, THIS THE BUNKER
SHOT FROM STEPH CURRY.
A LITTLE FRISKY WITH
THE TEE SHOT
SO THAT LEFT FOR THE
PAR PUTT AND THE ONE
POINT FOR THE NBA
GREAT.
NOW TONY ROMO.
SECOND SHOT.
THE LEADER WITH 24
POINTS
THREE-POINT LEAD OVER
DEREK LOWE AND JACK
WAGNER
A PRETTY WAYWARD TEE
SHOT, PETER.
>> THAT'S ALL YOU ARE
THINKING ABOUT, IS
LAYING IT UP IN THE
THREE-FOOT CIRCLE.
DID A GOOD JOB OF
THAT.
>> YEAH, ALMOST DID
ONE BETTER THAN THAT.
>> ALMOST.
>> MEANWHILE, OVER TO
THE OTHER SIDE.
>> CHARLES BARKLEY
SEE THAT MINUS 9
THAT'S REALLY GOOD
HE HAS PLAYED VERY,
VERY WELL.
OH, WHAT A SHOT!
>> CHARLES.
>> WHAT A SHOT
SIR CHARLES.
>> AT THE 6th.
>> YEAH, HE COMING OFF
A PAR BACK AT 5 WHERE
HE PICKED UP A POINT.
>> CHARLES TRYING TO
RECORD HIS BEST EVER
SCORE HERE IN THIS
FORMAT
>> AND HE ALREADY MADE
A BIRDIE ON THIS
ROUND, TOO, SECOND
HOLE OF THE DAY.
>> FANTASTIC FOR HIM,
JIMMY.
>> YEAH, PETER AND
STEVE, THIS WAS JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE FOR BIRDIE.
LET'S SEE IF IT MAKES
IT ALL THE WAY
IT'S GOING TO COME UP
SHORT.
SO STILL LOOKING AT A
LITTLE BIT OF A SLIDER
AND THERE IS CURRY
NICELY DONE.
GOOD UP AND DOWN FROM
THE BUNKER AND BACK.
SO A POINT FOR STEPH
GETS TO 9 POINTS.
>> JIMMY, WHAT
IMPRESSES ME ABOUT
STEPH, WHEN HE IS
PUTTING HE STAYS WITH
THE PUTT NO MATTER
WHAT, WHETHER HE
MISSES IT OR MAKES IT.
HE STAYS WITH THE
STROKE
THERE IS NO ANXIETY.
HE DOESN'T JUMP OUT OF
IT
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU
KNOW, YOU MIGHT CALL
IT A YIP OR A JUMP OUT
OF IT.
I REALLY THINK HE HAS
A GREAT STROKE.
>> WELL, SHOULDN'T
SURPRISE ANYBODY THAT
THE GUY HAS SOME
TOUCH, RIGHT, PETER?
>> YEAH.
>> TIMBERLAKE FOR THE
PAR.
>> NOW, WE HAVE SEEN
THE SAME THING WITH
JUSTIN
HE STAYS IN THE
STROKE
SO WATCH THIS.
WATCH HIS HEAD
LET'S SEE IF HE STAYS
ALL THE WAY THROUGH
AND HOLDS HIS FINISH
WITHOUT MOVING HIS
BODY
WELL, HE LOOKED A
LITTLE BIT.
>> THAT'S GOOD SHOT
RIGHT THERE.
>> STUCK THAT IN.
>> A POINT FOR THE
GRAMMY WINNER.
SO HE GETS TO 10
AND JUST THE SLIGHTEST
MOVEMENT FROM
TIMBERLAKE SENDS THE
CROWD WILD
ISN'T THAT WHAT ROCK
STARS DO, OR POP
STARS, WHATEVER YOU
WANT TO CALL THEM?
TONY ROMO TO ADD TO
THE LEAD
24 POINTS.
CURRENTLY JUST THE ONE
IN FRONT OF DEREK
LOWE
MAKE IT TWO.
SO ROMO WITH 25
POINTS
THE TWO-SHOT LEAD OVER
DEREK LOWE AND FOUR
OVER JACK WAGNER
LET'S GO BACK OVER TO
6.
>> LET'S SEE IF SIR
CHARLES CAN DROP IN A
BOGEY PUTT
>> DOUBLE HIP
REPLACEMENT FOR THIS
GUY, STEVE
HE SAID HE GAINED 85
POUNDS BUT HE'S LOST
20 OF THEM.
>> TELL YOU WHAT
HE LOOKS GOOD.
HE LOOKS HEALTHIER
HE IS PLAYING BETTER
HE HAS A SHORT GAME
LIKE PHIL MICKELSON.
>> NOW, NOW, NOW
>> TELL YOU WHAT
CHARLES IS ONE OF THE
BIGGEST STARS IN THE
FIELD EVERY YEAR
BUT WHEN YOU ARE STEPH
CURRY OR JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE OR THE
DEFENDING CHAMPION
TONY ROMO YOU HAVE THE
MARQUEE TO YOURSELVES
THIS WEEK.
>>> AND BACK AT 17
HERE IS ANOTHER GUY SO
POPULAR HERE THROUGH
THE YEARS, JERRY RICE.
THE HALL OF FAMER.
AT THE PAR 3
TALK ABOUT PEOPLE WHO
LOVE THEIR GOLF.
>> WOW.
>> NOT A HITCH TO BE
SEEN FROM CHARLES,
HUH?
>> NO.
A LITTLE SHORT RIGHT,
BUT A GOOD MOTION.
NO HITCH
CHECK OUT THAT BUNKER
PLAY FROM CHARLES
COMING UP.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
>> IT'S CHARLIE AND
CHARLES.
>> CHARLES, YOU ARE
DISAPPOINTING THE
FANS
THEY LIKE TO WATCH YOU
STRUGGLE
HOW ABOUT CHARLES
BARKLEY PLAYING SOME
GOOD GOLF TODAY?
MAN, YOU ARE HAVING
SOME FUN
YOU WARMED UP GREAT.
I AM LOVING THAT YOU
BRING IT TO THE GOLF
COURSE
WHAT'S GOING GOOD FOR
YOU TODAY?
>> I PLAYED REALLY
WELL TODAY, AS WELL AS
I COULD PLAY
SHOUT OUT TO MY
TEACHER, STAN UTLEY.
HE HAS BEEN WORKING
WITH ME FOR A YEAR
I HAVE BEEN HUMILIATED
AND EMBARRASSED UP
HERE FOR THE LAST 25
YEARS.
IT'S GOOD TO PLAY GOOD
GOLF
I AM PLAYING VERY
WELL
GOT TO KEEP IT GOING
FOR THE WEEKEND.
>> WHAT IS THE BIGGEST
THING STAN HELPED YOU
OUT WITH
>> STAND TALL.
ONE OF THE REASONS I
HESITATE IS BECAUSE I
AM CRUNCHED OVER
HE WANTS ME TO STAND
TALL AND DON'T DUCK
DOWN BECAUSE MY HEAD
IS COMING DOWN FIVE
INCHES WHEN I SWING
NORMALLY
HE TALKED TO ME ABOUT
STANDING TALL AND THE
SECOND THING WAS
PROBABLY THE MOST
IMPORTANT.
RELEASE THE CLUB HEAD.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GREAT TO SEE
IT'S WORKING
YOUR CADDIE TOLD ME
WHATEVER I DO, DON'T
TELL YOU THAT YOU ARE
ON TRACK TO HAVE YOUR
BEST ROUND EVER HERE
TODAY.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU
LIKE TO TALK TRASH
I'M TALKING A LITTLE
TRASH.
YOU GOING TO FINISH
STRONG
>> I AM GOING TO
FINISH STRONG.
STAN UTLEY, THANK YOU.
>> APPRECIATE IT,
CHARLES.
>> GREAT TO SEE
>> YOU KNOW, SO MANY
PEOPLE THINK THAT HE
REALLY CAN'T PLAY.
HE WAS ONCE AN 8
HANDICAP, SHOT 78.
AND WE TAKE A LOOK AT
LARRY FITZGERALD WHO
HAD THAT BUFFALO PUTT
BEAUTIFUL PUTT ON THE
16th HOLE.
HOW ABOUT A BEAUTIFUL
TEE SHOT ON 17
ANYONE WITH A
HELICOPTER-HOLE $1
MILLION.
HALF GOES TO THE
GOLFER
THE OTHER TO THE
STOWERS INSTITUTE FOR
MEDICAL RESEARCH ON
BEHALF OF AMERICAN
CENTURY.
HERE IS A GUY WITH A
SMOOTH SWING
RAY ALLEN.
PETER, HOW ABOUT THAT
SWING, ESPECIALLY FOR
A GUY THAT BIG
>> IT'S SILKY.
IT'S SMOOTH.
AND IT'S PRETTY GOOD
>> HE IS A PLUS 1.
AND HE ONLY STARTED
PLAYING IN COLLEGE,
WHICH HAS GOT TO MAKE
ANYBODY WHO HAS
STRUGGLED WITH THIS
GAME OVER TIME JUST
CRAZY.
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY
FIRST ROUND OF THE
AMERICAN CENTURY
CHAMPIONSHIP
TONY ROMO IN THE LEAD.
RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
Come.
We're about to begin.
Yeah!
I'm a magic cat.
I love it.
And now for the
icing on the cake.
[ hiss ]
>>> ALL RIGHT.
18, STEPH CURRY.
TRYING TO CLOSE HIS
FIRST ROUND IN STYLE
PLAYING OUT OF TURN
BECAUSE THE LEADER,
TONY ROMO, DROVE IT
INTO TROUBLE ON THE
RIGHT SIDE INTO THE
TREES.
WE WILL GET TO THAT IN
A MINUTE.
>> DID YOU SEE THAT?
IT WAS JUST 116.
>> AMAZING.
>> ON HIS SECOND SHOT.
THAT IS A HUGE DRIVE.
>> POUNDED THAT ONE
OFF THE TEE.
WE GO BACK ONE TO 17.
>> AND BACK AT 17, WE
SAW THE BEAUTIFUL TEE
SHOT A MOMENT AGO FROM
LARRY FITZGERALD
CAN HE CAPITALIZE?
YES, HE DOES, BARELY
IN THE RIGHT SIDE OF
THE HOLE
SO THE BIRDIE FOR THE
GREAT RECEIVER
BACK OVER TO 18.
>> AND JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE'S THIRD
FROM JUST OFF THE
FAIRWAY.
>> KIND OF A DIFFICULT
ANGLE HERE TO THAT
FRONT LEFT HOLE
LOCATION
GOOD SHOT RIGHT THERE.
>> SOLID PLAY FROM
JUSTIN AND STEPH
NOW BACK AT 17.
>> AGAIN LIKEWISE WE
SAW THE BEAUTIFUL TEE
SHOT FROM RAY ALLEN.
OH
SO RAY ALLEN WITH A
MISSED OPPORTUNITY
THERE.
A DISAPPOINTING PAR
FOR THE NBA GREAT.
BACK OVER TO 18 ONCE
AGAIN NOW.
>> AND THE TREVAILSES
OF TONY ROMO AND
NOTAH.
>> HE FOUND HIMSELF
INSIDE THE PENALTY
AREA AND HE THOUGHT
THAT HE WAS GOING TO
GET RELIEF BECAUSE IF
HE WOULD HAVE TRIED TO
PLAY THE BALL WHERE IT
STOOD IN THE PENALTY
AREA HE WOULD HAVE
BEEN STANDING ON THE
CART PATH.
SO THAT RULING DID NOT
GO IN HIS FAVOR.
HE TO TAKE A ONE-SHOT
PENALTY.
OUT OF THE PENALTY
FIRST, THE BALL ENDED
UP ON THE CART PATH
AND HE TOOK RELIEF
FROM THE CART PATH
WHERE YOU SEE HIS BALL
NOW JUST ABOUT 110
YARDS INTO THIS HOLE.
>> DID YOU FOLLOW ALL
THAT
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> GOT IT.
>> WELL ARTICULATED.
>> HE'S GOT AN ANGLE
HERE
JUST NEEDS IT TO COVER
THESE BRANCHES
AND IT GETS OVER
SEE IF HE GETS IT
ONLINE
OKAY
IT'S FINE.
>> HAS A BIRDIE PUTT
>> YOU LOVE THE
CONFIDENCE FROM
ATHLETES LIKE THAT
YOU HEAR WHAT HE SAID?
IS IT OKAY IF I MAKE
THIS
>> A LITTLE BIT OF FUN
WITH THE FANS THERE.
ALONG THE LAKE
WHAT A VIEW.
WITH ALL THOSE PEOPLE
ALONG THE SHORE AND IN
THE WATER.
STEPH CURRY SO POPULAR
HERE WITH ALL AGES,
BUT THE KIDS
ESPECIALLY
THEY COME OUT, THEY
GET THEIR FIRST LOOK
AT THE GAME HERE THIS
WEEK AT THE AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
PERHAPS THEY WANT TO
TAKE UP THE SPORT
THEMSELVES BECAUSE THE
STARS LIKE STEPH IN
PERSON
>>> AND THE HALL OF
FAMER JOHN SMOLTZ FOR
BIRDIE
TENTH APPEARANCE HERE.
BEST FINISH TIED FOR
SECOND IN 2010
FIRST TIME WE HAVE
SEEN ANYBODY LEAVE THE
FLAGSTICK IN, JIMMY.
>> YEAH, HE SAYS HE
TRAVELED SO MUCH
LATELY, 28 OF THE LAST
30 DAYS.
HE SAYS I DON'T EVEN
THINK MY DOG REMEMBERS
ME AT THIS POINT
LOVES HIS GOLF
BACK OVER TO 18.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT TONY
ROMO CAN DO HERE AT
HIS LAST HOLE OF THE
DAY.
>> IN SPITE OF ALL THE
TROUBLE OFF THE TEE
AND THE PENALTY DROP,
STILL HAS A CHANCE AT
BIRDIE
NOT A HIGH PERCENTAGE
CHANCE, PETER, BUT
THIS IS ONE HE REALLY
WOULD LIKE TO GET
INSIDE THAT THREE-FOOT
CIRCLE, GET OUT OF
HERE WITH A PAR AND
LOOKS LIKE TAKE THE
FIRST ROUND LEAD.
>> THIS IS A TRICKY
PUTT
IT'S GOING TO GO
DOWNHILL, TURN TO HIS
RIGHT.
ONCE YOU GET PAST THAT
HOLE, IT'S JUST GOING
TO KEEP ON TRICKLING
SO THIS IS JUST A LAG
RIGHT HERE
OH
>> HE LIKED THAT ONE
FOR AN AWFULLY LONG
TIME.
>> PUTTING WELL FROM
LONG DISTANCE.
THOSE LAG PUTTS HAVE
BEEN CLOSE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
REMEMBER WHEN HE DID
PLAY THE 18 TEE BYRON
NELSON, HE GONE TO A
LONGER LENGTH
SPLIT-GRIP PUTTER.
DIDN'T HAVE MUCH
SUCCESS WITH IT.
I PLAYED MANY ROUNDS
WITH TONY AND KNOWN
HIM TO BE A VERY
ADEQUATE PUTTER.
HE TEKTSED HIM THE
NEXT WEEK AND SAID GET
RID OF THE LONG PUTTER
AND GET YOUR OLD
FAITHFUL BACK IF YOUR
HANDS.
>> NOTAH, WHAT'S IT
LIKE PLAYING WITH HIM
IN PRACTICE ROUNDS
HOW COMPETITIVE IS HE?
>> HE WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT THE BET IS WHEN
YOU STEP ON THE FIRST
TEE.
IT WAS ALWAYS USUALLY
IN HIS FAVOR
BUT IT GOT TO A POINT
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
PLAYING WITH HIM I HAD
TO GIVE HIM TWO, THREE
SHOTS A SIDE
THEN IT GOT TO THE
POINT WHERE WE WERE
PLAYING ALMOST EVEN,
MAYBE HALF A SHOT A
SIDE
SO HE IS VERY SKILLED
AND REALLY WORKED AT
HIS GAME AND IMPROVED.
>> SUCH A GOOD GUY
BUT WHEN HE GETS ON TO
THAT PLAYING SURFACE,
BOY, HE WANTS TO RIP
YOUR HEART OUT, WHICH
IS WHAT MAKES HIM SUCH
A GOOD COMPETITOR.
TIMBERLAKE NOW
>> JUST DIDN'T GET ANY
PUTTS TO FALL ON THIS
BACK SIDE.
>> NOTAH, IN MY
EXPERIENCE, THE
PRACTICE ROUNDS I
PLAYED WITH PHIL
MICKELSON, HE ALWAYS
WANTED TO HAVE
SOMETHING ON THE LINE
WHETHER IT WAS FIVE
BUCKS, WHETHER IT WAS
LUNCH.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN
ANYTHING
BUT PHIL WANTED TO
KNOW THE GAME BECAUSE
THAT JUST, IT GOT HIM
GOING.
AND THAT'S THE WAY
SOME PLAYERS APPROACH
EVERY ROUND THEY PLAY.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
THERE IS DIFFERENT
APPROACHES OUT HERE.
YOU HAVE THE GUYS THAT
LIKE TO BEAT BALLS AND
PRACTICE AND NOT SPEND
MUCH TIME ON THE GOLF
COURSE
BRYSON DeCHAMBEAU
MIGHT FALL IN THAT
CATEGORY
AND THEN GUYS WANT TO
PLAY, GUYS LIKE ROMO,
MICKELSON.
PUT A LITTLE BIT OF
MONEY.
>> LET'S SEE IF STEPH
CAN ALL OF A SUDDEN
GET TO 15 POINTS
>> THIS WOULD BE A
NICE WAY TO FINISH OFF
THE DAY.
>> GET THERE
YEAH
OKAY.
>> I'M IMPRESSED WITH
HIS PUTTING STROKE,
THE WAY HE GOES
THROUGH HIS ROUTINE.
THERE IS NO ANXIETY
WHEN HE HITS IT.
OF COURSE, YOU THINK
ABOUT THE WAY THAT HE
SHOOTS JUMP SHOTS.
THERE IS NO ANXIETY
THERE.
HE JUST COMPLETES THE
STROKE JUST LIKE HE
DOES WITH THE PUTTER.
>> THE ONLY ONE
UNHAPPY ABOUT THOSE
SIX POINTS IS HIS
FATHER DELL.
ALTHOUGH DELL HAS THE
FIVE-POINT LEAD OVER
HIS SON STEPH AFTER 18
HOLES.
>> THAT IS SOME KIND
OF EAGLE
>> NOW TONY ROMO, FIVE
BIRDIES ON THIS BACK
NINE
AND THAT FOR PAR AND
ONE POINT AFTER
DRIVING IT IN TROUBLE.
26 POINTS IS THE MARK
SET BY TONY ROMO
THE DEFENDING
CHAMPION.
>> HIS LAST THREE
ROUNDS AT THIS EVENT,
TODAY 26, AND THE LAST
TWO ROUNDS LAST YEAR
WHEN HE WON 26 AND 27.
SO WATCH ROMO THIS
WEEKEND.
>> TIMBERLAKE CLOSES
OUT.
26, 15, AND 11 FOR
THOSE THREE.
FOLLOWED BY THE
LARGEST GALLERY BY FAR
OF ANY GROUP
LOOK AT THOSE
SNOW-CAPPED MOUNTAINS.
JUST AN AMAZING SCENE
HERE ALONG THE SHORE
OF LAKE TAHOE.
AS WE LOOK AT STEPH'S
EAGLE PUTT
TO GO FROM 9 TO 15
WITH ONE STROKE.
LOOK AT THE REACTION
FROM STEPH
YEAH
CU
CURRY HE WILL TAKE AN
EAGLE AT THE 18th.
YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THE
LEADERS.
TONY ROMO IN A
FAMILIAR SPOT.
THAT'S WHERE HE ENDED
UP LAST YEAR ATOP THE
LEADERBOARD.
CAN HE MAKE IT BACK TO
BACK
OFF TO A FAST START
WITH 36 HOLES TO PLAY
HERE AT THE AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
IN YEAR NUMBER 30.
>>> IF YOU LIKE SEI
YOUNGS, PETER, THIS
WOULD BE YOUR GROUP.
TOM SMOLTZ
TOM GLAVINE.
>> THEY PLAYED A LOT
OF GOLF TOGETHER WHEN
THEY WERE WITH THE
ATLANTA BRAVES.
>> SEVEN CY YOUNGS
BETWEEN THIS GROUP,
GUYS
HOW ABOUT 9,062
STRIKEOUTS
>> NOT BAD.
>> HOW ABOUT 66 YEARS
IN THE BIG LEAGUES
>> NOT BAD
>> HOW ABOUT ALL THREE
OF THEM IN THE HALL OF
FAME
>> AMAZING.
>> AND MADDUX FOR A
WHILE CARRIED A
SCRATCH HANDICAP.
>> YOU TALKED ABOUT
THE THREE GUYS,
SMOLTZ, GLAVIN, MADDUX
WITH SEVEN CY YOUNGS
ROGER WOULD SAY I GOT
THAT
SABERHAGEN IN, HE LED
THE ROYALS TO THE
WORLD SERIES
CHAMPIONSHIP
SMOLTZ, BY THE WAY, AS
GREAT A STARTER HE
WAS, HE WAS A GREAT
RELIEVER THAT GOT HIM
INTO THE HALL OF FAME
AND MAYBE A BETTER
ANALYST.
HE IS SO GOOD ON TV,
EXPLAINING EVERYTHING
TO FANS ON FOX
LISTEN TO HIM COME
PLAYOFF TIME AND TELL
ME YOU HAVE EVER HEARD
A BETTER ANALYST ON
TELEVISION IN
BASEBALL
HE IS ABSOLUTELY GREAT
CALLING A GAME.
>> AND NOW PLAYING
QUITE A BIT OF GOLF ON
THE PGA TOUR
CHAMPIONS.
I SHOULDN'T SAY QUITE
A BIT OF GOLF.
HE PLAYED THREE OR
FOUR TOURNAMENTS OUT
THERE.
>> AND THERE IS TOM
GLAVINE, THE CRAFTY
LEFTY.
>> STEVE GLAVIN TOLD
ME THESE GUYS THINK
THEY MAY HAVE PLAYED
1,000 ROUNDS OF GOLF
TOGETHER.
>> SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
>> GOOD FRIENDS.
GREAT COMPETITORS.
AMAZING ATHLETES
CHARLES BARKLEY NOW AT
8.
>> WOW
HOW ABOUT THAT
>> AND THAT IS A
LITTLE BIT EARLIER
>> OKAY.
COME OFF THAT SLOPE.
>> SURE.
>> NOT MUCH SPIN
COMING OUT OF THE
ROUGH.
>> WHEN THE FORMAT OF
THIS EVENT CHANGED,
PETER, IN 2003, TO
WHAT IT IS CURRENTLY,
THE MODIFIED STAIBFORD
SCORING SYSTEM,
CHARLES BARKLEY IN
2011 IN THE THIRD
ROUND THAD MINUS 16
POINTS
HE HAS GUARANTEED
HIMSELF THE BEST ROUND
IN THIS FORMAT IN THIS
EVENT SINCE 2003.
>> THIS FOR BIRDIE.
>> TREMENDOUS TOUCH
FROM THE BIG MAN.
>> AND THAT'S GOING TO
BE FOR A PAR AND ONE
POINT.
IT'S NOT EVEN CLOSE
IT'S GOING TO BE HIS
REST ROUND IN THE
MODIFIED STABLEFORD
SCORING SYSTEM
GOOD FOR CHARLES
GOOD FOR STAN UTLEY,
AS WELL.
>> I HAVE WORKED WITH
STAN
I SENT HIM A TEXT AND
SAID DID YOU HEAR THAT
SIR CHARLES SENT YOU A
BIG THANK YOU AND A
SHOUT OUT?
>> LET'S SEE IF
CHARLES CAN WIGGLE
THIS PAR PUTT HOME
OH, WHAT A STROKE.
DROPS DOWN TO 10
MINUS 10 FOR CHARLES.
>> WITH ONE TO PLAY.
>> GOOD FOR HIM.
>> IT'S FANTASTIC.
NOW JAY DeMARCUS
INCREDIBLY TALENTED
VOCALIST, BASS
GUITARIST, PIANIST,
MEMBER OF RASCAL
FLATTS, AND HE IS A
GOOD PUTTER, TOO.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT?
HE WAS SO GREAT LAST
NIGHT.
HE AND JOE DON ROONEY
LEADING THE WAY FOR
RASCAL FLATTS DURING
CELEBRITY KARAOKE.
TONY ROMO DID NOT GET
ON STAGE LAST NIGHT
AND SING, BUT HE DID
PUT HIMSELF RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE MIX
AS HE IS THE LEADER BY
THREE POINTS AFTER DAY
ONE OF THIS AMERICAN
CENTURY CHAMPIONSHIP
AND WHAT A DAY IT WAS.
>> WELL, IT'S NO
SURPRISE TO SEE ROMO
ON TOP
HE GOT OFF TO A SLOW
START.
THE DEFENDING
CHAMPION
HE CAME BACK IN GREAT
FASHION.
BUT KEEP YOUR EYE ON
DEREK LOWE
HE WAS MY GUY
STARTING, AND I'M
GOING TO RIDE HIM ALL
THE WAY TO SUNDAY.
>> 23 POINTS
HE IS THREE POINTS
BEHIND TONY ROMO, BUT
TONY HAS THAT
DEFENDING CHAMPION
STATUS
SO HE KNOWS HOWTO
FINISH HERE AT
EDGEWOOD
DEREK LOWE, YOU NEVER
KNOW, HE HAS BEEN GOOD
ALL WEEK LONG.
HEREE IS AFTER THE
FIRST DAY, JUST THREE
POINTS BEHIND TONY
ROMO
FOR ALL OF THE HARD
WO