>> MISTAKEN ADDRESS.
D.C. LEADERS REACT TO NEWS OF
AN AMBULANCE BEING SENT TO THE
WRONG ADDRESS FOR THE SECOND
TIME IN THE LAST MONTH.
>>> EYES IN THE SKY OVER
BALTIMORE.
SURVEILLANCE PLANES MONITORING
TTHE CITY.
SOME ARE UPSET ABOUT THE
PROGRAM.
WE'LL EXPLAIN WHY.
IF YOU HAVE CHRISTMAS GIFTS TO
BUY.
WE HAVE THE STORES CATERING
THE TRUE PROCRASTINATORS.
FOX5 MORNING AT 7:00 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>> ♪
>> 7 O'CLOCK ON THIS MONDAY
MORNING.
GOOD MORNING.
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>> I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR.
APOLOGIZE IF YOU'RE ONE OF
THOSE PROCRASTINATORS.
I HATE TO CALL NAMES.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR PLAN.
OKAY.
IF YOU'RE WAKING UP THIS
MORNING, SPECIAL PEOPLE,
HERE'S A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
RIGHT NOW.
CAPITOL WHEEL.
>> GET A QUICK CHECK ON
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC FROM
TUCKER AND ERIN.
TUCK WE'LL START WITH YOU.
>> STEVE, A QUIET START TO OUR
DAY ALTHOUGH IT'S CHILLY.
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE
20'S AND LOW 30'S.
WE'LL BE IN FOR PARTLY SUNNY
AND MILDER CONDITIONS TODAY.
I'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS ON
TODAY'S FORECAST AND OUR
CHRISTMAS EVE CHRISTMAS DAY
FORECAST MOMENTARILY.
ERIN, GOOD MORNING.
>> MONDAY MORNING, 7: ZERO
ONE, BIG PROBLEMS IN MARYLAND.
95 NORTHBOUND CRASH BLOCKING
MULTIPLE LANES AT 100.
TRAFFIC GETTING BY BUT A HUGE
BACKUP.
A CLOSER LOOK AT THAT AND THE
REST OF YOUR COMMUTE AS WE
CONTINUE.
>> 7:01.
BREAKING NEWS OVERNIGHT.
ONE PERSON HAS LOST THEIR LIFE
AFTER A SINGLE CAR CRASH EARLY
THIS MORNING ON THE BW
PARKWAY.
THIS HAPPENED AROUND 1:00 A.M.
ALL LANES HAVE REOPENED ON THE
BW PARKWAY NEAR I-95.
PARK POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING
WHAT -- 195.
WHAT CAUSED THIS CRASH.
PARK POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING
>>> A WILD MORNING FOR A
WHAT CAUSED THIS CRASH.
PERSON IN ARLINGTON WHO ENDED
>>> A WILD MORNING FOR A
UP IN A BODY OF WATER IN
PERSON IN ARLINGTON WHO ENDED
CREEK.
UP IN A BODY OF WATER IN
POLICE SAY IT STARTED WITH A
CREEK.
SINGLE VEHICLE CRASH.
POLICE SAY IT STARTED WITH A
THEY SAY THE PERSON FLED THE
SINGLE VEHICLE CRASH.
SCENE OF THE ACCIDENT SOMEHOW
THEY SAY THE PERSON FLED THE
GOT STUCK IN 4-MILE CREEK.
SCENE OF THE ACCIDENT SOMEHOW
EVENTUALLY THE PERSON WAS
GOT STUCK IN 4-MILE CREEK.
RESCUED TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL
EVENTUALLY THE PERSON WAS
WITH NONLIFE-THREATENING
RESCUED TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL
INJURIES.
WITH NONLIFE-THREATENING
>> IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY, AN
INJURIES.
INVESTIGATION UNDER WAY INTO A
>> IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY, AN
MASSIVE HOUSE FIRE IN
INVESTIGATION UNDER WAY INTO A
POOLESVILLE.
MASSIVE HOUSE FIRE IN
THIS IS WHAT FIREFIGHTERS
POOLESVILLE.
ENCOUNTERED WHEN THEY GOT
THIS IS WHAT FIREFIGHTERS
THERE LAST NIGHT.
ENCOUNTERED WHEN THEY GOT
HEAVY FIRE AT A HOME ON BUD
THERE LAST NIGHT.
ROAD.
HEAVY FIRE AT A HOME ON BUD
THE HOMEOWNERS WERE NOT HOME
ROAD.
AT THE TIME OF THE FIRE WHICH
THE HOMEOWNERS WERE NOT HOME
CAUSED OVER $300,000 IN
AT THE TIME OF THE FIRE WHICH
DAMAGE.
CAUSED OVER $300,000 IN
FIRE INVESTIGATORS STILL
DAMAGE.
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT THE CAUSE
FIRE INVESTIGATORS STILL
BUT THEY SAY IT COULD HAVE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT THE CAUSE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH A WOOD
BUT THEY SAY IT COULD HAVE
STOVE.
SOMETHING TO DO WITH A WOOD
>> 7:02 RIGHT NOW.
STOVE.
AND DEVELOPING NEWS RIGHT NOW,
>> 7:02 RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE LEARNING NEW DETAILS
AND DEVELOPING NEWS RIGHT NOW,
ABOUT A 911 CALL THAT
WE'RE LEARNING NEW DETAILS
REPORTEDLY SENT FIREFIGHTERS
ABOUT A 911 CALL THAT
TO THE WRONG ADDRESS IN THE
REPORTEDLY SENT FIREFIGHTERS
DISTRICT ON SATURDAY.
TO THE WRONG ADDRESS IN THE
FOX5's AYESHA KAHN IS
DISTRICT ON SATURDAY.
FOLLOWING THIS STORY THIS
FOX5's AYESHA KAHN IS
MORNING AND JOINS US LIVE FROM
FOLLOWING THIS STORY THIS
NORTHWEST D.C. WHERE IT
MORNING AND JOINS US LIVE FROM
HAPPENED.
NORTHWEST D.C. WHERE IT
GOOD MORNING.
HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: HEY, THERE,
GOOD MORNING.
YEAH, THANKFULLY THE EMERGENCY
WASN'T AS SERIOUS.
WE'RE LEARNING SOMEBODY ON
SATURDAY MORNING WAS COOKING
HOT DOGS IN A POT.
WELL, THAT POT THEN BURNED AND
STARTED CREATING SMOKE IN THE
AREA BUT BECAUSE FIRE CREWS
WERE SENT TO THE WRONG
ADDRESS, IT TOOK THEM SIX
MINUTES TO GET THE CORRECT
ADDRESS HERE ON GIRARD STREET
IN NORTHWEST.
NOW, A PUBLIC SAFETY ADVOCATE
TELLS FOX5 THAT HE FLAGGED THE
ISSUE AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
THIS ALL MATTERS.
BECAUSE JUST LAST MONTH, THE
OFFICE OF UNIFIED
COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR KARIMA
HOLMES WAS FACING QUESTIONING
FROM D.C.'S COUNCIL MEMBERS
ABOUT THE FOUR MINUTE DELAY TO
AN AUGUST FIRE THAT ENDED IN
THE DEATHS OF A MAN AND A
NINE-YEAR-OLD BOY.
NOW, WHAT YOU ARE ABOUT TO
HEAR IS SOME OF THE AUDIO
DISPATCHED FROM SATURDAY
MORNING'S FIRE CALL FROM OPEN
MHZ THAT WAS FIRST OBTAINED BY
DAVE STATTER.
HE'S A PUBLIC SAFETY ADVOCATE
AND ALSO THE OWNER OF STATTER
911.COM.
>> ENGINE 26 TEXT
COMMUNICATIONS.
THIS HAS FIVE FLOORS IN THE
NOTES.
THERE'S NO STRUCTURE IN THIS
AREA THAT'S FIVE FLOORS.
WE HAVE THE WRONG HYDRANT.
>> Reporter: NOW, DAVE
STATTER WHO KEEPS TABS ON D.C.
FIRE ON HIS WEB SITE SAYS THAT
A LITTLE AFTER A 11:00 A.M. ON
SATURDAY, D.C. FIRE WAS
DISPATCHED TO 1432 GIRARD
STREET NORTHEAST WHEN IN FACT
THE CORRECT ADDRESS WAS 1432
GIRARD STREET NORTHWEST WHERE
WE ARE THIS MORNING.
NOW, THAT'S ABOUT 14 TO 15
MINUTES AWAY.
NOW, AFTER THE MISTAKE WAS
REALIZED A SPOKESPERSON FOR
OUC SAYS CREWS WERE DISPATCHED
ACCORDINGLY AND HERE AT THE
NORTHWEST BUILDING WE TALKED
WITH A FEW RESIDENTS LAST
NIGHT.
ONE OF THEM IS ACTUALLY THE
COUSIN OF THE WOMAN WHO LEFT
THE HOT DOGS COOKING ON THE
STOVE.
SHE ASKED THAT WE NOT SHOW HER
FACE.
>> MY AUNT DID ACTUALLY SAY
THAT SHE CALLED MULTIPLE TIMES
AND IT TOOK THEM FOREVER TO
COME.
>> Reporter: NOW, THE
SPOKESPERSON FOR OUC ALSO SAYS
THAT THE 911 DISPATCHER WHO
MISHANDLED THE CALL WILL BE
SPOKEN WITH AS THIS WILL BE
HANDLED AS AN INTERNAL
PERSONNEL MATTER.
BACK TO YOU.
>> AYESHA THANKS.
>>> AUTHORITIES INVESTIGATING
A MASSIVE PILEUP OVER THE
WEEKEND IN SOUTHERN VIRGINIA
ON I64 NEAR WILLIAMSBURG.
DOZENS OF PEOPLE HURT IN THIS
CHAIN REACTION CRASH.
51 PEOPLE WITH INJURIES
RANGING FROM MINOR TO
LIFE-THREATENING.
NO FATALITIES REPORTED THOUGH
BUT NEARLY 70 VEHICLES
INVOLVED.
BOTH SIDES OF THE HIGHWAY SHUT
DOWN FOR HOURS.
OFFICIALS STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT CAUSED THE CRASH BUT THEY
SAY WHETHER MAY HAVE PLAYED A
ROLE.
>> WE DO NOT KNOW THE CAUSE OF T
WE DO KNOW THAT FOG AND ICY
ROAD CONDITIONS WERE CAUSATIVE
FACTORS IN THIS MULTI-VEHICLE
CRASH.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN FAR WORSE
AND LUCKILY WE HAVE NO --
THERE'S NO CONFIRMED FATALS,
NO MAJOR INJURIES AT THIS
TIME.
>> AUTHORITIES SAY IT COULD
TAKE SEVERAL DAYS BEFORE THEY
WRAP UP THEIR INVESTIGATION.
>> ♪
>> ALL RIGHTY.
TUCKER BARNES BACK WITH US.
HEY, TUCK.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> YEAH, GOING TO SING A SONG,
"QUIET WEATHER."
IT DOESN'T GO LIKE STORMY
WEATHER.
>> YOU'RE MAKING UP SONGS.
>> DRY AROUND HERE.
NEXT COUPLE DAYS SANTA
COLUMNING OF COURSE TOMORROW
NIGHT AND WEDNESDAY LOOKS
GOOD.
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP IT DRY
RIGHT THROUGH THE END OF THE
WEEK.
STARTING A STRETCH OF 50'S,
YES, 50'S.
>> 50'S.
>> I'M 50 AND I CAN STRETCH.
ALLISON I CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT
THINKING OF IT.
REAGAN NATIONAL 31 THIS
MORNING.
20'S -- HEY LISTEN CHILLY OUT
THERE THIS MORNING.
DULLES IS 24, 27 BWI MARSHALL.
MOST OF US IN THE 20'S TO
START THE MORNING AS YOU'RE
KICKING OFF YOUR DAY HERE AND
WE'RE STARTING OFF WITH JUST
SOME HIGH CLOUDS OUT THERE,
KIND OF A PARTLY SUNNY START
FOR US.
NOTICE WE'VE GOT MORE CLOUD
COVER, THICKER CLOUD COVER TO
THE SOUTH.
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD STORM
SYSTEM DOWN ACROSS THE
CAROLINAS STRECHING DO UNTO
FLORIDA.
NOT A GREAT START DOWN THERE.
WE'LL LOOK AT THAT STORM IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES BUT FOR US&
A PARTLY SUNNY DAY TODAY AND A
MILDER DAY.
WE'LL START TO GET WARMER AIR
WORKING IN LATER THIS
AFTERNOON AND WE SHOULD SEE
DAYTIME HIGHS IN THE LOW TO
MID-50'S.
54.
WE'LL GO 54 THIS AFTERNOON SO
A MILDER DAY THAN YESTERDAY
AND A DRY DAY.
WINDS OUT OF THE SOUTH HERE AT
FIVE TO 10.
OKAY, PLENTY MORE ON YOUR
SEVEN-DAY FORECAST INCLUDING
CHRISTMAS EVE AND CHRISTMAS
DAY RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER.
ERIN HAS GOT YOUR ROADS.
GOOD MORNING.
>> 7:07 TUCK AND BIG PROBLEMS
IN MARYLAND ON 95 NORTHBOUND
OUTSIDE THE CAPITAL BELTWAY.
MULTIPLE LANES BLOCKED BY A
CRASH AT 100.
WE'RE SEEING SIGNIFICANT
SLOWDOWNS.
YOU CAN SEE YOU'RE PARKED IN
THE CAMERA BY MARYLAND 175.
I'D AVOID 95 NORTHBOUND.
TAKE BW PARKWAY.
IT'S ALL GREEN ALL GOOD RIGHT
THERE.
BIG BACKUPS THOUGH.
SKYFOX IS HEADING BACK TO BASE
SO WE'LL TAKE A LOOK.
395 LOOKS GOOD EDSALL ROAD TO
THE 14TH STREET BRIDGE.
CRASH ON GUNSTON IN LORTON.
7 EASTBOUND A CRASH.
SINGLE RIGHT LANE GETS BY AT
CASCADES PARKWAY.
66 EASTBOUND NORMAL VOLUME IN
MANASSAS.
OVERALL THOUGH NO MAJOR
DELAYS.
MANASSAS THROUGH THE BELTWAY
HEADING OUT ON THE WESTBOUND
SIDE MAYBE YOU'RE HEADED
TOWARDS THE PLANES YOU'RE IN
GOOD SHAPE THERE.
HOLLOWAY GETAWAY TRAFFIC IS
QUIET.
TO AND FROM DALE CITY, 95 WIDE
OPENED.
METRO IS ON TIME.
SO WE'LL TAKE THOSE VOLUME
CONDITIONS TODAY.
BACK TO YOU.
>> POLICE ARE SEARCHING FOR
THE PEOPLE RESPONSIBLE FOR A
MASS SHOOTING OUTSIDE OF A
HOOKAH LOUNGE IN BALTIMORE.
SEVEN PEOPLE WERE SHOT ON
SUNDAY MORNING, YESTERDAY
MORNING WHILE STANDING IN LINE
TO GET INSIDE.
POLICE ARE LOOKING FOR UP TO
FOUR SUSPECTS INCLUDING TWO
SHOOTERS.
ALL THE VICTIMS ARE EXPECTED
TO BE ALL RIGHT.
POLICE RECOVERED THE SUSPECT'S
CAR NEARBY.
THEY'RE NOW TRYING TO MATCH UP
WITNESS ACCOUNTS WITH
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO TO TRACK
DOWN THE PEOPLE RESPONSIBLE.
>> BALTIMORE STEPPING UP ITS
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION UNIT BY
USING SURVEILLANCE AIRPLANES
TO HELP LAW ENFORCEMENT FIGHT
VIOLENT CRIME PART OF A PILOT
PROGRAM WHICH WILL BEGIN NEXT
YEAR.
HOWEVER CIVIL LIBERTY GROUPS
SAY IT AFFECTS THE PRIVACY
RIGHTS OF PEOPLE IN THE CITY.
FOX'S GARRETT TENNEY HAS MORE
ON THE STORY.
>> Reporter: THESE CAMERAS
WILL CAPTURE ALMOST EVERYTHING
HAPPENING IN THE CITY, WHETHER
YOU'RE OUT WALKING YOUR DOG,
PICKING UP YOUR KID FROM
SCHOOL OR ROBBING A BANK.
THOSE IMAGES WILL BE RECORDED
AND SAVED FOR POLICE TO LOOK
THROUGH.
YOU CAN'T ACTUALLY MAKE OUT
ANYONE'S FACES THOUGH.
THE PLANES WILL BE FLYING
ROUGHLY 8,000 FEET IN THE AIR
SO PEOPLE LOOK BLURRY DOTS BUT
POLICE SAY THAT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH FOR THEM TO BE ABLE TO
TRACK THE MOVEMENTS OF A
PERSON OR A CAR AFTER A CRIME
HAS BEEN COMMITTED.
DURING THIS PILOT PROGRAM THE
CITY'S POLICE CHIEF SAYS THE
PLANES WON'T BE USED FOR LIVE
SURVEILLANCE AND WILL BE
LIMITED TO INVESTIGATING
SERIOUS CRIMES AFTER THE FACT
INCLUDING MURDERS, SHOOTINGS
AND ARMED ROBBERIES.
ON FRIDAY, CHIEF HARRISON SAID
HE WANTS TO BE AS TRANSPARENT
AS POSSIBLE WITH THIS PROGRAM
AFTER A SIMILAR ONE WAS SHUT
DOWN THREE YEARS AGO WHICH THE
PUBLIC DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT UNTIL
A REPORT BY BLOOMBERG REVEALED
THE SECRET MASS SURVEILLANCE
RECORDINGS.
>> I'VE DECIDED TO PROCEED
WITH THIS PROPOSED PILOT
PROGRAM BECAUSE IT COULD
REPRESENT YET ANOTHER TOOL IN
THE TOOLBOX TO SOLVE AND DETER
VIOLENT CRIMES IN OUR CITY.
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT WE ARE
TRANSPARENT ON HOW THE PROGRAM
WILL AND WILL NOT BE USED.
>> Reporter: THIS
ANNOUNCEMENT COMES AS
BALTIMORE IS WRAPPING UP ONE
OF ITS MOST VIOLENT YEARS ON
RECORD WITH MORE THAN 330
HOMICIDES AND MORE THAN 1300
ROBBERIES ACCORDING TO THE
BALTIMORE SUN.
THE ACLU ARGUES THIS IS AN
EXTREME VIOLATION OF THE
FOURTH AMENDMENT.
IT CREATES A VIDEO RECORD OF
EVERYWHERE EVERYONE GOES EVERY
TIME THEY WALK OUTSIDE.
IF THE POLICE DID THAT IN REAL
LIFE IN PERSON ON OUR STREETS
WE WOULD NEVER ACCEPT IT.
THE POLICE CHIEF SAID THIS
PILOT PROGRAM WILL LIKELY
START IN MAY WHEN VIOLENT
CRIME TYPICALLY STARTS TO PICK
UP IN THE CITY AND THEN AFTER
FOUR TO SIX MONTHS HE'LL
DECIDE HOW EFFECTIVE IT'S BEEN
AND WHETHER OR NOT TO KEEP IT
AROUND.
IN WASHINGTON, GARRETT TENNEY,
FOX NEWS.
>> ♪
>> 7:10 RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE FOLLOWING, ALLISON --
>> FOLLOWING BREAKING NEWS
RIGHT NOW, A SAUDI COURT HAS
DECIDED THE FATE OF THOSE
INVOLVED IN THE MURDER OF
"WASHINGTON POST" JOURNALIST
JAMAL KHASHOGGI.
FIVE PEOPLE WERE SENTENCED TO
DEATH IN SAUDI ARABIA FOR
KILLING KHASHOGGI LAST YEAR
INSIDE OF THE SAUDI CONSULATE
IN ISTANBUL.
THREE OTHER PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
SENTENCED TO PRISON.
KHASHOGGI WAS A KNOWN CRITIC
OF THE SAUDI GOVERNMENT.
>> UP NEXT, WIZARDS GUARD
ISAIAH THOMAS SUSPENDED FOR
DEMANDING RESPECT FROM A FAN.
>> AND GET READY FOR A LOT OF
COMPANY ON AREA ROADS
ESPECIALLY THE DAY AFTER
CHRISTMAS.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
>> WIZARDS GUARD ISAIAH THOMAS
WILL BEGIN SERVING A TWO GAME
SUSPENSION TONIGHT WHEN THE
TEAM TAKES ON THE KNICKS.
THOMAS WAS SUSPENDED FOR GOING
INTO THE STANDS TO CONFRONT A
FAN WHO CUSSED HIM OUT A
COUPLE TIMES.
SECURITY ESCORTED THOMAS BACK
DOWN TO THE COURT AFTER THE
FAN APOLOGIZED.
THE WIZARDS WENT ON TO LOSE
THE GAME 125 TO 108.
>> REDSKINS WRAP UP THEIR
SEASON IN DALLAS AGAINST THE
COWBOYS AFTER A LOSS TO THE
GIANTS AT HOME.
THE SKINS FOUGHT BACK MULTIPLE
TIMES TYING IT UP BEFORE
LOSING IN OVERTIME.
GIANTS WON THE TOSS THEY
SCORED THE TOUCHDOWN.
DWAYNE HASKINS HAD TO BE TAKEN
OFFEOFF THE FIELD IN THE THIRD
QUARTER.
WE'LL SEE IF HE PLAYS ON
SUNDAY.
>>> RAVENS WILL HEAD INTO THE
PLAYOFFS NUMBER ONE SEED.
THEY CLINCHED THE TOP SPOT AND
HOME FIELD ADVANTAGE
THROUGHOUT THE PLAYOFFS.
THE WIN OVER THE BROWNS
YESTERDAY.
LAMAR JACKSON ANOTHER HUGE
GAME, ANOTHER HUGE YEAR.
HIS JERSEY IS A HUGE SELLER.
RAVENS SAY THEY'RE SOLD OUT
RIGHT NOW SO IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO GET ONE FOR CHRISTMAS YOU
ARE OUT OF LUCK.
ONE PROGRAMMING NOTE BOTH THE
RAVENS AND REDSKINS GAMES
WHICH HAD BEEN AT 1 O'CLOCK ON
SUNDAY BOTH NOW MOVED TO A 4
4:25 P.M. KICKOFF.
BOTH GAMES ON AT 4:25.
THE REDSKINS RIGHT HERE ON
FOX5.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
TUCKER BARNES, WHO WILL YOU
ROOT FOR?  GOOD MORNING.
>> HERE'S MY TAKE ON THE
SKINS.
OTHER THAN THE HASKINS INJURY
YESTERDAY I THOUGHT THE SKINS
PLAYED A PERFECT GAME.
THEY PLAYED WITH A LOT OF
HEART.
THEY CAME BACK, DID THEY NOT?
>> EXCEPT FOR GIVING UP THE 41
POINTS THEY PLAYED A GREAT
GAME.
>> THEY'RE A FLAWED TEAM BUT
THEY'RE STILL GOING TO GET
THEIR DRAFT PICK NOW.
>> HASKINS HAD A NICE GAME.
YOU GOT SOME FLASHES OF HIS
TRUE POTENTIAL NOW.
>> YES.
>> YAY!
>> I LIKE IT, STEVE.
I SEE THE GLASS AS HALF FULL.
>> COME ON, KIDS.
>> YEAH.
GET ON BOARD .
>> [LAUGHTER]
>>> THEY'RE ON THE 20 YEAR
PLAN, STEVE.
31 IN WASHINGTON.
30 IN LEONARDTOWN.
LOOK AT MANASSAS, 22 DEGREES.
20'S NORTH TO NORTH.
CHILLY START TO YOUR DAY.
WINCHESTER 23 DEGREES.
CULPEPER 25.
CLOUDS AND SUN, THAT'S WHAT WE
CAN EXPECT TODAY, KIND OF A
MIX OF CLOUDS AND SUN.
WE'LL GO PARTLY SUNNY, HOW
ABOUT THAT?  WITH THE THICKER
CLOUD COVER TO OUR SOUTH THIS
MORNING.
THE REASON WHY, THERE'S AN
AREA OF LOW PRESSURE DOWN HERE
AND LOT -- THAT IS NOT A GREAT
WAY TO START OFF YOUR HOLIDAY
WEEK IF YOU'RE IN FLORIDA WITH
THE CLOUD COVER AND THE HEAVY
RAINS ON THE EASTERN PART OF
THE STATE OUT IN THE BAHAMAS.
THIS STORM IS GOING TO SIT
HERE AND DRIFT FOR THE NEXT 24
HOURS BUT THINGS WILL BE
GRADUALLY IMPROVING DOWN THERE
AS WELL AS WE GET CLOSER TO
CHRISTMAS DAY.
FOR US JUST CLOUD COVER.
A LITTLE MILDER THAN
YESTERDAY, 54 DEGREES.
CHRISTMAS EVE 50 DEGREES.
DAYTIME HIGHS ON CHRISTMAS DAY
40.
WE'LL NOT HAVE ANY WINTER
WEATHER OR SNOW ANY TIME SOON.
NEXT CHANCE OF RAIN MAYBE THE
END OF THE WEEKEND.
ERIN GOOD MORNING.
>> TUCKER BARNES 7:17 AND BIG
PROBLEMS ON THE ROAD RIGHT
NOW.
THIS COULD IMPACT YOU IF
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET TOWARD
THE PHILADELPHIA AREA TODAY OR
JUST TOWARDS BALTIMORE MAYBE.
95 NORTHBOUND MULTIPLE LANES
BLOCKED AT 100.
WE HAVE TRAFFIC GETTING BY BUT
A FEW MILES OF BACKED UP
TRAFFIC BY 175.
YOU CAN SEE HOW WE ARE AT A
CRAWL.
PRETTY NASTY OUT THERE.
BW PARKWAY A WIDE OPENED.
I'D ADVISE THAT TOWARDS THE
BWI AREA.
EDSALL ROAD TO THE 14TH STREET
BRIDGE QUIET IN TERMS OF
VOLUME.
I WOULD SAY FOR THIS MONDAY
MORNING SINCE IT IS A HOLIDAY
WEEK TRAFFIC IS LIGHTER THAN
USUAL.
FEW PROBLEM AREAS AND METRO
RAIL LINES ON TIME.
BACK TO YOU.
>> HAPPENING TODAY, PEOPLE
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND HERE IN
THE DMV ARE HEADING OUT OF
TOWN FOR THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
>> WITH JUST DAYS TO GO BEFORE
CHRISTMAS DAY, IT'S SURE TO BE
A BUSY ONE.
HOLLY IS HERE WITH MORE NOW.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, YEAH, THIS
REALLY ISN'T A NEWS FLASH
HERE.
IF YOUR LAST MINUTE TRIP IS
TODAY OR TOMORROW YOU NEED TO
GIVE YOURSELF PLENTY OF TIME.
AAA SAYS A RECORD NUMBER OF
AMERICANS ARE EXPECTED TO
TRAVEL THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
A RECORD 115 MILLION AMERICANS
ARE EXPECTED TO TRAVEL THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
THE HIGHEST TOTAL IN ALMOST 20
YEARS.
MOST OF THEM WILL DRIVE WITH
THE WORST TRAFFIC EXPECTED THE
DAY AFTER CHRISTMAS.
>> A LOT OF TRAFFIC AND A LOT
OF AGGRESSIVE TAXICAB DRIVERS.
>> Reporter: NEARLY
7 MILLION TRAVELERS ARE
EXPECTED TO FLY.
A 5 PERCENT INCREASE FROM LAST
YEAR AND THE MOST SINCE 2003.
>> GOING TO AIRPORTS MORE
STRESSFUL.
YOU'RE STUCK IN TRAFFIC AS YOU
GO.
THERE'S A BUNCH OF PEOPLE ALL
AROUND.
YOU CAN'T REALLY FIND A SPOT
TO SIT WHEN WAITING FOR YOUR
PLANE.
>> IT'S MORE EXPENSIVE AND A
LITTLE MORE INCONVENIENT BUT
YOU'RE GOING TO PLACES WHERE
YOU'RE EXCITED TO SEE PEOPLE
SO IT'S WORTH IT.
>> Reporter: AIRLINE
OFFICIALS RECOMMEND GETTING TO
THE AIRPORT AT LEAST TWO HOURS
AHEAD OF YOUR FLIGHT AND THE
T.S.A. SUGGESTS WAITING TO GET
WHERE YOU'RE GOING BEFORE
WRAPPING PRESENTS.
IF THEY NEED TO BE INSPECTED,
AGENTS WILL HAVE TO OPEN THEM
UP.
>> ANYTHING THAT YOU WANT TO
BRING THROUGH ANY OF THE
SECURITY CHECKPOINTS NEEDS TO
BE ABLE TO BE OPENED.
SO, MAYBE NOT PUT THAT
ELABORATE WRAPPING JOB ON YOUR
PRESENTS WHEN YOU'RE FLYING
OUT.
>> Reporter: NOTICE THOSE
MAKING HOLIDAY TREKS SAY IT'S
NOT ABOUT THE JOURNEY, IT'S
ABOUT THE THE DESTINATION.
>> IT'S A TIME TO UNWIND
RELAX.
>> CHRISTMAS FOR ME IS
SPENDING TIME WITH FAMILIES SO
GIFTS DON'T MATTER AS MUCH.
>> Reporter: BUT LET'S BE
HONEST, GIFTS CAN BE FUN, TOO.
>> MY BEAST X ULTRA ZORD
AMAZON EXCLUSIVE THE ZORDS
THAT COME ABPENNSYLVANIA OF APAE
ZORDS.
>> DO YOUR PARENTS PLAY THIS
WITH YOU.
>> NO.
>> Reporter: GOT TO LOVE
SOMEBODY THAT KNOWS WHAT THEY
WANT.
MOST POPULAR DESTINATION FOR
HOLIDAY TRAVELERS THIS YEAR
ACCORDING TO ADVANCED BOOKINGS
FROM AAA IT'S THE SUNNY SKIES
AND WARMER WEATHER IN ORLANDO,
FLORIDA.
ALLISON.
>> IT DOES SOUND PRETTY NICE.
>> NICE GETAWAY RIGHT ALTHOUGH
IT'S RAINING DOWN THERE NOW.
HOPEFULLY IT WILL CHANGE
BEFORE CHRISTMAS.
>> THANKS, HOLLY.
>>> WELL, LOOKING AT THINGS
BACK HERE IN OUR AREA, WAZE IS
WORKING TO KEEP YOU SAFE THIS
WINTER IN PARTNERSHIP WITH
VDOT THEY HAVE A FEATURE THAT
.VDOT CAN SEND OUT EMERGENCY
RESPONSE TEAMS TO DEAL WITH
DIFFICULT TRASH ISSUES CAUSED
BY WINTRY WEATHER CONDITIONS.
>> HISTORIC FLORIDA LANDMARK
SEVERELY DAMAGED AFTER THE
WEEKEND AFTER A BIG RIG
CRASHED INTO IT.
THIS WAS YESTERDAY MORNING
JUST SOUTH OF ORLANDO WHEN A
SEMI TRUCK DRIVER CRASHED INTO
THE DESERT INN.
THANKFULLY NOBODY WAS HURT.
THE INN BUILT BACK IN THE
1880S OVER THE YEARS THE
LANDMARK HAS BEEN A RESTAURANT
HOTEL GAS STATION DECLARED A
HISTORICAL BUILDING IN 1994.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT 1880S
FLORIDA THERE WAS NOT A LOT
AROUND THEN.
NOT A LOT THAT'S LEFT.
>> ♪
>> THAT'S COOL.
>>> 7:20.
COMING UP NATIONAL PARK
ENTHUSIASTS HAVE A NEW
LOCATION TO VISIT AND ALL THEY
HAVE TO DO IS HEAD OUT WEST.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALSO HAPPY HANUKKAH.
THE JEWISH HOLIDAY NOW UNDER
WAY WITH THE LIGHTING OF THE
NATIONAL MENORAH.
IT IS 7:21.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
I'm LáDeia, and there's
more to me than HIV.
There's my career...
my cause...
and creating my dream home.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO is for
adults who are starting
HIV-1 treatment and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines dolutegravir
or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2 medicines
in 1 pill
to help you reach and
then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day
with food
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if you're
allergic to any of its
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,
liver problems, and
liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash and
other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,
including hepatitis B or C.
Don't use DOVATO if you plan
to become pregnant
or during the first 12
weeks of pregnancy
since one of its ingredients may
harm your unborn baby.
Your doctor should do a
pregnancy test
before starting DOVATO.
Use effective birth control
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache,
diarrhea, nausea, trouble
sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment
with DOVATO is right
for you.
>> ♪
>> HANUKKAH OFFICIALLY UNDER
WAY BEGINNING AT SUNDOWN
YESTERDAY.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE GATHERED
ON THE ELLIPSE FOR THE
LIGHTING OF THE NATIONAL
HANUKKAH MEMORIAL THE MENORAH.
IT BEGAN IN 1979 WHEN JIMMY
CARTER LIT THE MENORAH.
IT COMMEMORATES THE
REDEDICATION OF THE SECOND
TEMPLE IN JERUSALEM.
>> IF YOU HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO VISIT D.C.'S OUTDOOR
HOLIDAY MARKET, TODAY IS YOUR
LAST CHANCE.
IT'S THE 15TH YEAR FOR THE
MARKET WHICH FEATURES SHOPPING
PERFORMANCES HOLIDAY TREATS.
IT'S LOCATED ON F STREET
NORTHWEST BETWEEN SEVENTH AND
NINTH.
THE DOWNTOWN MARKET WILL BE
OPENED TODAY FROM NOON UNTIL
8:00 P.M. SO PRETTY MUCH ALL
DAY.
D.C. CITY OFFICIALS SAY THE
MARKET WILL OPEN FOR BUSINESS
RAIN ARCHINE.
BUT NO RAIN TODAY, RIGHT,
TUCK.
GOOD DAY TO GO CHECK IT OUT.
>> JUST ALL SHINE.
>> GREAT DAY.
WE'LL HAVE CLOUDS THIS
AFTERNOON.
KIND OF A PARTLY SUNNY DAY BUT
IT WILL ACTUALLY BE ON THE
MILD SIDE OF THINGS.
TYPICAL HIGH IN THE MID 40'S.
LOW TO MID-50'S LATER TODAY.
THAT'S A LIVE SHOT.
THE SUN IS GETTING UP.
WITH IT A MIX OF BLUE SKY WITH
CLOUD COVER ACROSS THE AREA.
THERE IS A STRONG SYSTEM JUST
TO OUR SOUTH.
LOOK AT ALL THE CLOUD COVER AS
YOU GET SOUTH OF US SO THICKER
CLOUDS AS YOU HEAD DOWN
TOWARDS CHARLOTTESVILLE AND
RICHMOND THIS MORNING AND
AGAIN THERE'S THIS STRONG
STORM SYSTEM DOWN HERE TO OUR
SOUTH.
SO IF YOU'RE TRAVELING TODAY,
HITTING THE ROADS YOU'LL
ENCOUNTER SOME PRETTY GOOD
RAINS DOWN INTO THE CAROLINAS.
THERE ARE FLOOD WATCHES FOR
PARTS OF GEORGIA THIS MORNING.
RAIN DOWN INTO THE BEACHES IN
FLORIDA.
BUT FOR US, A PARTLY SUNNY AND
QUIET AFTERNOON.
54 DEGREES.
WE LOOK GOOD FOR CHRISTMAS EVE
AND CHRISTMAS DAY, RIGHT
AROUND 50 WITH PARTIAL
SUNSHINE.
WE'LL KEEP IT DRY THROUGH THE
END OF THE WEEK.
I TOLD SANTA I NEED A BRAND
NEW COMPUTER, I NEED A NEW
PHONE.
I NEED --
>> IT'S THE SEASON FOR
GRATITUDE AND WE'RE GRATEFUL
FOR YOU TUCKER AND YOU'RE
GRATEFUL FOR EVERYTHING YOU
HAVE AROUND YOU TOO HOW ABOUT
THAT.
>> PERFECT.
>> AND ALL THE THINGS YOU
ASKED SANTA.
IF YOU'RE TAKING THE CAPITAL
BELTWAY TOWARD BALTIMORE I
WOULD SAY HOSPITAL ON BW
PARKWAY.
THAT WILL... HOP ON BW
YOU DON'T WANT TO SIT IN MESS
PARKWAY.
THIS MORNING.
YOU DON'T WANT TO SIT IN MESS
395 LOOKS GOOD.
THIS MORNING.
FOURTEENTH STREET BRIDGE, KEY
395 LOOKS GOOD.
BRIDGE, AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE
FOURTEENTH STREET BRIDGE, KEY
QUIET.
BRIDGE, AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE
BELTWAY IS LOOKING GOOD.
QUIET.
GUNSTON DRIVE CLOSED.
BELTWAY IS LOOKING GOOD.
CRASH AT POHICK BAY DRIVE WITH
GUNSTON DRIVE CLOSED.
A DOWNED TREE.
CRASH AT POHICK BAY DRIVE WITH
SEVEN EASTBOUND CRASH WITH A
A DOWNED TREE.
SINGLE RIGHT LANE GETTING BYE
SEVEN EASTBOUND CRASH WITH A
CASCADES PARKWAY.
SINGLE RIGHT LANE GETTING BYE
VOLUME IS LIGHT ENOUGH IT'S
CASCADES PARKWAY.
NOT CAUSING A MAJOR IMPACT.
VOLUME IS LIGHT ENOUGH IT'S
66 IS WIDE OPENED 95 TO AND
NOT CAUSING A MAJOR IMPACT.
FROM DALE CITY LOOKING GOOD.
66 IS WIDE OPENED 95 TO AND
270 IS QUIET FROM FREDERICK
FROM DALE CITY LOOKING GOOD.
AND METRO IS ON TIME.
270 IS QUIET FROM FREDERICK
STEVE AND ALLISON.
AND METRO IS ON TIME.
>> ♪
STEVE AND ALLISON.
>> STILL TO COME THIS MORNING,
>> ♪
IMMIGRATION REMAINS A HOT
>> STILL TO COME THIS MORNING,
TOPIC IN THIS COUNTRY.
IMMIGRATION REMAINS A HOT
>> AND IN MARYLAND, ONE
TOPIC IN THIS COUNTRY.
LAWMAKER IS WORKING ON A BILL
>> AND IN MARYLAND, ONE
THAT WOULD BAN PRIVATELY RUN
LAWMAKER IS WORKING ON A BILL
IMMIGRANT DETENTION FACILITIES
THAT WOULD BAN PRIVATELY RUN
AND PHASE OUT THE STATE'S ROLE
IMMIGRANT DETENTION FACILITIES
IN IMMIGRATION DETENTION.
AND PHASE OUT THE STATE'S ROLE
DELEGATE VAUGHN STUART WILL
IN IMMIGRATION DETENTION.
JOIN US LIVE IN STUDIO TO TALK
DELEGATE VAUGHN STUART WILL
MORE ABOUT THIS WHEN WE
JOIN US LIVE IN STUDIO TO TALK
RETURN.
MORE ABOUT THIS WHEN WE
>> ♪
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
♪ CHESTNUTS ROASTING ON AN
OPEN FIRE ♪
>> WE HADN'T CHECKED IN WITH
THAT BEAUTIFUL TREE AT THE RIO
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS, AND STILL
SO GORGEOUS.
SHINING SO BRIGHTLY.
COMING UP ON 7:30 RIGHT NOW ON
THIS MONDAY MORNING.
>>> LET'S CHECK OUR TOP STORIES
NOW AT 7:30.
>>> U.S. PARK POLICE
INVESTIGATING A SERIOUS CAR
CRASH THAT UNFORTUNATELY KILLED
A WOMAN WHO WAS A PASSENGER IN
THAT CAR AND SENT THE DRIVER TO
THE HOSPITAL.
THIS HAPPENED OVERNIGHT.
POLICE SAY THE VEHICLE SLAMMED
INTO A TREE ON BW PARKWAY IN
LAUREL AROUND 1:00 THIS MORNING.
NOW WE'RE TOLD THE DRIVER, A M
MAN, WAS FLOWN TO THE HOSPITAL
IN SERIOUS BUT STABLE CONDITION.
>>> A DRIVER IS IN THE HOSPITAL
THIS MORNING AFTER CRASHING INTO
4-MILE CREEK IN ARLINGTON,
VIRGINIA.
ARLINGTON FIRE SAYS THE DRIVER
WAS INVOLVED IN A CRASH BEFORE
TAKING OFF AND DRIVING INTO THE
WATER.
THIS HALL LAPPED AT SOUTH 4-MILE
RUN IN -- SONG GLEBE ROAD BEFORE
4:00 A.M.
OFFICIALS SAY THE DRIVER WHO
CRASHED INTO THE CREEK IS
EXPECTED TO BE ALL RIGHT.
>>> A VIRGINIA SENATOR TRYING TO
CRACK DOWN ON DISTRACTED DRIVING
IN THE STATE.
SENATOR SCOTT SORI BELL WILL
INTRODUCE LEGISLATION TODAY THAT
WOULD BAN HAND-HELD PHONES WHILE
DRIVING IN THE COMMONWEALTH.
THE NEWS CONFERENCE HAPPENING
THIS AFTERNOON AT THE TRANSURBAN
OPERATION CENTER IN ALEXANDRIA.
THE LAWMAKER WILL CALL ON HIS
COLLEAGUES TO HELP PASS WHAT HE
SAYS IS LIVE-SAVING MEASURES.
>>> STEVE?
>> AL, THANKS VERY.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT HOW
MONTGOMERY COUNTY HAS HANDLED
IMMIGRATION RELATED ISSUES THIS
YEAR AND ONE OF THE LAWMAKERS
THERE LOOKING TO TAKE A BIG
STAND THAT WOULD IMPACT THE
ENTIRE STATE OF MARYLAND.
JOINING US NOW DELEGATE STEWART
TO TALK WHAT COULD COME OUT OF
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY WHEN IT
MEETS LATER JANUARY.
WHAT IS IT SPECIFICALLY YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR.
>> I'VE GOT A BILL FORT UPCOMING
LEGISLATIVE SESSION THAT WOULD
PHASE OUT MARYLAND'S ROLE IN ICE
DETENTION FACILITIES AND BAN NEW
FACILITIES IN THE STATE.
>> SO WHAT'S THE BIG REASON THAT
YOU HAVE SPECIFICALLY BEHIND
GETTING RID OF THE ONES THAT ARE
THERE NOW, THREE IN MARYLAND,
AND MAKING SURE NO MORE COME IN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WELL, TO ME IT'S AN ISSUE OF
WHAT ICE HAS BEEN PERPETRATING
ACROSS THIS COUNTRY.
NEWS REPORTS HAVE BEEN VERY
CLEAR.
YOU HAVE PEOPLE WHO'S MEDICAL
NEEDS ARE NOT BEING TAKEN CARE
OF, SLEEPING ON THE FLOOR,
LIGHTS ARE ON 24/7.
PEOPLE ARE BEING MISTREATED IN
THIS COUNTRY IN ICE DETENTION
TAFFLE THE WILLS, AND I'VE BEEN
HORRIFYING TIDE AT THE REPORTS.
AND SO MY VIEW IS PRETTY SIMPLE.
MARYLAND SHOULD NOT BE COMPLICIT
IN THIS DID HE BRASS HAVE THE.
MY CONSTITUENTS 45% OF THEM WERE
NOT BORN IN THIS COUNTRY, AND SO
THE FEWER DETENTION FACILITIES
WE HAVE THAT MEANS THE FEWER
BEDS WE HAVE AND THAT REDUCES
THE LIKELIHOOD THAT ONE OF MY
CONSTITUENTS WOULD BE DETAINED
FOR NO REALLY GOOD REASON, AND
LOCKED UP IN ONE THESE
FACILITIES WHERE, YOU KNOW, WHO
KNOWS WHAT THE HOW THEY'LL BE
TREAT.
>> NO FACILITIES IN MONTGOMERY
COUNTY.
WE HAVE THREE EXISTING IN
MARYLAND AND POSSIBILITY OF MORE
COMING IN.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THAT PEOPLE IN
THOSE AREAS RIGHT NOW WOULD BE
THRILLED WITH THIS NEWS AND
MIGHT BE SAYING, HEY, WHAT'S A
GUY FROM MONTGOMERY COUNTY DOING
SAY WHAT WE SHOULD BE DOING IN
OUR BACKYARD.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN THERE ARE THREE EXISTING
FACILITIES OWE EACH MAKE ABOUT
$100 PER IMMIGRANT PER NIGHT.
AND TO ME WHAT I WOULD SAY IS,
THOSE FACILITIES HAVE MY
CONSTITUENTS THERE.
SO AS LONG AS MY CONSTITUENTS
ARE BEING IMPACTED, I HAVE A SAY
AS MONTGOMERY COUNTY LEGIS
LEGISLATURE.
WE'RE NEARING CHRISTMAS TWO DAYS
AWAY.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE FAMILY
MEMBERS IN MY BACKYARD IN MY
NEIGHBORS IN PLACES LIKE ASPEN
HILL AND GLENN MON CONSULT
PUTTING UP STOCKINGS FOR FAMILY
MEMBERS WHO ARE BEING HELD IN
ICE DETENTION FACILITIES AND
THEY HAVE NO IDEA HOW THEY'RE
BEING TREATED OR HOW THEY'RE
MISTREATED.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE FOLKS COME
HOME, KIDS COME HOME TO THEIR
HOUSE THIS CHRISTMAS WEEK AND
THEY'RE GOING TO FIND THEIR
PARENT IS NO LONGER THERE
BECAUSE THEY WERE PICKED UP ON
SOME SORT OF BOGUS -- FOR SOME
SORT OF BOGUS REASON.
WHAT DONALD TRUMP HAS DONE HE'S
CHANGED THE IMMIGRATION POLICY.
HE'S THE NOT FIRST PRESIDENT TO
MISTREAT IMMIGRANTS BUT HE'S
ESCALATOR.
FOR ANY REASON HE'LL TRY TO FIND
IMMIGRANT UNDO YOU MEANED AND
PUT THEM IN ONE OF THEIR
FACILITIES.
>> YOU'VE BEEN PASSIONATE BEFORE
YOU GOT INVOLVED IN POLITICS
RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS MAY BE YOUR OPINION.
THIS MAY BE WHERE YOU ARE.
A LOT OF BILLS INTRODUCED THEY
DON'T GO ANYWHERE WITHOUT THE
SUPPORT.
>> OF COURSE.
YOU'RE STILL TRYING TO RALLY
SUPPORT IN THE SENATE IN
ANNAPOLIS.
HOW DO YOU SEE THINGS PLAYING
OUT RIGHT NOW AS FAR AS THAT
LEVEL OF SUPPORT?
>> WHEN THIS IDEA FIRST CAME TO
ME FROM THE IMMIGRATION
ADVOCATES I FIGURED THIS WOULD
BE A BILL I WOULD THROW OUT
THERE, IT WOULD RAISE ATTENTION
TO THIS ISSUE, RAISE ATTENTION
WHAT ICE IS DOING IN THIS
COUNTRY MAYBE IT WOULD FIZZLE
OUT.
HOWEVER I'VE HAD A LOT OF
CONVERSATIONS WITH MY COLLEAGUES
IN BOTH THE HOUSE AND THE SENATE
EVEN OH OVER THE PAST FEW DAYS
AND PAST FEW WEEKS THAT HAVE
GIVEN ME A LOT OF OPTIMISM THIS
BILL HAS LEGS AND I THINK IT
WILL PASS.
>> WE'VE ALREADY SEEN IN THE
LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS A LOT OF
BACK AND FORTH BETWEEN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY OFFICIALS AND
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT WHEN IT
COMES TO THIS.
HAVE YOU GOTTEN ANY BACKLASH
FROM THE FEDS?  HAVE YOU FELT
ANY PRESSURE?  HAVE YOU HAD ANY
CONTACT WITH THEM.
>> I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM THEM AT
ALL.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN WHAT'S
HAPPENING HERE AND MONTGOMERY
COUNTY THE FOLKS -- I'LL BE VERY
CLEAR.
THE FOLKS IN THESE DETENTION
FACILITIES IN MARYLAND AND
ACROSS THE COUNTRY BY AND LARGE
HAVE COMMITTED NO CRIME.
THEY'RE NOT VIOLENT.
THEY'RE NOT DANGEROUS MUCH THIS
NOT AN ISSUE OF US COOPERATING
WITH ICE TO MAKE SURE WEE DEPORT
PEOPLE WHO MURDERED OR RAPED
SOMEONE.
THESE ARE FOLKS I HAD A
CONSTITUENT IN MY DISTRICT WHO
WAS HELPING HIS UNCLE CUT A TREE
DOWN IN HIS YARD AND STATE
AGENCY OFFICIAL SHOWED UP, WROTE
HIM A TICKET FOR NOT HAVING A
TREE CUTTING LICENSE AND NOW
HE'S SPENT 100 DAYS IN THE
FREDERICK DETENTION FACILITY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHEN IS THE NEXT STEP GOING TO
HAPPEN IN ANNAPOLIS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LEGISLATURE SESSION STARTS
JANUARY 8th.
I'LL FILL THE BILL A COUPLE DAYS
AFTER THAT.
I'LL HAVE A FILE ALSO IN THE
SENATE AND HOPEFULLY WE'LL SEE
THIS BAD BOY PASS SOMETIMES THIS
LEGISLATIVE SESSION.
>> A LOT MORE ABOUT IT.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> 7:35.
LET'S GET OVER TO TUCKER WITH A
CHECK OF THE FORECAST.
>> STEVE, I LIKE THAT MARYLAND
FLAG BEHIND YOU.
LOOKING GOOD.
PARTLY SUNNY AND 50S LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
AND NICE MILD TREND AS WE GET
INTO CHRISTMAS EVE, CHRISTMAS
DAY.
KEEP IT QUIET AROUND HERE
WEATHER WISE NOTHING TO BE
TERRIBLY CONCERNED ABOUT ANY
TIME SOON.
31 TO START YOUR MORNING.
IT IS CHILLY ACROSS THE REGION.
MUCH OF THE AREA IN THE 20S OUT
THERE.
PITTSBURGH 28 DEGREES.
35 THIS MORNING IN RICHMOND
NOTICE THE CLOUD COVER THICKEST
TO OUR SOUTH EARLY THIS MORNING
AND YOU CAN SEE THE THICK CLOUD
COVER DOWN INTO PARTS OF
RICHMOND AND CHARLOTTESVILLE.
ALL ASSOCIATED WITH A STORM
SYSTEM BRINGING HEAVY RAINS TO
THE CAROLINAS TALK MORE ABOUT
THAT COMING UP THAT WILL BE THE
WORST OR OUR FORECAST PARTLY
SUNNY CONDITIONS AND MILD TEMPS
THIS AFTERNOON IN THE 50S.
ERIN.
>> 7:36 RIGHT NOW.
TUCK, WE ARE KEEPING OUR EYES ON
THE ROADS AND SKYFOX OVER SOME
BREAKING NEWS AN ACTIVE VEHICLE
FIRE SMOKE BILLOWING INTO THE
AIR THIS IS O'DELL ROAD IN BE
BELTSVILLE, MARYLAND.
WE'RE WORKING ON GATHERS DETAILS
BUT YOU CAN SEE THE FIRE
DEPARTMENT SEEMS TO HAVE GOTTEN
MOST OF THE FLAMES UNDER CONTROL
AT THIS POINT NO REPORT OF ANY
INJURIES.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW.
DOWNED POLE IN THE ROAD AS WELL
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE O'DELL ROAD
IN BELTSVILLE OPENING ANY TIME
SOON.
BIG DELAYS 95 NORTHBOUND CRASH
BLOCKING MULTIPLE LANES AT 100.
TRAFFIC GETS BY WITH DELAYS
HEAVY BACK TO THEME BACK TO YOU.
.
>> ARE WE FAMILIAR WITH SNOW
GLOBING?  APPARENTLY, IT'S THE
NEWEST DATING TREND THAT MAY
LEAVE YOU TAKING DOWN CHRISTMAS
LIGHTS ALONE.
>>> PLUS, THE BLAST FROM THE
PAST RIGHT HERE ISN'T RETURNING
IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
WHY MOTOROLA'S SCHEDULED REBOOT
OF ICONIC RAZOR FLIP PHONE HAS
TO BE PUSHED BACK AGAIN.
7:37.
♪
♪♪
I'm Jimmy Dean
and ah mother nature sure
doesn't cut any corners
when she paints a
morning like that.
And we know there is no
shortcut to quality.
And that's why we
use nothing but
the very best sausage
that money can buy.
Paint yourself a
beautiful morning.
>> SNOW GLOBING THE LATEST TREND
TAKING HOLIDAY SEASON BY STORM
ACCORDING TO COSMOPOLITAN THE
TERM RECEIVERS TO COUPLE WHO'S
APPEAR TO BE MORE INVOLVED THAN
THEY ACTUALLY ARE.
THE EFFECT WILL BE BROUGHT ON BY
ROMANTIC HOLIDAY THEMED OUTINGS
WHEN THE FESTIVITIES ARE OVER
AND THE MAGIC OF THE HOLIDAYS
ARE DONE THEY FADE AWAY.
SNOW GLOBING COUPLES CAN REALIZE
THEY WEREN'T AS INVESTED IN
THEIR PARTNERS AS THEY ONCE
THOUGHT.
PERHAPS IT WAS THE BRIGHT LIGHTS
OF THE HOLIDAY SEASON AND THE
RELATIONSHIP ENDS RIGHT AFTER
NEW YEAR'S.
WITH THAT HAPPY HOLIDAYS!
>> GOOD LUCK.
>>> THE FORCE IS WITH A GROUP OF
NEWBORNS AT A HOSPITAL IN
FLORIDA.
THEY'RE DRESSED AS STAR WARS
CHARACTERS TO CELEBRATE THE
RELEASE OF STAR WARS.
>> CUTE.
>> RISE OF SKYWALKER.
THAT IS SO PRECIOUS.
LOOK AT THE LITTLE ONES.
ALL RIGHT.
AMONG THE CHARACTERS, LUKE,
PRINCESS LEA, OF COURSE BABY
YODA AND BB8 IS IN THERE
SOMEWHERE.
>> HOSPITALS ARE START TO GO OUT
DO EACH OTHER.
>> LOOK AT THE TWO OF THEM.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> GOOD FOR THEM.
>> WELCOME TO THE WORLD LITTLE
ONES.
♪
>>> STILL TO COME THIS MORNING
DISTRICT TO THE NAUGHTY LIST ONE
OF THE PLACES TO AVOID IF YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR A NICE AND FRIENDLY
VISIT.
>>> IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>>> FIRST THOUGH LET'S CHECK OUT
MIKE THOMAS.
MIKE IS IN ALEXANDRIA.
HI, MIKE.
>>> YOU GOT THAT RIGHT, ALLISON.
GOOD MORNING.
HOLIDAY TRAVELS HAVE BROUGHT US
TO ALEXANDRIA NAMED RECENTLY ONE
OF OPRAH MAGAZINES TOP CHRISTMAS
DESTINATIONS MUCH IT'S GORGEOUS
HERE.
WE GOT THE ALEXANDRIA HARMONIZE
SORRIES HARMONIZING FOR US THIS
MORNING.
WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU ALL
ABOUT THE EVENTS COMING UP IN
ALEXANDRIA THIS HOLIDAY SEASON
COMING UP RIGHT AFTER THE BREAK.
PLEASE JOIN US.
STICK WITH US.
FOX5 MORNING NEWS AT 7:00 ROLLS
ON AFTER THE BREAK.
♪
>>> IN TODAY'S BUSINESS BEAT
MOAT ROLE LA RAZR REVIVAL
DELAYED AND THE STORE CATERING
TO ALL OF OUR LAST MINUTE
SHOPPER FRIENDS OUT THAT.
MYSELF INCLUDED.
JOINING US FROM THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK STUDIO TRACEE CARRASCO.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> SO, YOU KNOW, I MEAN IT'S
JUST BUSINESS, AND MAYBE I HATE
WHEN IT WE CALL PEOPLE
PROCRASTINATORS NASTY LITTLE
LABEL.
PEOPLE YOU KNOW SOMETIMES WAIT
OR THINGS GET IN THE WAY.
SO FOR ALL OF US, THERE ARE
STORES OPEN.
>> YES.
I AM INCLUDED IN THAT
PROCRASTINATOR WHATEVER GROUP IT
IS, I STILL HAVE CHRISTMAS GIFTS
TO BUY.
BUT ACCORDING TO THE NATIONAL
RETAIL FEDERATION, 6% OF
AMERICANS ARE GOING TO WAIT
UNTIL TOMORROW CHRISTMAS EVE TO
BUY THEIR FINAL GIFTS.
THANKFULLY THERE ARE A NUMBER OF
RETAILERS CATERING TO THOSE WHO
WAIT UNTIL THE LAST MINUTE.
I THINK THE MVP MIGHT BE KOHL'S.
THEY ARE OPEN FOR 24 HOURS.
THEY HAVE BEEN OPEN FOR 24 HOURS
SINCE FRIDAY.
SO YOU CAN GO AND FINISH UP YOUR
SHOPPING AT ANY HOUR.
BUT, YES, A NUMBER OF OTHER
RETAILERS ARE GOING TO BE OPEN.
TARGET OPEN TOMORROW UNTIL 10:00
P.M. AS WELL AS K MART, PLACE
SEE'S APPLE, BED, BATH AND
BEYOND, BEST BUY, COSTCO, CVS
MOST OF THEM OPEN 24 HOURS AND
OPEN ON CHRISTMAS DAY WALGREENS
MANY OF THE BIG DEPARTMENT
STORES ARE GOING TO BE OPEN A
LOT OF THEM OPEN THROUGH
DINNERTIME.
SO YOU MIGHT WANT TO CHECK THE
SPECIFIC WEB WEBSITS OR GIVE THA
CALL.
IF THERE'S A STORE THAT YOU
REALLY WANT TO GO TO, BUT A LOT
OF THEM OPEN THROUGH DINNERTIME
TOMORROW SO YOU CAN GET ALL
THOSE GIFTS AND THEN HEAD OUT TO
YOUR FAMILY FESTIVITIES.
>> GIFT IN HAND.
ALL RIGHT.
>> YES.
>> LET'S END WITH WHAT YOU WON'T
HAVE THE MOTOROLA RAZR PHONE.
>> YES.
THIS WAS ANNOUNCED BACK IN
NOVEMBER TO ROTOR ROLL LAB WOULD
BE COMING OUTWEIGH REBOOT OF ITS
RAZR PHONE.
YOU REMEMBER THAT ONE REALLY
POPULAR BACK IN THE EARLY
2,000S.
THEY SAID THEY WOULD BE COMING
OUT WITH IT.
IT WAS GOING TO BE $1,500.
WELL, PRE-ORDERS WERE EXPECTED
TO START ON DECEMBER 26th WITH
THE DELIVER RECEIVE THESE PHONES
EXPECTED SOMETIME IN JANUARY.
HOWEVER, BECAUSE OF THE DEMAND,
IT HAS OUT PACED THE SUPPLY THAT
THEY'VE REALLY STARTED PLANNING
FOR.
THEY SAY THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO PUSH THAT DATE BACK.
SO YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO PLACE THAT PRE-ORDER ON
DECEMBER 26th.
YOU'RE LIKELY GOING TO GET THAT
PHONE A LITTLE LATER THAN
PREVIOUSLY EXPECTED.
BUT THIS IS GOOD NEWS.
BECAUSE MORE PEOPLE WANT THE
PHONE THAN THEY WERE EXPECTING.
THEY THIS ISN'T A TECHNICAL
ISSUE LIKE WE SAW WITH THE
SAMSUNG THE FOLDABLE PHONE THEY
CAME OUT WITH JUST A LITTLE BIT
AGO.
THEY HAD TECHNICAL ISSUES WITH
THAT AND THAT IS WHAT DELAYED
THAT PHONE LAUNCH.
SO WE WILL SEE HOW MANY PEOPLE
ACTUALLY PRE-ORDER THIS RAZR
PHONE.
I'M VERY CURIOUS TO SEE WHO WILL
SPEND $1,500 FOR A FLIP PHONE.
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL WAIT AND SEE.
TRACEE HAVE A GREAT DAY.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> THANKS, BYE-BYE.
>> OKAY.
BYE.
>>> TUCKER THOSE PHONES WERE
COOL.
THE RAZRS.
>> I REMEMBER THEM.
>> RAZR.
NO O.
>> OH, YEAH.
I WAS WATCHING A MOVIE IN THE
'80 AS COUPLE DAYS AGO.
>> YEAH.
>> TECHNOLOGY HAS COME SO FAR
WHERE WE WERE AT WHEN WE WERE
GROWING UP.
SPEAKING OF THE '80S,
PRACTICALLY HAVE TO GET BACK TO
FIND THE LAST TIME WE HIT SNOW
ON CHRISTMAS DAY.
LAST FLAKES FALLING 2010.
LOOK AT THAT LAST MEASURABLE
SNOW 2002.
RECORD SNOWFALL BACK IN 1962.
WE HAD 5.4 INCHES.
IT WILL NOT BE A WHITE CHRISTMAS
THIS YEAR AS WE'RE JUST GOING TO
BE TOO HIELD.
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE THE DAYTIME
HIGHS WE'LL BE IN THE 50INGS
AROUND HERE THE NEXT SEVERAL
AFTERNOONS.
31 TO START YOUR MORNING IT IS
CHILLY EARLY THIS MORNING.
22 IN MANASSAS.
DULOS 24.
30 IN LEONARDTOWN AND ANNAPOLIS.
PLENTY COLD ENOUGH YOU WANT THE
COAT WHEN YOU HEAD OUT THIS
MORNING.
DAYTIME HIGHS WILL TOP OUT IN
THE MIDDLE 50S.
PARTIAL SUNSHINE OUT THERE.
CLOUDS THICK TO OUR SOUTH.
THE REASON WHY A STORM SYSTEM TO
OUR SOUTH.
BRINGING RAIN TO PLACES THAT
REALLY DON'T WANT IT THIS TIME
OF YEAR AS WE'RE KICKING OFF THE
HOLIDAY WEEK.
A LOT OF RAIN ON THE EASTERN
SIDE OF FLORIDA THERE DOWN AT
THE BEACHES ALL THE WAY DOWN TO
MIAMI THIS MORNING IT'S RAINING
AND VERY HEAVY RAINS INTO PARTS
OF THE CAROLINAS.
MUCH OF GEORGIA UNDER A FLASH
FLOOD WATCH.
THIS STORM SYSTEM IS GOING TO
SIT HERE AND SPIN FOR THE NEXT
24 HOURS.
EVENTUALLY GETTING PUSHED OUT TO
SEA.
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE DEFINITELY
A WET 24 HOURS IF YOU'RE HEADED
SOUTH LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
FOR US DRY CONDITIONS.
50S AROUND YESTERDAY WE WERE IN
THE 40S LITTLE MILDER THAN
YESTERDAY LOW TO MID 50S
EXPECTED LATER THIS AFTERNOON
AND THERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY
FORECAST.
NOTICE HOW QUIET WE KEEP IT FOR
THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS.
50 TOMORROW.
CHRISTMAS EVE LOOKS GREAT.
SANTA WILL I PROMISE HAVE ON
TIME DELIVERY FOR YOU EARLY
WEDNESDAY MORNING.
CHRISTMAS DAY LOOKS GREAT.
NICE AND MILD AROUND HERE FOR
THE END OF THE WEEK.
MAYBE SOME RAIN BY NEXT SUNDAY.
SUNDAY.
>> YOU SOUND LIKE -- IS THAT A
COMMERCIAL FROM SOMETHING.
>> NO, THAT'S JUST -- I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET TO BREAKING TRAFFIC
NEWS.
O'DELL ROAD AT ELLINGTON DRIVE
IN MARYLAND IN BELTSVILLE
PARTICULARLY EARLIER VEHICLE
FIRE STILL OUT THERE BLOCKING
BOTH DIRECTIONS.
YOU HAVE TO DETOUR AROUND IT
THERE'S A DOWNED POLE AS WELL.
THEY CONTAINED THE FLAMES AND
THE SMOKE SO THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
NO WORD ON INJURIES YET.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
AS WE MAKE OUR WAY GUN SON DRIVE
CLOSED.
DETOUR AROUND THAT ONE.
THEY'RE WORKING ON GETTING THAT
CLEARED OUT OF THE WAY.
UNDER INVESTIGATION.
395 NICE AND QUIET TO THE 14th
STREET BRIDGE.
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE MORNINGS
BECAUSE IT IS THE MONDAY
CHRISTMAS WEEK WE ARE SEEING
VERY LIGHT VOLUME AROUND THE
DMV.
IF YOU HAVE TO WORK TODAY YOU
WON'T RUN INTO ANY SLOW DOWNS
THROUGH MANASSAS, GAINSVILLE,
CENTREVILLE LOOKING GOOD IN
FAIRFAX.
THE BELTWAY ITSELF IS VERY
PLEASANT IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY AND 952 AND FROM DALE
CITYWIDE OPEN.
270 LET'S JUST TAKE A MOMENT TO
ENJOY THAT.
WIDE OPEN FLOWING FRIEHLLY FROM
FREDERICK DOWN THROUGH URBANA AS
YOU GET INTO THE ROCKVILLE TO
THE SPLIT.
METRO RAIL LINES ALSO ON TIME.
HOW ABOUT THAT, GUYS?  BACK TO
YOU.
>>> DISTRICT MAY HAVE PRISS
TEACH AND POWER AND GREAT PEOPLE
IN IT, BUT NEW SURVEY FOUND D.C.
DOESN'T HAVE A LOT OF MANNERS,
TOO.
BUSINESS INSIDER SURVEY RANK THE
CITY AS THE THIRD RUDEST IN THE
COUNTRY.
SOME BLAME IT POLITICS.
95% OF ALL RESPONDENTS RATED
D.C.
NEW YORK AND LOS ANGELES TOP THE
SURVEY WE'RE IN GOOD COMPANY.
LOOK AT THE TOP FIVE CITIES.
>> I SUPPOSE SO.
>> THERE'S A NEW NATIONAL PARK
TO ADD TO YOUR BUCK LIST.
WHITE SANDS NATIONAL MONUMENT IN
NEW MEXICO UPGRADED TO NATIONAL
PARK STATUS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SIGNING THE ACT
ON FRIDAY MAKE THE OFFICIAL
CHANGE.
WHITE SANDS 275 SQUARE MILES OF
DESERT SAND DUNES.
WITH THE WORLD'S LARGEST
COLLECTION OF ICE AGE FOSSIL
ARRIVED FOOTPRINTS.
THE ADDITION WHITE SANDS BRINGS
THE TOTAL NUMBER OF NATIONAL
PARKS UP TO 62.
>>> 7:50.
LET'S LOOK AT THE GOOD DAY GUEST
LIST.
TODAY WE'LL HEAR FROM STAR WARS
ACTOR LEGENDARY ACTOR BILLY DEE
WILLIAMS.
KEVIN SAT DOWN WITH WILLIAMS TO
DISCUSS THE CONCLUSION OF THE
TRILOGY.
WE'RE HAVING A LITTLE FUN WITH
TOYS IN THE LOFT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A REP FROM
THE TOY INSIDER, NOT ONLY WILL
WE LEARN ABOUT SOME OF THE
HOTTEST TOYS FOR CHRISTMAS, BUT
WE'RE GOING TO COMPETE TO SEE
WHO CAN UNBOX, CHANGE THE
BATTERIES AND STUFF STOCKINGS
THE FASTEST.
AND IF YOU'RE CRAVING SOME
COMFORT FOOD WE'VE GOT YOU
COVERED THIS MORNING.
WE'RE MAKING SHRIMP JUMP BA LAY
YA LIVE IN THE LOFT.
CHEF JOHN BEHIND NECK KEY FISH
BY JOSE ANDRES SHOWS US HOW TO
MAKE THIS DISH.
WE'LL GET A PEEK AT THEIR NEW
YEAR'S EVE MENU.
>> SOUNDS DELICIOUS.
UM-HMM.
>> COUNTDOWN TO CHRISTMAS
WINDING DOWN NOW AND SO IS OUR
HOLIDAY TOUR OF HOW YOU
CELEBRATE THE SPECTACULAR SE
SEASON.
>> TODAY THE FESTIVITIES
CONTINUE IN PLACE THAT'S CALLED
MAGICAL, ROMANTIC AND PERFECT
PLACE TORE A CHRISTMAS MOVIE.
SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
ALEXANDRIA, AND THAT'S WHERE WE
FIND OUR MIKE THOMAS THIS
MORNING.
GOOD MORNING, MIKE.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
ALLISON.
TO BE SHARE ANYWHERE I HAPPENING
TO IS MAGICAL AND ROMANTIC.
THAT'S KIND OF THE THEME.
GOOD MORNING EVERYBODY.
WE'VE BEEN ALL OVER THE DMV OVER
THE PAST FEW WEEKS.
CHECKING OUT ALL THAT THE
HOLIDAYS HAVE TO OFFER IN OUR
AREA.
AND NOW WE HAVE ARRIVED AT OLD
TOWN ALEXANDRIA RECENTLY NAMED
ONE OF THE BEST OLD CHRISTMAS
VILLAGES TO VISIT HERE.
WE'RE RIGHT DOWN IN MARKET
SQUARE AND HERE TO TILLS ALL
ABOUT IT CLAIRE, WITH VISIT
ALEXANDRIA.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> SO ACCOLADES KEEP ON ROLLING
IN, RIGHT?  TELL US ABOUT THIS
OPRAH MAGAZINE.
>> YES, NAMED ONE OF THE MOST
MAGICAL CHRISTMAS TOWNS ACROSS
THE WORLD AND IT'S OBVIOUS.
COME TO OLD TOWN DURING THE
HOLIDAYS IT'S LIKE BEING IN A
REAL LIFE DICK KINS VILLAGE.
YOU CAN STROLL DOWN THE KING
STREET MILE UNDER A CAN NAPPY OF
TWINKLING LIGHTS, FOR COZY
RESTAURANTS, INDEPENDENT ABOUT
COOKS, TUCKED INTO ONE EIGHTH
CENTURY ARCHITECTURE.
>> SO MUCH TO SEE.
SEGMENT DRIVING IN THE SUN IS UP
NOW SO IT'S NOT IN QUITE THE
BRILLIANCE THAT IT WAS WHEN I
DROVE IN.
EVERYTHING IS LIT UP.
WREATHS ON EVERY BUILDING IT
LOOKS ABSOLUTELY GORGEOUS AND
CHRISTMAS SEE.
SO MANY EVENTS GOING ON AS WE
APPROACH THE CHRISTMAS HOLIDAY.
>> YES.
>> ONE THAT I'M RATHER INTRIGUED
BY I'VE ALWAYS WONDERED WHAT
DOES SANTA TO GET HIMSELF READY
TO DELIVER GIFTS.
TURNS OUT DOES HE A LITTLE BIT
OF WATER SKIING, AM I RIGHT?
>> YES, STILL TIME TO COME TO
ALEXANDRIA ON CHRISTMAS EVE AT
1:00 O'CLOCK.
IT'S THE 34th ANNUAL WATER
SKIING SANTA SHOW ON THE POTOMAC
RIVER.
>> THAT'S DIFFERENT.
I MEAN SO IT'S RIGHT DOWN HERE
WHERE THE FOLKS GO TO SEE THAT
HAPPEN?
>> YES.
TWO OF OUR OTHER BIGGEST EVENTS
OF THE SEASON THAT ARE EARLIER
IN THE MONTH SCOTTISH CHRISTMAS
WALK PARADE AND HOLIDAY BOAT
PARADE OF LIGHTS.
YOU CAN TAKE PART IN WATER
SKIING ALEX LEXAN AT A, FIRST NT
ALEXANDRIA IS COMING UP AS WELL.
>> THEY'RE DOING A LOT IN MOUNT
VERNON TO CELEBRATE THE HOLIDAY.
>> CHRISTMAS PAST MEETS
CHRISTMAS PRESENT AT GEORGE
WASHINGTON'S MOUNT VERNON OVER
AND DAVE INCLUDING CHRISTMAS AND
NEW YEAR'S DAY.
THEY HAVE HOLIDAY PROGRAMS AND
TOURS EVERY DAY.
>> AS WE HEAR THE CAROLERS I
CAN'T HELP BUT THINKING OF
WINTER WONDERLAND.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY IMMERSE
YOURSELF IN A WINTER WONDERLAND
HERE IN ALEXANDRIA WHICH HAS TO
DO WITH THIS FIGURE BEHIND US.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> TILLS ABOUT THIS AND THE
WINTER WONDERLAND.
>> WE HAVE ICE AND LIGHTS AT
CAMERON RUN A WINTER VILLAGE.
BEAUTIFULLY LITTLE PHOTO OPS
LIKE THE STAR YOU SEE HERE AS
WELL AS ICE SKATING, HOT
CHOCOLATE, SHOPPING AND LOTS OF
OTHER FUN.
>> TO WRAP THINGS UP WE'VE
GOTTEN BEYOND CHRISTMAS NOW.
THE FUN DOESN'T STOP.
WE HAVE ACTIVITIES FOR THE NEW
YEAR AS WELL.
TELL US ABOUT THAT.
>> CELEBRATING 25 YEARS THIS
FIRST NIGHT ALEXANDRIA WHICH HAS
LIVE MUSIC AND MORE IN 25 INDOOR
VENUES SO YOU CAN BE NICE AND
WARM AS WELL AS KIDS CARNIVALS,
DANCE PARTY ON THE WATERFRONT
AND FIREWORK AT MIDNIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO MUCH TO DO.
CLAIRE, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> REAL QUICK BEFORE WE GO I GOT
TO SAY HI TO JOE.
YOU ARE THE DIRECTOR OF THE
ALEXANDRIA HARMONIZERS BEHIND
US.
>> I AM.
>> TELL US ABOUT THE GROUP.
>> THE GROUP IS ABOUT -- IT'S
ACTUALLY ABOUT 100 MAN GROUP
THAT'S BEEN HERE IN ALEXANDRIA
FOR 72 YEARS.
>> OH, WOW THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
>> YES.
>> CONCERTS ALL YEAR LONG.
WE JUST WENT TO THE UK LAST Y
YEAR.
WE SANCTITY HE HAD DIN BUREAU
FRINGE FESTIVAL WE PERFORMED
FORT CELEBRATION OF D TODAY.
NORMANDY FRANCE.
WE PERFORM ALL OVER THE WORLD.
>> THAT IS ABSOLUTELY
INCREDIBLE.
>> REALLY HAPPY TO SHARE OUR
HARMONY HERE IN LEX.
>> CAN FOLKS CATCH US BEFORE
CHRISTMAS.
>> YOU CAN'T ACTUALLILY THIS IS
THE LAST OPPORTUNITY.
WE HAD OUR SHOW THIS PAST
WEEKEND.
BUT WE'RE HERE REHEARSING EVERY
TUESDAY HERE IN ALEXANDRIA.
>> AWESOME.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU TO THE GROUP FOR
COMING OUT THIS MORNING.
GUYS, SO MUCH MORE TO TALK ABOUT
COMING UP WITH OUR HOLIDAY
SERIES HERE IN ALEXANDRIA.
WE'LL SEE YOU IN THE
8:00 O'CLOCK HOUR FOR MORE FUN
AND MORE HOLIDAY MAGIC.
BACK OFF TO YOU.
>> LOVE IT, MIKE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE ONLY THING WE DON'T HAVE
TUCKER IS THE WEATHER TO GO
ALONG WITH THE SEASON MUCH IT'S
GOING TO BE PRETTY MILD THIS
WEEK.
>> BUT WE'RE OFF TO COLD START
CERTAINLY FEELING LIKE THE
HOLIDAYS EARLY THIS MORNING.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE, YOU KNOW,
WE'RE NOT TALKING IN ORDER
TEMPERATURES HERE.
IT'S JUST GOING TO BE ON THE
MILD OF THINGS THE NEXT COUPLE
OF DAYS.
32 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
THAT'S A LIVE SHOT BEHIND ME
HERE.
YOU CAN SEE WE'VE GOT KIND OF
PARTLY TO MOSTLY CLOUDY
CONDITIONS AT THE MOMENT.
THAT WILL BE THE THEME TODAY.
I THINK WE'LL GET SOME SUNSHINE
THIS AFTERNOON PARTICULARLY LOTS
OF CLOUDS ASSOCIATED WAY PRETTY
GOOD STORM SYSTEM JUST TO OUR
SOUTH BRINGING HEAVY RAINS INTO
THE CAROLINAS.
LOOK AT THAT ALL THE WAY DOWN TO
FLORIDA.
BOY THAT IS NOT BEACH WEATHER
LATER TODAY.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR FLORIDA.
MORE ON THAT COMING UP.
FOR US A QUIET WEEK AND A
RELATIVELY MILD WEEK.
STEVE IS RIGHT NO WINTER WEATHER
ON THAT SEVEN DAY FORECAST.
IN FACT NEXT CHANCE FOR RAIN
SUNDAY.
HI.
>> SURFING SANTA.
>> I MEAN YEAH I GUESS.
>> I MEAN IT'S NOT THAT WARM BUT
YOU NEVER KNOW.
RIGHT NOW CLAIRE RAH BARTON
CRASH SOUTHBOUND AT CHAIN
BRIDGE.
SLOW DOWNS THERE BE PREPARED.
95 NORTHBOUND CRASH TWO RIGHT
LANES BLOCK AT 100 CARLOS IS
WATCHING WANTS TO POP THAT
SYSTEM LIVE THERE WE GO.
YOU CAN SEE IN THE CAMERA TWO
LEFT LANES GETTING BUY
SIGNIFICANT DELAYS BACK TO 32.
BW PARKWAY DEALING WITH BAILOUT
TRAFFIC.
CAUTION.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>>> KEEP IT RIGHT HERE TO FOX5
MORNING.
SO MUCH MORE AHEAD IN OUR 8:00
A.M. HOUR.
>> WITH A MAP IN HAND AND A APP
ON HIS PHONE ONE LOCAL TEACHER
IS TAKING THE CONCEPT OF A JOG
THROUGH THE CITY WHOLE NEW
LEVEL.
HE PLANS TO RUN EVERY ROAD AND
EVERY ALLEY IN THE DISTRICT.
>> WOW.
>> WE'LL FIND OUT HOW MUCH THAT
ADDS UP TO COMING UP.
>> OKAY.
♪
KAY.
Did you know Comcast Business
goes beyond fast with
a Gig-speed network,
complete Internet reliability,
cloud-based security.
That's huge.
Advanced voice solutions,
WiFi to keep everyone connected,
video monitoring.
Wow.
Business TV,
cloud apps and support.
I need that.
It's everything a small
business owner needs.
Save over $200 a month
on Internet and Voice
with our new business packages
starting at $99.99.
Call 1-800-501-6000.
Is skincare from around the
world better than Olay?
To find out, Olay faced the
world.
We tested our vitamin B3 formula
and beat Japan's top
moisturizers.
And even the $400 French cream.
Olay Regenerist faced
131 premium products
from 12 countries, Over 10
years.
Olay's hydration was unbeaten
every time.
Olay. Face anything.
Want a light as air feel? Try
Olay Whips.
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
♪
>>> OOH, STEVE, IT'S ALMOST H
HERE.
8:00 A.M. ON MONDAY MORNING AND
THE COUNTDOWN TO CHRISTMAS
MORNING JUST TWO DAYS AWAY.
DECEMBER 23rd AFTER ALL.
>> GETTING THERE.
ADDING TO THE HOLIDAY SPIRIT
TODAY THE FIRST FULL DAY OF
HANUKKAH WHICH MEANS THE 8-DAY
FESTIVAL OF LIGHTS IS OFFICIALLY
UNDERWA.
>> MORE GOOD NEWS MOTHER NATURE
SEEMS TO BE IN THE HOLIDAY
SPIRIT AS WELL.
TEMPERATURES WILL BE IN THE 50S
ALL WEEK LONG.
>> LET'S GET RIGHT TO TUCK
CONCERN ERIN FOR OUR FIRST CHECK
ON WEATHER AND TRAFFIC.
TUCK, WE'LL START WITH YOU.
>> 50S LATER TODAY, ALLISON, 20
AND LOW 30S RIGHT NOW.
TAKE YOUR COAT AS YOU HEAD OUT
THIS MORNING.
CHILLY START TO THE DAY BUT A
NICE MILD FINISH EXP EXPECTED.
DETAILS ON THAT WEATHER COMING
UP ERIN.
>> 8:00 O'CLOCK STRAIGHT UP.
CRASH ON NEW HAMPSHIRE AVENUE.
JUST THE CENTER LANE GETTING BY
AT RUPERT ROAD.
ICY CONDITIONS REPORTED.
TAKE IT SLOW OUT THERE.
WE'LL TAKE A FULL LOOK AROUND
THE DMV NEXT.
>> HEADLINES 8:00 O'CLOCK.
BREAKING OVERNIGHT COURT IN
SAUDI ARABIA SENTENCED FIVE
PEOPLE TO DEATH FOR THE MURDER
OF WASHINGTON POST REPORTER JEW
MAL KHASHOGGI.
HE MURDERED IN THE SAUDI LAST
YEAR BY A TEAM OF SAUDI AGENTS.
SAUDI MEDIA REPORTS THREE OTHERS
WERE SENTENCED TO PRISON TIME.
THE CROWN PRINCE DREW
INTERNATIONAL CONDEMNATION FOR
THE KILLING.
SEVERAL AUDI AGENTS INVOLVED
WORKED DIRECTLY FOR HIM BUT THE
CROWN PRINCE HAS DENIED ANY
INVOLVEMENT.
>>> ALSO, BREAKING OVERNIGHT A
WILD SCENE IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
A PERSON HAD TO BE RESCUED FROM
A CREEK AFTER THAT PERSON WAS
INVOLVED IN A SINGLE VEHICLE
CRASH AND THEN LEFT THE SCENE OF
THE ACCIDENT AND DROVE INTO THE
CREEK.
FIRST RESPONDERS HAD TO PULL
THAT DRIVER OUT OF THE WATER.
THEY WERE EXPECTED TO BE ALL
RIGHT.
NO WORD ON IF ANY CHARGES WILL
BE FILED.
>>> AND IN MARYLAND, U.S. PARK
POLICE INVESTIGATING A SERIOUS
CRASH THAT KILLED A WOMAN WHO
WAS A PASSENGER IN A CAR AND
SENT THE DRIVER TO THE HOSPITAL
OVERNIGHT.
POLICE SAY THE VEHICLE SLAMMED
INTO A TREE ON THE BW PARKWAY IN
LAUREL AROUND 1:00 THIS MORNING.
WE'RE TOLD THAT DRIVER A MAN WAS
SLOAN TO THE HOSPITAL IN SERIOUS
BUT TABLE CONDITION.
>>> AND ICY ROADS AND FOG MAY
HAVE LED TO THIS MASSIVE PILEUP
THAT HAPPENED OVER THE WEEKEND
NEAR WILLIAMSBURG, VIRGINIA,
ALONG INTERSTATE 64.
69 VEHICLES WERE INVOLVED AND 51
PEOPLE WERE HURT INCLUDING SOME
WITH SERIOUS INJURIES.
POLICE SHUT DOWN BOTH SIDES OF
THE HIGHWAY FOR HOURS.
>> MORE TROUBLE ON THE ROADS AS
WELL AT LEAST WITH EMERGENCY
SERVICES WE'RE GETTING NEW
DETAILS ABOUT A 911 CALL THAT
REPORTEDLY SENT FIREFIGHTERS TO
THE WRONG ADDRESS OVER THE
WEEKEND IN THE DISTRICT.
NOW THE OUT COME WASN'T BAD BUT
THERE ARE CERTAINLY A LOT OF
WHAT IFS BEING ASKED.
AYESHA KAHN LIVE THIS MORNING IN
COLUMBIA LIGHTS WITH THE LATEST
FOR US.&
>> AYESHA.
>> GOOD MORNING.
LIKE YOU SAID FORTUNATELY THIS
WAS NOT SERIOUS EMERGENCY.
HOWEVER, WE ARE FINDING OUT THAT
ON SATURDAY MORNING SOMEONE IN
THE BUILDING WHERE THE SMOKE
HAPPENED WAS COOKING ACTUALLY
HOTDOGS IN A POT.
THAT POT BURNED AND IT CREATED
SMOKE IN THAT IMMEDIATE AREA.
BUT THEN WHEN DISPATCHERS SENT
THE CREWS TO THE WRONG ADDRESS,
THEY FINALLY GOT THE RIGHT
ADDRESS IT TOOK THEM SIX MINUTES
TO GET TO GIRARD STREET HERE IN
NORTHWEST.
NOW THE PUBLIC SAFETY ADVOCATE
WHO FLAG THIS ISSUE TELLS FOX5
THIS ALL MATTERS BECAUSE LAST
MONTH THE OFFICE OF UNIFIED
COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR FACED
QUESTIONING FROM D.C.'S COUNCIL
MEMBERS ABOUT THE FOUR MINUTE
DELAY TO AUGUST FIRE THAT ENDED
IN THE DEATH OF A MAN AND A
NINE-YEAR-OLD BOY.
NOW WHAT YOU'RE ABOUT TO LISTEN
TO IS SOME OF THE AUDIO
DISPATCHED FROM SATURDAY
MORNING'S FIRE CALL FROM OPEN
MHZ OBTAINED BY DAVE SAD CARD.
THE OWN ARE IN OF STODDARD
911.COM.
>> ENGINE 26 TO COMMUNICATIONS.
IT SAYS 54 IN THE NOTES.
THERE'S NO STRUCTURE IN THIS
AREA THAT'S FIVE FLOORS.
>> DAVE WHO KEEPS TABS ON DC
FIRE AND EMS ON HIS WEBSITE SAYS
THAT A LITTLE AFTER 11AM ON
SATURDAY D.C. FIRE WAS
DISPATCHED TO 1432 GIRARD STREET
NORTHEAST WHEN IN FACT THE
CORRECT ADDRESS WAS 1432 GIRARD
STREET NORTHWEST WHICH IS ABOUT
14 TO 15 MINUTES AWAY.
NOW, AFTER THE MISTAKE WAS
REALIZED, SPOKESPERSON FOR OUC
SAYS THAT CREWS WERE DISPATCHED
ACCORDINGLY.
NOW HERE AT THE NORTHWEST
BUILDING WE TALKED TO A FEW
RESIDENTS.
ONE OF THEM IS THE COUSIN OF THE
WOMAN WHO LEFT THE DOGS COOKING
ON THE STOVE.
SHE ASKED WE NOT SHOW HER FACE.
>> MY AUNT SAID SHE CALLED
MULTIPLE TIMES AND IT TOOK THEM
FOREVER TO COME.
>> Reporter: THE SPOKESPERSON
FOR OUC SAYS THAT THE 911
DISPATCHER WHO MISHANDLED THE
CALL WILL BE ADDRESSED AS AN
INTERNAL PERSONAL MATTER.
BACK TO YOU.
>> AYESHA, THANKS.
IT COULD BE ANOTHER COUPLE OF
WEEKS BEFORE THE IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS MOVES FORMER PELOSI IS
WAITING TO HAND OVER ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT TO THE SENATE.
DEMOCRATS ISSUED NEW DEMANDS FOR
MITCH MCCONNELL TO CALL
WITNESSES.
THE PRESIDENT REFUSED TO PROVIDE
FOR THE HOUSE INVESTIGATION.
WHILE HOUSE DEMOCRATS SAY
THEY'RE CONFIDENT THE SENATE
WILL BEGIN THE TRIAL SOMETIME IN
JANUARY.
>>> ALL RIGHTY.
COMING UP ON 8:05.
FIRST CHECK OF WEATHER IN THE
8:00 A.M.
>> I HAVE MIXED EMOTIONS ABOUT
THE WEATHER.
HERE'S WHY.
I'D LOVE TO HAVE WINTER WIDER
SNOW FALLING OUT THERE
BECAUSE --
>> WHITE CHRISTMAS.
TOLLLY GET IT.
>> I UNDERSTAND A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE TRAVELING.
THIS IS NOT THE PERFECT TIME TO
DO IT.
>> RIGHT.
>> EITHER WAY IT WILL BE MILD
MUCH WE'RE NOT LOOKING AT ANY
WINTER WEATHER ANY TIME SOON.
>> WE'LL TAKE IT.
>> GOING TO GRANDMA'S HOUSE
COMING HOME IT WILL BE QUIET FOR
THE NEXT WEEK.
>> PERFECT.
THANK YOU.
>> STARTIN T STRETCH IN THE
50S STARTING LATER THIS
AFTERNOON, AND WE'LL KEEP THE
STREAK GOING RIGHT INTO NEXT
WEEKEND.
IS COL T SRT YOUR MORNING
HERE MDAYORNG.
32 AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
20S DULLES.
25 DEGREES.
28 AT BWI MARSHALL.
SATELLITE/RADAR VERY QUIET WITH
THE EXCEPTION OF CLOUD COVER AND
PARTICULARLY THICK AS YOU GET TO
THE SOUTH.
SO LOWER EASTERN SHORE, CENTRAL
VIRGINIA, SOUTHERN MARYLAND, YOU
GUYS HAVE THE MOST OF THAT
CLOUDINESS.
THE REASON WHY, THAT IS NOT A
GREAT WAY TO START OUT YOUR
HOLIDAY WEEK.
IT'S RAINING DOWN IN THE
CAROLINAS DOWN INTO FLORIDA
EARLY THIS MORNING.
BIGGER STORM SYSTEM DOWN THERE.
IT WILL NOT GET ANY FURTHER
NORTH.
HIGH PRESSURE BLOCKING IT.
SO FOR US THAT MEANS JUST SOME
CLOUDS TODAY.
OTHERWISE A DRY AND MILDER
AFTERNOON.
YESTERDAY 40S.
TODAY 54 DEGREES.
SO ENJOY A NICE AFTERNOON.
PERFECT FOR GOING OUT SHOPPING.
WHICH WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I'M A 6% ER.
>> YOU ARE?
>> YEAH.
>> IN WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
6% OF PEOPLE HAVEN'T STARTED
SHOPPING YET.
THAT'S ME.
>> IS THAT THAT LOW.
>> I'M SURPRISED.
>> YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU TUCKER.
I'M AMONG YOU.
>> OKAY G.
>> I'LL SEE YOU OUT THERE.
>> I'LL BE SHOPPING TOO.
I THOUGHT I WAS DONE BUT THEN I
FORGOT SOME EXTRA ITEMS THAT I
NEED TO GIFT.
NEW HAMPSHIRE AVENUE CRASH ICY
CONDITIONS REPORTED AS WELL TAKE
IT SLOW OUT THERE.
CENTER LANE IS BLOCKED -- CENTER
LANE GETS BY AT RUPERT ROAD
OUTER LANE IS BLOCKED.
THERE YOU HAVE THAT.
CLARA BARTON CRASH SOUTHBOUND AT
CHAIN BRIDGE.
GW PARKWAY SOUTHBOUND DELAYS IN
THE SAME AREA.
95 NORTHBOUND TWO RIGHT LANES
BLOCKED BY A CRASH AT 100 LOOK
AT THAT LONG LINE OF SLOW RED.
YOU CAN SEE IT IN THE CAMERA.
BACKED UP PRETTY SOLID BACK TO
32.
NOW PREVIOUSLY BW PARKWAY WAS A
BETTER BET BUT NOW PEOPLE ARE
BAILING OUT AND WE'RE SEEING
THOSE BW PARKWAY NORTHBOUND
DELAYS AS WELL.
HEADING TOWARD BWI FACTOR IN
THAT EXTRA TIME.
QUIET ON THE WAY TO REAGAN
NATIONAL AND DULLES.
LORE DON GUNSTON DRIVE CLOSED AT
POE HICK BAY DRIVE.
395 WIDE OWN FROM HE HAD SAD
ROAD TO THE 14th STREET.
FREEWAY LOOK GOOD.
66 IS RAT SPEED AS WELL.
I HAD HOT SAUCE ON MY BREAKFAST
SANDWICH I NEED SOME WATER MUCH
IT'S HARD TO TALK WHEN YOU HAVE
THAT MUCH SPICE GOING ON.
BACK TO YOU.
>> ERIN, THANK YOU.
8:07.
DEATH TOLL FROM THAT MASSIVE
VOLCANO ERUPTION IN NEW ZEALAND
HAS UNFORTUNATELY RISEN NOW.
AT LEAST 17 PEOPLE HAVE NOW DIED
AFTER A WOMAN FROM ATLANTA
PASSED AWAY AT A HOSPITAL LAST
NIGHT.
TWO MORE PEOPLE ARE STILL
UNACCOUNTED FOR.
OFFICIALS BELIEVE THEIR BODIES
HAVE LIKELY WASHED OUT TO SEA.
SEVERAL AMERICANS WERE AMONG THE
DEAD AND INJURED.
COUPLES FROM RICHMOND AND
MONTGOMERY COUNTY ARE AMONG
THOSE HURT.
>>> IN TEXAS DNA TESTING
EXPECTED TO BE DONE TODAY ON A
NEWBORN BABY WHO WAS FOUND ALIVE
AFTER A WOMAN BELIEVED TO BE THE
BABY'S MOTHER WAS FOUND
STRANGLED TO DEATH INSIDE OF A
CAR.
THE WOMAN'S FRIEND IS BEHIND
BARS CHARGED WITH KIDNAPPING.
HEIDI BRUSARD AND HER NEWBORN
DAUGHTER MARGOT WERE REPORTED
MISSING IN AUSTIN ON DECE
DECEMBER 12th BY BRUSARD'S
BOYFRIEND AND FATHER OF THE B
BABY.
MOTIVE FORT ALLEGED KIDNAPPING
REMAINS UNCLEAR.
>>> PARAMEDIC IN NORTH CAROLINA
BEHIND BARS ACCUSED OF KILLING
HIS WIFE WITH A PRODUCT MANY
PEOPLE HAVE IN THEIR MEDICINE
CABINETS.
HOLLY HAS MORE FOR US FROM THE
NEWSROOM.
HOLLY.
>> I SWEAR STEVE LIKE A MADE FOR
TV MOVIE.
THE ALLEGED MURDER ADVICE SCENE
EYE DROPS.
35-YEAR-OLD JOSHUA HUN CONDUCT
SORRY CHARGED WITH FIRST DEGREE
MURDER IN THE DEATH OF HIS WIFE
STACEY.
SHE DIED IN SEPTEMBER OF 2018.
INITIALLY HER DEATH WAS SAID TO
BE FROM NATURAL CAUSES.
HOWEVER, HER MOTHER RAISED A RED
FLAG ALERTING INVESTIGATORS TO
POSSIBLE INSURANCE FRAUD.
PROSECUTORS NOW SAY HUN SUCKER
WAWANTED HIS WIFE' TWOS $50,000
LIVE INSURANCE POLICY.
A VILE OF HIS WIFE'S BLOOD HELD
BACK FROM THE ORGAN AND TISSUE
DONATION PROCESS AFTER HER DEATH
AND AN EXAMINATION OF THE BLOOD
FOUND HIGH LEVELS OF A TOXIC
INGREDIENT THAT IS VISINE EYE
DROPS.
HE GAVE VARYING ACCOUNTS OF HIS
WIFE'S DEATH AND DURING THE
INVESTIGATION HIS CO-WORKERS
TESTIFIED THAT HE SEEMED QUOTE
UNAFFECTED BY HIS WIFE'S SUDDEN
DEATH.
HIS FORMER MOTHER-IN-LAW AND CO
WORKERS CLAIM HE WAS PUBLICLY
DATING ANOTHER WOMAN SIX MONTHS
AFTER HIS LATE WIFE'S PASSING
MUCH HE'S BEING HELD NOW ON MORE
THAN $1 MILLION BAIL.
>> 8:09.
HOLLY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> THE PARENTS OF 18-YEAR-OLD
COLORADO GIRL HAVE FILED A
LAWSUIT AFTER THEY SAY SHE
SUFFERED SEVERE BRAIN DAMAGE
FOLLOWING BREAST END HANGS MANY
SURGERY.
EMILY WIN HAD BEEN IN A SEMI
CONSCIOUS STATE SINCE UNDER
GOING THE PROCEDURE IN AUGUST.
HER PARENTS CLAIM THAT SHE WAS
LEFT UNATTENDED FOR 15 MINUTES
WHILE UNDER ANESTHESIA.
AND DURING THAT TIME SHE STOPPED
BREATHING AND WENT INTO CARDIAC
ARREST.
DUE TO WHAT THE LAWSUIT CLAIMS
WAS IMPROPER ANESTHESIA ADD SAID
BY A NURSE INSTEAD OF AN
ANESTHESIOLOGIST.
NOW HER PARENTS LAWYERS ALSO
CLAIM THE DOCTORS OFFICE WAITED
FIVE HOURS BEFORE CALLING 911.
ATTORNEYS FOR THE DOCTOR'S
OFFICE MEANTIME SAY HER
COMPLICATIONS WERE UNRELATED TO
THE SURGERY.
>>> LET'S SWITCH BEERS NOW.
GET YOUR COMPUTER MOUSE READY TO
TRACK THE BIG MAN IN RED.
UP NEXT, WHEN YOU CAN START
FOLLOWING SANTA'S JOURNEY.
>> PLUS STREET ARTIST AT IT
AGAIN WITH ANOTHER POLITICAL
PIECE.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
HOLIDAY STATUE.
>> LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AS WE TAKE
YOU TO THE BREAK.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC ON THE 5'S
INCLUDING YOUR CHRISTMAS DAY
FORECAST NEXT.
♪
♪♪
♪ JINGLE BELL ♪
People aren't talking
about Giant's
sustainable shrimp
wrapped in prosciutto.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's the little things
that make entertaining easy,
leaving more time for
those closest to you,
during the holidays.
It's The IKEA Winter Sale.
Aka-the-up-to-50%-off-
already-low-prices-sale.
Aka-the-look-we-can-touch-every
thing-before-we-buy-it-sale.
Aka-the-I-can't-believe-
you-draged-me-here-
I-never-want-to-
leave-here-sale.
Aka-the-if-I-never-
get-out-of-here-
it-was-nice-knowing-
all-of- you-sale.
Aka-the-I'm-rethinking-
my-position-on-shopping.
Aka-the-all-these-savings-
can-reduce-stress.
Aka-we-can-get-storage-
for-our-storage-sale.
Aka-the-BTW-ICYMI.
Aka-the-this-is-too-good-
for-a-dad-joke-sale.
FOMO-IRL-FTW-sale.
What?
Yea meatballs,
meatballs, meatballs.
People aren't talking
about Giant's delicious
with real honey.      d
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
leaving more time for tho,
during the holids.
♪
>>> 8:13 RIGHT NOW.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE GATHERING TS
LARGEST MENORAH INONORF THE
THE FOURTH AERSARY OF THE
NATIONAL MENORAH LIGHTING STA
ARTED BYREDENTIMMY
CART.
>> INPAIN AT CHRISTMAS THE FAT
ONE ISN' SANTAT' EL GODOH.
TALKING AUT T COUNTRY RICHEST -
YES, SIR, RICHEST LOTRY IN THE
WORLD.
IS YEAR SHARED PRIZE
$22 MILLION.
>> NOT BAD.
>> THE DWING TEVIS
E LOT EVERYON WS
>> SOME DO WI IT BREAL?
I LIKE A LOTTERY WHERE
EVERYBODY WINS.
ME,
INMOUS STREET AIST BANKS SEE
IN TIME F MAKING POLITICAL STATT
WI SCAR OF BHLEHEM
THE -- STAR O BETHLEHEM WITH A
BULLET HOLE SHED L STAR.
DISPLA AT THE WALDF HOT A
EST HSE IN BHLEM
DESIGNED BY BASEE AND FILD.
MAKING STENT.
>>TEVE, NEED LAST NU HELP
OM Y.
STOCKING STUFF.
>> CHEET OR DOROS
>> WHOO, THIS TIME O YEAR --
>> CHEOSECSE DITOS MAKE
YOUR BREH FUNKYND I DON'T
FEEL LE IT.
>> CHEOSIV YESUE.
>> THEYO.
>>ITHER RHER THAT A AECD.
>> THANK YOU.
>>ETOS.
THANK YOU.
>> FLAMINGOT?
>>HATEVER FLAVOR YOU LIKE.
I LIK
SAME FOR ME.
>> FORECAST
ITOING TO COST ME KNOW,
>>> 32 NOW WASHITON. T SRT YOUR
AFTEOONND AITE WARME
TH YESTERDAY
UAN SEEHE 20S INREDERICK
23EGREES.
22 MANASSAS.
S MORNG LEONARDTOWN.
CLOYD COR EECLLY AS YOU
T SOUTH OF TOWN CENTRALD THA
IS A*SST WH A STRG
ART
BRGS V THE
D TTOMET BEACH DAY FLORI THERE.
OUDS AUND. FURTHER
OCKT BUT IT WIL KEEPOM FORECASTG
THE AFTERNOON SO WLL G PARTLY
SUY.
A MILAY WITH OUR WINDS OUT
HE SOUTH THAT QUITEETCH
OFEATHER, THURSDAY, FRIDA
FOR CHRISTMASVE,
CHMASOR SHOE
BEAUFU
D JUSKIND OFEASONABLY CL
ANDHENE'LL BEBOUTSTMAS DAY.
ALLIGHTIET FORECAST HERE FOR
ATHER COOPERATES
'LLEE TRAIC COOPERATES
THIS MNI WIT ERI
>> ORALL TUCK IEON THEROADS IN T
NEW CSH LEHH WAY CLOSED
RIGHTOWCRASBLOCKING ALL LANES IH
DIRECTIONS.
BETWEEN HOLLY OF A AND LA G
TODAY ROAD.
TAKE 66, 66 EAST AESTBOUND
IT'S9 RIGHT NOW THAT ISWARD THI.
NOT THE ON PBLEM AREA WE'RE UP
AGNST.
NE HAMHIRE AVENUE TELLING
TH I C WATCH FOR BIGSH SCENE TAN
LANE.
THAT IMPACTING OUR RIDE.
CLAR BARN PARKWAYRASH
SOUTHBOU ATHAIN BRIDGE.
DEYS I B DIRECTIS.
OULITTL BIT LEE ONW PARKWAY
QUT.
95 NORTHBOUND CRASH BIGELAYS
OM 3TO WHEREIGHT LANES
YOU CAN SEE WE'RE BUMPER
BUER SOUTHBOUND TRTHBOUND TRAFFE
CLOSED AT POE HICK BAY DRIVE.
BARIDGE NICE AND QUIETND
I'LL SEND IBACK TO YOU
>> EN, THA YOUERY MUC
HAVE YOUEA ABO SW
GLOBG?  IT'OTS NHAOU
THINITHEAD,T'S A RELATIONSHIP
TREND TH APPARTLY IS P
UP THI YR.
WELXP.
IT'S 8:17.
♪
♪♪
YTRENSNOWLONG, WELL, IT'S
E OF THEY STORM.
ACCORDING T
IS COUPLES APPR TOHAHEYUA ACTLLY
ARE.
SO THEY'LL AITTL B
FINDMS THEELVES I SKATINGEXCHAIO
HOLIDAY PARTIES ALL COZIED UP IN
THE SPIRIT OF H BUT
RE NOTNTO EACH OTH SO
ARHEHTHE HIDAYS ARER, SO
RELATIONIP AGHT AEREW YEA
ON BGHTER NOTE FOR THE
NOWECAUSE NORADAS STARTER
THE OIC COUNTDOWN FORE SOON.
THE OFFIAL CNTDOWN F T
THE ONLINE TOOL LOU FOLW
NTA CLAND HIS REIEERBE AS THEY Y
AT 6:00 O'CLOCK TOMORROW.
YOU CAN C OUT SANSS
H T PDL TTHEEANTIME AND G LOOK U
LEFT SOMEBODYIL AEAR INHE
PUDDLE IN JUSTENTCHEA
>> ATLE D TO ME WHEN I SAW
IT EARLIER BECSE THE'S
SOMETANDIN GUARD OVER
PUDDLE. FRON.
>> THE PE>> WHO'S THAT.
>> IT LK LIK AIT OR
MEBODYLEADG FOR HP AND
THEY'RE GON
>>HAT WAUN.N OTTER O
>> HI. GUYS.
GOOMOG, STEVE.
>>'RE HAVING AAR OVER
WE'RE HAN.
AT WSKED SANTA FOR. GETTING CHES
>>TEVE
FANCIER FROME. PRESENT
OTO PUT THERESSE
YOU TUCK.
LET'S DO TORT YOUR MNING.
>> Y G NERVOUS AND CHOKED.
CLOUD COVER TO S O MORNG
D MILDEREMPETURES O
50 THI AFTERNOON ANDE WILL TO M
THE' A STRONREA OF LOWATELLITE .
PRSURE JTO OUR SOUTH,
E NORTHERN EDGEF TT CLOUD
VE CANOPYTINGNTO OUR
ON T RAIN WLOTAKET
UR NORTH.
HIGH PREUR WIL IT FOW TOWARDSAM.
T'S NOT BEA WEAER.
>>O.
>> UUM
BUTNGSILL IROVEOWN
THERE THE NEXT COLEAYS.
FORATION WEATHER.
ODAY.
WE KEEP IT NICE A D.
I HE TWEET REQUEST FOR
>>REYONE.
>> SINCE WRE WORKINGHI
TWUSWEE OF ONE EVERYEO
THE HOLIDAYEASON. PART?
>> GETTING TO WK WH YOUGU
>> AWW YOU'RO SUITE.
LOT TWA COMMUTE
OUT OF TOWN, OVER OUR MAJS
ARE QET
DO HE A F PROBLEM AREASLOSURE L
OF A LAD.
KEEP TO 66 CLEAR OF THOSE HAMPSE
AVUE.
ALSO 95 OUT BYRASH
CAUSINGLARA BN
RKWA SOUTH ARASHT
ME IE.
IF Y'R TING T G TO WORK
WE DID THISORNG,
>>HA YOURIN.
>>> CI THA RY FORCETO
KE DO YOUO MAKE THAT DECISION
OVERHEAST THREEEEKS FOX
D. CARESAS BN COLLECT
DIAPERS A WIP TO BENEFITHE
TODA W IT'S DONATION DAY. ONHED.
HELL M FHING.
THIS TIM ORR ANYIME O
YEAR TOEL FAMILIES WHO ND
.
THEEASON
RIGH
ND CORRI FRO GREATERD
D.C. AANDLL
GOT -- WE GOT DIAPERSHERE.
>> WE DO
HAVEIKE0, WHAT,
35,000
>>5,00
AIOR 50.
WE'R GOING TO MAKE IT.
OTHERUSESS WHS CLECTDIAPSRE BNGT
>> RIGHT.
>> WRE GOING T HIT0.
>> I LOV IT.
JUST RIN
THIS DATION WLO HP
FAMILIES HER
EVERYONTH
LL BDIBU FAMILIES IN HE, HUGEELR
WHAT WE'REOINGUCHT'O
INCRLE WAYOR PEOPLE TO
AND KNOW ABO O W.
>>YEERS ON A BABY MEANS THING TT
ITEANS I CAN GET TO MY J.
>>ES.
>>T ANS I KNOW MBABYILL
BEITTL B BTER THAT DAY.
H ME  THE PSICADIAPER.
>> IT
AN YAL AUT THAT?
>> I THINK WHEN PEOPLE THINK
ABOUTHIRE DOI A
PRECIO CUTE TNG, ANDHA I
WANT PEOPLE TONOIS IS
OUFAMI'S LIVES.
AND FOR A FAMY WITHOUT
RESOURS,HEY' BG
APS IN T LOW INCOME
NEIGHBOROD THEY'REAYING TWO
OR THREE TES WT'RE
NG THEM AT THE BIG BOX STORET.
>> WE'RNOT SAYG THIS IS
SMALHING.
THISS A LOT O
FAMILIES WORKING.
THIS BRE A MILK THIS IS FARE.
IS IS NT
>>
FOR HAVTHRE K WHETHAOS A MOM TOE
DIERO MH OF FE I JT WERE
MAKINGHEEXT RHT.
>> OR THE NEXT TWO HOUR OKA.
>>IGSO DIAPERS D A LOT MOR THAN
JUST BE DPER.
>> THAN JUST CLOTHE THETTOM
>> EXACTLY.
>> WE SEEUSINESSES COMGN
KINGHEONIO FOU'R
GO 50,000 DIAPED YOUE WRE
RK.
>>WE ARE.
>> OUT DYOUEL AT HOME.
>> CAN YOU STILL COMEOWN.
DIAPERWE'L BERENT DONAT HER
YOUAN ALSO GO ON O IS OVE GREER
D.C.IAPE BANK.ORG AND GET
PERS, WEANT
DONAONSUT WE ALSO YOUR TE Y ENEY
FOHI ISSUE.
>> ABSOLTH IS A LOT OF MOVG PTS.
CO'M GOING T TALK WITH
EVE FROM GSS HOPPER MOVERS
WHO IS GET ALL THESE
>>HAT' R.OMEWHERE,IG
>>DORNG
>> I D'T REMEMBER H CRINES
UN US.
>> MEAN W? HA THE
KNOW, PEOE NEED DIAPERS
DT'S J GREAT C
RIG
>> WE'RE HAPPY T HELWHE WE
CAN.
SO YOU'L BEING A THESE
DIPER BK
DAY.
>> DON'T WANT  T VERY LAS
DIAPER MAKE THAT P AWHERE.
>>'T GO ANYWH
OD MORNING.NYEREITHEWE SUSINSESN
WHAREOU WITH.
SERVICE COMPANY.INTST
>>HAHAVE Y DONE TOD.
>> SO WE BROUGHT -- WEHT
2400IAPERS.
>> MY GOSH.
A LOT OF OUR
>>HANK YOU
THANKS TO OUR ELOYEES, O
EY HAPPY TOT IT FEELS GOOD,GUS W
SO WE'LL B HERE.M.
EHEG INVER,
THE TOPND IT'SLL FOR
FAMILIESN OUR AREA.
SO I'METTI EMOTIONAL
I KNOW
WE'LL HIT TT 50,000 DIAPER
MARK TAY.
ALL RIG.
ERE IT I
[ APPLAU ]
>> WE'LL BE RIG BAC
♪
♪♪
Do scrubbingrease el like
a workout?