HE RODE EVERY LINE AND EVERY
MILE OF METRO BUT WHY?  WE'LL
FIND OUT.
AND TELL YOU WHAT HE THINKS
ABOUT OUR RAIL SYSTEM.
FOX5 MORNING AT 7:00 A.M.
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> ♪
>> LOG THE MILES -- ADDED THE
MILES I'VE LOGGED OVER THE
YEARS ON METRO.
GOOD MORNING.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US ON
THIS THURSDAY.
I'M STEVE CHENEVEY.
>> I'M ALLISON SEYMOUR.
IF YOU'RE JUST WAKING UP THIS
MORNING, AND HOW ABOUT A LIVE
LOOK OUTSIDE ON THIS THURSDAY
DECEMBER 12TH.
THAT'S COLD OUTSIDE.
30 DEGREES.
BUNDLE UP.
>> GOT SOME SUNSHINE EARLY
THIS MORNING BUT IT'S THOSE
TEMPERATURES TUCK WE'RE
KEEPING AN EYE ON TODAY.
>> YEAH, IN FACT, DAYTIME
HIGHS WILL ONLY BE IN THE
UPPER 30'S TO ABOUT 40 SO VERY
COLD THIS MORNING AND THEN A
CHILLY AFTERNOON.
BUT I WILL HAVE ALL THE
DETAILS ON YOUR FORECAST.
YOU'LL WANT TO SEE IT.
WE HAVE RAIN ON THE WAY, MAYBE
ANOTHER WINTRY MIX ON THE WAY
SO LOTS OF WEATHER TO TALK
ABOUT.
ACTIVE PATTERN COMING.
DETAILS IN JUST A MINUTE.
STACEY GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
SLOW RIDE ON 95 NORTHBOUND
THIS MORNING.
THE RIGHT SHOULDER IS BLOCKED
AT LORTON ROAD DUE TO A CRASH.
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT AND
GIVE YOU A COMPLETE LOOK AT
THE DMV COMING UP.
>> LET'S GET TO SOME NEWS
BREAKING OVERNIGHT.
WE'LL START IN ALEXANDRIA
WHERE A CHILD WAS RESCUED
AFTER FLAMES BROKE OUT INSIDE
A FOUR STORY APARTMENT
BUILDING.
HAPPENED ABOUT 1 O'CLOCK IN
THE MORNING ON THIS NORTH
PATRICK STREET.
THEY ENTERED TO FIND THE FIRE
IN A KITCHEN.
>>> FIREFIGHTERS WERE ABLE TO
LOCATE THAT CHILD WHO WAS
TREATED BY PARAMEDICS OUTSIDE.
STILL WORKING TO GET AN UPDATE
ON THAT CHILD'S CONDITION.
THE RED CROSS IS STILL ON THE
SCENE ASSISTING OTHER
RESIDENTS.
>> TO MONTGOMERY COUNTY NOW
WHERE FIREFIGHTERS RESPONDED
TO AN EARLY MORNING FIRE IN
WHITE OAK.
85 FIREFIGHTERS IN FACT
RESPONDED TO THE FIRE ON
COLUMBIA PIKE.
FLAMES RIPPED THROUGH TWO
TOWNHOMES.
NOW 15 PEOPLE ARE WITHOUT A
HOME INCLUDING 10 ADULTS, FIVE
CHILDREN, FOUR PETS.
THIS FIRE STARTED ON THE
SECOND FLOOR.
THERE IS $700,000 ESTIMATED IN
DAMAGE.
>> DEVELOPING IN THE DISTRICT
THIS MORNING, A 12-YEAR-OLD
BOY RECOVERING IN THE HOSPITAL
AFTER HE WAS SHOT IN NORTHEAST
D.C.
POLICE SAY A GUNMAN OPENED
FIRE IN THE CLAY TERRACE
NEIGHBORHOOD ON DIX STREET
JUST AFTER 9 O'CLOCK LAST
NIGHT.
STILL DON'T KNOW THE EXTENT OF
THE BOY'S INJURIES BUT WE KNOW
HE WAS BREATHING AND CONSCIOUS
WHEN TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL.
NO WORD YET ON ANY SUSPECTS
THIS MORNING.
>> THIS MORNING VIRGINIA
ARLINGTON POLICE ON THE
LOOKOUT FOR THE MAN ACCUSED OF
TRYING TO ABDUCT A 14-YEAR-OLD
GIRL.
THIS HAPPENED TUESDAY NIGHT AS
SHE WAS WALKING A LITTLE BOY
HOME FROM SCHOOL IN ARLINGTON
HEIGHTS.
NOW, AS THEY TURNED THE CORNER
ONTO SOUTH IRVING, THE GIRL
REALIZED A MAN WAS FOLLOWING
THEM.
THE SUSPECT THEN GRABBED HER
BUT SHE FOUGHT BACK AND THE
MAN RAN OFF.
POLICE ARE HOPING SOMEONE IN
THE AREA MIGHT HAVE CAPTURED
THE MAN ON A HOME SECURITY
CAMERA.
>> WE'RE TRACKING METRO THIS
MORNING AND WE ARE IN FOR
ROUND TWO OF A METRO SUMMER
SHUTDOWN.
>> THE TRANSIT AGENCY MAKING
MORE REPAIRS TO PLATFORMS IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
THE OVERHAUL SURE TO CLOSE
THREE METRO STATIONS AND
CRIPPLE A FOURTH ONE.
MELANIE ALNWICK JOINS US NOW
FROM THE VIENNA METRO STATION
WITH THE DETAILS.
WHEN IS THE PAIN GOING TO
COME, MEL?
>> Reporter: WELL, I THINK
WE'VE GOT A LITTLE BIT OF TIME
TO PREPARE.
LET'S GET THROUGH WINTER FIRST
AND THEN WE CAN START LOOKING
TOWARD SUMMER.
YOU CAN SEE HERE AT THE VIENNA
METRO STATION IT'S A PRETTY
POPULAR STATION.
THIS IS THE END OF THE LINE
FOR THE ORANGE LINE BUT IT
WON'T BE OVER THE SUMMER
BECAUSE THE LAST THREE
STATIONS ON THE ORANGE LINE
WILL CLOSE FROM MEMORIAL DAY
TO LABOR DAY.
IT'S JUST 7 MILES OF RAIL BUT
IT'S GOING TO HAVE A BIG
IMPACT ON RIDER.
VIENNA DUNN LORRING AND EAST
FALLS CHURCH WILL BE UNDER
CONSTRUCTION 24 N-/SEVEN THIS
SUMMERRER WHILE THE OLDER
STATIONS GET NEW PLATFORMS.
SLIP RESISTANT TILES, STAIN
STEEL PLATFORM STATIONS WITH
CHARGING SYSTEMS AND
SURVEILLANCE SYSTEMS.
THE WEST WEST FALLS CHUMP STATIN
CHURCH STATIONWILL BE THE END O.
IT WILL REMAIN OPENED WITH
REDUCED SERVICE.
THE WORK WILL SLOW DOWN
SERVICE ON THE SILVER LINE
FROM McLEAN TO WIEHLE-RESTON
EAST AND PASSENGERS ARE JUST
ABSORBING THE NEWS.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE SOME
DEFINITELY A LOT OF ALTERNATE
CHANGING TRAVEL.
I HOPE THEY CAN AFFORD IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE A MESS.
>> Reporter: WELL, AS BEFORE
METRO WILL PROVIDE SHUTTLE BUS
SERVICE AND ENCOURAGE PEOPLE
TO USE ALTERNATIVES.
THOSE DETAILS ARE GOING TO BE
FINALIZED AND PUBLICIZED IN
MARCH.
NOW, YOU MAY HAVE HEARD THAT
THE PLATFORM IMPROVEMENT
PROJECT WOULD BE COMING TO THE
YELLOW AND THE GREEN LINES.
THAT HAS BEEN RESCHEDULED SO
THAT'S BEING PUSHED BACK.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE CARE
OF THE ORANGE LINE PLATFORMS
FIRST.
STEVE AND ALLISON.
>> OKAY, WE'VE GOT TIME TO
MENTALLY PREPARE.
THANK YOU.
>> MEL'S ALL BUNDLED UP THIS
MORNING.
YOU CAN SEE THE BREATH IN THE
AIR ITS COLD OUT THERE TUCK.
>> YES, IT'S COLD AND CRISP.
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAYBE NOT SO
MUCH ENTHUSIASM FOR IT.
YEAH, COLD AND CRISP.
20'S, LOW 30'S EARLY.
UPPER 30'S FOR DAYTIME HIGHS.
THAT'S GOING TO DO IT AS WE'RE
IN FOR A COLD AFTERNOON BUT A
SUNNY AFTERNOON BUT STORM
FREE.
>> THERE'S THE BRIGHT SIDE OF
IT.
>> OUT AND ABOUT SHOPPING
DOING THAT KIND OF THING
GETTING READY FOR THE
HOLIDAYS, IT WON'T BE A BAD
DAY.
30 AT REAGAN NATIONAL, 20'S
DULLES, 27 DEGREES.
28 BWI MARSHALL.
REAGAN NATIONAL BY THE WAY
FIRST OFFICIAL SNOW OF THE
YEAR YESTERDAY.
.3-INCHES.
YES, .3-INCHES BUT WE'RE ON
THE BOARDS.
SATELLITE AND RADAR COULDN'T
BE QUIETER.
TRAVELING TODAY, UP AND DOWN
THE EASTERN SEABOARD WE'RE IN
GOOD SHAPE, HITTING THE
ROADS -- WELL, I'LL LET STACEY
TELL YOU ABOUT THE ROADS BUT
AT LEAST WEATHER-WISE YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO HAVE ANY PROBLEMS
WHEN YOU'RE HITTING THE ROADS.
IT WILL BE NICE AND QUIET AND
IT WILL BE COLD THIS
AFTERNOON, CHILLY THIS
AFTERNOON, UPPER 30'S TO ABOUT
40.
SO, IF YOU'RE WORKING
OUTDOORS, MAKE SURE YOU'RE
READY IF YOU'RE GOING OUT FOR
A WALK, THAT KIND OF THING
YOU'RE READY FOR A COLD DAY.
48 TOMORROW.
RAIN RETURNS LATE IN THE
AFTERNOON.
WILL BE WITH US TOMORROW NIGHT
INTO THE DAY ON SATURDAY.
I'LL HAVE THE WEEKEND FORECAST
AND ON THE SEVEN-DAY WE'VE GOT
ANOTHER CHANCE FOR A WINTRY
MIX AROUND HERE.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW WHEN THAT
ARRIVES IN JUST A MINUTE.
STACEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
WE ARE KEEPING YOU UP TO DATE
ON THE ROADS THIS MORNING.
LET'S TALK ABOUT VIRGINIA 7.
WE'VE GOT A CRASH RIGHT AT
BARON CAMERON AVENUE.
THE RIGHT LANE IS BLOCKED
BECAUSE OF THAT.
AS YOU CAN SEE IN THIS VDOT
SHOT, IT WILL DEFINITELY SLOW
YOU DOWN IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA
THIS MORNING.
LOOKING AT 95 NORTHBOUND, THE
RIGHT SHOULDER IS BLOCKED
AFTER LORTON ROAD DUE TO A
CRASH.
IT IS SLOW MOVING THERE.
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO JUST ABOUT
5 MILES PER HOUR IN THE THICK
OF THINGS.
MOVING OVER TO 395 AND 395 NORTD
WE HAVE THE LEFT LANE BLOCKED
BECAUSE OF A CRASH RIGHT AFTER
DUKE STREET.
THAT WILL TIE YOU UP AS YOU
MAKE YOUR WAY THROUGH
ALEXANDRIA.
ON THE INNER LOOP, THE ON RAMP
TO CENTRAL AVENUE IS BLOCKED
THIS MORNING DUE TO A CRASH
THAT HAPPENED EARLIER.
STILL TRYING REBOUND FROM THAT
CRASH.
SO, DO YOU HAVE SOME RESIDUAL
DELAYS THERE.
AND THEN MOVING OVER TO 66
EASTBOUND, IT'S SLOW MOVING
FROM MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY
WITH SPEEDS AT 30 MILES PER
HOUR.
STEVE, ALLISON.
>> ♪
>> 7:06 RIGHT NOW.
NEW YORK CITY POLICE CONTINUE
TO INVESTIGATE THE BRUTAL
MURDER OF AN 18-YEAR-OLD
COLLEGE STUDENT.
THE NEW YORK DAILY NEWS
REPORTS THAT SHE WAS FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
THE FRESHMAN BARNARD COLLEGE
STUDENT WAS FATALLY STABBED
DURING A MUGGING IN UPPER
MANHATTAN IN A NEIGHBORHOOD
THERE WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
POLICE SAY TESSA MAJORS WAS
WALKING THROUGH MORNING SIDE
PARK JUST STEPS AWAY FROM
COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY.
SHE WAS THEN APPROACHED BY A
GROUP OF MEN WHO POLICE SAY
ROBBED THEN STABBED HER
MULTIPLE TIMES BEFORE RUNNING
OFF.
>> LET'S GET TO THE LATEST ON
THIS WEEK'S TRAGIC SHOOTING AT
A JEWISH MARKET IN JERSEY
ACROSS THE RIVER FROM NEW YORK
CITY.
TWO OF THE VICTIMS LAID TO
REST LAST NIGHT AND THIS
MORNING THE SHOOTOUT STILL
SPARKING NEW FEARS OVER
ANTISEMITISM.
>> HOLLY JOINING US WITH
DETAILS ABOUT THE VICTIMS AND
THE SUSPECT.
>> THIS MORNING AUTHORITIES
ARE STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT MOTIVATED THESE
ATTACKERS.
A MAN AND A WOMAN TO
DELIBERATE TO PULL UP THAT
THAT KOSHER GROCERY STORE.
>> A COMMUNITY COMING TOGETHER
TO BID AN EMOTIONAL GOODBYE TO
THREE OF THE BYSTANDERS KILLED
TUESDAY WHEN TWO ARMED
SUSPECTS EXCHANGED GUNFIRE
WITH POLICE FOR HOURS IN THE
STREETS OF JERSEY CITY, NEW
JERSEY.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE GATHERED
WEDNESDAY NIGHT FOR THE
FUNERALS OF 24-YEAR-OLD MOSHE
DEUTSCHE AND 31-YEAR-OLD MEN
DEE FERENCZ.
TUESDAY'S GUN BATTLE AND
STANDOFF ENDED AT A KOSHER
MARKET AND LEFT A TOTAL OF SIX
PEOPLE DEAD INCLUDING VETERAN
POLICE DETECTIVE JOSEPH SEALS
THREE BYSTANDERS INSIDE THE
STORE AND SUSPECTS 47-YEAR-OLD
DAVID ANDERSON AND 50-YEAR-OLD
FRANCINE GRAHAM.
AUTHORITIES HAVE NOT
DETERMINED A MOTIVE BUT THE
CITY'S MAYOR BELIEVES THE
LOCATION WAS TARGETED IN AN
ANTISEMITIC ATTACK SPARKING
FEARS OF MORE ATTACKS ON THE
JEWISH COMMUNITY.
>> THERE ISN'T A PERSON THAT'S
NOT AFFECTED.
EVERYONE IS SCARED WALKING THE
ROAD.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP WEIGHING IN
ON THE TRAGEDY AT A HANUKKAH
RECEPTION AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> WITH ONE HEART AMERICA WHAT
WAS THATS FOR THE LIVES LOST
WITH ONE VOICE WE VOW TO CRUSH
THE MONSTROUS EVIL OF
ANTISEMITISM WHENEVER AND
WHEREVER IT APPEARS.
>> A FEW MINUTES LATER, THE
PRESIDENT SIGNING AN EXECUTIVE
ORDER AIMED AT COMBATING
ANTISEMITISM ON COLLEGE
CAMPUSES.
>> A.
[APPLAUSE]
>> OFFICIALS SAY THE TWO
SHOOTERS IN THE RAMPAGE ARE
ALSO THE PRIME SUSPECTS IN THE
KILLING OF AN UBER DRIVER IN
NEARBY BAYONNE, NEW JERSEY.
STEVE.
>> HOLLY THANKS.
IN NEW ZEALAND THIS MORNING
MILITARY SPECIALISTS ARE GOING
TO LAND ON WHITE ISLAND.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO
RECOVER THE BODY OF EIGHT
PEOPLE AFTER MONDAY'S
ERUPTION.
SCIENTISTS BELIEVE ANOTHER
ERUPTION IS POSSIBLE, IT'S
CERTAINLY A RACE AGAINST TIME
NOW BECAUSE RAIN IS SET TO
MOVE IN AND IF THAT RAIN MIXES
WITH THE VOLCANIC ASH IT COULD
CREATE CONCRETE THAT COULD
ENCASE THE BODIES AND MAKE
THEIR RECOVERY AND
IDENTIFICATION MUCH MORE
DIFFICULT.
>> LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS
IN PERU CONFISCATED 2 TONS OF
COCAINE FROM SEMI --
SUBMERSIBLE WATERCRAFT OFF THE
COAST OF PERU.
IT'S LIKELY THE DRUGS WERE
HEADED RIGHT HERE TO THE
UNITED STATES.
10 PEOPLE ON BOARD THE
WATERCRAFT ARE IN POLICE
CUSTODY.
OFFICIALS INTERCEPTED THE
SUBMARINE WHICH WAS NOT
AUTHORIZED TO BE SAILING.
>> ON CAPITOL HILL THE HOUSE ONO
UP WHERE IT LEFT OFF WITH
MEMBERS PROPOSING AMENDMENTS
TO THE ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT
BEFORE A FINAL VOTE.
THAT VOTE EXPECTED TO FALL
ALONG PARTY LINES AS
REPUBLICANS ARE BLASTING THE
DEMOCRATS SAYING THEY ARE
RUSHING THE PROCESS.
>> WE'VE DEALT WITH THE FACTS.
THEY'RE PRETTY SIMPLE.
NOTHING HAPPENED.
WHEN YOU HAVE TRUTH ON YOUR
SIDE IT'S REALLY EASY TO
DEBATE.
>> DOES THE EVIDENCE SHOW
CLEARLY THAT THE PRESIDENT
COMMITTED THESE ACTS?  DO THEY
RISE TO THE LEVEL OF
IMPEACHABLE HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS.
WHAT ARE THE CONSEQUENCES FOR
OUR NATIONAL SECURITY, FOR THE
INTEGRITY OF OUR ELECTIONS AND
FOR OUR COUNTRY IF WE FAIL TO
ACT.
>> MEANWHILE A POLL OUT OF
MONMOUTH UNIVERSITY SHOWS
50 PERCENT OF AMERICANS OPPOSE
IMPEACHING AND REMOVING THE
PRESIDENT.
A VOTE IN THE FULL HOUSE IS
EXPECTED NEXT WEEK.
>>> STILL AHEAD A POPULAR
NIGHTCLUB HAS BEEN A STAPLE IN
ARLINGTON FOR NEARLY TWO
DECADES CLOSING ITS DOORS FOR
GOOD.
>> PLUS, A PUSH TO LOOSEN
MARIJUANA LAWS IN THE
COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA.
BOB.
>> Reporter: YEAH, ALLISON,
THE TOP LAW ENFORCER IN THE
COMMONWEALTH IS NOW ON BOARD
WITH THOSE EFFORTS.
WE'LL SMOKE OUT THE DETAILS
FOR YOU WHEN FOX5 NEWS MORNING
CONTINUES.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
Welcome to our
Lipton tea factory.
Where these sun-soaked
tea leaves
are picked at the peak
of freshness.
For a naturally smooth taste.
And drinking Lipton
every day
can help support a
healthy heart!
>> TWO CHICAGO PARK WORKERS
ARE OKAY AFTER THIS.
THE SALT TRUCK SLID ON THE ICE
ISN'T THAT IRONIC RIGHT INTO
LAKE MICHIGAN.
WORKERS WERE ABLE TO ESCAPE.
WINDSHIELD WIPERS STILL GOING.
>> LOOK AT THE AUTOMATIC
WIPERS, THEY'RE STILL GOING.
>> DETECTED MOISTURE ON THE
WINDSHIELD.
>> OH, BOY.
>> LIGHT SNOW BLANKETED
CHICAGO YESTERDAY.
TEMPERATURES AROUND
17 DEGREES.
TRYING TO DO GOOD AND SPREAD
THE SALT BUT INSTEAD ENDED UP
IN THE DRINK.
>> WE KNOW WHAT A LITTLE ICE
CAN DO.
DOESN'T TAKE MUCH TO START
SLIPPING AND SLIDING.
THAT'S NOT A CONCERN TODAY.
ALTHOUGH IT IS PLENTY COLD.
REAL QUICK IN CHICAGO, 22 TO
START YOUR MORNING AND RIGHT
ACROSS THE MIDATLANTIC AND NEW
ENGLAND WE ARE IN FOR A VERY
COLD START HERE OR WE ARE
HAVING A VERY COLD START.
30 IN WASHINGTON THIS MORNING.
MOST OF OUR REGION LOCALLY IN
THE 20'S TO KICK OFF YOUR DAY.
BUFFALO 14, DETROIT 17 THIS
MORNING.
GOING TO BE A QUIET ONE.
NICE LOOKING AFTERNOON FOR US.
LOTS OF SUNSHINE TO ENJOY ON
YOUR THURSDAY.
BUT IT WILL BE A THEY'LL DAY.
MAKE SURE YOU'VE GOT LAYERS ON
IF YOU'RE WORKING OUTDOORS,
YOU'RE READY FOR THE COLD.
OUR DAYTIME HIGHS PROBABLY IN
MANY SPOTS WON'T REACH
40 DEGREES.
WE'RE GOING TO GO 40 AT REAGAN
NATIONAL BUT FOR THE REST OF
US, IT'S GOING TO BE A -- JUST
A SUNNY BUT VERY CHILLY
AFTERNOON AGAIN WITH DAYTIME
HIGHS  IN THE UPPER 30'S TO
ABOUT 40.
GOOD SHAPE FOR OUR THURSDAY.
A STORM ACROSS THE GULF.
THAT WILL PUSH INTO OUR REGION
TOMORROW MORNING.
CLOUD COVER AT DAY BREAK.
LATE IN THE AFTERNOON AND
DURING THE EVENING HOURS WE
START TO GET SHOWERS MOVING
IN.
THERE WE ARE AT 3 O'CLOCK
TOMORROW AFTERNOON AND SHOWERS
WILL CONTINUE OVERNIGHT FRIDAY
INTO MUCH OF OUR SATURDAY.
SATURDAY'S GOING TO BE A WET
DAY.
DAYTIME HIGHS ARE GOING TO BE
IN THE LOW 50'S SO IT WILL BE
JUST RAIN AROUND HERE BUT IT'S
GOING TO BE NO DOUBT ABOUT IT
A SOAKING WET SATURDAY.
WE'LL BE CONCERNED ABOUT
WHAT'S HAPPENING ON MONDAY.
40 TODAY.
AND THEN THERE'S YOUR RAIN
SHOWER ACTIVITY FRIDAY NIGHT
INTO SATURDAY.
AND BY MONDAY AND TUESDAY, WE
COULD DO ANOTHER ROUND OF
WEATHER AND I JUST WANT TO
SHOW YOU QUICKLY HERE OUR
MONDAY FORECAST COULD START AS
A PERIOD OF WINTER WEATHER SO
AGAIN, WINTER WEATHER AROUND
HERE IS POSSIBLE INCLUDE
SOMETHING SNOW OR A WINTRY MIX
MONDAY AFTERNOON BEFORE THIS
TRANSITIONS ALL OVER TO RAIN
LATER MONDAY NIGHT AND EARLY
TUESDAY.
THAT WILL BE THE NEXT TIME
FRAME WE'RE LOOKING FOR WINTER
WEATHER.
THAT'S MONDAY.
TODAY SUNNY, 40.
STACEY.
>> PROBLEMS IN ALEXANDRIA THIS
MORNING.
TELEGRAPH ROAD CLOSED AT
WILTON ROAD.
THIS IS DUE TO AN EARLIER
CRASH AND ICY CONDITIONS.
SO, TUCKER IS RIGHT, IT IS
CHILLY OUT THERE THIS MORNING.
NOW, ON ROUTE 7 IF YOU'RE
HEADING EASTBOUND WE HAVE A
CRASH RIGHT AT BARON CAMERON
AVENUE.
IT'S BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE.
THAT WILL DEFINITELY SLOW YOU
UP A BIT.
MOVING ON TO 95 NORTHBOUND, WE
ALSO HAVE A CRASH.
THIS IS BLOCKING THE RIGHT
SHOULDER, RIGHT AFTER LORTON
ROAD.
AS YOU CAN SEE IN THIS VDOT
SHOT, TRAFFIC IS CRAWLING ON
95 NORTHBOUND RIGHT AFTER
LORTON ROAD.
IT IS SUPER, SUPER SLOW.
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO ALMOST
5 MILES PER HOUR IN THE THICK
OF THINGS SO YOU MAY WANT TO
HEAD OUT A LITTLE EARLY THIS
MORNING.
395 IS REBOUNDING FROM A
CRASH.
IT'S BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE
AFTER DUKE STREET AND FINALLY,
AS WE MONITOR THAT CRASH ON
THE INNER LOOP, THERE IS A
CRASH THIS MORNING RIGHT AS
YOU GET ON THE INNER LOOP AT
CENTRAL AVENUE.
THAT ON-RAMP IS NOW BLOCKED SO
STILL TRYING RECOVER FROM THAT
EARLIER CRASH.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
ANY QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C.
ON TWITTER.
>> ♪
>> WELL, LONG TIME
ESTABLISHMENT CLOSING ITS
DOORS THIS MORNING CLARENDON
BALLROOM IS GOING TO SHUT DOWN
FOR GOOD.
>> MAN.
>> NOT THIS MORNING.
IT WILL CLOSE IN 2020.
BUT THIS MORNING WE'RE
BRINGING YOU THE NEWS.
BEEN IN THE BUSINESS BAR
BUSINESS FOR NEARLY TWO
DECADES NOW.
SO, GOING TO GO OUT WITH A
BANG WITH A NEW YEAR'S EVE
PARTY.
HERE'S A FUN FACT.
CLARENDON BALLROOM'S DOORS
FIRST OPENED TO THE PUBLIC ON
NEW YEAR'S EVE IN 2000, TURN
OF THE MILLENNIUM.
>> YES.
>> OPENED ON THE NEW YEAR'S
EVE 2000, CLOSING ON THE NEW
YEAR'S 2020.
>> AND OPEN AND GRAND CLOSING.
>> IF YOU WANT TO GRAB A
TICKET TO THE LAST BIG BASH
THEY'RE AVAILABLE BUT GOING
FAST.
>> I WONDER WHY.
>> FOR A NIGHTCLUB/RESTAURANT
TYPE THING, 20 YEARS IS PRETTY
GOOD LIFETIME.
>> IT'S A GOOD RUN.
>> YEAH.
>> D.C. AND MARYLAND
DECRIMINALIZED MARIJUANA FOR
YEARS BUT IN VIRGINIA IT
HASN'T HAPPENED.
YOU COULD STILL GO TO CHANGE
FOR POT POSSESSION.
>> THAT COULD CHANGE.
VIRGINIA OFFICIALS ARE LOOKING
TO EXPAND THE MEDICAL
MARIJUANA OFFERINGS.
>> BOB BARNARD IN GEORGETOWN.
>> Reporter: CAN BE
CONFUSING KEEPING TRACK OF ALL
THE LAWS AROUND THE REGION.
HERE IN THE DISTRICT IT IS
STILL ILLEGAL TO SELL
MARIJUANA AND YET D.C. POLICE
SAY MORE AND MORE PEOPLE ARE
DOING THAT.
OUR CAMERAS WERE AT THE SCENE
OF A RECENT DRUG BUST, ONE OF
TWO HERE IN GEORGETOWN.
THESE WERE SHOPS, THEY'RE
MERCHANTS AND TENANTS ACCUSED
OF SELLING MARIJUANA AND LACED
PRODUCTS.
HERE IN THE DISTRICT, THOUGH,
IT IS NOT AGAINST THE LAW TO
POSSESS SMALL AMOUNTS OR TO
SMOKE MARIJUANA.
IN MARYLAND THERE'S AN EFFORT
TO LEGALIZE EDIBLES LIKE
BROWNIES FOR MEDICINAL
PURPOSES.
IN VIRGINIA ATTORNEY GENERAL
MARK HERRING YESTERDAY HOSTED
A DAY LONG SUMMIT WITH THE
CANNABIS CAUCUS TO CONSIDER
DECRIMINALIZING MARIJUANA
POSSESSION.
>> I ALSO THINK VIRGINIANS ARE
READY FOR THIS.
POLLING SHOWS THAT THE VAST
MAJORITY OF VIRGINIANS SUPPORT
DECRIMINALIZATION AND A
MAJORITY SUPPORT LEGALIZATION.
THE LEGISLATURE HAS BEEN
BEHIND WHERE THE PEOPLE ARE.
THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY TRY TO
GET THIS RIGHT.
>> THERE'S PEOPLE WHO ARE
GOING THROUGH CHEMOTHERAPY,
THERE'S PEOPLE WHO HAVE
EXTREME FORMS OF NAUSEA AND
WASTING SYNDROME AND ARE
UNABLE TO EAT.
WHEN ANY MEDICAL MARKET FIRST
STARTS, YOU HAVE VERY LIMITED
PRODUCTS THAT ARE AVAILABLE TO
YOU.
SO, WHAT I'M REALLY EXCITED TO
SEE IS TO SEE A FULL AND
ROBUST MEDICAL CANNABIS
INDUSTRY HERE IN MARYLAND.
>> Reporter: NOW, TRACY
MILLER OWNS A MEDICAL
MARIJUANA DISPENSARY IN
ROCKVILLE.
VIRGINIA IS CONSIDERING
CLEARING THE RECORDS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE CONVICTED
OF MINOR DRUG OFFENSES.
AS FAR AS THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT IS CONCERNED,
THOUGH, MARIJUANA POSSESSION,
SELLING, DISTRIBUTING IS STILL
ILLEGAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, BOB THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> OTHER NEWS NOW, IHOP
COOKING UP A NEW RESTAURANT
CHAIN.
WITH PLANS TO OPEN A LOCATION
RIGHT HERE IN THE DISTRICT IN
THE AREA.
WE'LL FILL YOU IN.
>> ALSO REV DOWN.
A COLLEGE BASKETBALL PLAYER
CELEBRATING A BIG PLAY
ACCIDENTALLY PUNCHES THE REF
IN THE NOGGIN.
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT COMING UP
AT 7:30.
>> OOH.
(VO)
The moth,
struggles in the spider's web.
Unaware that an exhilarating
escape is just within reach.
Defy the laws of human nature.
At the
Season of Audi Sales Event.
Step right up!
Try the all new Tyson
Air Fried Chicken.
With 75% less fat.
It's all pleasure and no guilt.
Plus we air fry it
before you buy it.
It's the best thing to happen
to fried chicken since...
fried chicken.
>> ♪
>> 7:23.
CAPS STAR ALEX OVECHKIN ABOUT
TO PICK UP ANOTHER HONOR, THIS
TIME THE PRESTIGIOUS WAYNE
GRETZKY INTERNATIONAL AWARD.
HE DELIVERS AND HE COLLECTS.
THE MOSCOW MEITIV WITH SUCH A
BIG IMPACT ON ADVANCING HOCKEY
IN THE UNITED STATES.
HIS CRAZY EIGHTS PROGRAM
PROVIDED MORE THAN 5,000
TICKETS TO HELP UNDERSERVED
CHILDREN ATTEND THE GAME.
NATIONALS FANS MIGHT BE A
LITTLE SAD THIS MORNING AS
THEY WAKE UP.
WE KNEW IT WAS COMING THOUGH.
SUPERSTAR THIRD BASEMAN
ANTHONY RENDON HEADED TO THE
WEST COAST AFTER WINNING THE
WORLD SERIES HERE IN
WASHINGTON.
CAME UP THROUGH THE
ORGANIZATION, WAS A DRAFT PICK
OF THE NATIONALS.
THE FREE AGENT THIRD BASEMAN
NOW HEADING TO L.A. SIGNED A
SEVEN YEAR, $245 MILLION
CONTRACT WITH THE LOS ANGELES
ANGELS.
AT LEAST HE'S NOT IN THE
DIVISION, TUCKER.
>> HE BROUGHT US A WORLD
SERIES.
GOT TO BE HAPPY.
>> IS THAT THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HIM AND BRYCE HARPER
FOR THE ATTITUDE THAT I'M
SEEING.
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> AMONGST THE TWO OF YOU.
>> A LOT OF DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE TWO BALL PLAYERS, TOO.
>> I AGREE.
>> IF YOU WANT TO SEE CUTE
VIDEO STEVE GO WATCH THE VIDEO
OF THE CAPS PUPPY REUNITING
WITH OVIE WHEN HE CAME BACK
FROM A ROAD TRIP.
>> LOVE THAT CAPS PUPPY.
>> SUPER CUTE.
WINDS OUT OF THE NORTH AND
EAST AT 10.
FEELING LIKE 21.
WE'RE COLD.
MOST OF OUR REGION IN THE 20'S
TO START YOUR MORNING.
BRIGHT SUNSHINE EXPECTED UP
AND DOWN THE EASTERN SEABOARD.
MIDATLANTIC COULDN'T LOOK
NICER.
HIGH PRESSURE RIGHT OVERHEAD.
JUST A FEW CLOUDS LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE'RE IN GOOD SHAPE.
IT'S A VERY ACTIVE WEATHER
PATTERN.
BY ACTIVE I MEAN STORMY OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS SO WE'RE
GOING TO KEEP IT QUIET TODAY.
WE'RE GOING TO GET RAIN
SHOWERS BACK IN THE FORECAST
LATE FRIDAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RAIN.
AND SATURDAY LOOKS LIKE A
SOGGY WET UNPLEASANT DAY.
UNLESS YOU'RE A DUCK OR ME.
52.
AND THEN 51 ON SUNDAY BEFORE
WE COULD DO ANOTHER ROUND
EARLY NEXT WEEK.
LISTEN, THIS COULD START AS A
WINTRY MIX MONDAY AFTERNOON
ITS POSSIBLE THAT NORTH AND
WEST WE GET SOME ACCUMULATIONS
BEFORE IT CHANGES TO ALL RAIN
EARLY TUESDAY.
SO, ACTIVE WEATHER PATTERN.
LET'S SEE IF WE GOT ACTIVE
ROADWAYS AND JAM THAT CAM.
STACEY, YOU'RE CATCHING ON
HERE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED -- YOU LAUGH
AT MY JOKES AND THAT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO ME.
>> OKAY.
>> NOT MANY PEOPLE DO.
[LAUGHTER]
>> OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, TUCKER.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SOUTHEAST-SOUTHWEST FREEWAY.
WE HAVE A CRASH RIGHT BEFORE
THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS ALL THE WAY
BACK TO 395.
SO THAT WILL DEFINITELY TIE
YOU UP THIS MORNING.
SPEAKING OF 395, WE'VE GOT
DELAYS ALL THE WAY FROM
SEMINARY ROAD TO THE 14TH
STREET BRIDGE.
THAT'S QUITE TYPICAL FOR THIS
TIME OF MORNING.
AS WE LOOK AT TELEGRAPH ROAD
IN ALEXANDRIA, RIGHT AT WILTON
ROAD, IT IS CLOSED.
THIS IS DUE TO AN EARLIER
CRASH.
IN ADDITION TO ICY CONDITIONS.
SO, YOU WANT TO TAKE CARE AND
WATCH OUT FOR THAT THIS
MORNING.
ON ROUTE 7, WE HAVE A CRASH IF
YOU'RE HEADING EASTBOUND.
THIS IS RIGHT AT BARON CAMERON
AVENUE.
IT'S BLOCKING THE RIGHT LANE.
THAT WILL SLOW YOU DOWN.
AND FINALLY ON 95 NORTHBOUND
WE HAVE A CRASH THAT IS
BLOCKING THE RIGHT SHOULDER AT
LORTON ROAD.
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO ABOUT
5 MILES AN HOUR.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
QUESTIONS, STACEY FOX5 D.C. ON
TWITTER.
>> WE HAVE SOME BREAKING NEWS
RIGHT NOW.
WE WANT TO GET TO SKYFOX OVER
THE SCENE OF A HOUSE FIRE.
THIS IS PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY
RIGHT NOW.
FORT WASHINGTON.
ROWLAND LANE AND RIGHT ALONG
THE WATER THERE, YOU CAN SEE
SOME HEAVY SMOKE COMING FROM
BOTH STORIES OF THAT BUILDING.
WHEN FIRE CREWS ARRIVED.
SO, YOU SEE THE FIRE TRUCK
THERE AND IT'S KIND OF TOUGH
TO SEE THE STRUCTURE ITSELF.
IT'S REALLY BLANKETED BY ALL
OF THAT WHITE SMOKE.
OF COURSE THAT MEANS THERE'S
WATER BEING PUT ON THAT FIRE.
SO, THEY'RE PUTTING IT OUT BUT
AT THE SAME TIME HEAVY SMOKE
STILL ON THE SCENE THERE IN
FORT WASHINGTON.
>> ♪
>> FIGHTING CHILDHOOD OBESITY.
COMING UP, THE WORST HABIT
CONTRIBUTING TO KIDS THAT ARE
OVERWEIGHT.
>> PLUS, WHAT'S UP WITH THIS
GUY?  WHAT HE DID WHILE
VISITING D.C. THAT A LOT OF
PEOPLE IN D.C. DON'T REALLY
ENJOY.
BUT HE LOVED IT.
HIS GRADE FOR OUR METRO SYSTEM
COMING UP.
>> ♪
♪♪
If you're living with a
condition,
Kaiser Permanente's integrated
care team will help you
get through life without
missing a beat.
Kaiser Permanente. Thrive.
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.
♪
TAKE A LOOK BACK RIGHT NOW FORT
WASHINGTON THERE YOU CAN SEE THE
STRUCTURE THAT HAS BEEN BURNING
THERE IN FORT WASHINGTON PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY ON ROLAND LANE.
THAT SMOKE COMING OUT OF THE
TWO-STORY HOME.
FIREFIGHTERS ON SCENE.
YOU SEE THEM THERE ON THE
GROUND.
ON THE ROOF OF THAT HOME AND
THEY HAVE THE LADDER TRUCK
AROUND TO THE SIDE TO THE LEFT
OF THAT HOME.
SO WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON IT.
NO WORD ON ANY INJURIES AT THIS
POINT, BUT DEFINITELY HEAVY
SMOKE PRESENCE THERE AS
FIREFIGHTERS ARE IN AND ON AND
AROUND THAT HOME.
>>> LET'S CHECK SOME OTHER TOP
STORIES AT 7:30.
>>> START IN ALEXANDRIA, WHERE A
CHILD WAS RESCUED OVERNIGHT
AFTER A FIRE BROKE OUT THERE.
IT WAS INSIDE OF A FOUR-STORY
APARTMENT BUILDING.
>> THIS HAPPENED AROUND 1:00
A.M. IN THE 900 BLOCK OF NORTH
PATRICK STREET.
SMOKE SHOWING FROM A THIRD FLOOR
UNIT WHEN CREWS GOT THERE THEY
ENTERED TO FIND THE FIRE IN A
KITCHEN.
NOW DURING A SEARCH OF THE
APARTMENT FIR FIGHTERS CAN
LOCATE A CHILD WHO WAS THEN
TREATED BY PARAMEDIC OUTSIDE.
WE'RE WORKING TO GET UPDATE ON
THAT CHILD'S CONDITION AND WE'VE
ALSO JUST LEARNED A SECOND
RESIDENT IS BEING TRANSPORTED TO
THE HOSPITAL.
>>> IN THE DISTRICT THIS
MORNING, A 12-YEAR-OLD BOY
RECOVERING AFTER HE WAS SHOT IN
NORTHEAST D.C.
GUNMAN OPENED FIRE IN THE CLAY
TERRACE NEIGHBORHOOD ON DICK
STREET JUST AFTER 9:00 LAST
NIGHT.
STILL DON'T KNOW THE EXTENT OF
THE BOY'S INJURIES BUT WE ARE
TOLD HE WAS BREATHING AND
CONSCIOUS WHEN TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
NO WORD ON ANY SUSPECTS THIS
MORNING.
>>> WE WISH HIM WELL.
>>> THOUSANDS GATHERED TO MOURN
TWO VICTIMS OF THE JERSEY CITY
SHOOTING NOW OFFICIALS SAY IT'S
CLEAR THE JERSEY CITY KILLERS
TARGET ADD JEWISH DELI BUT THEY
HAVEN'T ESTABLISHED A MOTIVE FOR
THE ATTACK.
TWO ATTACKERS IDENTIFIED IN THE
PAST AS BLACK HEBREW ISRAEL
LIGHTS.
ONE SUSPECT POSTED ANTI JEWISH
AND ANTI POLICE MESSAGES ON
SOCIAL MEDIA BEFORE THE ATTACKS.
THEY'RE ALSO SUSPECTS IN A
NEARBY KILLING OVER THE WEEKEND
IN ADDITION TO THE JERSEY CITY
ATTACK.
>>> TODAY A FEDERAL APPEALS
COURT SET TO CONSIDER WHETHER
THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER
RECEIVED A FAIR TRIAL.
DZHOKHAR, CONVICTED IN 2015 FOR
THE 2,013 ATTACK THAT HE CARRIED
OUT WITH HIS OLDER BROTHER.
THREE PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
MORE THAN 250 OTHERS INJURED.
LAWYERS FOR ARE SEEKING TO HAVE
HIS DEATH SENTENCE OVERTURN
ARGUING DID HE NOT GET A FAIR
TRIAL BECAUSE JURORS WERE
EXPOSED TO RELENTLESS MEDIA
COVERAGE AFTER THE ATTACK.
>>> WE HAVE UPDATE ON A STORY
FROM SEPTEMBER EARLIER THIS
FALL.
THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE SAYS
MORE THAN 112,000 SHIRTS
DESIGNED BY A FOURTH GRADER HAVE
BEEN SOLD RAISING NEARLY A
MILLION DOLLARS FOR CHARITY.
THE UNIVERSITY CREATOR THE
T-SHIRTS YOU MIGHT REMEMBER
AFTER A FOURTH GRADER WAS
BULLIED FOR HOMEMADE VERSION TO
PARTICIPATE IN COLLEGE COLORS
DAY AT HIS SCHOOL.
THE SCHOOL PROCEEDS FROM THE
SALE OF THE T-SHIRT WILL GO TO
STOMP OUT BULLYING.
>> WE TALKED ABOUT IT WHEN IT
HAPPENED.
WHAT GREAT JOB THE UNIVERSITY OF
TENNESSEE DID.
>> YEAH.
>> THEY POSTED ON THEIR SOCIAL
MEDIA NOT JUST CONGRATULATIONS
FOR ALL THE MONEY BUT WE'LL SEE
YOU WHEN YOU'RE READY TO GO TO
COLLEGE.
>> AMAZING.
ALL RIGHT.
KEEP BEING YOU, LITTLE GUY.
TIME RIGHT NOW 7:33.
LET'S GIVE YOU A LOOK AT THE
GOOD DAY GUEST LIST.
WE'RE GETTING TECH SAVVY FOR
COMPUTER SCIENCE EDUCATION WEEK.
A COUPLE OF NINJAS WILL STOP BY
AND DEMONSTRATE CODING
TECHNIQUES FOR KIDS FOR DRONES
AND ROBERTS TO RAISE AWARENESS
OF SCIENCE EDUCATION AND THE
IMPORTANCE OF TECHNOLOGY
TRAINING FOR YOUNG PEOPLE.
>>> IT IS THE HOLIDAYS.
SO WE GOT SOME HOLIDAY COCKTAIL
IDEAS TO HELP BEEF UP YOUR
CELEBRATION.
THE MANAGER OF THE 2941 HERE IN
THE DISTRICT WILL STOP BY TO
DEMONSTRATE SOME IDEAS.
>>> AND TWO NEW CELEBRITIES
UNMASKED ON LAST NIGHT' THE MASK
SINGER.
DID YOU GUESS CORRECTLY?  ONE OF
THE TWO HAS TIES RIGHT HERE TO
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
SO WE'RE GOING TO BRING YOU ALLY
DETAILS.
GOOD DAY D.C. YOU DO NOT WANT TO
MISS IT.
>> WHICH I WAS NOT AWARE OF.
I LOOK FORWARD TO FINDING OUT
ALL ABOUT THAT TODAY ON GOOD
DAY.
I LOVE THE LOCAL CONNECTIONS.
>>> BEFORE WE GET OVER TO TUCKER
CELEBRATION GONE WRONG FOR THE
ILLINOIS SENATOR HE ACTUALLY
PUNCHED THE REFEREE RIGHT IN THE
HEAD AFTER A LATE BASKET IN THE
WIN OVER MICHIGAN LAST NIGHT.
>> TERRIBLE.
>> SO EXCITED WITH THE UPSET THE
REF REMAINED DOWN FOR A COUPLE
OF MINUTES HOLDING HIS HEAD.
EVENTUALLY WALKED IT OFF BUT WAS
LATER TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL FOR
FURTHER EVALUATION.
THAT PLAYER PROBABLY NOT FEELING
SO GOOD ABOUT THAT MOVE BUT
OBVIOUSLY LOOKS CLEARLY
ACCIDENTAL.
>> OH YEAH.
>> TUCK, I KNOW YOU WATCHED THE
CAPS GAME.
DID YOU ZEO RETAKE OUT THE REF
IN THE GAME.
>> I CERTAINLY DID.
>> CROSS CHECK IN THE CORNER.
>> REV TOOK A HARD FALL.
>> ACCIDENTAL I GUESS.
>> I WOULD HOPE SO.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
COLD TEMPERATURES TO START YOUR
MORNING.
30 AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
MOST OF THE AREA IN THE 20S OUT
EARLY.
JUST GOT A TWEET, HEY, TUCKER IS
THIS OUR DEFENDANT MORNING OF
THE SEASON?  WELL IT'S ONE MUCH
OUR COLDEST FOR SURE.
EVERYBODY IS BELOW FREEZING.
26 IN NEW YORK.
AND BOSTON THIS MORNING EASTERN
SEABOARD COULDN'T BE QUIETER.
MID ATLANTIC LOOKS GREAT TODAY.
SUNSHINE DAYTIME HIGHS ABOUT
40 DEGREES.
ENJOY TODAY BECAUSE THINGS WILL
GET STORMY AGAIN BY LATE
TOMORROW AND INTO THE WEEKEND
AND WE MIGHT EVEN HAVE ANOTHER
ROUND OF WINTRY MIX AROUND HERE
EARLY NEXT WEEK.
LOTS TO TALK ABOUT.
WE'LL HAVE DETAILS ON THAT
COMING UP YOUR FORECAST FOR
TODAY IS A NICE ONE.
39 DEGREES.
IT WILL BE CHILL.
TAKE A JACKET.
STACEY, HI.
>> TUCKER, TELL MY DAUGHTER TO
REMEMBER HATS AND GLOVES.
TUCKER SAID YOU NEED THEM TODAY.
>> RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT THE
SOUTHEAST SOUTHWEST FREEWAY THIS
MORNING.
WE'VE GOT A CRASH RIGHT BEFORE
THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS ALL THE WAY
BACK TO 395.
SO YOU MAY WANT TO HEAD OUT A
LITTLE EARLY THIS MORNING.
LOOKING AT 395 NORTHBOUND,
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS FROM SEMINARY
ROAD TO THE 14th STREET BRI
BRIDGE.
DEFINITELY GOING TO SLOW YOU
DOWN.
AND IN ALEXANDRIA, TELEGRAPH
ROAD IS CLOSED AT WILTON ROAD.
THIS IS DUE TO AN EARLIER
COLLISION THIS MORNING.
IN ADDITION TO ICY CONDITIONS.
AND FINALLY, IF YOU ARE ON ROUTT
BARRON CAMERON AVENUE THE RIGHT
LANE IS BLOCKED BECAUSE OF A
CRASH.
ALLISON, STEVE?
>> FIGHTING CHILDHOOD OBESITY.
NEXT THE WORST HABIT
CONTRIBUTING TO OVERWEIGHT KIDS.
>> ALSO, WHAT HOME DEPOT IS
SAYING ABOUT THE NUMBER OF
THEFTS IN STORES NATIONWIDE.
SHOPLIFTERS HITTING THEM HARD
AND THE SWIFT BACKLASH THE HOME
IMPROVEMENT STORE IS FACING THIS
MORNING.
THAT'S ALL COMING UP.
IT IS 7:36.
♪
♪♪
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
Every year,
air medical services save
hundreds of thousands of lives.
But after the emergency,
time and again,
insurance companies
deny coverage,
second guessing doctors,
nurses and first responders...
Now "big insurance"
is lobbying congress.
Asking for restrictions
on air medical services.
Eliminating patients'
access to life-saving care
and destroying jobs
all in exchange for bigger
profits for insurance companies.
Tell Congress,
put patients first,
not big insurance.
>>> WE DO HEALTH ALERT FOR YOU
THIS MORNING WHEN IT COMES TO
CHILDREN AND FIGHTING OBESITY.
THERE'S NEW RESEARCH THAT SHOWS
WATCHING TELEVISION IS THE
NUMBER ONE FACTOR LINKED TO
OVERWEIGHT CHILDREN.
THE STUDY EXAMINED LIFESTYLE
HABITS OF ABOUT 1500 CHILDREN
AND IT FOUND NOT ONLY DOES
TELEVISION DISRUPT SLEEP IT CAN
ALSO PERSUADE KIDS TO MAKE POOR
EATING CHOICES BECAUSE OF THE
ADVERTISEMENT FOR A LOT OF
SWEETS.
>>> ALASKA AIRLINES BACK WITH
ITS ANNUAL FREEBIE FOR PEOPLE
WHO GO OUT FOR THE HOLIDAYS FOR
ONE DAY ONLY DECEMBER 20th
AIRLINE WILL GIVE FREE PRIORITY
BOARDING TO ANY PASSENGER WHO
WEARS AN UGLY HOLIDAY SWEATER.
IT'S TO CELEBRATE NATIONAL UGLY
SWEATER DAY AND TO REDUCE TRAVEL
BY HAVING A LITTLE FUN.
>> I'LL HAVE TO GET ONE AND BOOK
A FLIGHT AND MAKE HE WORK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> LOTS OF THINGS TO DO FOR THE
20th.
>> CHECKLIST THIS TIME OF THE
YEAR SO LONG.
>> COMING UP WE'RE GOING TO CHAT
WITH D.C. TOURIST WHO DID
SOMETHING PRETTY REMARKABLE ON
METRO AND THE GRADE THAT HE
GIVES OUR TRANSIT AGENCY. AGENC.
IN ALEXANDRIA TODAY.
WIS?
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU.
WELL HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF A
SPORT CALLED FOOTS ALL IF YOU
HAVEN'T YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET
USED IT TO BECAUSE COMING UP
NEXT WE'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
THIS SUPPORT THAT'S CALLED FOOTS
ALL AND HOW IT'S TAKING HOLD
HERE IN ALEXANDRIA ON A YOUTH
LEVEL AND UP.
FOX IF FIVE MORNING CONTINUES
AFTER THE BREAK.
♪
>>> 7:43 ON THURSDAY MORNING.
TIME FOR OUR BUSINESS BEAT.
IHOP COOKING UP A NEW RESTAURANT
CHAIN WITH PLANS TO OPEN A
LOCATION RIGHT HERE IN THE DMV.
JOINING US NOW FROM THE FOX
BUSINESS NETWORK STUDIO TRACEE
CARRASCO.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> LET'S START THOUGH WITH HOME
DEPOT.
SO THEY'RE BLAMING THE OPIOID
CRISIS FOR WHAT'S GOING ON IN
THEIR RETAIL STORES, AND GETTING
BACKLASH FOR THIS.
>> YES.
SOME INTERESTING COMMENTS MADE
YESTERDAY FROM THE CHIEF
EXECUTIVE CRAIG MANEAR WITH AN
INVESTORS YESTERDAY HE SAID
"THIS IS HAPPENING EVERYWHERE IN
RETAIL.
WE THINK THIS TIES TO THE OPIOID
CRISIS BUT WE'RE NOT POSITIVE ON
THAT "OF COURSE HE'S TALKING
ABOUT THE THEFT OF MERCHANDISE
FROM HOME DEPOT STORES ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
HE DIDN'T CITE ANY SPECIFIC
REPORTS OR RESEARCH TO BACK UP
THIS CLAIMS BUT HE SAYS
ORGANIZED CRIME THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT THE COMPANY HAS
NOTICED HAS INCREASED
SIGNIFICANTLY.
THAT THEY'RE SEEING THESE
CRIMINALS STEALING MERCHANDISE
STORING IT IN WAREHOUSES AND
THEY SAY THAT CRIMINALS ARE
BECOMING MUCH BOLDER BECAUSE
THEY'RE ABLE TO SELL A LOT OF
THIS MERCHANDISE ON THE
INTERNET, AND THEN ALSO, OF
COURSE, THEY BELIEVE THAT THE
ADDICTIVE NATURE OF OPIOIDS IS
CONTRIBUTING TO THIS AS WELL.
IN FACT, THEY EVEN LOWERED THEIR
FORECAST FOR SALES NEXT YEAR
BECAUSE OF THIS CLAIM.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THERE IS ANY
SORT OF RESEARCH BEHIND IT, BUT
ALREADY GET GETTING SOME BACKLAN
SOCIAL MEDIA ON TWITTER A LOT OF
PEOPLE CRITICIZING THE COMPANY
SAYING HOW CAN YOU RELATE THE
TWO?  WE DID SEE SHARES OF HOME
DEPOT YESTERDAY FALLING BY 2%.
>> OKAY.
LET'S END WITH SOMETHING KIND OF
NEAT.
IT'S I GUESS A FASTER VENUE IF
YOU WANT A SHORT STACK OF IHOP
PANCAKES.
>> YES.
IHOP COMING OUT WITH A NEW
CONCEPT RESTAURANT MUCH IT IS
CALLED FLIPPED.
IT IS GOING TO FOCUS ON FAST
CASUAL DINING.
SO INSTEAD OF ALL OF THE TABLES
THAT YOU WOULD SEE IN A NORMAL
RESTAURANT AND THE SERVERS, IT'S
JUST GOING TO BE A RESTAURANT
WITH A FEWER TABLES FOCUSING
MORE ON PEOPLE GRABBING
BREAKFAST ITEMS OR LUNCH ITEMS
AND TAKING THEM TO GO.
YOU CAN PLACE YOUR ORDERS ON
ONLINE.
THEY'RE STILL GOING TO BE
SELLING PANCAKES IN ADDITION TO
THAT COFFEE OTHER BREAKFAST
THINGS LIKE BREAKFAST BURRITOS
AND BREAKFAST SANDWICHES.
THINGS LIKE SALADS TO GO SO THIS
IS SOMETHING THEY'RE FOCUSING
ON.
THEY WANT TO EXPAND IN THIS
BECAUSE THEY THINK IT WILL DO
WELL IN BIG CITIES.
THEY'RE STARTING OUT WITH ONE IN
ATLANTA.
THEY DO PLAN ON BRINGING THEM TO
OTHER BIG CITIES INCLUDING RIGHT
THERE IN D.C., SAN FRANCISCO,
NEW YORK AND DENVER.
THOSE ARE THE OTHERS ON THEIR
LIST.
>> I THINK IT WILL BE SUPER
SUCCESSFUL.
WE'LL TEST IT OUT RIGHT HERE IN
D.C.
>> LET ME KNOW.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
IT WILL BE FRIYAY.
>> HAVE A GOOD ONE.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO IT
ALREADY.
YOU'RE IN A GREAT MOOD TODAY,
AL.
>> AREN'T I ALWAYS IN A GREAT
MOOD?
>> OF COURSE YOU ARE I THINK
IT'S THE SUNSHINE AND FRIDAY EVE
THAT ARE DOING IT.
>> IT'S THE HOLIDAYS!
>> IT REALLY DOES START TO FEEL
LIKE THE HOLIDAYS.
>> WE'RE NOT SNOWED IN.
EVERYBODY MADE IT YESTERDAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
IT IS COLD.
IT'S FEELING LIKE THE HOLIDAYS
TEMPERATURE WISE EARLY THIS
MORNING.
LET'S SHOW YOU CURRENT NUMBERS,
AND 30 IN WASHINGTON TO START
YOUR DAY.
LOOK AT ALL YOUR 20S.
MOST EVERYBODY BACK IN THE 20S.
SO CERTAINLY ONE MUCH OUR
COLDEST STARTS SO FAR THIS
MORNING.
WALDORF 26, GOOD MORNING, BOWIE
27 OUT TO THE WEST FAIRFAX
26 DEGREES.
27 IN SPRINGFIELD.
25 UP IN GERMANTOWN.
EVERYBODY AGAIN LOOKING AT SOME
FREEZING TEMPERATURES HERE EARLY
THIS MORNING.
SO MAKE SURE ARE ALL READY TO GO
WITH A COLD TEMPERATURES WHEN
YOU HEAD OUT THIS MORNING.
WINCHESTER AND MARTINSBURG
WINNING OUR COLD SWEEPSTAKES
IT'S A CONTEST REALLY 21 DEGREES
OUT TO THE WEST TO START YOUR
MORNING.
LEONARDTOWN IS 28.
WE LOOK GREAT.
SUNNY, BRIGHT AND FOR THE MOST
PART BEAUTIFUL WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF VERY COOL
TEMPERATURES THIS AFTERNOON.
SO ONLY UPPER 30S FOR YOU MAYBE
WE'LL GET TO 40.
THAT'S GOING TO TO TO DO IT A SM
FREE DAY.
I CAN'T PROMISE WE'LL STAY STORM
FREE.
I CAN'T EVEN SAY THAT FIVE TIMES
FAST.
FOR THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS WE
GOT A STORM ACROSS NORTHERN
GULF.
THIS IS GOING TO SLIDE UP INTO
OUR AREA DURING THE DAYTIME
HOURS TOMORROW, AND BY LATE
TOMORROW AFTERNOON, TOMORROW
EVENING WE'LL HAVE RAIN SHOWERS.
JUST RAIN BUT CERTAINLY SOME
RAIN AROUND HERE FOR THE
OVERNIGHT HOURS FRIDAY INTO THE
DAY ON SATURDAY.
SO IT'S A WET SATURDAY.
AND THEN HERE'S OUR SETUP FOR
MONDAY.
SO WHEN YOU GET BACK TO WORK AND
SCHOOL NEXT WEEK I KNOW WE'RE
NOT FOCUSED ON IT RIGHT NOW, BUT
MONDAY WE COULD HAVE ANOTHER AIR
OF LOW PRESSURE OVERRUNNING WE
MAY START AS A PERIOD OF WINTER
WEATHER THAT'S ONE MUCH OUR
WEATHER MODELS FORECASTING
WINTER WEATHER MONDAY MORNING
THAT GRADUALLY TRANSITIONS TO
RAIN MONDAY AFTERNOON AND MONDAY
NIGHT.
KEEP THAT TIME FRAME IN MIND
EARLY NEXT WEEK.
BUT TODAY 40 DEGREES.
WE'LL FOCUS ON TODAY.
40 AND NICE.
STACEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
SO WE ARE KEEPING UP TO DATE ON
THE ROADS THIS MORNING.
LET'S START WITH 270 SOUTHBOUND.
WE HAVE A CRASH THAT HAS BEEN
REPORTED RIGHT AFTER MONTROSE
ROAD.
SLOWING YOU DOWN A BIT.
YOU'VE GOT SPEEDS DOWN TO
20 MILES PER HOUR HOPEFULLY
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS WILL BE ON
SIGHT SOON.
MOVING ON TO YOUR MARYLAND
DRIVE, THINGS ARE AS THEY SHOULD
BE ON THE OUTER LOOP FOR THIS
TIME OF MORNING.
IN THE THICK OF THINGS YOU'RE
DOWN TO 10 MILES AN HOUR.
95 AND THE BALTIMORE WASHINGTON
PARKWAY ARE MOVING ALONG.
ON 295 SOUTHBOUND, YOU'VE GOT
POCKETS OF TRAFFIC I'LL SAY.
LET'S KEEP IT LIGHT.
POCKETS OF TRAFFIC.
SPEEDS DOWN TO 5 MILES PER HOUR.
FIVE TO 8 MILES AN HOUR IN THE
THICK OF THINGS ALSO CONGESTION
IS BUILDING ON 50 THIS MORNING.
AND FINALLY, THE SOUTHEAST
SOUTHWEST FREEWAY IS A LITTLE
SLOW THIS MORNING BEFORE THE
THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS TO 395 DUE TO
A CRASH.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
>>> STACEY, THANKS.> STACEY, TH.
COMMUTE RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS -- WE'LL HAVE A LITTLE
FUN.
IF YOUR MORNING COMMUTE INVOLVES
TAKING METRO CAN YOU IMAGINE
RIDING NOT JUST ONE STOP TO STOP
BUT EVERY MILE OF THE METRO RAIL
SERVICE?
>> IF YOU'RE CURIOUS HOW MANY
MILES THERE ARE, THE ANSWER IS
117.
THAT'S IF YOU TAKE EVERY LINE
EVERY STOP EVERY MILE AROUND
D.C., MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA.
SOMEBODY DID IT.
CAME IN FROM OUT OF TOWN, DID IT
FOR FUN.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
INTENTIONALLY ROAD METRO FOR 11A
COUPLE OF DAYS.
IF YOU'RE WONDERING WHY, WELL SO
ARE WE.
HE'S PRETTY PASSIONATE ABOUT
PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION.
JOINING US NOW FROM HIS HOME IN
INDIANAPOLIS IS JEROME HORN.
JEROME, JEROME, JEROME, WE HAVE
QUESTIONS FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
>> HI, GOOD MORNING, STEVE.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO RIDE.
>> GOOD MORNING, GERM.
WHY DID YOU DECIDED TO THIS?
>> YEAH.
I'M A BIG FAN OF PUBLIC
TRANSPORTATION.
I ACTUALLY WORK IN THE TRANSIT
INDUSTRY.
I WORK FOR THE TRANSIT SYSTEM IN
INDIANAPOLIS, AND YOU KNOW D.C.
METRO RAIL IS JUST ONE OF THE
KIND OF PREMIER METRO SYSTEMS IN
THE UNITED STATES, AND I WANTED
TO RIDE THE WHOLE SYSTEM AND
CHECK OUT ALL OF THE STATION
ARCHITECTURE, AND REALLY JUST,
YOU KNOW, END JOIN IT AND KIND
OF TAKE NOTES OF PEOPLE GETTING
ON AND OFF AND DID YOU HAVE
SECTIONS OF THE SYSTEM, AND
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S A GREAT ASSET TO THE
WASHINGTON METROPOLITAN AREA.
>> I LOVE YOUR PASSION FOR IT,
JEROME.
I'LL STOP YOU FOR A SECOND.
WHEN YOU SAY ONE OF THE PREMIER
METRO SYSTEMS, THAT MAY BE THE
CASE IN THE BIG PICTURE BUT TO
RIDERS ON A DAILY BASIS, YOU'RE
GOING TO GET SOME ARGUMENTS FROM
SOME PEOPLE HERE IN D.C. THAT
DON'T LOVE IT SO MUCH.
WHAT DID YOU FIND IS A POSITIVE
ABOUT THE SYSTEM HERE IN D.C.?
>> YEAH.
THINK POSITIVE IS THE SYSTEM
COVERS THE METROPOLITAN AREA
PRETTY WELL.
GENERALLY, IT'S PRETTY FAST AND
CONVENIENT.
SO THOSE ARE THE POSITIVE THINGS
I FOUND ABOUT THE SYSTEM.
>> AND THINGS THAT WE COULD
IMPROVE ON?
>> YEAH.
THINGS THAT COULD BE IMPROVED
ON.
OBVIOUSLY THE SYSTEM TODAY IS
CARRYING A LOT MORE PEOPLE THAN
IT WAS DESIGNED FOR INITIALLY.
SO SOMETIMES IT'S OVERCROWDED
DURING RUSH HOUR.
OBVIOUSLY THE SYSTEM HAS HAD
MAINTENANCE PROBLEMS, TRACK
FIRES AND THINGS LIKE THAT THAT
HAPPENED ON SOMEWHAT REGULAR
BASIS.
BUT YOU KNOW FOLLOWING THE
SYSTEM FROM A FAR IT DEFINITELY
SEEMS LIKE THINGS HAVE IMPROVED
THOUGH OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS,
BUT FOR SURE FIGURING OUT WAYS
TO GET MORE TRAINS MORE OFTEN
AND MOVE MORE PEOPLE THROUGH
THOSE STATIONS WOULD BE VERY
HELPFUL.
>> I'M GOING TO ASK YOU A COUPLE
QUESTIONS RAPID FIRE STYLE.
FIRST OF ALL, WAS THERE ANY
PARTICULAR LINE OR STOP THAT YOU
LIKED THE MOST WHEN YOU RODE ALL
117 MILES HERE IN D.C.?
>> YEAH.
I THINK MY FAVORITE STOPS ARE
THE TRANSFER STATIONS AND
PARTICULARLY I'M JUST A FAN OF
L'EFANT PLAZA.
I'M NOT SURE WHY.
I KNOW PIERRE L'EFANT ACTUALLY
DESIGNED THE ORIGINAL CITY OF
WASHINGTON, D.C. SO JUST
FASCINATED BY HIM AND I JUST
LOVE THAT TRANSFER STOP.
REALLY GREAT PLACE TO SEE
PEOPLE.
>> YOU ALSO SAY YOU CONSIDER
TRANSIT SYSTEMS TO BE SEXY.
JEROME, I GOT TO ASK YOU, ARE WE
A SEXY SYSTEM AND HOW DO YOU
CATEGORIZE SEXY WHEN IT COMES TO
METRO?
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY.
METRO IS DEFINITELY A VERY SEXY
SYSTEM.
AND YEAH, I'D CATEGORIZE IT AS
PRETTY SEXY FROM THE
ARCHITECTURE OF THE STATIONS TO
JUST THE LINES THEMSELVES AND
THE COVERAGE OF THE NETWORK.
IT'S A PRETTY SEXY SYSTEM WHEN
IT WORKS WELL.
>> WHEN IT WORKS WELL.
THAT IS THE KEY.
ALL RIGHT.
JEROME, WE LOOK FORWARD TO MORE
ANALYSIS FROM YOU.
I'M GLAD YOU HAD A CHANCE TO
CHICK OUT ALL 117 MILES.
THANKS FOR JOINING US THIS
MORNING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
TAKE CARE.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
JEROME GREW UP IN BALTIMORE.
ALL HIS DREAM GROWING UP TO RIDE
THE METRO IN D.C.
TOOK ADVANTAGE OF IT RIDING
EVERY SINGLE MILE.
>> YEAH, DID HE.
MAN HAS GOT A PASSION FOR IT.
THANKS, JEROME.
>>> LET'S HEAD ON OVER TO
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
WISDOM SPENDING THE MORNING IN
ALEXANDRIA WHERE THERE'S A
REALLY NEW COOL SPORTS TEAM
DRAWING IN BIG CROWDS.
WHAT'S GOING ON, WIS?
>> STEVE AND AL SOY SON, HAVE
YOU EVER HEARD OF FOOTS ALL?
NO.
>> I HAVE NOT.
>> WASN'T A RHETORICAL QUESTION.
YOU HAVE NOT.
ALLISON?
>> I HAVE ACTUALLY.
>> YOU HAVE?  OKAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT BUT I
HAVE HEARD THE TERM.
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
ALL ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW A LOT OF
PEOPLE IN ALEXANDRIA ARE GETTING
ON BOARD WITH THIS.
I HAVE MARK AND CHRIS HERE WITH
ME THEY'LL HE TELL US BOWS
FOOTSALL.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE BALL
BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE SOCCER AND
RUNNING AROUND LIKE SOCCER A NET
LIKE IN SOCCER BUT LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENT.
FIRST LET'S TALK ABOUT THE BALL.
>> YEAH, SO THE BALL IS ACTUALLY
ONE SIZE SMALLER THAN YOUR
TYPICAL SOCCER BALL.
>> UM-HMM.
>> ALSO WEIGHTED.
SO WHEN IT HITS THE GROUND
THERE'S NOT REALLY THAT MUCH
BOUNCE SO IT ALLOWS THE FREE
FLOWING PLAY TO KIND OF KEEP
FAST ACTION AND KIND OF KEEP
THINGS ROLLING.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHEN YOU DROP IT LET'S DO A
LITTLE TEST HERE ON LIFE TV IT
DOESN'T BOUNCE LIKE A SOCCER
BALL THEN IT --
>> A LOT SMALLER.
>> SO YEAH YOU CAN PICK IT UP
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT SMALLER.
TELL US -- I'LL GIVE THAT TO Y
YOU.
>> TELL US WHY THIS IS PICKED
UP?  THIS HAS BEEN AROUND FOR A
NUMBER OF YEARS HERE IN THIS
AREA BUT PICKING UP STEAM.
>> WE STARTED FUTSAL PROGRAM
SEVEN OR EIGHT YEARS AGO AND
REALLY IT WAS FOR US A WAY TO --
WE WANTED TO FIND A WAY TO KEEP
THE KIDS ACTIVE DURING THE
WINTER.
AND SO BETWEEN THE SOCCER
SEASONS WHICH TYPICALLY FALL
BETWEEN THE FALL AND SPRING
SEASON WE SAW AN OPPORTUNITY TO
FIND A WAY TO KEEP OUR KIDS
ACTIVE PLAYING HAVING FUN AND
ENJOYING THE ENVIRONMENT DURING
THE WINTER.
>> SO THERE'S LEAGUES AND REC
PLAY SO THERE'S ALL OF THE
ABOVE?
>> YES.
>> WE ACTUALLY HAVE A FUTSAL
LEAGUE THAT HOSTS 250 TEAMS
DURING THE WINTER.
WE HAVE A FUTSAL BALL PROGRAM
IT'S AN INTRODUCTION TO FUTAL
SKILLING BUILDING PROGRAM AND WE
ALSO HAVE OUR FUTTSAL PROGRAM.
>> IT'S FIVE ON FIVE UNGOT SUBS
AND THAT KIND OF THING, RIGHT.
>> CORRECT, YEAH.
IT'S LESS PLAYERS SO YOU'RE
LOOKING AT 5V5.
NOT YOUR INDOOR SOCCER WHERE YOU
CAN USE THE WALLS.
WE'RE LIMITED BY THE LINES.
SO REQUIRES A HIGHER LEVEL OF
TECHNIQUE AND TECHNICAL SKILLS
TO KEEP THE BALL IN PLAY AND
KEEP IT IN ACTION.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
COOL, COOL.
WE'RE TO THE DONE HERE.
WE'LL LEARN MORE ABOUT FUTSAL.
I KNOW YOU GOT TO GO TO SCHOOL.
RUN REAL QUICK SO EVERYBODY CAN
BE ON TV.
RUN, RUN, RUN, RUN, RUN.
YA'LL TIRED?
>> YEAH.
>> YA'LL GOT TO GO TO SCHOOL
TODAY.
EVERYBODY GET IN.
WHEN YOU GO TO SCHOOL YOU CAN
TELL THEM YOU ACTUALLY HAD AN
EXCUSE FOR BEING LATE BECAUSE
YOU WERE ON TV DOING FUTSAL.
>> EVERYBODY HAD A GOOD TIME OUT
HERE PLAYING FUTSA.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PART,
RUNNING?
>> DRIBBLING.
>> SCORING.
>> SHOOTING.
>> PASSING.
>> SCORING.
>> DOING DIFFERENT SKILLS.
>> GOOD, GOOD.
SHOOTING AND SCORING.
THOSE ARE ALSO MY FAVORITES AT
ANY SPORT I DO.
WE'LL LEARN MORE ABOUT FUTSAL.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> YA'LL HAVE A GOOD DAY.
WE'LL LEARN MORE ABOUT FUTSAL
THROUGHOUT THE SHOW.
MORE LESSONS COMING UP.
>> WHEN YOU SAID RUN YOU WERE SO
AUTHORITATIVE I WAS ABOUT TO
RUNWAY CROSS STUDIO.
HE SAID RUN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THANKS WISDOM.
I'M GOING TO DRAFT TUCKER NUMBER
ONE IN OUR FOX5 FUTSAL LEAGUE
SEASONED SOCCER PLAYER.
YOU CAN TRANSFER OVER.
>> PICK ME, PICK ME!
>> TAKES ME LIKE THIS TO MOVE
ACROSS THE SOCCER FIELD NOW.
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
WINDS OUT OF THE EAST AT FIVE.
FEELING LIKE 26.
WE ARE GOING TO BE IN FOR
BEAUTIFUL LOOKING DAY BUT A
CHILLY AFTERNOON AGAIN MOST OF
THE AREA HERE IN THE 20S TO
START THE MORNING.
SO MAKE SURE YOU'RE READY FOR A
COLD WINTER MORNING AS YOU HEAD
OUT.
OTHERWISE A NICE LOOKING DAY.
MID ATLANTIC COULDN'T BE
QUIETER.
TRAVELING TODAY I CAN TELL YOU
BIG PICTURE IT SHOULD BE NICE
QUIET DAY NOT A LOT HAPPENING
ACROSS THE EASTERN SEABOARD
HERE.
IN FACT MOST OF THE COUNTRY
FAIRLY QUITE TODAY.
CAN'T PROMISE THE SAME BY LATE
TOMORROW.
RAIN RETURNS SATURDAY LOOKS WET
AND SOGGY MAYBE A WINTRY MIX
CHANGING TO RAIN LATER MONDAY
INTO TUESDAY.
THAT TIME FRAME WE GOT TO WATCH
CAREFULLY.
WE'LL TWEET ABOUT IT IN A LITTLE
BIT.
ALL RIGHT.
STACEY.
>> THANKS TUCKER.
IT'S BEEN A BESTIE SEE COMMUTE
IN THE DMV.
LET'S TALK ABOUT TELEGRAPH ROAD.
IT WAS CLOSED EARLIER RIGHT AT
WILTON ROAD BECAUSE OF A CRASH.
THE CRASH HAS BEEN CLEARED AND
TELEGRAPH ROAD IS NOW REOPENED.
THEE 95 NORTHBOUND YOU'VE GOT
DELAYS FROM SEMINARY ROAD TO THE
14th STREET BRIDGE AND FINALLY
ON 66 EASTBOUND YOU'VE GOT YOUR
USUAL POCKETS OF TRAFFIC WITH
SPEEDS DOWN TO 10 MILES PER HOUR
IN THE THICK OF THINGS.
BACK TO YOU.
♪
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
♪
>>> ALL RIGHTY.
8:00 A.M. ON THIS -- ALMOST SAID
IT FRIDAY EVE.
IT'S THURSDAY MORNING.
WE LIKE TO CALL IT FRIDAY EVE
AROUND HERE.
>> GOOD MORNING.
WE'RE DOWN HERE IN THE
ASSIGNMENT DESK AREA OF OUR
NEWSROOM.
WE'RE CONTINUING TO TRACK YOUR
TOP STORIES THIS MORNING
INCLUDING WHEN IT COMES TO METRO
A HEADS UP FOR METRO RIDERS AS
WE COULD ONCE AGAIN SEE LENGTHY
DELAYS THAT COULD LAST FOR
MONTHS AND WE'LL TALK ABOUT
THAT.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT SUMMER.
>>> PLUS, REALLY IT'S EVERY
PARENT'S NIGHTMARE TALKING ABOUT
TRAGEDY IN NEW YORK CITY.
A COLLEGE STUDENT 18 YEARS OLD
MURDERED IN AN APPARENT ROBBERY
AND WE'RE LEARNING THAT THE
VICTIM HAD TIES TO VIRGINIA.
>>> ALSO ANOTHER WARNING ABOUT
HACKERS WHEN IT COMES TO
SECURITY CAMERAS.
SO WE'LL GET YOU THE INFORMATION
YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THAT.
FIRST THOUGH LET'S CHECK IN WITH
TUCKER AND STACEY GET A QUICK
CHECK HOUR ON WEATHER AND
TRAFFIC.
TUCK, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
>> THANKS, STEVE.
WEATHER WILL BE ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFULLY LOOKING TODAY BUT
IT'S COLD.
31 IN WASHINGTON.
20S OUT THERE.
I'LL HAVE ALL THE DETAILS ON A
FROSTY THURSDAY AND THEN A
SOMEWHAT STORMY WEEKEND.
DETAILS IN JUST A MINUTE.
STACEY.
>> THANKS, TUCKER.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY MORNING AND
WE'VE GOT PROBLEMS ON THE
FREEWAY RIGHT BEFORE YOU GET
INTO THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
WE'VE GOT A CRASH THAT'S CAUSING
SOME MAJOR DELAYS.
I'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT AND
GIVE YOU A COMPLETE LOOK AT DMV
COMING UP.
>>> ALL RIGHTY.
AND SPEAKING OF THE COMMUTE LAST
HOUR WE MET A MAN WHO ROAD EVERY
SINGLE INCH OF METRO BUT I'M
SURE -- ENJOYED IT BUT I'M SURE
RIDERS AROUND THESE PARTS WILL
BE SCRATCHING THEIR HEADS.
WHAT A HEADACHE TO COME IN A
COUPLE OF MONTHS AS WE GET READY
FOR MORE PLATFORM IMPROVEMENTS.
>> TALKING ABOUT THE ORANGE AND
SILVER LINE NORTHERN VIRGINIA
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT YOU RIGHT
NOW.
REPAIRS THAT COULD LAST FOR
MONTHS.
COULD IMPACT SHUT DOWN THREE
STATIONS IMPACT A FOURTH.
MELANIE ALNWICK OUT THERE THIS
MORNING IN VIENNA.
KEEPING AN EYE ON ALL THE
DETAILS FOR US.
MEL?
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GUYS.
SO THE VIENNA STATION HERE IS
CURRENTLY THE END OF THE ORANGE
LINE BUT THAT'S GOING TO CHANGE
WHEN THIS PLATFORM IMPROVEMENT
PROJECT BEGINS ONCE AGAIN OVER
THE SUMMER, AS THEY ARE NOW
SHUTTING DOWN THREE OF THE
STATIONS ON THE ORANGE LINE AT
THE VERY END FROM MEMORIAL DAY
UNTIL LABOR DAY.
YEAH IT'S GOING TO HAVE A BIG
IMPACT ON RIDERS.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE VIENNA
STATION DUNN LORING AND EAST
FALLS CHURCH THEY WILL BE UNDER
CONSTRUCTION 24/7 DURING THE MAT
FORM IMPROVEMENT PROJECT.
THEY'RE OLDER STATIONS SO THEY
CERTAINLY NEED NEW PLATFORMS UP
GRADES INCLUDE SLIPPERY SIFT TAN
TILES, BETTER LIGHTING, NEW
STAINLESS STEEL LAT FORM
SHELTERS WEREN'T CHARGING PORTS
AND NEW SURVEILLANCE SYSTEMS.
WEST FALLS CHURCH STATION WILL
REOPEN DURING ITS PLATFORM
RECONSTRUCTION BUT THERE WILL BE
SIGNIFICANT REDUCTION OF SERVICE
THERE AND THE WORK THAT WILL
ALSO SLOW DOWN SERVICE ON THE
SILVER LINE FROM MCLEAN TO
REALLY RESTON EAST AND
PASSENGERS ARE STARTING TO THINK
ABOUT HOW THEY'RE GOING TO GET
AROUND.
>> WE LIVE IN LIKE CHANTILLY
FAIRFAX AREA.
SO THIS IS LIKE THE ONLY WAY
THAT I'LL GO INTO D.C. BECAUSE I
DRIVING IN D.C. IS A NIGHTMARE.
I GUESS WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
DRIVE FARTHER WHICH KIND OF IS
NOT FUN.
>> Reporter: NOW AS BEFORE
METRO WILL PROVIDE SHUTTLE BUS
SERVICE AND ENCOURAGE PEOPLE TO
USE RIDE SHARE ALTERNATIVES.
THOSE DETAILS ARE GOING TO BE
FINALIZED IN MARCH AND OF COURSE
PUBLICIZED BY METRO AND BY US AS
WELL.
WE KNOW SHUTTLE BUS SERVICE THE
LAST TIME, GUYS, DID GET OFF TO
LITTLE BIT OF A ROUGH START, BUT
THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME THAT
THEY DID ALL OF THIS, SO THERE'S
HOPE PERHAPS THAT MAYBE IT WILL
GO A LITTLE SMOOTHER THIS TIME
AROUND.
GOT A LITTLE BIT OF TIME TO
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> MEL, THANKS VERY.
8:03.
DEVELOPING OVERNIGHT IN
ALEXANDRIA, NEW DETAILS NOW.
WE HAVE LEARNED IT WAS AN INFANT
WHO WAS RESCUED AFTER FLAMES
BROKE OUT INSIDE OF A FOUR-STORY
APARTMENT BUILDING.
THIS JUST AFTER MIDNIGHT ABOUT
1:00 O'CLOCK THIS MORNING IN THE
900 BLOCK OF NORTH PATRICK
STREET.
SMOKE HAD BEEN SHOWING FROM A
THIRD FLOOR UNIT WHEN CREWS
ARRIVED THEY ENTERED TO FIND
THAT FIRE IN THE KITCHEN DURING
A SEARCH OF THE APARTMENT
FIREFIGHTERS WERE ABLE TO LOCATE
THE INFANT WHO WAS THEN TREATED
BY PARAMEDICS OUTSIDE.
NO WORD ON THAT INFANT'S
CONDITION.
WE'LL HAVE MORE DETAILS FOR YOU
AS WE GET THEM.
>>> ALSO IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY,
FIREFIGHTERS RESPOND TO DO AND
EARLY MORNING FIRE IN WHITE
OAK85 FIREFIGHTERS RESPOND
TOLLING THAT FIRE ON COLUMBIA
PIKE.
FLAMES RIPPED THROUGH TWO
TOWNHOMES.
15 PEOPLE WITHOUT A PLACE TO
STAY, 10 ADULTS, FIVE CHILDREN
AND FOUR PETS.
THAT FIRE STARTED ON THE SECOND
FLOOR.
ABOUT $700,000 IN DAMAGES.
>>> DEVELOPING IN THE DISTRICT
NOW ON THIS THURSDAY 12-YEAR-OLD
BOY RECOVERING IN THE HOSPITAL
AFTER BEING SHOT IN NORTHEAST.
12 YEARS OLD.
THIS HAPPENED IN THE CLAY
TERRACE NEIGHBORHOOD ON DICKS
STREET JUST AFTER 9:00 LAST
NIGHT.
WE DON'T KNOW THE EXTENT OF THAT
BOY'S INJURIES.
WE DO KNOW THAT HE WAS BREA
BREATHING.
HE WAS CONSCIOUS WHEN HE WAS
TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL.
NO WORD ON SUSPECTS AT THIS
POINT.
>>> AND IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA,
ARLINGTON POLICE ON THE LOOK OUT
FOR A MAN ACCUSED OF TRYING TO
ABDUCT A 14-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
THIS HAPPENED ON TUESDAY NIGHT
AS SHE WAS WALKING A LITTLE BOY
HOME FROM SCHOOL IN ARLINGTON
HEIGHTS.
NOW AS THEY TURNED THE CORNER ON
TO SOUTH IRVING THAT GIRL
REALIZED THAT A MAN WAS
FOLLOWING THEM.
THAT SUSPECT GRABBED HER, BUT
SHE FOUGHT BACK AND THAT MAN RAN
OFF.
POLICE ARE HOPING SOMEONE IN THE
AREA MITT HAVE CAPTURED THE MAN
ON A HOME SECURITY CAMERA.
>> 8:05.
BIG NEWS THIS MORNING CHILLY OUT
THERE, TUCK.
>> PLAIN OLD COLD.
EVERYBODY BLOW FREEZING TO START
YOUR DAY.
LOTS OF 20S OUT THERE.
>> ONE OF OUR COLDEST MORNINGS
OF THE YEAR.
>> IT LOOKS NICE.
>> IT IS NICE.
IT WILL BE A BEAUTIFUL LOOKING
DAY.
GOING TO GET A LOT OF SUNSHINE.
IT WILL BE BRISK.
>> BLESS YOU.
I'M SO SORRY.
I APOLOGIZE PROFUSELY.
>> IT HAPPENS.
>> I HAVE A PROBLEM WHEN I
SNEEZE I'LL SNEEZE 27 TIMES IN A
ROW.
>> I TRIED TO STOP IT.
THERE ARE LOTS OF TRICKS.
NOTHING WORKED.
>> YOU HELL IT TOGETHER.
>> THANK YOU.
>> 31 AT REAGAN NATIONAL.
26 DULLES.
29BWI MARSHALL.
EVERYBODY OFF TO FROZEN START
HERE AND IT WILL BE VERY CHILLY
AFTERNOON WITH HIGHS IN THE
UPPER 30S.
THERE'S LIFE LOOK AT YOUR
SATELLITE/RADAR AND WE'RE
FEATURING QUITE TODAY.
SO LET'S TAKE THE BREAK BECAUSE
BY LATE FRIDAY AFTERNOON AND
THEN SATURDAY LOOKS LIKE A STORM
WILL BRING US A PERIOD OF RAIN
FOR MUCH OF SATURDAY AND PERHAPS
BY EARLY NEXT WEEK.
IN OTHER WORDS, WE GOT A STORMY
PATTERN AHEAD I'LL HAVE DETAILS
ON THAT.
BUT THERE'S A QUICK LOOK AT YOUR
WEEKEND FORECAST.
RAIN ON SATURDAY.
AND THEN PARTLY SUNNY ON SUNDAY.
NOTICE TEMPERATURES IN THE LOW
50S.
TODAY SUNSHINE 40 DEGREES THIS
AFTERNOON.
>> OKAY.
ENJOY THE DRY SKIES I GUESS.
>> MORE ON THE WEEKEND FORECAST
AND MAYBE A WINTRY MIX EARLY
NEXT WEEK COMING UP.
>> OH, YOU TEASE US, TUCKER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> TOO MUCH.
>> WOW!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE ARE STILL MONITORING
THAT CRASH ON THE FREEWAY THIS
MORNING.
THIS IS RIGHT BEFORE THE THIRD
STREET TUNNEL.
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS ALL THE WAY
BACK TO 395 BECAUSE OF THAT SO
YOU MAY WANT TO LEAVE A LITTLE
EARLY IF YOU'RE HEADING INTO THE
CITY.
IN ALEXANDRIA, WE HAD A CRASH
THIS MORNING RIGHT AT WILTON
ROAD AND TELEGRAPH ROAD.
IT CLOSED DOWN THAT PORTION OF
TELEGRAPH ROAD.
THE GOOD NEWS IS, IT HAS BEEN
REOPENED.
RESIDUAL DELAYS ARE LIGHT.
MOVING ON TO 395 NORTHBOUND,
YOU'VE GOT DELAYS FROM SEMINARY
ROAD TO THE 14th STREET
BRIDGE.
YOU CAN SEE LOTS OF PEOPLE ON
THE ROAD THIS MORNING IN THAT
VDOT SHOT.
AND 66 EASTBOUND FROM MANASSAS
TO THE BELTWAY IS AS IT SHOULD
BE.
WITH LITTLE POCKETS OF TRAFFIC
HERE AND THERE.
FINALLY, ON 270 SOUTHBOUND WE DO
HAVE A CRASH THAT HAS BEEN
REPORTED AFTER MONTROSE ROAD.
IT LOOK LIKE THAT WILL TIE YOU
UP QUITE A BIT THIS MORNING.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UP TO DATE AS
MORE INFORMATION COMES IN.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C. ON
TWITTER.
♪
>> WE HAVE NEW DETAILS COMING
OUT KNEE SEAL LAND THIS MORNING
IN THE EVIDENT TO TRY TO RECOVER
BODIES FROM THAT VOLCANO.
MILITARY SPECIALISTS WILL LAND
ON WHITE ISLAND TO TRY A DARING
RECOVERY TO BRING BACK THE
BODIES OF EIGHT VICTIMS AFTER
MONDAY'S ERUPTION.
SCIENTISTS BELIEVE ANOTHER
ERUPTION IS POSSIBLE.
IT IS CERTAINLY A RACE AGAINST
TIME BECAUSE RAIN IS SET TO MOVE
INTO THE AREA AND IF THAT RAIN
MIXES WITH VOLCANIC ASH IT COULD
CREATE A CONCRETE LIKE SUBSTANCE
ENCASED THE BODIES AND MAKE THE
RECOVERY AND IDENTIFICATION MORE
DIFFICULT.
>>> AS AUTHORITIES IN JERSEY
CITY, NEW JERSEY, CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE THE SHOOTING THAT
HAPPENED EARLIER THIS WEEK
LEAVING SIX PEOPLE DEAD, THE
FIRST VICTIMS HAVE BEEN LAID TO
REST.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE GATHERED TO
SAY FAIR REL TWO OF THOSE
VICTIMS LAST NIGHT.
ON TUESDAY A MAN AN WOMAN PULLED
UP TO THE KOSHER JEWISH MARKET
IN A STOLEN RENTAL VAN WITH GUNS
DRAWN AND STARTED FIRING AS THEY
ENTERED THE MARKET.
SIX PEOPLE DIED INCLUDING A
POLICE OFFICER.
THREE BYSTANDERS AND THE TWO
SHOOTERS.
AUTHORITIES STILL DO NOT KNOW A
MOTIVE ON THE ATTACK.
FEAR ARE MOUNTING THE SHOOTING
WAS ANTISEMITIC.
♪
>>> KNEW THIS MORNING,
18-YEAR-OLD COLLEGE STUDENT IS
DEAD AFTER SHE WAS BRUTALLY
ATTACKED IN NEW YORK CITY.
THERE ARE REPORTS SHE HAD TIES
TO VIRGINIA.
HOLLY IS IN THE NEWSROOM WITH
MORE NOW.
HOLLY, I SAID IT EARLIER, JUST
EVERY PAN'S NIGHTMARE WHEN YOU
SEND A CHILD OFF TO COLLEGE.
>> THERE WOULD BE NO
UNDERSTANDING THIS FOR SURE IF
IT WAS YOUR CHILD.
THE DETAILS REALLY ARE HORRIFIC,
THEY'RE TRAGIC, POLICE SAY IF
SHE WAS THE VICTIM OF A ROBBERY
GONE WRONG.
TESSA MAJORS WAS A FRESHMAN AT
BARNARD COLLEGE IN NEW YORK C
CITY.
REPORTEDLY FROM CHARLOTTESVILLE,
VIRGINIA.
HER FATHER IS A PROFESSOR AT
JAMES MADISON UNIVERSITY.
POLICE SAY SHE WAS WALKING
THROUGH A PARK IN UPPER
MANHATTAN LAST NIGHT WHEN SHE
WAS APPROACHED BY A GROUP OF
THREE OR FOUR MEN.
ONE OF THOSE SUSPECTS REPORTEDLY
JUST 16 YEARS OLD.
THOSE MEN ALLEGEDLY TRIED TO ROB
TESSA BEFORE STABBING HER
MULTIPLE TIMES IN THE STOMACH.
THE MEN THEN RAN AWAY.
TESSA MANAGED TO WALK TO NEARBY
STEPS HOWEVER SHE COLLAPSED IN
FRONT OF THE SECURITY GUARD
BOOTH.
NOW THE GUARD WAS ON PATROL AND
NOT ACTUALLY IN THE BOOTH AT THE
TIME.
THE GUARD FOUND HER A SHORT TIME
LATER AND CALLED 911.
BARNARD COLLEGE RELEASED A
STATEMENT SAYING IN PART, TESSA
WAS JUST BEGINNING HER JOURNEY
AT BARNARD AND IN LIFE.
WE MOURN THIS DEVASTATING MURDER
OF AN EXTRAORDINARY YOUNG WOMAN
AND MEMBER OF OUR COMMUNITY.
THE SCHOOL ALSO SAYS TESSA'S
PARENTS WERE EN ROUTE TO NEW
YORK CITY.
IT'S UNCLEAR IF THE SUSPECTINGS
ACTUALLY ROBBED TESSA OF
ANYTHING.
POLICE ARE STILL LOOKING FOR
THOSE SUSPECTS.
STEVE AND ALLISON.
>> HOLLY, THANKS VERY.
8:10.
STILL A AHEAD A WARNING ABOUT
RINK HOME SECURITY CAMERAS ONCE
AGAIN.
ONE FAMILY'S TERRIFYING ORDEAL
AFTER A HACKER GAINED ACCESS TO
THE CAMERA IN THEIR DAUGHTER'S
BEDROOM AND STARTED TALKING TO
THEIR EIGHT-YEAR-OLD.
>> PLUS, A HARROWING RESCUE
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
HEAR FROM THE MAN WHO JUMPED
INTO ACTION TO SAVE THAT LITTLE
DOG.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY.
♪
♪♪
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AS WE HEAD TO
BREAK.
♪
>> LOOK AT RIGHT UP THE ROAD IN
TENLEY TOWN FROM THE FOX5
STUDIOS.
>> OH, LOOK, IT'S LIZZO.
>> SHE'S ON TIME MAGAZINE.
♪
♪♪
>>> IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THIS YET
ON SOCIAL MEDIA TAKE A SECOND TO
WATCH IT IT IS A HEART STOPPING
MOMENT CAUGHT ON CAMERA IN TEXAS
INVOLVING A DOG AND A QUICK
THINKING MAN WHO JUMPED IN TO
HELP.
>> MY GOSH, THANK GOODNESS FOR
HIM.
TAKE A LOOK.
THAT DOG'S HOMEOWNER GOT ON TO
AN ELEVATOR.
SHE WALKED ON BUT SHE'S ON A
LEASH ON THE END OF THAT LEASH
HER SMALL DOG SHE ACCIDENTALLY
LEFT THAT DOG OUTSIDE OF THE
CLOSING DOORS THAT DOG WAS ON A
LEASH BUT THE OWNER WAS HOLDING
ON TO IT YOU KNOW WHAT THIS
COULD HAVE ENDED IN WHEN THE
ELEVATOR BEGAN TO MOVE THE MAN
KNEW HE ONLY HAD SHORT AMOUNT OF
TIME TO GET THAT LITTLE DOG FREE
FROM ITS LEASH AND SCRAMBLED TO
UNDO THE DOG'S COLLAR AND FREE
IT AND IT HAPPENED JUST IN TIME.
HERE HE IS.
>> THE DOG WAS SO FLUFF TEE I
COULDN'T GET TO IT EASILY YOU
SEE ME STRUGGLING TRYING UNDO
BECAUSE ALL THE FUR AROUND ITS
NECK.
I JUST HELD ON TO THE DOG THE
WHOLE TIME I COULD HEAR THE GIRL
BAWLING HER EYES OUT INSIDER THE
ELEVATOR FREAKING OUT.
>> OKAY.
YOU NEED TO HERO.
THERE'S YOUR HERO TODAY.
HE MANAGED TO FREE THAT LITTLE
SWEETHEART AND RETURN HIM TO HER
OWNER.
TO HIS OWNER.
YEAH.
>> JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
>> I DO LIKE THE THOUGHT.
AS A PET LOVER, I THOUGHT,
HONEY, PICK THAT BABY UP, LOOK
BEHIND YOU.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, IS HE ON THE
ELEVATOR WITH YOU?
>> SURE.
>> HE'S FILLING IN THE DETAILS
AND SAYING THAT SHE WAS ON THEIR
FREAKING OUT AND ALL OF THAT AND
SO, YEAH, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
SHE WAS REALLY SCARED TOO.
>> YUP.
THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JOB WELL DONE.
YESTERDAY WE DIDN'T HAVE THE
SNOW BUT WE DIDN'T CALL FOR THE
SNOW SO IT ALL WORK OUT.
THIRD OF AN INCH OF SNOW AT
REAGAN NATIONAL OFFICIALLY IN
THE RECORD BOOKS AS HAVING SNOW.
>> WE HAD IT.
>> HOW BIG IS THAT?
>> HERE'S AN INCH.
>> NOT MUCH.
>> THIRD OF AN INCH.
WE'LL BE FINE TODAY.
NICE AND QUIET.
COLD START TO THE DAY IN FACT
OVERNIGHT LOWS 2 20S LOOK ALL YR
20S EARLY THIS MORNING.
27 THIS MORNING BOWIE, GOOD
MORNING.
WALDORF, LA PLATA 27 DEGREES.
OUT IN ANNE ARUNDEL COUNTY
EDGEWATER 28.
24 IN LEESBURG.
VERY CHILLY TEMPERATURES LOCALLY
AND REGIONALLY HERE 21 THE
BOTTOM NUMBER OUT IN CUMBERLAND
GOING INTO OUR FRIENDS OUT IN
CUMBERLAND 21 IN MARTINSBURG AND
WINCHESTER CUMBERLAND --
CULPEPER 21.
YOU CAN SEE ONE OF OUR COLDEST
STARTS SO FAR THIS SEASON.
GOING TO BE BEAUTIFUL LOOKING
DAY.
HIGH PRESSURE OVERHEAD AND NICE
DWIGHT AFTERNOON FOR US IT WILL
BE A CHILLY AFTERNOON.
HIGHS IN THE UPPER 30S FOR MOST
OF US.
PERHAPS WE GET TO 40 IN DOWNTOWN
WASHINGTON.
AND WE'LL KEEP IT DRY TODAY.
CAN'T PROMISE WE'LL KEEP IT DRY
FOR TERRIBLY LONG PERIOD OF TIME
HERE AS RAIN WILL RETURN LATER
TOMORROW AND INTO THE DAY ON
SATURDAY.
SATURDAY IS GOING TO BE SOGGY
DAY.
SO IF YOU'RE GOING OUT TO GET A
CHRISTMAS TREE OR HEADED OUT
SHOPPING, YOU KNOW, JUST KIND OF
PLAN AHEAD HERE.
IT WILL BE A WET DAY WITH RAIN
MUCH OF THE DAY AND CHILLY
TEMPERATURES ON SATURDAY.
AND THEN I JUST WANT TO FOCUS
QUICKLY ON MONDAY AS IT LOOKS
LIKE WHEN THIS STORM MOVES IN ON
MONDAY IT'S A PROCESS CALLED
OVERRUNNING BUT POSSIBLE THAT'S
ONE OF OUR COMPUTER MODELS
SHOWING YOU THAT AT THE ONSET
HERE, WE PAY GET A PERIOD OF
WINTER WEATHER INCLUDING SNOW OR
PERHAPS A WINTRY MIX OF SLEET
MAYBE FREEZING RAIN MONDAY
AFTERNOON EARLY MONDAY EVENING
BEFORE IT TRANSITIONS OVER TO
ALL RAIN LATER MONDAY NIGHT.
SO THAT'S THE NEXT TIME PERIOD
TO KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR FOR
WINTER WEATHER.
AGAIN THAT WOULD BE MONDAY.
SO WE'RE IN GOOD SHAPE UNTIL
THEN.
40 THIS AFTERNOON SUNNY AND
COLD.
MORE ON WEATHER IN JUST A
MINUTE.
>> STACEY RUSH HAS YOUR MORNING
RUSH HOUR.
>> THANK YOU TUCKER.
I'LL TAKE THAT SUN.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE COLD BUT
I'LL TAKE THE SUN.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY COMMUTE IN THE
DMV THIS MORNING.
LET'S START WITH THE GOOD NEWS.
AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE LOOKS
PRETTY GOOD.
TRAFFIC IS AT SPEED.
95 AT MARYLAND 198 LOOKS GOOD.
NO PROBLEMS ON 395 AND DUKE
STREET.
HOWEVER, WHEN YOU LOOK AT 66 AND
THAT VDOT SHOT RIGHT AT 28 IT
LOOKS LIKE TRAFFIC IS MOVING AT
A CRAWL.
LOOKING AT 66 EASTBOUND, FROM
MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY, UM, I
GUESS THIS IS IN THE MIDDLE.
IT'S NOT GOOD, IT'S NOT BAD,
IT'S JUST WHAT YOU WOULD EXPECT
FOR A THURSDAY MORNING.
IN THE THICK OF THINGS YOU'RE
DOWN TO ABOUT 25 MILES AN HOUR.
AS WE MOVE OVER TO 95 NORTHBOUND
FROM DALE CITY TO THE BELTWAY,
TRAFFIC IS REALLY JUST CRAWLING.
YOU'RE DOWN TO 10 MILES PER HOUR
AT SOME POINT ON 95 NORTHBOUND
AND FINALLY, 395 NORTHBOUND
YOU'VE GOT SOME MAJOR DELAYS
FROM SEMINARY ROAD TO THE 14th
STREET BRIDGE.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
BACK TO YOU.
♪
>>> WELL NO SECRET THERE ARE
ON-GOING CONCERNS ABOUT HACKERS
GAINING ACCESS TO EVERY DAY
THINGS THAT WE HAVE IN OUR HO
HOMES.
>> THIS MORNING ONE FAMILY IS
LEARNING THE HARD WAY.
AFTER A HACKER GAINED ACCESS TO
A SECURITY CAMERA IN THEIR
DAUGHTER'S BEDROOM.
MAUREEN JOINS US WITH THIS
CREEPY MESSAGE THAT THE HACKER
HAD A FOR THAT LITTLE GIRL.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
THIS IS JUST SO FRIGHTENING LET
ME TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT THE
GIRL'S MOTHER SAYS SHE BOUGHT
THE CAMERA AS WAY TO KEEP AN EYE
ON HER THEE DAUGHTERS WHILE SHE
WAS AT WORK.
THE CAMERA WAS ONLY IN THE ROOM
FOR A FEW DAYS BEFORE HER
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER HEARD
SOMETHING STRANGE COMING FROM
THE CAMERA.
YOU'LL HEAR THE MUSIC THE MAN
PLAYED TO LURE THE LITTLE GIRL
INTO THE ROOM THEN NOTICE THE
GIRL WALKING AROUND THE ROOM
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE THE
MUSIC IS COMING FROM AND THEN
YOU'LL GOING TO HEAR SOME OF
WHAT HE SAID TO HER.
♪
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND.
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT
RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M SANTA CLAUS.
MOMMY!
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE MY BEST
>> I'M SANTA CLAUS.
FRIEND?
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE MY BEST
>> OH, MY GOODNESS SO
FRIEND?
FRIGHTENING EXCLAIM WENT ON FOR
>> OH, MY GOODNESS SO
NEARLY FIVE MINUTES UNTIL THE
FRIGHTENING EXCLAIM WENT ON FOR
GIRL WENT TO LOOK FOR HER DAD.
NEARLY FIVE MINUTES UNTIL THE
THE HACKER ALSO TRIED TO GET THE
GIRL WENT TO LOOK FOR HER DAD.
GIRL TO SAY A RACIAL SLUR.
THE HACKER ALSO TRIED TO GET THE
BUT THE FAMILY ISN'T SURE HOW
GIRL TO SAY A RACIAL SLUR.
LONG THE MAN WAS WATCHING THIS
BUT THE FAMILY ISN'T SURE HOW
LITTLE GIRL'S BEDROOM BEFORE HE
LONG THE MAN WAS WATCHING THIS
ACTUALLY BEGAN TALKING TO HER.
LITTLE GIRL'S BEDROOM BEFORE HE
THE FAMILY HAS SINCE DISCONNECT
ACTUALLY BEGAN TALKING TO HER.
THE CAMERA, OF COURSE, NOW RING
THE FAMILY HAS SINCE DISCONNECT
SAYS IT IS INVESTIGATING THE
THE CAMERA, OF COURSE, NOW RING
INCIDENT TO RELEASING A
SAYS IT IS INVESTIGATING THE
STATEMENT THAT SAYS IN PART,
INCIDENT TO RELEASING A
THIS INCIDENT IS NO WAY RELATED
STATEMENT THAT SAYS IN PART,
TO BREACH OR COMPROMISE OF
THIS INCIDENT IS NO WAY RELATED
RING'S SECURITY.
TO BREACH OR COMPROMISE OF
THE COMPANY REAFFIRM THE
RING'S SECURITY.
SECURITY STEPS PEOPLE SHOULD
THE COMPANY REAFFIRM THE
STAKE ARE TAKE INCLUDING ENABLE
SECURITY STEPS PEOPLE SHOULD
TWO FACTOR AUTHENTICATION ON
STAKE ARE TAKE INCLUDING ENABLE
THEIR RING ACCOUNT INSTEAD OF
TWO FACTOR AUTHENTICATION ON
SHARING, USE STRONG PASSWORDS
THEIR RING ACCOUNT INSTEAD OF
AND REGULARLY CHANGE YOUR
SHARING, USE STRONG PASSWORDS
PASSWORDS BUT AS YOU CAN SEE I'M
AND REGULARLY CHANGE YOUR
SURE THE FAMILY PROBABLY TOOK A
PASSWORDS BUT AS YOU CAN SEE I'M
LOT OF THESE STEPS BUT TO THINK
SURE THE FAMILY PROBABLY TOOK A
THAT THIS DEVICE COULD LET IN
LOT OF THESE STEPS BUT TO THINK
LITERAL AL STRANGER IN YOUR
THAT THIS DEVICE COULD LET IN
HOME, YOUR CHILD'S BEDROOM, IT'S
LITERAL AL STRANGER IN YOUR
CHILLING.
HOME, YOUR CHILD'S BEDROOM, IT'S
>> FOR HER TO SCREAM MOMMY AND
CHILLING.
FOR HIM TO CONTINUE.
>> FOR HER TO SCREAM MOMMY AND
>> MY GOSH.
FOR HIM TO CONTINUE.
>> WHAT A DESPICABLE PERSON
>> MY GOSH.
FIRST OF ALL.
>> WHAT A DESPICABLE PERSON
>> ABSOLUTELY.
FIRST OF ALL.
>> FIRST UP WHAT'S WRONG WITH
>> ABSOLUTELY.
PEOPLE UNFORTUNATELY WE'VE SEEN
>> FIRST UP WHAT'S WRONG WITH
THAT HAPPENS E SECOND OF ALL WE
PEOPLE UNFORTUNATELY WE'VE SEEN
TAKE IT AS A WARNING MAUREEN I'M
THAT HAPPENS E SECOND OF ALL WE
PERSONALLY TIRED OF THE
TAKE IT AS A WARNING MAUREEN I'M
COMPANIES THAT SAY IT'S YOUR
PERSONALLY TIRED OF THE
FAULT FOR NOT HAVING A STRONG
COMPANIES THAT SAY IT'S YOUR
ENOUGH PASSWORD.
FAULT FOR NOT HAVING A STRONG
>> GIVE ME A BREAK.
ENOUGH PASSWORD.
>> CLEARLY IT WAS A BREACH OF
>> GIVE ME A BREAK.
SECURITY.
>> CLEARLY IT WAS A BREACH OF
>> ABSOLUTELY IT WAS.
SECURITY.
YOU'LL FIND RINK MAKING
>> ABSOLUTELY IT WAS.
ADJUSTMENTS OR COMING OUT WITH
YOU'LL FIND RINK MAKING
ANOTHER STATEMENT IN THE DAYS TO
ADJUSTMENTS OR COMING OUT WITH
COME.
ANOTHER STATEMENT IN THE DAYS TO
THE GOOD NEWS THE LITTLE GIRL IS
COME.
OKAY.
THE GOOD NEWS THE LITTLE GIRL IS
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'VE CAUGHT
OKAY.
THIS PERSON.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'VE CAUGHT
>> HE'S MOTION ALLEY THAT'S A
THIS PERSON.
LOT.
>> HE'S MOTION ALLEY THAT'S A
>> I KNOW.
LOT.
IT'S CHILLING ANY WAY YOU CUT IT
>> I KNOW.
IT'S CHILLING.
IT'S CHILLING ANY WAY YOU CUT IT
>> YOU THINK SOMEBODY IS ALWAYS
IT'S CHILLING.
WATCHING.
>> YOU THINK SOMEBODY IS ALWAYS
>> 8:20.
WATCHING.
UP NEXT YOU MAY HAVE TAKEN SICK
>> 8:20.
DAYS FROM WORK WHAT ABOUT A
UP NEXT YOU MAY HAVE TAKEN SICK
HANGOVER DAY?  THE COMPANY --
DAYS FROM WORK WHAT ABOUT A
SAME THING.
HANGOVER DAY?  THE COMPANY --
>> THAT ENCOURAGES ITS EMPLOYEES
SAME THING.
TO DO SO.
>> THAT ENCOURAGES ITS EMPLOYEES
>> I THINK IT'S THE SAME THING,
TO DO SO.
RIGHT?  YOU'RE SICK TECHNICALLY.
>> I THINK IT'S THE SAME THING,
SO WE'LL GET INTO THAT, PLUS
RIGHT?  YOU'RE SICK TECHNICALLY.
WISDOM IS LIVE ON LOCATION IN
SO WE'LL GET INTO THAT, PLUS
ALEXANDRIA.
WISDOM IS LIVE ON LOCATION IN
WHAT'S UP, COACH?
ALEXANDRIA.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S UP, COACH?
SO WHAT'S UP IS WE'RE LEARNING
>>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL ABOUT FUTSAL.
SO WHAT'S UP IS WE'RE LEARNING
HOW IT'S DIFFERENT FROM SOCCER.
ALL ABOUT FUTSAL.
WE'LL TALK TO SOME OF THE MARES
HOW IT'S DIFFERENT FROM SOCCER.
INVOLVED IN THIS AND WHY IT'S
WE'LL TALK TO SOME OF THE MARES
SUCH A FAST-GROWING SUPPORT IN
INVOLVED IN THIS AND WHY IT'S
THE ALEXANDRIA AREA ON MANY
SUCH A FAST-GROWING SUPPORT IN
DIFFERENT LEVELS WHEN FOX5
THE ALEXANDRIA AREA ON MANY
MORNING CONTINUES AFTER THE
DIFFERENT LEVELS WHEN FOX5
BREAK.
MORNING CONTINUES AFTER THE
♪
♪♪
So you have ten years
experience...
I do.
but no PhD?
I do have a masters in early
childhood development.
you don't mind if I record this,
do you?
Uhh, no!
First Kid.
here's all the numbers, food's
in the fridge,
oh and Lucas likes to pull on
jewelry
so you might want to lose the
nose ring.
By their second kid, parents are
more likely to choose Luvs.
It absorbs 20x its weight
and the Triple Leakguards lock
away wetness
for outstanding leakage
protection.
Live, Learn, and Get Luvs.
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
>> 8:23.
UPDATE A STORY WE BROUGHT YOU A
SHORT TIME AGO.
THAT OVERNIGHT APARTMENT FIRE IN
ALEXANDRIA YOU SAW SOMEBODY
BEING WHEELED OFF THERE ON A
STRETCHER.
WE KNOW THAT NOW THERE WAS AN
ADULT WHO WAS TRANSPORTED IN
ADDITION TO THE INFANT WHO WAS
RESCUED.
THAT INFANT JUST SIX MONTHS OLD.
TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL FOR
OBSERVATION.
THERE YOU SEE THE ADULT WHO WAS
ALSO TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL AND
23 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN DISPLACED BY
THIS FIRE IN ALEXANDRIA.
STILL NO WORD ON THE CAUSE.
BELIEVED TO HAVE BROKEN OUT IN A
KITCHEN, THOUGH, OVERNIGHT.
>>> BLEEP.
GIANT BLEEP.
>> HOLIDAY LIGHT DISPLAY IN
KANSAS TURNING HEADS FOR ALL THE
WRONG REASONS.
THE DISPLAY CAN'T BE SHOWN ON
MORNING TELEVISION BUT LET'S
JUST SAY IT'S DEFINITELY NOT
SAFE FOR WORK EITHER.
THE WOMAN WHO CREATED IT DID SO
BY USING 60 FEET OF HOLIDAY
LIGHTS.
SHE SAID HER INTENTION WAS TO
GET PEOPLE TO LAUGH.
HOWEVER, NEIGHBORS DON'T THINK
IT'S FUNNY.
SHE HAS SINCE TAKEN IT DOWN.
>> INTERESTING WHICH PART OF WE
CHOSE TO BLUR.
ANY WAY, 8:25.
LET'S GET OVER TO STACEY AND
TUCKER FOR A CHECK OF THE
FORECAST.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
>> NOT GOING TO LIE.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT IT IS NOW.
>> I THINK YOU CAN FIGURE IT O
OUT.
>> THAT'S AWFUL.
FOR KIDS WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT.
>> I'M OUTRAGED.
>> ALLISON, ARE YOU WITH ME.
>> WHAT ARE THEY DOING.
>> WHAT ARE THEY THINKING.
>> WAWA ARE THEY THINKING?
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
31 IN WASHINGTON.
CHILLY TEMPERATURES TO START
YOUR DAY.
20S FOR MOST EVERYBODY ELSE.
IT'S GOING TO BE A VERY COOL
AFTERNOON ONLY -- ONLY REACH THE
UPPER 30S TO ABOUT 40 LATER
TODAY.
QUIET DAY WITH PLENTY OF
SUNSHINE DRY CONDITIONS LATER
TODAY.
RAIN SHOWERS RETURN LATE FRIDAY
IT'S GOING TO BE WET SOGGY
SATURDAY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE THAT ENDS AS A FLURRY ON
SUNDAY DON'T BE TOO CONCERNED.
BUT WE ARE MORE CONCERNED ABOUT
MONDAY.
POSSIBLE WINTER MIX THEN CHANGES
OVER TO RAIN MONDAY NIGHT BUT WE
MIGHT START WITH A PERIOD OF
SNOW MONDAY AFTERNOON.
STACEY.
>> THANKS TUCKER.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY MORNING IN THE
DMV.
PARTICULARLY BUSY ON THE FREEWAY
RIGHT BEFORE THE THEIR STREET
TUNNEL.
YOU'VE GOT MAJOR DELAYS BECAUSE
OF A CRASH THIS MORNING.
270 SOUTHBOUND IS LOOKING JUST
AS IT SHOULD FROM FREDERICK TO
THE BELTWAY WITH LITTLE POCKETS
OF TRAFFIC HERE AND THERE.
AND YOUR MARYLAND DRIVE IS OKAY
IN THE THICK OF THINGS YEAR DOWN
TO 10 MILES AN HOUR ON THE OUTER
LOOP.
STEVE, ALLISON?
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD EIGHT COT 30
TECHNOLOGY TO THE RESCUE.
>> YOU'LL MEET THE MARYLAND
TEENAGER WHO USED A POPULAR GAME
TO HELP SAVE HIS CHILDHOOD
SCHOOL.
WE'LL TELL YOU HOW IT ALL WORK
OUT AND WE'LL MEET HIM COMING
UP.
STAY WITH US.
♪
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get
a speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
I'm Jimmy Dean and uh,
at no additional
charge.
I wish I could tell ya how I
feel about a mornin' like this.
And that includes a
good hearty breakfast.
You need somethin' to kinda
warm the whole body up
and gets it going.
It's a great way to
kick off your day.
♪ CHEST NUTS ROASTING ON AN
OPEN FIRE ♪
>> COMING ON 8:30 ON THIS
THURSDAY MORNING PASSION WE HEAD
TO MONTGOMERY COUNTY AND TAKE A
LOOK AT THE CHRISTMAS TREE IN
RIO IN GAITHERSBURG.
LOOKS A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN IT
DID YESTERDAY MORNING WHEN HAD
SNOWFLAKES ON IT.
TODAY NOTHING BUT SUNSHINE AND
COOL TEMPERATURES.
SPEAKING OF MONTGOMERY COUNTY
WHAT WERE YOU DOING WHEN YOU
WERE IN HIGH SCHOOL?  MAYBE YOU
ENJOYED PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
WHAT BETHESDA TEEN USING A
POPULAR GAME TO HELP SAVE HIS
CHILDHOOD SCHOOL FROM CLOSING.
SAINT BARTHOLOMEW SCHOOL FACING
LOW ENROLLMENT NUMBERS THE TEEN
ADVOCATED FOR THE SCHOOL TO USE
THE EDUCATION EDITION OF MIND
CRAFT IN HOPES OF ATTRACTING
MORE STUDENTS.
OTHERS STEPPED IN TO HELP OUT.
JOINING MOW NOW THAT TEEN
PRESTON AND CHRISTIAN A TEACHER.
THANKS FOR JOINING.
>> PRESTON I WANT TO START WITH
YOU.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE THIS WAS
SOMETHING YOU WANTED TO DO?
>> BECAUSE I BELIEVE THAT
STUDENTS LEARN VERY WELL WHEN
THEY'RE ABLE TO EXPRESS THEIR
CREATIVITY AND THEIR LEARNING IN
THEIR CLASSROOM ENVIRONMENT AND
MIND CRAFT IS A GREAT WAY OF
DOING THIS.
I BELIEVE AND TEACHERS ARE WELL
ABLE TO USE THIS TO TEACH
STUDENTS IN VARIOUS WAYS LIKE
MAYBE THEY COULD TEACH A HISTORY
EXHIBIT BY INSTEAD OF MAYBE
LOOKING AT A TEXTBOOK THEY COULD
ACTUALLY SHOW A VERSION OF THE
HISTORY HISTORICAL BUILDING IN
MIND CRAFT THE STUDENTS COULD
EXPLORE AND SHAPE TO THEIR LI
LIKING AND I BELIEVE THAT'S A
GREAT WAY TO LEARN.
>> DIFFERENT PERSPECTIVE ON
LEARNING.
CHRIS, HOW DO YOU APPLY THAT I
GUESS TO THE REAL WORLD OF THE
CLASSROOM TALKING ABOUT THESE
STUDENTS?
>> CERTAINLY IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR THEM TO ENGAGE COLLABORATE
AND CREATE REALLY THE MOST FUN
PART ABOUT MINE CRAFT THE
ABILITY TO WHAT ENGAGES THE
STUDENTS AND AS ALWAYS,
EVERYTHING IS SUPPLEMENTED SO
IT'S NOT JUST TAKING A LOOK AT
VIDEOS OR AS PRESTON SAID THE
TEXTBOOK BUT AN OPPORTUNITY FOR
THEM TO ACTUALLY GO IN A WORLD
CREATE, EXPLORE, AND YOU CAN
ALWAYS SET UP LEARNING OBJECTIVE
ALONG THE WAY.
>> PRESTON, YOU'RE NOW AT ST.
JOHN'S HIGH SCHOOL.
THIS IS YOUR FORMER SCHOOL THAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO HELP OUT NOW.
WHY DID YOU WANT -- WHY THIS
PARTICULAR SCHOOL AND WHY DID
YOU WANT TO THEY WILL THEM OUT
SO MUCH.
>> I SPENT EIGHT YEARS AT SAINT
BARTHOLOMEW SCHOOL AND I BELIEVE
THAT THE SCHOOL MADE ME INTO THE
MAN I AM, AND I BELIEVE THAT
IT'S IMPORTANT TO GIVE BACK AND
GIVE THESE STUDENTS EVEN MORE
OPPORTUNITIES TO LEARN AND -- IT
JUST I BELIEVE THAT MORE
STUDENTS SHOULD HAVE THE
EXPERIENCE THAT I HAD.
>> YEAH.
AND AS FAR AS MAKING THE PITCH I
GUESS TO GET THIS DONE, HOW DID
YOU GO ABOUT DOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT THIS HAPPENED?
>> WELL, AS SOON AS I LEARNED OF
SOME -- AS SOON AS I LEARNED OF
DIFFICULTY AT SAINT BART'S I
REALIZED I HAD TO ACT AND I HAD
TO ACT QUICKLY, SO I WORKED WITH
MY PARENTS WHO AGREED TO PAY FOR
ALL THE LICENSING, THANK YOU,
BECAUSE THEY ARE VERY SUPP
SUPPORTIVE, AND I WORKED WITH
MICROSOFT PARTNER TO TRAIN ALL
OF THE TEACHERS AND ACTUALLY
LICENSE THE GAME IN THE COMPUTER
LAB.
>> THAT IS GREAT.
I KNOW YOU'RE BIG INTO CODING
YOURSELF, RIGHT?  IN SCHOOL AND
OUT OF SCHOOL.
WHICH ISANTASTIC AND A GREAT
SKILL TO PASS ALONG.
SO CHRIS, WHEN WE LOOK AT THE
BIG PICTURE OF THINGS NOW, UM,
HOW CLOSE WERE WE AS FAR AS
SAINT BART'S TO NOT BEING AROUND
ANY MORE, AND HAS THIS MADE AN
IMPACT ON THE BIG PICTURE OF
THINGS?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ADVERSITY BUILDS -- DOESN'T
BUILD CHARACTER IT REVEALS IT
AND THE RESPONSE FROM THE
STUDENTS, THE PARENTS, ALUMNI,
THE COMMUNITY HAS BEEN
ABSOLUTELY AMAZING THANKS TO OUR
WONDERFUL FATHER, WONDERFUL
PRINCIPAL, FRANK ENGLISH THE
OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT HAS BEEN
PREE TREMENDOUS AND COMMUNITY
RESPONSE THANKS TO FAMILIARS
LILIKELY HULLS HAS BEEN ABSOLUTY
WONDERFUL.
>> IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE SEVERAL
LESSONS HERE.
OBVIOUSLY ONE BEING THE IN
CLASSROOM LESSON WHAT YOU CAN
LEARN AND TAKE AWAY FROM THIS
STYLE OF LEARNING MINE CRAFT OR
HOWEVER YOU WANT TO INN CORP.
IT.
>> THE OTHER LESSON IS, FOR THE
CURRENT STUDENTS MAYBE HOW YOU
LOOK AT SOMEBODY LIKE PRESTON
JUST A STUDENT THERE A FEW YEARS
AGO ALREADY LOOKING TO GIVE BACK
TO TRY TO HELP OTHERS AT THE
SCHOOL.
HOW DO YOU INCORPORATE THAT INTO
THE LESSON PLAN?
>> CERTAINLY.
GOOD TEACHERS WILL TAKE THE TIME
TO LEARN THE STUDENTS, MEET THEM
THE BEST CLASSES ALWAYS BEEN
STUDENT LED.
SO THIS IS WONDERFUL OPPORTUNITY
FOR STUDENTS REALLY TO TAKE
OWNERSHIP OF THEIR LEARNING AND
IT'S TIME FOR THE TEACHERS TO
ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO RELY ON
STUDENTS LIKE -- FORMER STUDENTS
TO PRESTON TO SHOW US SOME OF
THE BRAND NEW WAYS OF LEARNING
AND BEST WAYS TO REACH OUR
STUDENTS.
>> PRESTON YOU GOT BIG CHANGES
COMING UP FOR YOU TOO.
GRADUATING HEADING OFF TO THE
NEXT STEP IN YOUR LIFE.
HOW GOOD DOES IT MAKE YOU FEEL
YOU'RE CONTRIBUTING TO SOME OF
THE OTHERS AT YOUR FORMER
SCHOOL?
>> I BELIEVE IT'S IMPORTANT.
I DO BELIEVE THAT GIVING BACK IS
IMPORTANT, AND THIS EXPERIENCE
HAS ALLOWED ME TO INTERACT WITH
MY COMMUNITY AGAIN AND I'M
REALLY THANKFUL FOR THE
EXPERIENCE.
>> IMPORTANT LESSONS IN LIFE AND
IN THE CLASSROOM.
GREAT JOB, PRESTON, ON ALL AND
CHRIS, I LOPE THIS WORKS OUT IN
THE BIGGER PICTURE, TOO, FOR THE
STUDENTS FOR THE SCHOOL ITSELF.
THANK YOU BOTH FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> JOB WELL DONE.
>> LET'S GET OVER TO TUCKER.
>> THANK YOU.
WE STARTED OUT BY SHOWING THAT
>> LET'S GET OVER TO TUCKER.
CHRISTMAS TREE AT RIO.
WE STARTED OUT BY SHOWING THAT
WE SEE NATIONAL HARBOR IN PRINCE
CHRISTMAS TREE AT RIO.
GEORGE'S COUNTY BUT, MAN N BLUE
WE SEE NATIONAL HARBOR IN PRINCE
SKIES FOLLOWING US EVERYWHERE
GEORGE'S COUNTY BUT, MAN N BLUE
TODAY.
SKIES FOLLOWING US EVERYWHERE
>> ABSOLUTELY GOING TO BE
TODAY.
BEAUTIFUL DAY, AND IT'S GOING TO
>> ABSOLUTELY GOING TO BE
START, YOU KNOW, IT FEELS LIKE
BEAUTIFUL DAY, AND IT'S GOING TO
WINTERTIME OUT THERE EARLY THIS
START, YOU KNOW, IT FEELS LIKE
MORNING.
WINTERTIME OUT THERE EARLY THIS
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE 20S.
MORNING.
AND EVEN WITH THAT BRIGHT
OVERNIGHT LOWS BACK IN THE 20S.
SUNSHINE WE'RE EXPECTING TODAY,
AND EVEN WITH THAT BRIGHT
MAYBE WE GET IN THE UPPER 30S TO
SUNSHINE WE'RE EXPECTING TODAY,
ABOUT 40.
MAYBE WE GET IN THE UPPER 30S TO
SO HIGH PRESSURE REAL DEAL HERE
ABOUT 40.
WITH VERY COLD AIR MASS IN PLACE
SO HIGH PRESSURE REAL DEAL HERE
EARLY THIS MORNING.
WITH VERY COLD AIR MASS IN PLACE
20 IN PITTSBURGH.
EARLY THIS MORNING.
13 IN BINGHAMTON.
20 IN PITTSBURGH.
26 IN NEW YORK CITY.
13 IN BINGHAMTON.
27 IN BOSTON.
26 IN NEW YORK CITY.
BOSTON SOME OF NEW ENGLAND WITH
27 IN BOSTON.
OUR LITTLE STORM THAT GAVE US
BOSTON SOME OF NEW ENGLAND WITH
THIRD OF AN INCH OF SNOW THEY
OUR LITTLE STORM THAT GAVE US
GOT TWO TO 4 INCHES UP THERE.
THIRD OF AN INCH OF SNOW THEY
THEY GOT THE JACKPOT WITH THAT
GOT TWO TO 4 INCHES UP THERE.
STORM YETTER.
THEY GOT THE JACKPOT WITH THAT
VERY VERY QUIET CONDITIONS UP
STORM YETTER.
AND DOWN THE MID ATLANTIC.
VERY VERY QUIET CONDITIONS UP
WE LOOK GREAT LATER THIS
AND DOWN THE MID ATLANTIC.
AFTERNOON.
WE LOOK GREAT LATER THIS
AGAIN HIGH PRESSURE KEEPS THINGS
AFTERNOON.
NICE AND DRY.
AGAIN HIGH PRESSURE KEEPS THINGS
IT WILL NOT STAY THIS WAY FOR A
NICE AND DRY.
VERY LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
IT WILL NOT STAY THIS WAY FOR A
IN FACT BY TOMORROW A DEVELOPING
VERY LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
STORM SYSTEM ACROSS THE NORTHERN
IN FACT BY TOMORROW A DEVELOPING
GULF WILL PUSH CLOUDS INTO OUR
STORM SYSTEM ACROSS THE NORTHERN
LEGION BY LATE FRIDAY AFTERNOON,
GULF WILL PUSH CLOUDS INTO OUR
FRIDAY EVENING A FEW SHOWERS
LEGION BY LATE FRIDAY AFTERNOON,
AROUND, AND THE SHOWERS IN FACT
FRIDAY EVENING A FEW SHOWERS
THE STEADY RAIN WILL CONTINUE ON
AROUND, AND THE SHOWERS IN FACT
AND OFF THROUGHOUT THE DAY ON
THE STEADY RAIN WILL CONTINUE ON
SATURDAY.
AND OFF THROUGHOUT THE DAY ON
SO I'LL HAVE MORE ON THE WEEKEND
SATURDAY.
FORECAST COMING UP BUT HERE'S
SO I'LL HAVE MORE ON THE WEEKEND
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
FORECAST COMING UP BUT HERE'S
SUNSHINE TODAY ABOUT 40.
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
THEN WE'LL CLOUD UP WITH SOME
SUNSHINE TODAY ABOUT 40.
LATE DAY RAIN FOR YOUR FRIDAY
THEN WE'LL CLOUD UP WITH SOME
AND AGAIN WE'LL DOT WEEKEND
LATE DAY RAIN FOR YOUR FRIDAY
FORECAST AND GUESS WHAT?
AND AGAIN WE'LL DOT WEEKEND
POSSIBILITY OF ANOTHER ROUND OF
FORECAST AND GUESS WHAT?
WINTRY MIX FOR THE REGION BY
POSSIBILITY OF ANOTHER ROUND OF
MONDAY.
WINTRY MIX FOR THE REGION BY
WE'LL LOOK AT THAT IN JUST A
MONDAY.
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
WE'LL LOOK AT THAT IN JUST A
STACEY RUSH, BACK TO YOU.
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
>> WOW.
STACEY RUSH, BACK TO YOU.
SAY IT AIN'T SO, TUCKER.
>> WOW.
NO MORE SNOW.
SAY IT AIN'T SO, TUCKER.
ALL RIGHT.
NO MORE SNOW.
SO THE ROADS HAVE BEEN BUSY THIS
ALL RIGHT.
MORNING.
SO THE ROADS HAVE BEEN BUSY THIS
LET'S START WITH 270 SOUTHBOUND.
MORNING.
WE HAVE A CRASH THAT'S BLOCKING
LET'S START WITH 270 SOUTHBOUND.
THE RIGHT LANE RIGHT BEFORE
WE HAVE A CRASH THAT'S BLOCKING
MARYLAND 80 THAT DEFINITELY SLOW
THE RIGHT LANE RIGHT BEFORE
YOU DOWN.
MARYLAND 80 THAT DEFINITELY SLOW
66 EASTBOUND IS SLOW AT TIMES.
YOU DOWN.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD
66 EASTBOUND IS SLOW AT TIMES.
EXPECT FOR THIS TIME OF MORNING
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD
FROM MAN NASS TO THE BELTWAY.
EXPECT FOR THIS TIME OF MORNING
AS WE MOVE ON TO 95 NORTHBOUND,
FROM MAN NASS TO THE BELTWAY.
DALE STOW TO THE BELTWAY IS
AS WE MOVE ON TO 95 NORTHBOUND,
SLOWLY BUT SURELY MOVING.
DALE STOW TO THE BELTWAY IS
YOU'VE GOT LITTLE POCKS OF
SLOWLY BUT SURELY MOVING.
TRAFFIC HERE AND THERE WITH
YOU'VE GOT LITTLE POCKS OF
SPEEDS DOWN TO ABOUT 20 MILES
TRAFFIC HERE AND THERE WITH
PER HOUR IN THE MOST CONGESTED
SPEEDS DOWN TO ABOUT 20 MILES
AREAS.
PER HOUR IN THE MOST CONGESTED
THEE 95 NORTHBOUND WE'VE GOT
AREAS.
YOUR TYPICAL DELAYS FROM
THEE 95 NORTHBOUND WE'VE GOT
SEMINARY ROAD TO THE 14th
YOUR TYPICAL DELAYS FROM
STREET BRIDGE.
SEMINARY ROAD TO THE 14th
AND AS WE LOOK AT THE SOUTHEAST
STREET BRIDGE.
SOUTHWEST FREEWAY, WE DO HAVE A
AND AS WE LOOK AT THE SOUTHEAST
CRASH RIGHT BEFORE THE THIRD
SOUTHWEST FREEWAY, WE DO HAVE A
STREET TUNNEL CAUSING SOME MAJOR
CRASH RIGHT BEFORE THE THIRD
DELAYS THIS MORNING.
STREET TUNNEL CAUSING SOME MAJOR
SO YOU MAY WANT TO HEAD OUT
DELAYS THIS MORNING.
EARLIER IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON
SO YOU MAY WANT TO HEAD OUT
THE FREEWAY THIS MORNING.
EARLIER IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON
MARYLAND DRIVE IS EXACTLY WHAT
THE FREEWAY THIS MORNING.
YOU WOULD EXPECT WITH SOME
MARYLAND DRIVE IS EXACTLY WHAT
TRAFFIC ON THE OUTER LOOP.
YOU WOULD EXPECT WITH SOME
HOWEVER, 95 AND THE BALTIMORE
TRAFFIC ON THE OUTER LOOP.
WASHINGTON PARKWAY LOOK GOOD.
HOWEVER, 95 AND THE BALTIMORE
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
WASHINGTON PARKWAY LOOK GOOD.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
UM NEXT FROZEN TWO SO POPULAR.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
SO WHY IS DISNEY GETTING SUED
UM NEXT FROZEN TWO SO POPULAR.
OVER THE MOVIE?
SO WHY IS DISNEY GETTING SUED
>> PLUS YOU'VE HEARD OF SICK
OVER THE MOVIE?
DAYS FROM WORK, RIGHT?  BUT WHAT
>> PLUS YOU'VE HEARD OF SICK
ABOUT A HANGOVER DAY?  THE
DAYS FROM WORK, RIGHT?  BUT WHAT
COMPANY THAT ACTUALLY ENCOURAGES
ABOUT A HANGOVER DAY?  THE
ITS EMPLOYEES TO CALL IT WHAT IT
COMPANY THAT ACTUALLY ENCOURAGES
IS.
ITS EMPLOYEES TO CALL IT WHAT IT
A DRUNK.
IS.
♪
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately to
severely active Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed relief
and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house needs
or recently had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how Janssen can help
you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start with
STELARA®.
♪
>>> BACK NOW AT 8:40.
SO DISNEY BEING SUED FOR USING
THE PHRASE TRUST YOUR JOURNEY AS
PART OF ITS FROZEN TWO RELEASE.
COMPANY IN NEVADA SAYS IT HAS
USED THAT PHRASE FOR YEARS AND
FIRST.
TMZ REPORTING TRUST YOUR JOURNEY
IS ACTUAL THE NAME OF THE
COMPANY.
IT CLAIMS THE PHRASE IS ALREADY
USED ON TRUST YOUR JOURNEY'S OWN
PRODUCTS.
THEY CLAIM DISNEY IS ILLEGALLY
USING IT ON FROZEN TWO
MERCHANDISE.
THE SUIT COULD HAVE BIG MONETARY
IMPLICATIONS FOR BOTH COMPANIES.
>>> HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF A
HANGOVER DAY?  I CAN'T COME IN
TODAY, I HAVE A HANGOVER.
INSTEAD OF I CAN'T COME IN, I'M
SICK IT'S A DAY PEOPLE TAKE OFF
WHEN THEY DRANK A LITTLE BIT TOO
MUCH BEFORE THE NIGHT BEFORE SO
THIS YEAR GERMAN COURT RULED
THAT HANGOVERS ARE IN FACT AN
ILLNESS AND PEOPLE CAN CALL IN
SICK BECAUSE OF THEM.
AND SLOWLY THE IDEA MAY BE
PICKING UP SOME SPEED.
IT COMES WITH SOME PERKS.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU CAN BE HONEST
WITH YOUR BOSS, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO LIE ABOUT WHY YOU MIGHT
BE CALLING OUT SICK.
RIGHT?  IN SOME PLACES IF YOU
USE A HANGOVER DAY YOU COULD
JUST CALL OUT FROM WORK FROM
HOMESTEAD AND WORKERS WHO WORK
AT JOBS WITH FLEXIBLE WORK
SCHEDULES REPORTEDLY FIND IT TO
BE REALLY POSITIVE.
>> THE BOSS CAN BE SUPER HONEST
AS WELL AND SAY GUESS WHAT, WE
DON'T WANT YOU ANY MORE.
>> WOW!
>> 8:41 I'M JUST SAYING.
STILL AHEAD WE THOUGHT WE WOULD
INTRODUCE TO ANOTHER VERSION OF
A POPULAR SPORT CALLED FUTSAL.
IT'S BEEN AROUND FOR AWHILE YOU
MAY NOT HAVE HEARD OF IT.
I WAS NOT FAMILIAR WITH IT.
I'M LEARNING ALONG WITH YOU.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE INDOOR SOCCER
BUT WITH SOME DIFFERENCES.
WHAT ARE THOSE DIFFERENCES?
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW COMING UP AND
WE'LL MEET SOME IF IT'S AL
PLAYERS AS.
IT'S 8:41.
THERE'S NO OFF SIDES EITHER.
SO LOTS OF ACTION.
(Military Mom)
Love you, miss you guys!
(Military Mom's Family)
Love you!
♪
(Joy Ofodu)
We got this!
♪
(Kids)
Wow! Santa was here!
(Military Mom's Husband)
Whoa.
How did this happen?
(Military Mom)
I think I know.
(Military Mom's Husband)
Merry Christmas honey.
(Military Mom)
Merry Christmas!
(Kids)
Look, it's snowing.
♪
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
OK, network inspection.
OK.
Connected to WiFi,
protected from threats.
Thermostat -
connected, protected.
Speaker, space vacuum...
Connected, protected. Shh.
Eh, this is not
connected or protected.
But, that's a family heirloom.
And, it's a family
security breach. It's gotta go.
With Xfinity xFi, if it's
connected, it's protected.
Pull the truck around.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
Internet for $39.99 a month
for 12 months.
Plus, ask about enhanced
network security
for all your
connected devices.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
♪
>>> 8:44.
GOOD DAY D.C. COMING UP IN JUST
A COUPLE OF MINUTES.
HERE'S WHAT'S ON THE DOCKET FOR
TODAY.
FIRST UP WE'LL GET TECH SAVVY
FOR COMPUTER SCIENCE EDUCATION
WEEK.
COUPLE OF YOUNG CODE NINJAS ARE
STOPPING BY THEY'LL DEMONSTRATE
CODING TECHNIQUES FOR KIDS WITH
DRONES AND ROBOTS.
PRETTY COOL STUFF.
ALL TO RAISE AWARENESS OF
SCIENCE EDUCATION AND THE
IMPORTANCE OF TECH TRAINING FOR
YOUNG PEOPLE.
>>> AND STEVE, GUESS WHAT.
>> GUWHAT.
>> IT'S THE HOLIDAYS.
WE'VE GOT HOLIDAY COCKTAIL IDEAS
TO HELP BEEF UP YOUR CELEB
CELEBRATION.
YESTERDAY WE FEATURED MOCKTAILS.
TODAY IT'S THE REAL THING, BABY.
♪
>> WE KIND OF WORKED IN THE REAL
THING YESTERDAY.
>> YEAH, WE DID.
>> WE MADE IT HAPPEN IN THE
SPIRIT OF THE HOLIDAYS.
OR SPIRITS PERHAPS.
TWO NEW CELEBRITIES UNMASKED ON
THE MASKED SINGER ONE OF THE TWO
HAS TIES TO THE D.C. AREA.
>> YEAH.
>> I DO BELIEVE YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO TALK WITH HER, AL.
>> ONE OF THE ELIMINATED LAST
NIGHT ALSO HAS TIES TO THE D.C.
AREA, TOO.
>> OH THE UM --
>> THE DUAL THREAT WE'LL CALL
HIM.
>> THE CHRISTMAS TREE GOT
ELIMINATE THE SHE IS FROM D.C.
AND THEN THING A MAGIC HE IS
FROM PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY.
CAN I SAY THIS?  I THINK I HAVE
A WEIRD, UM, COUGAR CRUSH ON HIM
NOW.
>> BECAUSE HE'S A BALL PLAYER OR
BECAUSE HE'S A SINGER.
>> BECAUSE HE'S A SINGER.
>> HE'S SMOOTH.
>> THERE'S A COUPLE MORE --
>> IS THAT WRONG.
>> CLUES FOR YOU.
>> I'VE BEEN DIPPING IN AND OUT
OF THE SHOW CHRISTMAS TREE
CHARACTER LOOKS LIKE A FRENCH
FRY GUY.
>> THE CHRISTMAS TREE WAS ANNA
GASTEYER.
WHO IS THAT PERSON THAT GOT HE
WILL FLAMED.
>> THING A MAGIC.
>> I GOT YOU.
HE LOOKS LIKE A FRENCH FRY GUY.
>> LOCAL BASKETBALL PLAYER.
>> OH REALLY?
>> HE'S FROM HERE.
>> I'LL STAY TUNED ON GOOD DAY.
>> OKAY.
>> WISDOM CALLED IT.
>> I SAW ANNA GET ELIMINATED.
31 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
20S IT'S COLD OUT EARLY THIS
MORNING.
26 IN HEY MARK.
LEESBURG 24 DEGREES.
28 IN DALE CITY.
LA PLATA 27 DEGREES.
SO VERY CHILLY TEMPERATURES TO
START YOUR DAY AND IT'S GOING TO
BE AFTERNOON DAYTIME HIGHS ONLY
IN THE UPPER 30S.
WE MIGHT GET TO 40 HERE IN
WASHINGTON.
BUT MANY OF YOU WITH STARTS IN
THE 20S WON'T GET OUT OF THE 30S
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
21 DEGREES THIS MORNING
MARTINSBURG.
27 IN WINCHESTER.
BEAUTIFUL WEATHER TODAY.
NO PROBLEMS AT ALL.
WE'VE GOT BIG AREA OF MY
PRESSURE OVERHEAD THAT WILL
DELIVER SUNSHINE AND A QUIET
THURSDAY FOR YOU.
JUST ON THE CHILLY SIDE LATER
TODAY ONCE THAT SUN GOES DOWN IT
WILL COLD AGAIN LATER TO
TONIGHT.
OUR NEXT SYSTEM ACROSS THE
NORTHERN GULF WILL SCOOT UP IN
OUR DIRECTION TOMORROW AFTERNOON
AND BY TOMORROW NIGHT WE'LL HAVE
PERIOD OF RAIN AROUND HERE WHICH
WILL CONTINUE INTO THE DAY ON
SATURDAY.
I THINK THIS ONE WILL BE MOSTLY
A RAIN EVENT BUT AS WE GET INTO
THE WEEKEND AND BY EARLY NEXT
WEEK MAYBE A WINTRY MIX AROUND
HERE.
I'LL SHOW YOU THAT SETUP IN JUST
A SECOND.
THAT'S YOUR FUTURE CAST TOMORROW
MORNING 8:00 O'CLOCK THE MORNING
COMMUTE GETTING TO SCHOOL FOR
YOUR FRIDAY WE SHOULD BE FINE
LATER IN THE DAY WE'LL GET SOME
SCATTERED SHOWERS ACROSS THE
REGION.
THERE WE ARE AT 5:00 O'CLOCK AND
SOME RAIN JUST ON OUR DOORSTEP
HERE TO THE SOUTH AND AGAIN SOME
SHOWERS OVERNIGHT FRIDAY AND
THEN MUCH OF THE DAY ON SATURDAY
WILL BE KIND OF WET AND SOGGY
WITH DAYTIME HIGHS IN THE LOW
50S.
ALL RIGHT.
EARLY NEXT WEEK GETTING BACK TO
WORK AND SCHOOL MONDAY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE OUR SETUP.
HIGH PRESSURE TO THE NORTH
PROCESS WE CALL OVERRUNNING SO
WARMER AIR MOVING IN A LOT OF
OVER COLD AIR AND IT'S POSSIBLE
LOOK AT THE SETUP HERE WE COULD
GET A PERIOD OF SOME WINTER
WEATHER AT THE ONSET OF OUR
EVENT MAYBE MONDAY AFTERNOON AND
EARLY MONDAY EVENING.
THE POSSIBILITY OF SNOW THAT
TRANSITIONINGS OVER TO SLEET,
FREEZING RAIN AND THEN ALL RAIN.
THIS IS NOT A GUARANTEE BUT ALL
OCCASIONS WE'LL START AT LEAST
FOR PARTS OF REGION PARTICULARLY
NORTH AND WEST WITH A PERIOD OF
WINTER WEATHER THAT WILL
TRANSITION OVER TO RAIN LATER
MONDAY INTO EARLY TUESDAY.
SO THAT'S SORT OF A PERIOD TO
WATCH THERE.
40 TODAY.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY FORECAST.
AGAIN RAIN SHOWERS THAT WILL BE
IT FRIDAY NIGHT AND SATURDAY.
AND THEN WE'LL LOOK OUT FOR THAT
WINTRY MIX POSSIBILITY MONDAY
INTO TUESDAY.
STEVE AND ALLISON, BACK OVER TO
YOU.
>> 8:48.
WE'VE HEARD OF SOCCER HAVE YOU
HEARD OF IF IT'S AL.
>> IT STARTED IN CENTRAL AMERICA
GAINING POPULARITY HERE IN THE
D.C. REGION.
SO THE BIG QUESTION, THAT I
HAVE, HOW IS IT DIFFERENT THAN
JUST CALLING IT INDOOR SOCCER.
>> YOU KNOW WHO'S GOT ALL THE
ANSWERS INCLUDING CALLING LAST
NIGHT'S MASKED SINGER YOU WERE
ABSOLUTELY, RIGHT, WIS, WISDOM
MARTIN HAS YOUR ANSWERS ABOUT
WHAT FUTSAL IS.
HE'S LIVE ON LOCATION IN
ALEXANDRIA.
GOOD JOB.
>> Reporter: YEAH, SOMETIMES
THEY CALL ME WISDOM FOR A RE
REASON.
>> I KNOW.
REPORT MORE OFTEN THAN NOT THEY
DON'T.
BECAUSE I WAS THE FIRST ONE BORN
AND THAT WAS MY DAD'S NAME.
>> OKAY.
>> Reporter: LET'S TALK ABOUT
FUTSAL I HAVE SOME PEOPLE THAT
ARE EXPERTS RIGHT HERE BESIDE ME
THEY'RE WARMING UP IN IN THE
BACKGROUND MUCH THIS IS KATIE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> THIS IS LILA.
GOOD GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT FUTSAL.
>> YUP.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE NOT
HEARD OF THIS.
IT LOOKS LIKE SOCCER.
FEELS LIKE SOCCER BUT LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENT.
EXPLAIN TO ME WHAT THE
DIFFERENCE IS.
>> ABSOLUTELY FUTSAL IS 5V5
PLAYED INDOOR AS YOU SEE HERE.
THESE ARE SOME OF THE OUR
PROFESSIONAL PLAYERS.
THIS FALL WE LAUNCHED MEN'S AND
WOMEN'S PROFESSIONAL TEAMS
BECAUSE WE WANT TO HELP, UM,
IMPROVE THE QUALITY OF ADULT IF
IT'S AL IN THE REGION AND CREATE
A PATHWAY FOR OUR PLAYERS.
LILA IS 81 OF OUR YOUTH PLAYERS
HAVING AN OPPORTUNITY TO TRAIN
WITH OUR WOMAN'S PRO TEAM.
>> WHAT IS IT ABOUT THIS SPORT
THAT YOU LIKE?  I ASSUME YOU
PLAYED SOCCER IN THE PAST AND
NOW YOU'RE PLAYING THIS.
SO THE BIG DIFFERENCES.
>> YEAH.
UM, THE SPEED OF PLAY IS A LOT
DIFFERENT.
THAT'S REALLY FUN TO EXPERIENCE
THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> IS IT HARDER OR --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> BECAUSE THIS IS FIVE ON FIVE.
IT'S A LITTLE -- THE FIELD OR
THE COURT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
SMALLER.
>> IT'S A LOT DIFFERENT.
I WOULDN'T SAY IT'S HARDER BUT A
LOT OF FUN.
>> THERE'S NOWHERE -- BALLS
FLYING EVERYWHERE.
>> THERE'S NOWHERE TO HIDE.
IT'S 5V5 YOU GOT TO BE QUICK
ALWAYS UNDER PRESSURE.
SOCCER SOMETIMES YOU CAN MAYBE
STAND ON THE WINK AND YOU DON'T
GET THE BALL FOR AWHILE.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS REALLY HELPS PLAYERS
IMPROVE THEY ARE THEY ARE
TECHNICAL SKILL AND SPEED OF
PLAY IN TIGHT SPACES.
>> WHY IS IT GROWING SO FAST IN
THIS AREA?  YOU GOT A LEAGUE
NOW.
WHY IS IT SO -- SO POPULAR ALL
OF A SUDDEN?
>> REALLY GOOD QUESTION.
HONESTLY ABOUT NINE YEARS AGO
LILA WHAT ONE OF OUR ORIGINAL IF
IT'S AL PLAYERS IN OUR REC
LEAGUE.
WE STARTED OFFERING THIS IN THE
WINTER TO KEEP KIDS ACTIVE,
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY
BASKETBALL.
BECAUSE IT'S FUN THE GAMES ARE
SHORT MUCH IT'S FAST IT HELPS
FOR SKILLS FOR OUTDOORS AND A
SPORT IN AND OF ITSELF WE TIE
COOK TOUGH OFF AND CREATED THE
LEAGUE.
WE NOW OFFER THE PRO TEAMS AS A
WAY SOMETHING FOR KIDS TO, YOU
KNOW, LOOK UP TO AND KIND OF
WORK TOWARDS.
WE HAVE A BIG TOURNAMENT COMING
UP IN JANUARY.
WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO BE
STADIUM ARMORY IN D.C.
WE'VE GOT -- YOU WALK IN THERE'S
SIX COURTS, AND SO I THINK JUST
KIND OF THE EXCITEMENT.
IT'S A SHORT SEASON.
IT'S FUN.
KIDS JUST LOVE IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?  WHAT'S SO
SPECIAL ABOUT THIS TO YOU TO
MAKE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
>> IT'S A SMALLER TEAM SO YOU
REALLY GET TO BE CLOSE WITH YOUR
TEAMMATES, AND YOU WORK WITH
THEM, AND YOU KIND OF DEVELOP
LIKE -- LIKE WORK AS A TEAM AND
YOU CAN BOND ON THAT AND IT
HELPS WITH OUTDOOR.
>> COOL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE'LL HANG OUT -- WE'LL LEARN
MORE ABOUT FUTSAL IN JUST A
MINUTE.
I'M GOING TO GO -- MAYBE I'LL GO
OUT AND KICK ONE OF THIS BALLS
AROUND.
>> PLEASE.
>> OR MAYBE NOT.
YOU KNOW, INJURIES AND AGE.
>> MUSCLE, YEAH.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT KNOW.
WE WARM UP A LOT.
OUR ADULT TEAMS WAY MORE THAN
THE KIDS TEAMS.
>> I DON'T HAVE TIME TO WARM UP.
SO, YOU KNOW, MAYBE I'LL LEAVE
THAT TO THE PROS.
MEMBER I'LL LEAVE THAT TO THE
PROS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
WE'LL LEARN MORE ABOUT FUTSAL
WHEN CAN HE BACK.
>> DO A KICK IN OR SOMETHING.
CEREMONIALLY GET THE GAME
STARTED.
YOU GOT THIS.
I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
>> WAIT.
STEVE, WAIT, STEVE, WAIT.
HERE YOU GO.
WAIT.
RIGHT.
HERE YOU GO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
RIGHT.
>> OH, BOY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THIS IS WHAT WE LIKE TO SEE.
>> OH, BOY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WISDOM, FAIR
>> THIS IS WHAT WE LIKE TO SEE.
ENOUGH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WISDOM, FAIR
YOU'RE WELCOME.
ENOUGH.
>> I THINK THERE'S A LITTLE ROOM
YOU'RE WELCOME.
FOR IMPROVE BUT I'M PROUD OF
>> I THINK THERE'S A LITTLE ROOM
YOU.
FOR IMPROVE BUT I'M PROUD OF
8:52.
YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
8:52.
>> I'M PROUD OF KEVIN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
KEV IS TALKING WITH ALL THE
>> I'M PROUD OF KEVIN.
SUPER STARS HE SITS DOWN WITH
KEV IS TALKING WITH ALL THE
LEGENDARY KATHY BATES CHAT ABOUT
SUPER STARS HE SITS DOWN WITH
HER ROLL IN THE FILM RICHARD
LEGENDARY KATHY BATES CHAT ABOUT
JEWEL ABOUT THE 1996 OLYMPIC
HER ROLL IN THE FILM RICHARD
BOMBING IN ATLANTA.
JEWEL ABOUT THE 1996 OLYMPIC
IT'S 8:52.
♪
GETTING ALL THE SCOOP BEHIND THE
SCENES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IT'S TIME FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA
MCCARTHY WITH COOL KEVIN
MCCARTHY.
>> RICHARD JEWELL OPENS
TOMORROW.
YESTERDAY YOU HEARD FROM CLINT
EASTWOOD ABOUT THE FILM.
IN THE STORY ABOUT CENTENNIAL
PARK BOMBING DURING THE OLYMPICS
OF 1996 I'M HAVING LITTLE BIT OF
TROUBLE THIS MORNING.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I SPOKE TO KATHY BATES, SAM
ROCKWELL AND JON HAMM ABOUT THE
SAME QUESTION I ASKED CLINT
EASTWOOD YESTERDAY WHICH IS
ABOUT THE IDEA OF RICHARD JEWELL
BEING BULLIED BY THE MEDIA AND
BULLIED BY THE FBI IN THE FILM
ITSELF.
THAT'S KIND OF THE STRUCTURE
THEY GIVE YOU.
I WANTED TO TALK TO THEM ABOUT
THEIR BULLYING EXPERIENCE WHEN
THEY WERE YOUNGER AND THESE
STORIES ARE INCREDIBLY FUNNY.
WATCH THIS.
>> RICHARD JEWELL IS AN INNOCENT
MAN.
>> SOMEBODY HEAVILY BULLIED IN
MIDDLE SCHOOL AND HIGH SCHOOL.
>> I WAS BULLIED.
>> I WAS GOING TO BRING UP YOU
HAVE A GREAT MOMENT IN THE
MOVIE.
>> I APOLOGIZED TO BOTH OF YOU
BY THE WAY.
>> JESUS, JOHN,.
>> HE WAS PRESIDENT OF THE
STUDENT COUNSEL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT SCENE WHEN YOU TELL
HIM -- RICHARD TO STAND UP FOR
HIMSELF.
STOP BEING A DOOR MAT.
>> YEAH.
>> PEOPLE ARE CALLING HIM RENT A
COP AND THEN I DON'T WANT TO
GIVE TOO MUCH AWAY HE DOES GET
TO STAND UP FOR HIMSELF.
>> THAT WAS SUCH A GRATEFUL
CIRCLE.
>> YES.
>> I WAS WONDERING FOR EACH OF
YOU INDIVIDUALLY GROWING UP WAS
BULLYING SOMETHING YOU DEALT
WITH AND IS THAT HOW YOU COULD
TAP INTO THAT MINDSET OF BEING
ABLE TO DELIVER A LINE LIKE THAT
TELL SOMEONE TO STICK UP FOR
THEMSELVES DON'T BE A DOOR MAT
ESSENTIALLY I'VE STRUGGLED WITH
THAT ALL MY LIFE.
I'M CURIOUS FOR EACH YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I GOT THE BLEEP KICKED ME OUT OF
ME AND I ONLY WON A COUPLE OF
FIGHTS.
I LOST MOST OF THEM.
ONCE IN AWHILE I'D GET IN A
GOOD, YOU KNOW, PUNCH.
I WENT TO A LOT OF DIFFERENT
SCHOOLS.
>> DID YOU HAVE THAT STAND UP
FOR YOURSELF MOMENT THOUGH.
>> YEAH,.
>> WHAT WAS YOURS I'M GOING TO
TELL MINE.
>> I JUST REMEMBER THERE WAS A
BIG GUY AND HE -- HE WAS
BULLYING ME AND I SOMEHOW I GOT
HIM IN A HEAD LOCK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AND I -- I DON'T KNOW BELIEVE
ME ONCE I GOT HIM THERE I
WOULDN'T LET GO OF HIM.
IF I LET GO OF HIM HE WAS GOING
TO KILL ME AND HE WAS CRYING HE
STARTED CRYING.
WE WENT TO THE PRINCIPAL'S
OFFICE AND THAT WAS IT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I STOOD UP TO
HIM.
BUT IT TOOK -- THEN OF COURSE I
GOT THE BLEEP KICKED OUT OF ME
MOST OF THE TIME.
>> FOR YOU WHAT'S YOUR STORY.
>> HIS NAME IS PAUL AND MANY IT
WAS SECOND GRADE HE SAID
SOMETHING AND I PUNCHED HIM IN
THE EYE.
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
>> THE NEXT WEEK WE HAD PARENTS
AND TEACHERS MY DAD CAME IN WITH
ME AND PAUL WAS THERE.
HE SAID LOOK DADDY, SHE'S THE
ONE.
SHE'S THE ONE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AMAZING.
>> THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
I THINK I GOT POPPED BY A FEW
>> AMAZING.
GIRLS WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
I THINK I GOT POPPED BY A FEW
>> AND THEN EARLIER IN FIRST
GIRLS WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
GRADE I KNOCKED SOME KIDS HAT
>> AND THEN EARLIER IN FIRST
OFF THEN -- IN THE THING HE HAD
GRADE I KNOCKED SOME KIDS HAT
SOME KIND OF DISEASE ON HIS
OFF THEN -- IN THE THING HE HAD
SCALP.
SOME KIND OF DISEASE ON HIS
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU WERE THE
SCALP.
BULLY.
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU WERE THE
>> THEY SAID I DID IT BECAUSE I
BULLY.
KNEW HE HAD A DISEASE.
>> THEY SAID I DID IT BECAUSE I
>> HE HAS TO RECLAIM HIS TIME.
KNEW HE HAD A DISEASE.
I WAS DOING CIRCLES LIKE THIS.
>> HE HAS TO RECLAIM HIS TIME.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
I WAS DOING CIRCLES LIKE THIS.
>> I WAS PRETENDING I HIT HIS
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
HAT HE HAD RINGWORM OR SOME
>> I WAS PRETENDING I HIT HIS
SOMETHING.
HAT HE HAD RINGWORM OR SOME
>> DID YOU HAVE A CRUSH ON HIM
SOMETHING.
AND YOU HIT HIM IN THE FACE.
>> DID YOU HAVE A CRUSH ON HIM
PAUL NEW YORK CITY.
AND YOU HIT HIM IN THE FACE.
PAUL, SORRY.
PAUL NEW YORK CITY.
>> HE'S A DENTIST NOW.
PAUL, SORRY.
>> SORRY FOR BRINGS THIS UP.
>> HE'S A DENTIST NOW.
>> DO IT.
>> SORRY FOR BRINGS THIS UP.
>> NO, PAUL.
>> DO IT.
>> THAT WAS AN AMAZING STORY.
>> NO, PAUL.
I USED TO RIDE THE BUS THIS MUST
>> THAT WAS AN AMAZING STORY.
HAVE BEEN BEFORE I WAS NINE
I USED TO RIDE THE BUS THIS MUST
BECAUSE MY MOM WAS STILL ALIVE
HAVE BEEN BEFORE I WAS NINE
BUT I -- I WOULD RIDE THE BUS TO
BECAUSE MY MOM WAS STILL ALIVE
SCHOOL AND BACK.
BUT I -- I WOULD RIDE THE BUS TO
AND MY MOM WAS SINGLE MOM SHE
SCHOOL AND BACK.
WAS ALWAYS AT WORK SO I HAD HAD
AND MY MOM WAS SINGLE MOM SHE
TO GET HOME AND LATCH KEY KID
WAS ALWAYS AT WORK SO I HAD HAD
THE WHEN HE WILL THING AND I
TO GET HOME AND LATCH KEY KID
REMEMBER GETTING PICKED ON BY
THE WHEN HE WILL THING AND I
OLDER KIDS ON THE BUS MANY I
REMEMBER GETTING PICKED ON BY
REMEMBER AT A CERTAIN POINT I
OLDER KIDS ON THE BUS MANY I
HAD MY STAR WARS LUNCH BOX IN MY
REMEMBER AT A CERTAIN POINT I
HAND.
HAD MY STAR WARS LUNCH BOX IN MY
>> NICE.
HAND.
>> NOT TODAY.
>> NICE.
AND CLOCKED THE GUY LIKE IN THE
>> NOT TODAY.
SIDE OF THE HEAD WITH THE STAR
AND CLOCKED THE GUY LIKE IN THE
WARS LUNCH BOX.
SIDE OF THE HEAD WITH THE STAR
>> THAT WILL DO IT.
WARS LUNCH BOX.
>> SHOCKED HIM AND MADE A THING
>> THAT WILL DO IT.
AND ALL THE THERMOS WENT
>> SHOCKED HIM AND MADE A THING
EVERYWHERE.
AND ALL THE THERMOS WENT
>> THOSE THINGS THEY MADE THEM
EVERYWHERE.
STURDY BACK THEN.
>> THOSE THINGS THEY MADE THEM
>> IT WASN'T ANY CHEAP PLASTIC
STURDY BACK THEN.
STUFF.
>> IT WASN'T ANY CHEAP PLASTIC
IT WAS METAL.
STUFF.
AND THE BUS DRIVE SCREECHES THE
IT WAS METAL.
BUS.
AND THE BUS DRIVE SCREECHES THE
MELEE IN THE BACK.
BUS.
KIDS EVERYONE SCREAMING AND
MELEE IN THE BACK.
YELLING.
KIDS EVERYONE SCREAMING AND
AND YEAH I GOT IN A LOT OF
YELLING.
TROUBLE FOR THAT.
AND YEAH I GOT IN A LOT OF
>> WE'RE IRISH.
TROUBLE FOR THAT.
WE ALWAYS GET INTO THE DUST UPS.
>> WE'RE IRISH.
YOU'RE IRISH, RIGHT.
WE ALWAYS GET INTO THE DUST UPS.
>> YEAH.
YOU'RE IRISH, RIGHT.
>> THAT NEEDS TO START TRENDING.
>> YEAH.
HASH TAG NOT TODAY.
>> THAT NEEDS TO START TRENDING.
>> CAN SOMEBODY PLEASE MAKE A
HASH TAG NOT TODAY.
MOVIE ABOUT SECOND GRADE KATHY
>> CAN SOMEBODY PLEASE MAKE A
BATES STANDING UP TO A BULLY.
MOVIE ABOUT SECOND GRADE KATHY
>> NOT THE SECOND PART WHERE SHE
BATES STANDING UP TO A BULLY.
MAY HAVE BEEN THE BULLY.
>> NOT THE SECOND PART WHERE SHE
>> MAY HAVE BEEN THE BULLY THE
MAY HAVE BEEN THE BULLY.
WHOLE POINT OF THAT STORY IS
>> MAY HAVE BEEN THE BULLY THE
RICHARD JEWELL'S CHARACTER IN
WHOLE POINT OF THAT STORY IS
THE MOVIE WAS BULLIED BY A LOT
RICHARD JEWELL'S CHARACTER IN
OF PEOPLE.
THE MOVIE WAS BULLIED BY A LOT
>> ABSOLUTELY.
OF PEOPLE.
>> THAT WAS THE IDEA OF HIM
>> ABSOLUTELY.
STANDING UP FOR HIMSELF.
>> THAT WAS THE IDEA OF HIM
SEND US YOUR BULLYING STORIES
STANDING UP FOR HIMSELF.
#GOODDAYDC.
SEND US YOUR BULLYING STORIES
WHEN DID YOU STAND UP FOR I
#GOODDAYDC.
DON'T HAVE SELF.
WHEN DID YOU STAND UP FOR I
>> NOT TODAY.
DON'T HAVE SELF.
>> THE NEWS IS NON-STOP.
>> NOT TODAY.
.GOOD DAY D.C. AT 9:00 A.M.
>> THE NEWS IS NON-STOP.
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
.GOOD DAY D.C. AT 9:00 A.M.
♪
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, 10 DAYS
♪
UNTIL WINTER.
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, 10 DAYS
BUT MOTHER NATURE DIDN'T GET THE
UNTIL WINTER.
MESSAGE.
BUT MOTHER NATURE DIDN'T GET THE
WE WOKE UP TO SOME OF THE
MESSAGE.
COLDEST WEATHER OF THE SEASON SO
WE WOKE UP TO SOME OF THE
FAR.
COLDEST WEATHER OF THE SEASON SO
NOW, WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON
FAR.
ANOTHER CHANCE FOR SNOWFLAKES.
NOW, WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON
>>> IT FEELS LIKE WINTER BUT
ANOTHER CHANCE FOR SNOWFLAKES.
METRO ALREADY LOOKING AHEAD TO