WOULDN'T BE MADE AVAILABLE TO
THE PUBLIC FOR AT LEAST A YEAR.
MEANTIME HEALTH AUTHORITIES IF
PEOPLE BECAME SICK THERE ARE
TREATMENTS AVAILABLE TO LESSEN
SYMPTOMS AND MEDICAL SUPPLIES
SUCH AS FACE MASKS ARE WIDELY
AVAILABLE IN THE COUNTRY.
>> THE NUMBER OF US CASES IS AT
57, MORE THAN 80,000 PEOPLE ARE
NOW AFFECTED WORLDWIDE.
2700 PEOPLE HAVE DIED.
IT'S THE DEATH RATE THAT HAS
AUTHORITIES PARTICULARLY
CONCERNED, MUCH HIGHER THAN THE
FLU, PER SE.
ITALY SAYS IT SAW A 45% INCREASE
IN JUST A DAY.
AND OTHER COUNTRIES IN EUROPE
ARE NOW SEEING THEIR FIRST
INFECTIONS.
IRAN IS ONE OF THE COUNTRIES
THAT HAS SEEN A SPIKE IN CASES
INCLUDING THE COUNTRY'S OWN
HEALTH MINISTER, THE MAN
PICTURED HERE ON THE LEFT.
AND YOU CAN SEE, THERE HE GOES,
DURING A RECENT NEWS CONFERENCE
WIPING HIS NOSE AND WIPING AWAY
SWEAT.
THE HEALTH MINISTER IS NOW IN
QUARANTINE WE'RE TOLD AND
RECOVERING.
>> FOR THE SECOND STRAIGHT DAY
THE FEAR OF THE CORONAVIRUS
SPREADING AND HURTING THE GLOBAL
ECONOMY HAS SENT THE STOCK
MARKET TUMBLING.
THE DOW JONES INDUSTRIAL FALLIN
ENDED THE DAY OFF BY 877 POINTS.
JUST YESTERDAY THE DOW FELL MORE
THAN 1,000 POINTS AND THE MARKET
AS LOST 7% OF ITS VALUE OVER
THE PAST FOUR DAYS.
>>> OH, I'D SAY LET'S DO A PICK
ME UP BUT NEXT WE'RE GOING TO
THAT RAINY WEATHER A LOT OF US
WOKE UP TO IT THIS MORNING AND
IF YOU'RE HEADED OUT THERE STILL
KIND OF GLOOMY, STILL DREARY OUT
THERE, YOU'RE LOOKING AT VIDEO
WE TOOK EARLIER FROM DOWNTOWN
DC.
>> BUT I HAVE SPOTTED THE
SUNSHINE.
>> OH, YOU DID, WHERE IS HE?
>> HER NAME IS CAITLIN ROTH.
>> OH, WOW, BLAKE YOU'RE SO
GENEROUS TODAY ON A DREARY ONE.
HELLO TO YOU BOTH.
THE RAIN HAS MOVED OUT, WHICH IS
AT LEAST GREAT, WE'LL GET A
BREAK UNTIL PROBABLY TOMORROW
NIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> SO IT'S A LITTLE FOGGY AND
DREARY AND THE FOG COULD BE AN
ISSUE TOMORROW MORNING ALWAYS
SOMETHING.
MILD TEMPERATURES WITH US, THE
RAIN HAS PASSED.
RIGHT NOW IN THE 50S, 54 HERE IN
WASHINGTON, 48 IN ANNAPOLIS, 52
IN MANASSAS, 50 ALONG 81.
VISIBILITY NOT BAD EXCEPT RIGHT
ALONG THE CHESAPEAKE, THAT'S
WHERE YOU LOW NUMBERS, ONE MINE
VISIBILITIES IN NUBILITY,
THREE-QUARTERS IN STEVENSVILLE
AND ONE AND THREE-QUARTERS OF A
MILE IN BALTIMORE.
SO WE HAVE A LOT OF MOISTURE IN
THE AIR THANKS TO THE RAIN THAT
CAME THROUGH EARLIER THIS
MORNING.
NO WIND TO MOVE IT OUT.
IT'S JUST SITTING AND THEN WHEN
IT'S SITTING ON TOP OF A BODY OF
WATER LIKE THE POTOMAC OR THE
CHESAPEAKE YOU CAN GET SOME OF
THAT FOG WHICH COULD BE LOCALLY
DENIES, WE PSE&G THAT TO
CONTINUE OVERNIGHT TONIGHT AND
MAY HAVE PATCHY DENIES FOG INTO
TOMORROW MORNING.
WARM FRONT MOVED THROUGH THE
AREAS, THERE'S THE SHOWERS NOW
NORTH AND EAST OF US.
IT WILL BE A WHILE BEFORE WE GET
OUR NEXT ROUND OF RAIN PROBABLY
NOT UNTIL AT LEAST 24 HOURS FROM
NOW.
SO THIS EVENING, YES, IT'S KIND
OF WET OUT.
DRIBSLE IS POSSIBLE, AS
TEMPERATURES ARE IN THE LOW 50S
THROUGH THE EVENING HOURS.
BY TOMORROW, WE'LL BE SETTING
OUR SITES ON THE NEXT ROUND OF
RAIN KIND OF A DIFFERENT SETUP.
MOST OF THE DAY IS DRY, THERE
COULD BE PATCHY DRIZZLE AND
ISOLATED SHOWERS TO START YOU
OFF AND AGAIN FOG.
SO PRETTY DREARY TO BEGIN THE
DAY.
I THINK WE GET A DRY BREAK
BEFORE THE COLD FRONT ARRIVES.
ONCE IT DOES, BETWEEN 6:00 AND
10:00 P.M. IN OUR WESTERN
SUBURBS, IT COULD BRING GUST WHY
I RAIN SHOWERS QUICKLY MOVING
OUT, WINDS INCREASING BEHIND IT
MAY EVEN BE A THUNDERSTORM OR
TWO MARGINAL RISK FOR STRONG
STORMS, THE BIGGEST CONCERN
WOULD BE GUSTY WINDS AS THEY
BLOW THROUGH.
NOT OUT OF THE QUESTION
ESPECIALLY THE WAY THIS WINTER'S
BEEN EVERYTHING RUNNING SO WARM.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE WATCHING
TOMORROW NIGHT.
TEMPERATURES TAKE A TUMBLE AFTER
THAT, WE'LL LOOK AT THE COLD AIR
HEADED OUR WAY COMING UP IN JUST
A BIT.
BLAKE.
>>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>>> DEVELOPING NOW DISTURBING
DETAILS ABOUT A MAN POLICE SAY
TRIED TO BLOW UP HIS CAR IN THE
PARKING LOT OF THE PENTAGON.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT MATTHEW
RICHARDSON, 19 YEARS OLD FROM
ARKANSAS.
COURT DOCUMENTS SHOW ETCHES
FIRST STOPPED BY PENTAGON POLICE
YESTERDAY MORNING IN THE
PENTAGON NORTH PARKING LOT.
THE OFFICER SAYS HE SAW
RICHARDSON TRY TO LIGHT A RAG ON
FIRE THAT WAS INSERTED INTO THE
CAR'S GAS TANK.
RICHARDSON TOOK OFF RUNNING
CROSSING ROUTE ONE, TEN, AND
WASHINGTON BOULEVARD BEFORE
JUMPING A FENCE INTO ARLINGTON
NATIONAL CEMETERY, THAT IS WHERE
HE WAS CAUGHT.
WE ALSO LEARNED RICHARDSON HAD
BEEN ARRESTED OVER THE WEEKEND
IN ARLINGTON AND CHARGED WITH
ASSAULTING A LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICER.
>>> NEW DETAILS MERGING NOW
ABOUT THIS, REMEMBER THIS
ALARMING ATTACK REPORTEDLY
INVOLVING A SYRINGE.
IT TOOK PLACE IN ANNE ARUNDEL
COUNTY AT CHRISTOPHER'S FINE
GOODS ON SHADY SIDE ROAD IN
CHURCH TON.
VIDEO SURVEILLANCE SHOWS THE
SUSPECT IN THE CAR AREA OUTSIDE
THE STORE BEFORE THE ATTACK
HAPPENS.
FOX5 SPOKE WITH THE VICTIM TODAY
ON THE PHONE.
SHE SAYS AT FIRST SHE THOUGHT IT
WAS A CIGARETTE BURN BUT
ULTIMATELY REALIZED SHE WAS
STUCK WITH A SYRINGE AFTER NOT
FINDING A HOLE IN HER LEGGINS.
SHE HAS NO IDEA IF SHE'S
INFECTED WITH ANYTHING BUT SHE
IS TAKING THREE PREVENTATIVE
MEDICATIONS FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
THE VICTIM CLAYS THE POLICE TOLD
HER THE SUSPECT MAY HAVE TRIED
TO STICK OTHER WOMEN.
>>> RIGHT NOW TWO YOUNG MEN EACH
ACCUSED OF RAPING 11 YEAR OLD
GIRLS.
THOSE TWO MEN, 19 AND 20 YEARS
OLD, ARE MONTGOMERY COUNTY HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENTS.
>> FOX5'S STEPHANIE RAMIREZ IS
LIVE OUTSIDE OF BETHESDA CHEVY
CHASE HIGH SCHOOL WHERE ONE OF
THE STUDENTS WAS ARRESTED.
STEPHANIE?
>> Reporter: HEY, WE MADE A
LITTLE CHANGE HERE, OUTSIDE OF
MONTGOMERY, BLARE, I CAN TELL
YOU TODAY, THOUGH, MULTIPLE
OFFICIALS, NOT JUST MCPS, WOULD
NOT INTERVIEW WITH US ON CAMERA
TODAY.
SOME SAYING AS TERRIBLE AS THESE
ALLEGED CRIMES ARE, THEY DID NOT
HAPPEN ON MCPS PROPERTY.
I CAN TELL YOU, THOUGH, THE
SCHOOL BEHIND ME, MONTGOMERY
BLAIR, MCPS DOES CONFIRM THIS IS
WHERE A 20 YEAR OLD WAS
ARRESTED.
THEY TELL US THAT POLICE PICKED
UP JONATHAN HERE ON
FEBRUARY 13TH.
COURT DOCUMENTS MENTIONED THE
SUSPECT AS THE VICTIM'S HALF
BROTHER AND THAT THE FATHER OF
THE 11 YEAR OLD HAD CALLED
MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE AFTER
DISCOVERING A CELL PHONE
BELIEVED TO HAVE BEEN GIVEN TO
THE GIRL BY THE SUSPECT.
THE SAME COURT DOCUMENTS SAY THE
PHONE HAD GRAPHIC AND SEXUAL
TEXT MESSAGES DESCRIBING WHAT
THEY ALLEGEDLY DID.
19 YEAR OLD LOPEZ WAS ARRESTED
AT BETHESDA CHEVY CHASE HIGH
SCHOOL A FEW DAYS AFTER.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT 11 YEAR OLD
VICTIM WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE
BUT COURT DOCUMENTS IN THIS CASE
SAY OVER THE SUMMER THE VICTIM
TALKED TO HER OLDER SISTER'S
BOYFRIEND AND THAT THAT PERSON
REPORTEDLY INVITED THE VICTIM
OVER TO PLAN A SURPRISE PARTY
FOR HER SISTER.
NOW, BOTH SUSPECTS WERE RECENTLY
ARRESTED ON WARRANTS.
COURT DOCUMENTS SAY THAT THEY
WERE HELD WITHOUT BOND.
I CAN TELL YOU ICE DID ALSO
LODGE A DETAINER FOR THE 20 YEAR
OLD SUSPECT.
WE WERE TOLD HE IS UNLAWFULLY
PRESENT.
HE IS AN UNLAWFULLY PRESENT
SALVADORIAN NATIONAL.
ANGIE.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU MORE ABOUT
THAT, BECAUSE AGE 20, THAT
SOUNDS PRETTY OLD TO BE ENROLLED
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
AND I KNOW THAT THAT HAS BEEN A
CONCERN AMONG MANY PARENTS SINCE
THIS NEWS BROKE.
>> REPORTER: SO I CAN TELL YOU,
MCPS, THEY ARE PUSHING BACK ON
THIS.
THEY SENT A LETTER HOME WITH
PARENTS AND STUDENTS TODAY
TALKING ABOUT IMMIGRATION AS
WELL AS STUDENT STATUS.
I GOT A COPY OF THAT LETTER AND
I JUST WANT TO UNDERLINE ONE OF
THE THINGS THEY SAID.
UNDER MARYLAND LAW, MCPS DOES
HAVE TO PROVIDE FREE PUBLIC
EDUCATION TO ALL STUDENTS.
SO MPS IS SAYING THAT IN THE
COUNTY, YOU HAVE TO SHOW BONA
FIDE RESIDENCY, CITIZEN OR NOT
CITIZEN AND ON TOP OF THAT YOU
HAVE TO BE AT A LOT OF FIVE
BEFORE SEPTEMBER 1ST OR 20
BEFORE THE FIRST DAY OF THE
SCHOOL YEAR, WHICH MEANS YOU
COULD HAVE A BIRTHDAY AND BE 21.
BUT IT IS THE STATE LAW.
THAT IS WHAT I'M BEING TOLD.
ANGIE.
>> WELL, THAT CLARIFIES IT FOR A
LOT OF PARENTS ASKING THOSE
QUESTIONS.
STEPHANIE RAMIREZ FOR US.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE'VE LEARNED HARVEY
WEINSTEIN IS AT A HOSPITAL, NOT
PRISON TODAY, OVER HEALTH
CONCERNS.
THE FORMER MOVIE PRODUCER WAS
CONVICTED YESTERDAY ON TWO
CHARGES, THIRD DEGREE RAPE AND
FIRST DEGREE CRIMINAL SEX ACT,
THAT MEAN'S HE'S A CONVICTED
RAPIST NOW.
HE WAS ON HIS WAY TO RIKERS
ISLAND WHEN THEY NOTICED HEART
PALPITATIONS AND HIGH BLOOD
PRESSURE.
THE 67 YEAR OLD USED A WALKER
DURING HIS TRIAL AND DEFENSE
ATTORNEYS NOW SAY THEY HAD TO
CONVINCE HIM TO USE IT.
>>> NOW WE WANT TO SHOW YOU SOME
TOP CAUGHT ON CAMERA MOMENTS.
A DARING RESCUE, LOOK AT THIS,
IN FLORIDA, ON SUNDAY BYSTANDERS
RUSHED INTO THAT WATER RIGHT NOW
TO HELP OUT THIS DRIVER WHO HAD
DRIVEN HER CAR INTO A CANAL
WHILE HAVING A SEIZURE.
YOU CAN HEAR THE PANIC RIGHT
THERE.
>> WOW.
>> RESCUERS HAD TO CUT HER LOOSE
FROM HER SEAT BELT.
IT WAS A RACE AGAINST THE CLOCK,
AGAINST TIME AS THE CAR QUICKLY
STARTED SINKING YOU SEE HOW FAST
THAT'S HAPPENING BUT THEY WERE
ABLE TO GET DRIVER OUT AND SHE
SAYS SHE'S SO THANKFUL TO BE
ALIVE.
>> I'D LIKE TO THINK I WOULD
RUSH IN BUT WATER IN FLORIDA IS
SO ALLIGATOR INFESTED I WOULD
THINK TWICE.
>> I KNOW.
ANOTHER FACTOR INVOLVED BUT
THANKFULLY THEY WERE ABLE TO GET
HER.
>> AN AMAZON DELIVERY TRUCK HIT
A HOME IN GEORGIA.
THE HOMEOWNER APPARENTLY PULLED
INTO HIS DRIVEWAY AND NOTICED
PART OF THE WALL NEAR HIS GARAGE
DAMAGED WHEN HE CHECKED HIS HOME
SECURITY CAMERA SHOWED THE
DELIVERY DRIVER GETTING OUT OF
THE VAN TO DELIVER A PACKAGE TO
THE FRONT PORCH WHILE THE DRIVER
WAS RUNNING INSIDE THE VAN
ROLLED INTO THE HOUSE.
LOOKED LIKE A SLOW ROLL, BUT
APPARENTLY CAUSED SOME DAMAGE.
THE DRIVER REPORTEDLY GOT BACK
IN THE VAN AND DROVE AWAY.
>> NOT GOING TO SAY I HAVEN'T
DONE SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> WELL, THE POLICE ARE
WATCHING, ANGIE.
>> MY OWN HOUSE.
MY OWN HOUSE.
>> OH, OKAY.
>>> SEA LION, LET'S TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING HAPPIER.
SAY SEA LION HEADING THE WRONG
WAY NEEDED HELP RETURNING TO
WATER.
IT ENDED MILES AWAY FROM HOME.
AUTHORITIES IN OREGON TEAMING UP
TO HELP THE WAYWARD TRAVELLER
RETURN TO THE COLUMBIA RIVER.
THEY HAD TO CORNER THE 600
POUND.
THAT'S HUGE, 600 POUNDS,
ROADBLOCK AND GET HIM LOADED UP
ONTO THE TRUCK.
IT TOOK A LOT OF COAXING AND
SEVERAL HOURS BUT THE CRABBY
VISITOR FINALLY MADE IT BACK
HOME SAFELY.
>> THIS THE OREGON TRAIL?  DO
YOU REMEMBER THAT NAME.
>> YEAH.
>> MY OXON DIED SHORTING THE
RIVER BUT THERE WAS NEVER
ANYTHING ABOUT A SEA LION.
>>> THE FAT CAT THAT GRABBED THE
DMV'S HEART HAS BEEN ADOPTED.
CHRISTMAS TIME WHEN EIGHT YEAR
OLD WILFORD WAS TAKEN IN BY THE
HUMANE RESCUE ALLIANCE.
HE HAS BEEN ADOPTED BY A FAMILY
NEAR COLLEGE PARK MARYLAND.
LOOK AT THAT FAT CAT.
WILFORD WILL NEED A LOT OF
ATTENTION.
HE HAS ASTHMA HAS A VET MONITOR
DIET AND EXERCISE.
THE FAMILY WERE PREVIOUSLY
PARENTS TO A 35 POUND CAT
ACCORDING TO DCS.
SO FAT CATS ARE THEIR BUSINESS
THERE FOR THAT HOUSE HOW OLD.
>> YES.
>> WE DO WANT TO SHOW YOU A
HEART WARMING REUNION, A LOCAL
POSTAL WORKER WAS REUNITED WITH
A MISSING TODDLER HE FOUND
EARLIER THIS MONTH.
KEITH ROLLINS LEARNED OF THE
MISSING ELKRIDGE BOY ON FOX5
BEFORE HEADING TO WORK.
HE SUDDENLY SAW THE BOY BAREFOOT
ON THE SHOULDER OF I95 WHEN HE
CALLED AUTHORITIES, CALLED 911
AND TODAY ROLLINS WAS REUNITED
WITH FIRST RESPONDERS AND LITTLE
ETHAN.
>> GOD JUST PUT ME IN THE RIGHT
PLACE AT THE RIGHT TIME.
WASN'T EVEN PAYING ATTENTION
WASN'T EVEN THINKING ABOUT IT.
JUST HAPPENED TO LOOK OVER THAT
WAY AND SAW HIM.
SO JUST BY GOD I SAW HIM.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
GOD BLESS YOU.
>> YOU MIGHT RECALL, THAT WAS A
REALLY COLD MORNING, AND HE SAID
WHEN HE FOUND HIM, LITTLE ETHAN,
WHO HAD DISAPPEARED ON
FEBRUARY 5TH WAS SHIVERING, WAS
COLD AND WET.
FORTUNATELY, THOUGH, HE WAS NOT
HURT.
>> AND AT THE TIME, YOU KNOW,
THE FAMILY'S HOUSE WAS IN A
NEIGHBORHOOD NEAR THE HIGHWAY,
BUT THEY COULDN'T FIGURE OUT HOW
THAT KID GOT THROUGH FENCING AND
BARRIERS ONTO THE HIGHWAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY EVER FOUND
OUT.
>> NO, BUT IF THERE'S ONE THING
I KNOW ABOUT KIDS, THEY CAN SHOW
UP ANYPLACE ANYTIME IN SPLIT
SECONDS.
>> SO MANY OF THESE STORIES END
HORRIBLY.
NICE TO HEAR A HAPPY ENDING.
>> STILL TO COME AN UPDATE ON
THE SOCIAL MEDIA SENSATION KNOWN
AS THE LEANING TOWER OF DALLAS.
CREWS TRIED TO DEMOLISH AND THE
CORE OF THE BUILDING WOULDN'T
FALL DOWN.
THEY TRIED AGAIN AND IT STILL
DIDN'T GO WELL.
>>> PLUS THE SIX YEAR OLD GIRL
PLACED IN HANDCUFFS, POLICE
RELEASING THAT SHOCKING VIDEO OF
A GIRL TAKEN AWAY FROM HER
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN A COP CAR.
>>> LIVE LOOK AT TRAFFIC AROUND
THE DMV AS RUSH HOUR RAMPS UP ON
THIS GRAY DREARY TUESDAY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
We made USAA insurance for
members like Kate.
A former Army medic, made of the
flexibility to handle
whatever Monday has in store and
tackle four things at once.
So when her car got hit, she
didn't worry.
She simply filed a claim on her
USAA app and said...
I got this.
USAA insurance is made the way
Kate needs it - easy.
She can even pick her payment
plan
so it's easy on her budget
and her life.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪
>> BACK NOW WITH SOME DISTURBING
POLICE BODY CAM VIDEO TO SHARE
WITH YOU.
IT SHOWS A LITTLE GIRL BEGGING
AND PLEADING OFFICERS NOT TO
TAKE HER TO JAIL.
>> PLEASE LET ME GO.
>> UGHH.
>> SIX YEAR OLD COULD I A ROLL
WAS
THREE EMPLOYEES.
AT ISSUE IS THE OFFICERS CALL TO
ARREST.
>> SHE'S EIGHT ISN'T SHE?
>> SHE'S SIX.
NOW SHE HAS BROKEN THE RECORD.
>> HE SO-CAL USUALLY SAID, WELL,
THERE GOES MY RECORD.
LIKE HE IS TALING.
THESE ARE NOTCHES ON HIS BELT.
>> WELL, THE OFFICER WHO
AUTHORIZED THE ARREST WAS LATER
FIRED FOR NOT GETTING SUPERVISOR
APPROVAL WHICH IS NEEDED WHEN
ARRESTING A CHILD UNDER THE AGE
OF 12.
THEY'VE SINCE DROPPED THE
CHARGES AGAINST SKY A AND
ANOTHER CHILD ALSO ARRESTED.
>>> ANOTHER DEMOCRATIC DEBATE
TONIGHT THE LAST BEFORE SOUTH
CAROLINA VOTES THIS WEEKEND.
SEVEN CANDIDATES WILL TAKE THE
STAGE IN CHARLESTON.
BERNIE SANDERS CURRENTLY HOLDS
THE DELEGATE LEAD AFTER
BACK-TO-BACK WINS THAT WILL
LIKELY MAKE HIM A BIG TARGET
TONIGHT.
MOON TIME THE NEWSPAPER HAS
ENDORSED PETE BUTTIGIEG AND THE
RECENT POLLING SHOWED JOE BIDEN
AS THE FRONT RUNNER.
TONIGHT'S DEBATE STARTS AT 8:00
O'CLOCK AND AIRS ON CBS.
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT
IS.
>> WHAT TIME'S THAT?
>> TIME FOR YOUR FAT TUESDAY
WEATHER.
>> IT IS FAT TUESDAY.
>> AM I THE ONLY ONE EXCITED
ABOUT MARDI GRAS OR PARTY GRAS.
>> IT'S A TUESDAY ON A WORK
WEEK.
ANGIE LAND EVERY DAY IS A PARTY
BUT FOR THE REST OF US.
>> BUT IF THERE'S ANYTHING THAT
CAN MAKE IT BETTER IT'S THE FACT
IT'S FAT TUESDAY NOT ANY OTHER
TUESDAY.
>> TRUE, THAT ELEVATES THE
AVERAGE TUESDAY.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO DRINK, YOU
GUYS CONTINUE.
>> YOU DRINK, YOU EAT, PUT ON
YOUR FATHERED BOW AS, YES IT IS
MARDI GRAS.
THERE ARE THINGS GOING ON AROUND
TOWN, THE RAIN HAS CLEARED OUT,
STILL NOT SO NICE OUT BUT THE
ACTUAL RAIN HAS COME TO AN END.
WE PICK THAT RIGHT BACK UP
TOMORROW NIGHT, AS I STRONG LOW
PRESSURE SYSTEM COMES BY GUSTY
COLD FRONT BRINGS STRONG WINDSEN
A A ROUND OF HEAVY RAIN ALTHOUGH
BRIEF ROUND TOMORROW NIGHT.
54 DEGREES OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW,
CLOUDY SKIES SUCCESS BEHIND ME
AND BEHIND THE CAPITOL WHEEL NO
SUNSHINE TODAY, A HEALTHY DOSE
OF RAIN SHOWERS THIS MORNING
ALONG A WARM FRONT THAT'S LIFTED
NORTH WASHED AND EVEN THOUGH YOU
CAN VERY CAN'T SEE IT ON RADAR
CLOUDS AND FOG AND DRIZZLE STILL
STUCK OVER US BUT THE FALLING
RAIN OFF TOWARDS OUR NORTH.
THIS EXTENDS ALL THE WAY BACK
TOWARDS LOW PRESSURE IN THE
CENTRAL PLAINS WHERE YOU SEE
SOME SNOW ACROSS PARTS OF
COLORADO AND KANSAS, EVEN THE
TEXAS PANHANDLE.
THAT WHOLE SYSTEM WILL MOVE
EASTWARD AND AS IT KIND OF
PUSHES THROUGH TOMORROW NIGHT,
RATHER DYNAMIC, AND WHEN WE SAY
DYNAMIC WE MEAN WE COULD EVEN
HAVE THUNDERSTORMS HERE IN
FEBRUARY.
SO WE'LL SEE.
THAT'S NOT A GUARANTY BUT I
THINK IT WILL BE MOSTLY A LINE
OF GUSTY RAIN SHOWERS.
TOMORROW NIGHT, BY THE WAY.
SO FOR THE METRO IT'S PROBABLY
EVEN AFTER THE EVENING COMMUTE.
AT LEAST WHAT WE THINK RIGHT
NOW.
OUT AHEAD OF IT IT WILL BE A
MILD DAY TOMORROW.
THE FRONT COMES THROUGH BRINGS
THE RAIN BRIEFLY AND THEN THE
WINDS WILL PICK UP AND IT WILL
BE RATHER GUSTY THROUGH
THURSDAY.
SO WE FAST FORWARD 24 HOURS,
THIS IS WEDNESDAY, TOMORROW AT
4:00 O'CLOCK, WINDS NOT SO BAD.
IN ADVANCE OF THAT FRONT WE'LL
START TO SEE THOSE GUSTS OUT OF
THE SOUTH AT ABOUT 20 TO 30
MILES AN HOUR, THIS IS AT 11:00
O'CLOCK.
FRONT CLEARS, WIND DIRECTION
CHANGES BUT IT STAYS RATHER
BLUSTERY OUT OF THE NORTH AND
WEST AND, IN FACT, IN SOME OF
THE HIGHER ELEVATIONS THEY COULD
SEE SOME GUSTS OVER 40 MILES AN
HOUR AT TIMES.
WE STAY PRETTY BREEZY THROUGH
THE DAY ON THURSDAY AND THAT'S
AS COLDER AIR WILL BE POURING
IN.
SO FEELING MUCH MORE LIKE WINTER
BY THURSDAY.
60 DEGREES, WE SHOULD HIT, OUT
AHEAD OF THAT RAIN AND WIND
TOMORROW NIGHT, AND THEN BY
THURSDAY IT'S BREEZY, MUCH
COLDER, 47 AND PROBABLY FALLING
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
SATURDAY LOOKS TO BE THE COLDEST
DAY OF THE WEEK, WE'LL HAVE A
PREVIEW OF THAT WEEKEND FORECAST
THAT'S STILL AHEAD.
ANGIE AND BLAKE, BACK OVER TO
YOU.
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>>> REMEMBER THE SOCIAL MEDIA
SENSATION, THEY'RE CALLING IT
THE LEANING TOWER OF DALLAS?  IT
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE KNOCKED DOWN
YESTERDAY, BUT IT'S STILL
STANDING AS YOU CAN SEE.
LAST WEEK VIDEO OF THE HIGH RISE
WENT VIRAL AFTER THE CORE HAVE
THE BUILDING SURVIVED AN
IMPLOSION SO YESTERDAY CREWS
WERE SUPPOSED TO DEMOLISH MUCH
WHATS LEFT BUT IF YOU CAN SEE IT
CLOSE UP, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
BELIEVE WHAT THEY USED.
>> I NEED TO SEE THIS.
>> THEY USED A WRECKING BALL BUT
IT'S LIKE THE SMALLEST WRECKING
BALL.
>> LIKE A MILEY CYRUS WRECK
>> HONESTLY HER'S WAS PROBABLY
BALL.
BIGGER BUT INSTEAD WE'RE LOOKING
>> HONESTLY HER'S WAS PROBABLY
AT THE PEOPLE.
BIGGER BUT INSTEAD WE'RE LOOKING
>> THEY'RE DUMFOUNDED.
AT THE PEOPLE.
>> LET'S GO TO THE SOUND.
>> THEY'RE DUMFOUNDED.
>> CAN'T BE DESTROYING THIS.
>> LET'S GO TO THE SOUND.
IT'S A NATIONAL LANDMARK.
>> CAN'T BE DESTROYING THIS.
WAIT.
IT'S A NATIONAL LANDMARK.
IS THAT?  IS THAT THE WRECKING
WAIT.
BALL?  THAT LITTLE THIMBLE.
IS THAT?  IS THAT THE WRECKING
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?  YOU
BALL?  THAT LITTLE THIMBLE.
CAN'T DESTROY THE LEANING TOWER
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?  YOU
OF DALLAS WITH A THIMBLE.
CAN'T DESTROY THE LEANING TOWER
>> THEY WERE RIGHT THE BUILDING
OF DALLAS WITH A THIMBLE.
DIDN'T COME DOWN.
>> THEY WERE RIGHT THE BUILDING
>> IS THAT THE WRECKING BALL?
DIDN'T COME DOWN.
>> THAT TINY THING YOU SEE IT?
>> IS THAT THE WRECKING BALL?
IT'S HARD TO SEE.
>> THAT TINY THING YOU SEE IT?
YOU WOULD THINK AFTER BEING
IT'S HARD TO SEE.
EMBARRASSED THE FIRST TIME THEY
YOU WOULD THINK AFTER BEING
WOULD THROW EVERYTHING AT IT THE
EMBARRASSED THE FIRST TIME THEY
SECOND TIME.
WOULD THROW EVERYTHING AT IT THE
>> LIKE DYNAMITE.
SECOND TIME.
>> CONSTRUCTION CREWS GAVE UP
>> LIKE DYNAMITE.
AND WENT HOME AFTER USING THAT
>> CONSTRUCTION CREWS GAVE UP
LITTLE WRECKING BALL ALL DAY TO
AND WENT HOME AFTER USING THAT
TRY TO MAKE A DENT IN THE
LITTLE WRECKING BALL ALL DAY TO
PROBLEM.
TRY TO MAKE A DENT IN THE
>> THEY NEED TO SECURE THE
PROBLEM.
FOUNDATION AND THIS NEEDS TO BE
>> THEY NEED TO SECURE THE
OUR NEW LEANING TOWER OF POSSESS
FOUNDATION AND THIS NEEDS TO BE
A IN THE U.S. STATE SIDE AND
OUR NEW LEANING TOWER OF POSSESS
THEY NEED TO MAKE IT A TOURIST
A IN THE U.S. STATE SIDE AND
ATTRACTION, CAPITALIZE OFF OF
THEY NEED TO MAKE IT A TOURIST
IT.
ATTRACTION, CAPITALIZE OFF OF
>> DALLAS IS A MUCH SHORTER FLY.
IT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> DALLAS IS A MUCH SHORTER FLY.
>> WE COULD MAKE THAT LOOK
>> EXACTLY.
PRETTY, PUT SOME COLUMNS ON IT
>> WE COULD MAKE THAT LOOK
GOOD TO GO.
PRETTY, PUT SOME COLUMNS ON IT
>> PROBLEM SOLVED.
GOOD TO GO.
>>> STILL TO COME WE ARE GOING
>> PROBLEM SOLVED.
TO TALK ABOUT YOUR DOGS AND
>>> STILL TO COME WE ARE GOING
CATS.
TO TALK ABOUT YOUR DOGS AND
LEAVING YOUR PETS AT HOME DURING
CATS.
THE DAY, WE KNOW IT CAN CAN BE
LEAVING YOUR PETS AT HOME DURING
TOUGH, THE WAY THEY LOOK AT YOU
THE DAY, WE KNOW IT CAN CAN BE
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
TOUGH, THE WAY THEY LOOK AT YOU
WHAT SOME PEOPLE WOULD BE
WHEN YOU LEAVE.
WILLING TO GIVE UP, THOUGH, IF
WHAT SOME PEOPLE WOULD BE
THEY COULD BRING THEIR FERRY
WILLING TO GIVE UP, THOUGH, IF
FRIENDS TO WORK.
THEY COULD BRING THEIR FERRY
THE ANSWERS ACTUALLY MIGHT
FRIENDS TO WORK.
SURPRISE YOU.
THE ANSWERS ACTUALLY MIGHT
STAY WITH US.
SURPRISE YOU.
♪
Nobody wants to pay for things
thatat they don't use.
It's time to say bye to
the bundle.
Now, you can break the bundle
when you mix
and match on Fios, the
100% fiber-optic network.
We need fast internet because
we're always streaming
something.
Choose the internet speed that
works for you
and if you want TV, choose your
package.
I want my channels and nothing
else.
Switch now with internet plans
starting at just $39.99 per
month.
No extra fees. No annual
contracts.
Plus, get up to $200 in Visa
Prepaid Cards.
Only paying for the services
that I want - that's the future.
Only on Verizon.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
I'm Amy Klobuchar and I approve
this message.
We live in a country of shared
dreams.
That no matter where you come
from.
No matter the color of your
skin.
No matter who you love.
That you can make it in the
United States of America.
So I stand before you today
as the grandaughter of an iron
ore miner.
As the daughter of a teacher and
a newspaperman.
As the first woman elected to
the U.S. Senate from the state
of Minnesota.
And a candidate for president of
the United States.
♪
>> TIME TO TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
IS TRENDING, CAITLIN IS JOINING
US FOR THESE AND FIRST UP A NEW
VIDEO TREND THAT WE'VE BEEN
TRACKING WHERE TWO PEOPLE FLIP
POSITIONS.
TAKE A LOOK.
♪
>> THISISTIC TOCK RIGHT?
>> IT'S VERY TIK TOK.
IT'S THE SONG FLIP THE SWITCH BY
QUAVO FEATURING DRAKE.
MORE AND MORE VIDEOS HAVE
DROPPED UP OF PEOPLE DOING IT
INCLUDING THIS ONE.
>> LOOK AT THAT VIDEO.
VIDEO QUALITY.
♪
>> THAT IS SO MUCH BETTER.
>> OH, MY.
WELL, GUESS WHO THAT WAS.
>> OH, MY GOD I LOVE THAT CARMEN
SAN DIEGO HAT.
>> AND THE WIG THAT MAYBE TUCKER
FOUND UNDERNEATH HIS DESK.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
>> IS THAT AN AUSTIN POWERS LID?
>> WE'RE NOT SURE HE HAS ALL
KINDS OF WIGS AND FEATHER BOAS.
WE DID THIS EARLIER TODAY NOT
HAVING EVER SEEN IT BEFORE BUT
IT IS THAT SONG, BUT I JUST
FLIPPED THE SWITCH, FLIP FLIP.
>> IF YOU'RE NEW VIEWERS TO FOX5
OR DON'T WEAR OUR MORNING SHOW
CAITLIN IS ENGAGED TO OUR
MORNING METEOROLOGISTS TUCKER
BARNES AND YOU CAN SEE THEY'RE A
MATCH MADE IN HEAVEN.
>> HE'S PUTTING ON MAKEUP I'M
WEARING A PANTS SUIT.
YOU FLIP THE SWITCH, THE LIGHT
GOES OFF AND THEN YOU SWITCH
CLOTHES WITH YOUR PARTNER.
DON'T ASK ME WHY THIS CAUGHT ON.
IT ALSO HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH
TURNING THE WATER ON IN THE
BATHROOM.
>> DON'T ASK WHY?  THAT'S WHY
IT'S CAUGHT ON.
I NEED TO SEE MORE.
>> WE DON'T NEED AN EXPLANATION,
WE WANT MORE VIDEOS.
>> WELL, IT WASN'T DONE ON ONE
TAKE SO I'M SURE THERE ARE
OUTTAKES.
>> I'M JEALOUS THAT YOU CAN
SHARE CLOTHES WITH YOUR HUSBAND
THAT YOU'RE THE SAME SIZE.
>> DO WE LOOK LIKE THE SAME
SIZE.
>> HE IS A LITTLE BUSTY.
>> STRETCHY DRESSES.
>> I DID LIKE WEARING THE MEN'S
WEAR CAN I SAY?  I FELT VERY
ANNIE HALL IN IT.
>> VIRGINIA'S GOVERNOR CHANGES
THE SENTENCING RULES FOR
JUVENILES IN THE STATE, HAS BIG
COMPLICATIONS, WHAT IT COULD
MEAN FOR THE DC SNIPER, LEE BOYD
MALVO, HE HAS A LIFE SENTENCE.
NOW HE MAY BE ELIGIBLE FOR
PAROLE, GET YOUR PHONES OUT
BECAUSE THIS IS THE TOPIC OF OUR
FOX5 INSTAPOLL.
♪
♪♪
For hundreds of years
America systematically
stole Black lives,
Black freedom and Black labor.
And I know my story would've
turned out very differently
if I had been Black.
So today I'm proposing a
sweeping strategy
to invest in Black
wealth creation.
The wealth gap
is inextricably linked
to the racial
inequalities of the past,
and I'm determined to
make breaking that link
a centerpiece of my
presidency.
This home is equipped with Gig
Speed Internet from Xfinity.
There's this game-time
Internetting room. So fun.
And then there's this work
-from-home Internetting room.
Finally, the open-concept
Internetting room.
This is not an open house.
But your front door was open,
so technically it is.
Get gig speed and the
coverage you need with Xfinity
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get $100
back with this great offer.
Plus, get a free
upgrade to Gig speed.
That's a savings of
$360. Switch today.
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
NOW TIME FOR A LOOK AT OUR TOP
STORIES THAT WE CONTINUE TO
FOLLOW.
A TOWN HOUSE FIRE IN
GAITHERSBURG PROMPTED A LOT OF
CONCERN TODAY.
FLAMES AND HEAVY SMOKE GREETED
FIRE FIGHTERS ON OAK SHADE ROAD
NEAR CLOPPER ROAD.
THEY WERE ABLE TO RESCUE SEVERAL
DOGS INSIDE AND THANKFULLY NO
ONE WAS HURT.
>>> LAWMAKERS IN MONTGOMERY
COUNTY JUST APPROVED A LAW TO
REQUIRE LANDLORDS TO PROVIDE AIR
CONDITIONING.
DETACHED SINGLE FAMILY HOMES AND
CERTAIN HISTORIC PROPERTIES ARE
EXEMPT.
HIGH SUMMER TEMPERATURES ARE
ESPECIALLY DANGEROUS FOR THE
COUNTY'S GROWING NUMBER OF
SENIOR CITIZENS.
ONCE THE BILL IS SIGNED IT WOULD
TAKE EFFECT IN 90 DAYS.
>>> TODAY FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN
ADVISOR ROGER STONE WAS BACK
BEFORE THE SAME JUDGE WHO
SENTENCED HIM TO MORE THAN THREE
YEARS IN PRISON LAST WEEK.
HE'S ASKING FOR A NEW TRIAL.
STONE WAS CONVICTED OF LYING TO
CONGRESS, OBSTRUCTION AND
WITNESS TAMPERING AS A RESULT OF
THE MUELLER REPORT INTO 2016'S
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN MEDDLING
BY RUSSIA.
THE DEFENSE IS EXPECTED TO ARGUE
THAT THE JURY WAS BIASED AND
COMMITTED MISCONDUCT.
>>> VIRGINIA'S GOVERNOR TODAY
DEFENDED HIS SIGNATURE ON A BILL
THAT REWRITES SENTENCING RULES
FOR JUVENILES.
THE RESULT COULD MEAN DC SNIPER
LEE BOYD MALVO MAY ONE DAY BE
CONSIDERED FOR PAROLE.
FOX5'S TOM FITZGERALD IS
FOLLOWING THIS CASE CLOSELY.
SO FITZ THIS MEANS ANYTHING WITH
A LIFE SENTENCE IN VIRGINIA, IF
THEY'RE GIVEN THAT SENTENCE WHEN
THEY'RE UNDER 18, NOW HAS TO BE
ELIGIBLE FOR PAROLE?
>> Reporter: YEAH.
WELL, IT'S NOT JUST ANYBODY.
THIS SPECIFICALLY REFERS TO
JUVENILES IN VIRGINIA WHO WERE
SENTENCED WITHOUT EVER HAVING
THE POSSIBILITY OF PAROLE.
I WAS IN HERE WHEN THESE
ARGUMENTS IN THE MALVO CASE WERE
HEARD BEFORE THE SUPREME COURT
JUSTICES AND WHEN YOU SAT IN
THAT HEARING THAT DAY, IT SEEMED
LIKELY THAT THE JUSTICES WERE
GOING TO OVERTURN VIRGINIA'S
LAW.
NOT JUST ON THE MERITS OF LEE
BOYD MALVO'S CASE BUT BECAUSE
THERE HAD BEEN SEVERAL SUPREME
COURT CASES WHICH RULED THAT
JUVENILES HAD THE RIGHT TO BE
ELIGIBLE FOR PAROLE.
SO WHAT GOVERNOR NORTHAM DID IN
SIGNING THIS LAW YESTERDAY WAS
ALLOW FOR THAT POSSIBILITY OF A
JUVENILE HAD BEEN SENTENCED IN
VIRGINIA WITHOUT THE POSSIBILITY
OF PAROLE, THAT IF THEY HAD
SERVED 20 YEARS, BLAKE, THEY
WOULD, IN FACT, BE ELIGIBLE.
HOWEVER, WHEN IT COMES TO LEE
BOYD MALVO, IT'S VERY UNLIKELY
HE IS EVER GOING TO SEE THE
LIGHT OF DAY OUTSIDE OF PRISON
WALLS.
AND FOR A VERY GOOD REASON.
YOU KNOW, NOT ONLY, YOU KNOW,
THE DEPRAVITY OF THE CRIMES HE
WAS CONVICTED OF, THE MURDERS OF
THE DC REGION.
A LOT OF US WERE HERE AND
EXPERIENCED THAT, HE'S ALSO
FACING SIX LIFE SENTENCES IN THE
STATE OF MARYLAND WHERE SOME OF
HIS OTHER VICTIMS WERE KILLED.
SO WHILE A LOT OF THE ATTENTION
GOES TO THE FACT THIS THIS WAS
MALVO'S CASE IT'S UNLIKELY MALVO
HIMSELF WILL EVER REALLY BENEFIT
AND HAVE THE POSSIBILITY OF
PAROLE.
>> THIS BRINGS UP THE BROADER
ISSUE THOUGH THAT WHEN A CRIME
HAPPENS IN SEVERAL STATES AND
SOMEONE IS CONVICTED IN ONE
STATE WHY IT MAY BE NECESSARY
FOR ANOTHER STATE TO STILL
PURSUE THEIR CHARGES BECAUSE, IN
THIS CASE, IN THE UNLIKELY EVENT
HE WERE TO GET OUT OF JAIL SINCE
MARYLAND HAS TAKE CONVICTION
THEY COULD TAKE HIM IMMEDIATELY
INTO CUSTODY.
THE PATCH WORK OF SENTENCING TO-
LAWS WE HAVE ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
THAT PEOPLE BEHIND SOME OF THE
SENTENCING REFORMS ACROSS THIS
COUNTRY HAVE POINTED TO.
ONE STATE SAY IN TEXAS HAS A
SENTENCING GUIDELINE IN ONE
CRIME WHERE ANOTHER STATE SAY IN
MARYLAND IT'S A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT SET OF RULES.
THAT IS WHY THE SUPREME COURT
WAS BROUGHT INTO THIS.
BUT WE SPOKE WITH DOUG GANSLER
TODAY, THE FORMER ATTORNEY
JENNIFER THE STATE OF MARYLAND.
HE PROSECUTED LEE BOYD MALVO AND
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR GETTING
THOSE CONVICTIONS THAT LED TO
THOSE SIX LIFE TERMS.
GANSLER SAID TODAY THAT EVEN
THOUGH HE WAS THE PROSECUTOR
THAT, YOU KNOW, GOT THESE
CHARGES IN MARYLAND, HE GREASE
WITH THIS MOVE TODAY.
NOT BECAUSE HE IS ANY FAN OF LEE
BOYD MALVO OR EVER THINKS THAT
HE SHOULD GET OUT OF PRISON BUT
HE DOES THINK THERE IS SOME
GRAVITY HERE TO CONSIDER WHEN
YOU'RE SENTENCING THESE
JUVENILES ESPECIALLY AFTER
THEY'VE SERVED TWO DECADES OF
THEIR SENTENCE.
IT WOULD ULTIMATELY BE UP TO THE
PAROLE BOARD TO MAKE THOSE
DECISIONS, NOT POLITICIANS AND
NOT GOVERNORS.
>> AND JUST BECAUSER' ELIGIBLE
FOR PAROLE DOESN'T MEAN IT WILL
EVER HAPPEN.
TOM FITZGERALD LIVE FOR US THANK
YOU.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY.
>>> THAT BRINGS US TO TODAY'S
FOX5 INSTAPOLL SHOULD PEOPLE
SERVING LIFE TERMS FOR CRIMES
CONSIDERED AS MINORS BE
CONSIDERED FOR PAROLE.
YOU CAN VOTE ON FOX5DC.COM OR ON
THE FOX5 NEWS APP.
AND LOOKS LIKE RIGHT NOW YOU ARE
OVERWHELMINGLY SAYING NO.
KEEP THOSE VOTES COMING.
STILL TO COME, ANGIE, WHAT DAY
IS IT?
>> HERE, I GOT YOU SOMETHING,
BLAKE.
GO AHEAD, PUT THEM ON.
>> THESE ARE BIG BEADS, WHAT DID
YOU HAVE TO DO FOR THESE, ANGIE?
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
THAT'S RIGHT, KEEP THE KING
CAKE, KEEP THE HURRICANES
FLOWING, BECAUSE, GUESS WHAT?
WE ARE GOING TO CHECK IN WITH
MR. GARY MCGRADY FOR A LITTLE
MARDI GRAS OR PARTY GRAS.
>> OUR NEWS ROOM.
>> MICHAEL COLLIER SHOW US WHAT
YOU'RE WORKING WITH.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT WE
ARE ALL ABOUT MARDI GRAS.
>> IT'S LIKE LIB RAPY TUESDAY.
PRODUCER MARIANA.
>> SHE IS OUT OF CONTROL.
>> SHE IS LOSING IT.
>> LIVE TO GARY COMING UP NEXT.
♪
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
This home is equipped with Gig
Speed Internet from Xfinity.
There's this game-time
Internetting room. So fun.
And then there's this work
-from-home Internetting room.
Finally, the open-concept
Internetting room.
This is not an open house.
But your front door was open,
so technically it is.
Get gig speed and the
coverage you need with Xfinity
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get $100
back with this great offer.
Plus, get a free
upgrade to Gig speed.
That's a savings of
$360. Switch today.
♪
>> THE FIRST BIG PARTY OF THE
YEAR IS RIGHT HERE.
NOT TIED TO THE SUPER BOWL.
IT'S WELL UNDERWAY RIGHT NOW IN
NEW ORLEANS.
>> AUTHORITIES, FAT US THE MARKS
THE FINAL DAY BEFORE THE START
OF THE EASTER SEASON AND IT'S A
GOOD EXCUSE FOR EVERYONE TO JUST
CELEBRATE, TURN THE LIGHTS ON,
GO CRAZY.
THERE WE GO.
DRESS UP, GET A DRINK ON.
FOX5'S GARY MCGRADY IS LIVE
TONIGHT SOAKING UP SOME OF THE
FUN.
APPEAR, OF COURSE, I MEAN, I
CAN'T THINK OF A BETTER PLACE TO
FIND YOU THAN BEHIND A BAR.
>> REPORTER: YEAH.
I'M JUST WORKING A LITTLE BIT
BEFORE WE DO THIS.
I HAVE PBR, THERE'S A GLASS OF
CHARDONNAY, TOO.
I'VE DONE THIS BEFORE, ALL
RIGHT?  MARDI GRAS, LOOK AT
EVERYBODY.
THEY HAVE JUST SHOWN UP, TOO.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU, POBOY
JIMMY'S, NOT JIM BUT JEFF,
CORRECT.
>> YES.
>> Reporter: YOU'RE THE OWNER
HERE.
>> YES, ONE OF THE PARTNERING
BEEN IN BUSINESS SIX YEARS, TWO
HERE.
LOCATIONS, THIS IS OUR FIFTH
BEEN IN BUSINESS SIX YEARS, TWO
ANNUAL MARDI GRAS CELEBRATION.
LOCATIONS, THIS IS OUR FIFTH
>> Reporter: WHAT DOES THAT
ANNUAL MARDI GRAS CELEBRATION.
MEAN.
>> Reporter: WHAT DOES THAT
>> A CELEBRATION FROM THE NEW
MEAN.
ORLEANS HERITAGE, FAT TUESDAY
>> A CELEBRATION FROM THE NEW
WHERE PEOPLE CELEBRATE THE
ORLEANS HERITAGE, FAT TUESDAY
HOLIDAY, KIND OF LIKE THE
WHERE PEOPLE CELEBRATE THE
HOLIDAY SEASON FOR THEM.
HOLIDAY, KIND OF LIKE THE
SO GOOD FOOD, GOOD DRINKS, GOOD
HOLIDAY SEASON FOR THEM.
SPIRITS, BEADS.
SO GOOD FOOD, GOOD DRINKS, GOOD
>> Reporter: GIVE ME AN EXAMPLE
SPIRITS, BEADS.
OF YOUR GOOD FOOD.
>> Reporter: GIVE ME AN EXAMPLE
BECAUSE THIS IS A LITTLE TASTE
OF YOUR GOOD FOOD.
OF NEW ORLEANS RIGHT HERE.
BECAUSE THIS IS A LITTLE TASTE
>> CORRECT.
OF NEW ORLEANS RIGHT HERE.
WE'RE KNOWN FOR OUR POBOYS.
>> CORRECT.
BUT WE ALSO HAVE GREAT SIGNATURE
WE'RE KNOWN FOR OUR POBOYS.
NEW ORLEANS DISHES, RICE, GUM
BUT WE ALSO HAVE GREAT SIGNATURE
BOW AND BEIGNETS OF COURSE.
NEW ORLEANS DISHES, RICE, GUM
>> WHAT'S SPECIAL.
BOW AND BEIGNETS OF COURSE.
WHAT ARE YOU MAKING.
>> WHAT'S SPECIAL.
>> HURRICANES AND PEACH
WHAT ARE YOU MAKING.
MARGARITA.
>> HURRICANES AND PEACH
>> YOU KEEP MAKING THOSE.
MARGARITA.
WATCH JOE AT WORK HE'S REALLY
>> YOU KEEP MAKING THOSE.
GOOD.
WATCH JOE AT WORK HE'S REALLY
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN AND HOW LONG
GOOD.
DOES THIS MARDI GRAS CELEBRATION
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN AND HOW LONG
GO EFFORTS WE'RE GOING FROM FOUR
DOES THIS MARDI GRAS CELEBRATION
TO 12, ALL DAY LONG.
GO EFFORTS WE'RE GOING FROM FOUR
IT'S ONE OF OUR BIGGEST EVENTS
TO 12, ALL DAY LONG.
OF THE YEAR.
IT'S ONE OF OUR BIGGEST EVENTS
WE LIKE TO BRING THE PEOPLE OUT,
OF THE YEAR.
GIVE THEM NICE GOOD DEALS, THE
WE LIKE TO BRING THE PEOPLE OUT,
SPECIALS.
GIVE THEM NICE GOOD DEALS, THE
>> WHAT THE SPECIALS.
SPECIALS.
>> 2-10 FOR THE HURRICANE
>> WHAT THE SPECIALS.
DRINKS, HAPPY OUR FOOD PRICES
>> 2-10 FOR THE HURRICANE
ALL DAY LONG.
DRINKS, HAPPY OUR FOOD PRICES
>> Reporter: THAT'S A BIG DRINK.
ALL DAY LONG.
>> THAT'S IT, TWO OF THOSE FOR
>> Reporter: THAT'S A BIG DRINK.
TEN.
>> THAT'S IT, TWO OF THOSE FOR
THATS A STAPLE DRINK, WE HAVE A
TEN.
HUGE FOLLOWING AND WE LIKE TO
THATS A STAPLE DRINK, WE HAVE A
MAKE SURE WE TAKE CARE OF OUR
HUGE FOLLOWING AND WE LIKE TO
PEOPLES.
MAKE SURE WE TAKE CARE OF OUR
>> Reporter: I'M GOING TO TALK
PEOPLES.
TO JOE.
>> Reporter: I'M GOING TO TALK
HOW MANY BOOZE DID YOU PUT IN
TO JOE.
THERE HOW MANY DIFFERENT
HOW MANY BOOZE DID YOU PUT IN
LIQUORS.
THERE HOW MANY DIFFERENT
>> THREE OR FOUR DEPENDING ON
LIQUORS.
THE LEVEL OF HURRICANE, WE HAVE
>> THREE OR FOUR DEPENDING ON
ONE TO CATEGORY 5, CATEGORY 5 OF
THE LEVEL OF HURRICANE, WE HAVE
COURSE IS THE MOST DANGEROUS.
ONE TO CATEGORY 5, CATEGORY 5 OF
>> Reporter: WE CALL IT CAT FIVE
COURSE IS THE MOST DANGEROUS.
IN THE BUSINESS.
>> Reporter: WE CALL IT CAT FIVE
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A CAT 3 pBE
IN THE BUSINESS.
CAT FIVES.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A CAT 3 pBE
>> REPORTER: I'LL BE THE JUDGE.
CAT FIVES.
IS IT READY.
>> REPORTER: I'LL BE THE JUDGE.
>> YES, IT IS.
IS IT READY.
>> Reporter: I'M TASTING FOR MY
>> YES, IT IS.
FRIENDS BLAKE AND ANGIE BACK
>> Reporter: I'M TASTING FOR MY
ENTER THE STUDIO.
FRIENDS BLAKE AND ANGIE BACK
>> THAT'S A PEACH MARGARITA.
ENTER THE STUDIO.
>> Reporter: THAT'S A PEACH
>> THAT'S A PEACH MARGARITA.
MARGARITA.
>> Reporter: THAT'S A PEACH
>> IT IS.
MARGARITA.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE
>> IT IS.
HURRICANE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE
>> THIS IS CAT 3.
HURRICANE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS MAJOR I'M
>> THIS IS CAT 3.
LETTING YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: THIS IS MAJOR I'M
>> JUST BE CAREFUL MR. MCGRADY.
LETTING YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: THAT'S MY DAD.
>> JUST BE CAREFUL MR. MCGRADY.
YOU CAN CALL ME GARY.
>> Reporter: THAT'S MY DAD.
ALL THE BOOZE ON TOP.
YOU CAN CALL ME GARY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
ALL THE BOOZE ON TOP.
>> WAIT A MINUTE YOU HAVE TO
>> OH, MY GOD.
GIVE THAT A LITTLE STIR.
>> WAIT A MINUTE YOU HAVE TO
>> REPORTER: MY FRIEND JOE, MY
GIVE THAT A LITTLE STIR.
FRIEND JEFF, POURING BOOZE,
>> REPORTER: MY FRIEND JOE, MY
SPECIALS, LOTS OF PO BOYS.
FRIEND JEFF, POURING BOOZE,
BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
SPECIALS, LOTS OF PO BOYS.
>> THANK YOU GARY.
BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
IT'S A CAT FIVE HERE IN THE
>> THANK YOU GARY.
STUDIO.
IT'S A CAT FIVE HERE IN THE
>> Reporter: THAT WENT STRAIGHT
STUDIO.
TO THE HEAD.
>> Reporter: THAT WENT STRAIGHT
>>> LOOK AT STUFF BLOWING ALL
TO THE HEAD.
OVER THE PLACE.
>>> LOOK AT STUFF BLOWING ALL
LOOK AT THIS OUT OF CONTROL.
OVER THE PLACE.
THIS IS THE THING, WE LOOK LIKE
LOOK AT THIS OUT OF CONTROL.
WE'VE BEEN BEHIND THE BAR, OKAY?
THIS IS THE THING, WE LOOK LIKE
WE LOOK LIKE -- I MEAN, WE
WE'VE BEEN BEHIND THE BAR, OKAY?
SHOULD BE THE ONES BACK THERE
WE LOOK LIKE -- I MEAN, WE
MAKING DRINKS.
SHOULD BE THE ONES BACK THERE
THE RULE, THOUGH, IS LIKE ISN'T
MAKING DRINKS.
IT AN OUNCE FOR EVERY OUNCE OF
THE RULE, THOUGH, IS LIKE ISN'T
ALCOHOL AN OUNCE OF JUICE.
IT AN OUNCE FOR EVERY OUNCE OF
>> SO LIKE 50/50?
ALCOHOL AN OUNCE OF JUICE.
>> SOMETHING.
>> SO LIKE 50/50?
>> THAT'S STILL A STRONG DRINK.
>> SOMETHING.
>> MAYBE.
>> THAT'S STILL A STRONG DRINK.
ALL RIGHT.
>> MAYBE.
>>> STILL TO COME -- IS THAT
ALL RIGHT.
YOUR RULE WITH THIS ONE?
>>> STILL TO COME -- IS THAT
>> YEAH.
YOUR RULE WITH THIS ONE?
>> THE ACADEMY AWARD WINNING
>> YEAH.
MOVIE PARASITE HAS STRUCK A
>> THE ACADEMY AWARD WINNING
DEAL, YOU'LL NOW BE ABLE TO
MOVIE PARASITE HAS STRUCK A
WATCH IT FROM THE COMFORT OF
DEAL, YOU'LL NOW BE ABLE TO
YOUR HOME.
WATCH IT FROM THE COMFORT OF
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE IT WILL BE
YOUR HOME.
STREAMING COMING UP.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE IT WILL BE
>>> AND THE BILLBOARD MUSIC
STREAMING COMING UP.
AWARDS IS TWO MONTHS AWAY AND
>>> AND THE BILLBOARD MUSIC
THEY'VE JUST ANNOUNCED THEIR
AWARDS IS TWO MONTHS AWAY AND
HOST FOR THIS YEAR'S SHOW.
THEY'VE JUST ANNOUNCED THEIR
CAITLIN WE FINALLY HAVE AN
HOST FOR THIS YEAR'S SHOW.
AWARDS SHOW WITH A HOST.
CAITLIN WE FINALLY HAVE AN
>> WHAT A NOVEL CONCEPT.
AWARDS SHOW WITH A HOST.
I KNOW.
>> WHAT A NOVEL CONCEPT.
LOOK AT THAT.
I KNOW.
BY THE WAY A PLUS ON THE
LOOK AT THAT.
COSTUMES AND BLAKE I DON'T KNOW
BY THE WAY A PLUS ON THE
WHAT HAPPENED.
COSTUMES AND BLAKE I DON'T KNOW
I THOUGHT YOU DID MORE COSTUMES.
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> I WAS UNDER DURESS HERE.
I THOUGHT YOU DID MORE COSTUMES.
WHEN ANGIE BRINGS LIKE EIGHT
>> I WAS UNDER DURESS HERE.
DIFFERENT OPTIONS IT'S HARD TO
WHEN ANGIE BRINGS LIKE EIGHT
SAY NO TO ALL OF THEM.
DIFFERENT OPTIONS IT'S HARD TO
>> I BRING OUT THE BEST IN HIM
SAY NO TO ALL OF THEM.
THAT'S THE TRANS LA IS.
>> I BRING OUT THE BEST IN HIM
>> YOU DO ANGIE AND BLAKE
THAT'S THE TRANS LA IS.
SOMETIMES IT'S EASIER TO JUST GO
>> YOU DO ANGIE AND BLAKE
ALONG.
SOMETIMES IT'S EASIER TO JUST GO
>> GIVE IN, YES.
ALONG.
>> MY HUSBAND WILL TELL YOU.
>> GIVE IN, YES.
>> RIGHT?  TAKE A CUE FROM
>> MY HUSBAND WILL TELL YOU.
ANGIE'S HUSBAND.
>> RIGHT?  TAKE A CUE FROM
GO ALONG WITH IT, YOU LOOK GOOD
ANGIE'S HUSBAND.
IN THE NECKLACE.
GO ALONG WITH IT, YOU LOOK GOOD
IT IS FAT US THE OF COURSE, IF
IN THE NECKLACE.
YOU'RE HEADING OUT TONIGHT THE
IT IS FAT US THE OF COURSE, IF
RAIN HAS COME TO AN END BUT WE
YOU'RE HEADING OUT TONIGHT THE
HAVE MORE RAIN TOMORROW NIGHT,
RAIN HAS COME TO AN END BUT WE
GUSTY RAIN SHOWERS ACTUALLY
HAVE MORE RAIN TOMORROW NIGHT,
LITTLE UNUSUAL FOR FEBRUARY WE
GUSTY RAIN SHOWERS ACTUALLY
SHOW YOU THE FORECAST COMING UP
LITTLE UNUSUAL FOR FEBRUARY WE
WHEN FOX5 AT 4:00 RETURNS.
SHOW YOU THE FORECAST COMING UP
♪
4:00 RETURNS.
♪♪
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
Wow!
That's Ensure Max Protein,
with high protein
and 1 gram sugar.
It's a sit-up, Banana!
Bend at the waist!
I'm tryin'!
Keep it up. You'll get there.
Whoa-hoa-hoa!
30 grams of protein,
and one gram of sugar.
ENSURE Max Protein.
♪
>> A CELEBRITY EXCLUSIVE COMING
UP ON FOX5 NEWS AT 5:00.
>> SARAH SIMMONS IS IN THE NEWS
ROOM WITH MORE ON WHAT THEY'RE
WORKING ON IN THE NEXT HOUR.
HI, SARAH.
>> HI, GUYS.
WE HAD A STAR SIGHTING IN THE DC
AREA, MAJOR CELEBRITY WAS
SPOTTED EARLIER TODAY.
HERE'S A HINT.
WAITING OUTSIDE WAS OUR OWN
KEVIN MCCARTHY, FOX5
PHOTOGRAPHER NELSON JONES AS
DOZENS OF TEEN-AGE GIRLS.
NOT THE TRIFECTA I WOULD
NORMALLY PUT TOGETHER.
BUT THE VIDEO IS SOMETHING
YOU'LL ONLY SEE ON FOX5.
PLUS WE HAVE AIRLINES THAT ARE
UNDER FIRE.
WHAT ONE ORGANIZATION IS DOING
TO MAKE IT EASIER FOR FAMILIES
TO SIT TOGETHER ON AIRPLANES
WITHOUT HAVING TO PAY EXTRA FOR
IT.
AND COULD THE HAPPIEST PLACE ON
EARTH BE THE KEY TO WEIGHT LOSS?
THE IMPACT THAT DISNEY LAND
COULD HAVE ON YOUR DIET.
MY GUESS IS YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO
EAT AFTER YOU GET THERE NOW
BECAUSE DIDN'T THEIR TICKET
PRICES JUST GO UP TO LIKE 200
BUCKS?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT PLUS LAST TIME
WE WERE THERE WE BOUGHT A
CHICKEN LEG THE SIZE OF MY FACE.
THEY SELL THESE THINGS.
>> FOR LIKE $50.
>> THEY'RE LIKE CLUBS.
SO I DON'T GET THAT.
OKAY.
>> EACH FAMILY MEMBER JUST TAKES
A SIDE AND YOU'RE ALL SEATING
THE SAME ONE.
>> THANK YOU SARAH.
>>> PET FREDLY ON THE RISE
ACCORDING TO ZIP RECRUIT, AND
PLOYS SAY WHAT THEY'RE WILLING
TO GIVE UP TO BRING THEIR PETS
TO WORK.
NEARLY HALF SURVEYED SAYING
HAVING A PET IN THE OFFICE MAKES
THE ATMOSPERE MORE POSITIVE.
THEY'D GIVE YOU FREE FAX CATERED
MALES EMPLOYEEDISCOUNTS AND ONE
VACATION DAY.
>> IF WE HAD SNACKS, WE HAVE
GOLD FISH.
>> WE HAVE SNACKS YOU JUST HAVE
TO PAY A LOT FOR THEM.
>>> WHEN IT COMES TO HOW YOUR
LIFE PLAYS OUT COULD IT ALL BE
IN THE CARDS?  THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO FIND OUT.
SO ON FAT TUESDAY IT IS ALL
ABOUT THE FUTURE ON THE OH MY
GOFF SHOW.
WE GOT OUR FIRST TAROT READING
WITH EMILY FROM WOVEN PSYCHE.
>> SO I'VE DONE TAROT READINGS
ON STAGE AT CAB RAY
PERFORMANCES.
>> DO YOU SING WITH THE CAB RAY
DECK?
>> THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
♪
>> YOU MADE CLEAR YOU'RE NOT A
PSYCHIC.
>> I THINK WHAT WE'RE DOING IS
EMPOWERING PEOPLE TO CREATE THE
FUTURE THAT THEY WANT.
>> I'M INTERESTED IN KNOWING THE
KIND OF STUFF PEOPLE WANT TO
KNOW.
>> A LOT OF MY CLIENTS REALLY
WANT TO MAKE A MARK ON THE WORLD
THEY WANT TO MAKE THE WORLD A
BETTER PLACE.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET THAT
HERE.
>> JENNIFER'S LIKE HOW CAN I
HAVE MORE -- OH, YEAH.
♪
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, EMILY DID ACTUALLY READ
OUR CARDS AND ALL I KNOW IS MINE
HAD A BIG MONEY TREE GROWING SO
I WAS LIKE OKAY I LIKE THAT.
KEEP THE CARDS GOING.
FOR MORTAR ON AND EVERYTHING
MARDI GRAS YOU CAN CHECK OUT THE
SHOW EPISODE 38, WATCH THE OH MY
GOFF SHOW ON YOUTUBE OR JUST
LISTEN TO IT ON APPLE POD CASTS,
SPOTIFY ANYWHERE YOU FIND YOUR
FAVORITE POD CASTS.
>> YOU TRY TO KEEP THINGS
POSITIVE AND BEFORE SHE CAME ON
YOU SAID HAVE YOU EVER DONE A
TAROT READING.
I SAID YEAH.
SHE SAID WHAT KIND OF THINGS DO
THEY TELL YOU.
I SAID THEY CAN GET DARK THEY
TELL YOU REAL STUFF.
>> SHE DID A LIGHT READING.
I WAS SCARED AND SAID NO DEATH
CARD.
SHE EXPLAINED TO ME THE DEATH
CARD ISN'T SOMETHING YOU SHOULD
NOT BE EXPLAINED OF BECAUSE IN
TAROT IT MEANS A REBIRTH OF
SOMETHING NOT THAT WE'RE ALL
GOING TO DIE.
>> WELL, WE ALL ARE GOING TO
DIE.
>> NOT LIKE TOMORROW.
>>> LITTLE MONSTERS GET READY
LADY GAGA WILL RELEASE HER NEW
SONG LADY LOVE ON FRIDAY.
SHE HAD MADE THE ANNOUNCEMENT
SOCIAL MEDIA.
IT'S HER FIRST SINGLE SINCE THE
ONE WITH BRADLEY COOPER IN A
STAR IS BORN.
YOU MIGHT REMEMBER IT WAS LEAKED
ON LINE NO WORD IF THAT'S THE
FINAL VERSION BUT WE FIND OUT
FRIDAY.
>>> KELLY CLARKSON IS BACK AGAIN
TO HOST THE BILLBOARD MUSIC
AWARDS THE THIRD YEAR IN A ROW.
SHE HAS OPENED THE SHOWS WITH A
IMMEDIATELY OF SONGS FROM THE
ARTISTS.
THE SINGER AND VOICE COACH IS
HOSTING HER OWN SHOW.
THE 2020 AWARDS WILL BE HELD IN
LAS VEGAS AND IT AIRS APRIL 29TH
AND IF I RECALL CORRECTLY LAST
YEAR SHE WAS SUPER SICK BUT SHE
STILL WENT ON, THE SHOW MUST GO
ON, AND SHE HOSTS IT.
>> IN SUCH A POLITICALLY
CHARGED, THERE ARE SO FEW THAT
ARE TAINTED BY POLITICS AND
SHE'S ONE.
>> SHE'S ONE.
>>> HULU ANNOUNCED IT WILL
EXCLUSIVELY STREAM THE FILM
PARASITE.
IT HAS A PARTNERSHIP WITH NEON
WHO PRODUCED IT.
IT WILL BE AVAILABLE TO STREAM
APRIL 8TH 9.
IT MADE HISTORY AT THE ACADEMY
AWARDS AS THE FIRST FOREIGN
MOVIE TO WIN BEST PICTURE, ALSO
WON BEST DIRECTOR BEST SCREEN
PLAY AND BEST INTERNATIONAL
FILM.
ANGIE WATCHED IT.
>> I WATCHED IT RIGHT BEFORE I
CAME INTO WORK, AND, I MEAN,
IT'S HEAVY.
IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN.
SO I'M JUST --
>> BUT YOU SAID IT WAS GREAT.
>> IT'S GREAT, THOUGH.
FANTASTIC, VERY DESERVING.
>> LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE ON THIS
GLOOMY GET DEEPER INTO
THE EVENING TO SEE IF THIS
STARTS TO BECOME OR NOT BECAUSE
WE CERTAINLY HAVE A GOOD SET UP
FOR IT WITH ALL THE LEFT OVER
MOISTURE FROM THIS MORNING
AROUND SO THAT'S THE ISSUE FOR
THE COMMUTE TOMORROW MORNING.
TOMORROW NIGHT, IT'S A STRONG
COLD FRONT COMING THROUGH, GUSTY
pLINE OF RAIN SHOWERS,
REMINISCENT OF A SUMMERTIME
SQUALL LINE IS EXPECTED.
I DON'T KNOW THAT WE'LL
NECESSARILY BE DOING
THUNDERSTORMS BUT I DO THINK
WE'LL HAVE SOME BRIEFLY HEAVY
RAIN AND VERY GUSTY WINDS.
IT WILL STAY WINDY EVEN BEHIND
THAT FRONTAL PASSAGE, AND THAT
WILL TRANSITION US INTO THURSDAY
WHERE IT WILL BE WINDY AND
COLDER AND FEELING LIKE WINTER.
WE HAVE MANY DAYS THIS WINTER
THAT HAVE FELT LIKE SPRING AND,
IN FACT, SPRING IS ACTUALLY
GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER.
23 DAYS, OUR COUNTDOWN MAP HAS
BEGUN.
THURSDAY MARCH 19TH AT 11:51
P.M.
BUT, LIKE I SAID, THIS WINTER
HAS BEEN MORE WHITE THAN WET AND
MORE SPRING THAN WINTER BECAUSE
DAYS OF MEASURABLE RAIN
INCLUDING TODAY WE'VE SEEN 40
DAYS OF RAIN THIS WINTER, THREE
DAYS OF MEASURABLE SNOW AND WE
ALL KNOW THAT HASN'T AMOUNTED TO
MUCH.
SO OVER TEN INCHES OF WATER SO
FAR, JUST SIX TENTHS OF AN INCH
OF SNOW FOR THIS YEAR AND, YOU
KNOW WHAT?  I THINK THAT'S GOING
TO BE IT.
GOT TO BE HONEST.
DON'T SEE OTHER CHANCES FOR SNOW
BEFORE THIS WINTER COMES TO A
CLOSE.
SHOWERS HAVE LIFTED NORTHWARD
ALONG THE WARM FRONT, WE HAVEN'T
CLEARED OUT ALONG THE RAIN HAS
STOPPED.
TEMPERATURES MILD IF NOT
STAGNANT.
THE WARM FRONT'S NORTH OF US BUT
WE DIDN'T REALLY GET TOO WARM.
54 HERE, 48 IN NAB, 50 IN
BALTIMORE, 52 DULLES, 54 IN
CULPEPER.
FOR TONIGHT, IF YOU HAVE PLANS,
YOU'RE STEPPING OUT, FAT
TUESDAY, CELEBRATIONS AROUND
TOWN, UMBRELLAS NOT REALLY
NEEDED, THERE MAY BE PATCHY
DRIZZLE OTHERWISE JUST CLOUDY
AND FOGGY WITH TEMPERATURES
AROUND 50 DEGREES TO ROUND OUT
THE NIGHT AT 11:00 O'CLOCK.
WATCH FUTURECAST, CAN'T RULE OUT
SOME SPRINKLES, LIGHT STUFF
OVERNIGHT, FOR THE DRIVE IN
TOMORROW WE'LL WATCH FOR FOG AND
DRIZZLE.
MUCH OF THE DAY WE'RE WAITING ON
THE COLD FRONT WHICH WILL BRING
THE RAIN AND THIS IS WHAT I WAS
TALKING ABOUT WITH THE SQUALL
LINE.
6:00 O'CLOCK TOMORROW NIGHT
SUBURBS SEEING SHOWERS, LIKELY
NOT TO GET INTO THE METRO UNTIL
AFTER THE EVENING COMMUTE, THIS
WOULD PUT IT BETWEEN 9:00 AND
10:00 P.M. THEN QUICKLY EXITING
STAGE RIGHT AND WE CLEAR OUT AND
TURN WINDY AND COLDER.
WE ARE OUTLOOKED FOR A MARGINAL
CHANCE OF STRONG STORMS
TOMORROW, THE MAYBE THREAT IS
THE GUSTY WINDS WITH THE FRONTAL
PASSAGE.
SO WE'LL SEE HOW THIS ALL
TRANSPIRES.
IT IS FEBRUARY, HOWEVER, IT HAS
BEEN AN UNUSUAL FEBRUARY, AND WE
CERTAINLY HAVE THE DYNAMICS IN
PLACE TO SEE SOME THUNDERSTORMS.
HERE'S YOUR PLANNER FOR
TOMORROW.
MOST OF THE DAY IS QUIET AND
MILD.
WE SHOULD GET CLOSE TO 60
DEGREES IN ADVANCE OF THOSE
SHOWERS.
SO LATE RAIN AND GUSTY FOR YOUR
WEDNESDAY, BREEZY AND COLDER
WITH FALLING TEMPERATURES
THURSDAY.
NOTICE INTO THE WEEKEND IT'S
CHILLY, DEFINITELY FEELS LIKE
WINTER, COLD, LOWS IN THE 20S,
HIGHS AROUND 40 ON SATURDAY, BUT
NOTHING ELSE TO COME ALONG WITH
IT, JUST SUNSHINE, SHOWERS
POSSIBLE AGAIN NEXT WEEK.
THAT'S YOUR SEVEN DAY.
BLAKE, BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU CAITLIN.
>>> STILL TO COME IT SEEMS DOGS
NEED THEIR COFFEE FIX AS WELL.
THESE PUPS GOING WILD FOR PUP
CHINOS AND THEIR ENTHUSIASM'S
ALL CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
WE'LL EXPLAIN COMING UP.
♪
EXPLAIN COMING UP.
♪♪
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
[ siren ]
Give me your hand!
I can save you...
Lots of money with
Liberty Mutual!
We customize your
car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need!
AND I AM TESTING
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>>  APPEARS FACEBOOK CANNOT GET
ENOUGH OF THESE DOGS WHO CANNOT
WAIT FOR THEIR STASH BUCKS:  ONE
OF THE DOGS JUMPED OUT OF THE
WINDOW ON TO THE DRIVE-THROUGH
LEGEND AND GOT BACK SAFELY INTO
THE CAR AND DID GET THE PUP
CHINOS.
>> THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
REWARD BAD BEHAVIOR.
>> YOU THINK EVERYBODY SHOULD
HAVE BEEN GOTTEN A PUP CHINO
EXCEPT THAT ONE.
>> THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> A THE 5:00, PENTAGON PLOT,
NEW DETAILS ABOUT A MAN THE FEDS
SAY TRIED TO BLOW-UP HIS CAR IN
A PENTAGON PARKING LOT AND IT
HAPPENED JUST DAYS AFTER HE WAS
ARRESTED FOR ASSAULTING A POLICE
OFFICER.
>>> PLUS, CORONAVIRUS CRISIS.
THE CDC IS ISSUING STERN NEW
WARNINGS TO AMERICAN PUTS AS THE
GROWING FEAR SENDS STOCKS
TUMBLING FOR A SECOND DAY IN A
ROW.
>>> AND A 6-YEAR-OLD GIRL
HANDCUFFED AT SCHOOL AND TAKEN
TO JAIL.
LET ME GO.
>> MORE OF THE STUNNING BODY
CAMERA FOOTAGE SPARKING OUTRAGE
ACROSS THE NATION.
YOUR NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> OFF THE TOP