BEEN FALLING SINCE EARLIER
THIS MORNING, WHEN WE HIT
40 DEGREES, NOW 37 IN
WASHINGTON, 34 BALTIMORE, 34
FREDERICK, 30, IN WINCHESTER
AND 26 IN CUMBERLAND, ALREADY,
AND THIS IS DEFINITELY STAY
INSIDE SNOW WEATHER RIGHT?
CURRENT WIND GUSTS RIGHT NOW
STILL OVER 20 MILES AN HOUR,
25-MILE AN HOUR WIND GUSTS
THERE, AT REAGAN NATIONAL, AND
BUSSING OUT THE WINDCHILL MAP.
HAVEN'T SEEN A LOT OF THIS
THIS WINTER BUT IT IS
NECESSARY TODAY.
BECAUSE STEPPING OUTSIDE RIGHT
NOW THIS AFTERNOON IT FEELS
LIKE 27 IN D.C., 24
GAITHERSBURG, FEELS LIKE THE
TEENS IN 81, FEELS LIKE THE
TEENS ALL DAY THERE.
THE FORECAST FOR TONIGHT.
IF YOU ARE HEADED OUT TO EAT
AROUND 6:00, 7:00 P.M.,
TEMPERATURES ALREADY AT
FREEZING, UNDER MOSTLY CLEAR
SKIES.
OUT LATE BY 9:00, 31 DEGREES,
THEN INTO THE 20'S BY
11:00 P.M.
SO IT IS A CHILLY VALENTINE'S
DAY NIGHT.
AND OVERNIGHT, IF WE HIT TWO
IT, WHICH IS OUR FORECASTED
LOW TEMPERATURE, WE HAVEN'T
BEEN THIS COLD SINCE DECEMBER.
SO IT IS TO HAS BEEN A WHILE.
SOME TEENS SHOWING UP NORTH
AND WEST, WEEKEND MAY START
OFF COLD BUT WE ARE GOING TO
ENDS ON MILD NOTE.
50 DEGREES, BEFORE THE WHOLE
WEEKEND'S OVER.
MUCH MORE ON THAT COMPLETE
FORECAST STILL AHEAD.
>> BLACK TO YOU.
>> CAITLIN, THANKS, WE WILL
CHECK BACK N TODAY LEARNING
NEW INFORMATION OF YOUNG CUP
FELL OUR AREA FOUND MURDERED
IN SOUTHWEST VIRGINIA, THE
SUSPECT 18 YEAR OLD HIGH
SCHOOL FOOTBALL PLAYER FROM
ALEXANDRIA, LOTS OF QUESTIONS
REMAIN ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
HERE.
>> FOX5'S STEPHANIE RAMIREZ IN
ALEXANDRIA NOW.
THERE ARE SO MANY QUESTIONS
THIS, STEPHANIE, ONE THE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE
SUSPECT AND THE COUPLE THAT
WAS MURDERED, AND ALSO, WHAT
THEY WERE DOING IN SOUTHWEST
VIRGINIA.
>> WELL, BLAKE, WE HAVE NEW
DETAILS TOED FROM THE
DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, VERGE
DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH SAYING
THAT BOTH VICTIMS WERE SHOT IN
THE HEAD.
A 18 YEAR OLD MUHAMMAD ALI THE
SUSPECT, TC WILLIAMS HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT CHARGED WITH
THEIR MURDER.
HE WAS ARRESTED AT THE HIGH
SCHOOL JUST YESTERDAY, AND THE
SCHOOL OFFICIALS HERE I'M TOLD
THEY SENT ANOTHER NOTE TO
STUDENTS TODAY.
WE'VE NOT SEEN IT YET.
THEY ARE NOT TALKING TO US ON
CAMERA TODAY EITHER SITING
THIS ONGOING INVESTIGATION.
BUT WE CAN TELL YOU WE ARE
LEARNING MORE ABOUT THIS
SUSPECT ON LINE.
WE LEARN'S FOOTBALL PLAYER
HERE, IN FACT, TC TITAN'S
FOOTBALL TWITTER PAGE SHARED
MESSAGE FROM THE ALEXANDRIA
CITY SCHOOLS ATHLETIC AND
STUDENT ACTIVITIES DIRECTOR
TELLING THE ENTIRE STUDENT
BODY NOT TO TALK WITH ANY
MEDIA ON TWITTER PAGE MATCHING
THE 18 YEAR OLD SUSPECT FOUND
POSTS SHOWING SUPPORT FOR
TITAN TEAMMATES, FOUND THE 18
YEAR OLD PROMOTING HIMSELF ON
FEBRUARY 10TH, TWEET READS:
UN SIGNED SENIOR DB LOOKING
FOR HOME TO SHOWCASE MY
MOTIVATION, DEDICATION,
APPRECIATION TO THE GAME.
I LOVE THE HUSTLE.
TWO DAYS BEFORE THAT TWEET IS
WHEN VIRGINIA STATE POLICE SAY
TWO FORMER MONTGOMERY COUNTY
NORTHWEST HIGH SCHOOL
STUDENTS, 19 YEAR OLD AYANA
MARTINS GRIFFIN, 21 YEAR OLD
JOEL, WERE FOUND SLAIN NEAR A
VEHICLE CRASH ON ROUTE 58 IN
HAL FAX COUNTY, VIRGINIA, SOME
225 MILES SOUTH OF ALEX ANDRE
A GUYS, I CAN TELL YOU WILL,
STATE POLICE IN ANNOUNCING
THEIR ARREST, THEY ALSO THANK
THE COMMUNITY, I'M TOLD THERE
WAS PHONECALL THAT HELPED LEAD
POLICE TO ARREST IN THIS CASE.
STILL A LOT OF INFORMATION, WE
MAY NOT LEARN IT UNTIL ALI DUE
IN COURT, SEEING ON STATE
COURT RECORDS THAT MAY NOT
HAPPEN UNTIL TUESDAY, FEBRUARY .
GUYS?
>> SO, STEPHANIE, WE KNOW TWO
SUSPECT WERE DATING EACH
OTHER.
DO WE KNOW WHERE THE SUSPECT
COMES IN?
WHAT THE RELATIONSHIP IS
THERE?
>> THOSE ARE STILL QUESTIONS
WE ARE TRYING TO GET ANSWERED.
I TALKED WITH THE FAMILY
TODAY, AYANA'S FATHER, HE TOLD
ME HE DOES NOT KNOW ALI AT
ALL, TALKED TO JOEL'S FAMILY,
DON'T KNOW WHY THE TWO WOULD
KNOW ALI.
STILL A LOT OF QUESTIONS
TRYING TO GET ANSWERED HERE.
POLICE STILL ASKING FOLKS IF
YOU KNOW ANYTHING OR KNOW ANY
OF THESE THREE TO CONTACT
THEM.
BLAKE?
>> STEPHANIE RAMIREZ LIVE FOR
US, THANKS, STEPHANIE.
>> THE UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND
OFFICIALLY INTRODUCES NEW
PRESIDENT TODAY.
DOCTOR DARRYL PINES WILL
BECOME THE NEW HEAD OF COLLEGE
MARK JULY.
DOCTOR PINES WILL SUCCEED
WALLACE LOW, CRITICIZED FOR
HIS LEADERSHIP OVER THE
HANDLING OF THE DEATH OF
FOOTBALL PLAYER, JORDAN
MCNAIR, THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
PINES DID ADDRESS TODAY.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> YOU KNOW, THE LOSS OF ANY
STUDENT IS AN ABSOLUTE
TRAGEDY.
THE LAST FEW YEARS HAVE BEEN
TOUGH FOR COLLEGE PARK, TOUGH
FOR AWFUL US.
I WAS HERE.
IT IT'S BEEN TOUGH.
I KNOW SOME THINGS HAVE BEEN
IMPLEMENTED.
BUT WHAT I WOULD LIKE DO IS
STUDY, TALK TO ALL OF THE
PEOPLE, I HAVEN'T TALKED TO
ALL OF THE PEOPLE YET.
IT IS SOMETHING I WOULD LIKE
TO ROLL MY SLEEVES UP, SEE
WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO DO
BETTER THINGS THAN WHAT WE
HAVE BEEN DOING BEFORE.
>> DOCTOR PINES HAS BEEN ON
THE COLLEGE PARK CAMPUS FOR 25
YEARS.
MOST RECENTLY, DEAN OF THE
SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING.
>> THE LATEST NOW ON THE
CORONAVIRUS, CHINA REPORTING
ANOTHER SHARP RISE IN THE
NUMBER OF PATIENTS, LET'S ZOOM
IN HERE TO THIS MAP THAT JOHNS
HOPKINS UNIVERSITY IS KEEPING
FOR US.
YOU SEE THE TOTAL ON THE TOP
LEFT OF YOUR SCREEN, THAT'S
THE TOTAL NUMBER OF CASINO
CASES TOPPING 64,000.
THAT WHITE NUMBER ON THE RIGHT
IS THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE WHO
HAVE DIED OVER 1300, A LITTLE
BIT OF GOOD NEWS IF YOU LOOK
AT THE GREEN NUMBER ON THE FAR
RIGHT, THE NUMBER WHO HAVE
RECOVERED FROM KINDS, AND ARE
NO LONGER THOUGHT HAVE IT.
THE VIRUS IN THE U.S. REMAINS
LARGELY CONTAINED.
WE ARE TALKING 15 CASES OF
CORONAVIRUS, ALMOST ALL OF
THEM HAD RECENTLY TRAVELED TO
CHINA IF WE GO, ZOOM IN IN THE
AREA.
PERSON TO NOTE THAT NONE OF
THE CONFIRMED CASES IN THE
UNITED STATES ARE IN OUR AREA,
OR ANYWHERE IN THE
MID-ATLANTIC.
>> HOPE IT STAYS THAT WAY.
IT COULD BE MAJOR STEP TOWARD
ENDING AMERICA'S LONGEST
RUNNING WAR IN AFGHANISTAN,
THE USA REPORTEDLY REACHED
DEAL WITH THE TALIBAN TODAY TO
REDUCE VIOLENCE IN THE
COUNTRY.
TRUES AGREEMENT IS EXPECTED TO
LAST ABOUT A WEEK.
BUT IT IS UNCLEAR WHEN IT WILL
ACTUALLY START.
IF THE TRUES HOLDS, THAT COULD
LEAD TO THE START OF PIES
TALKS WITHIN TEN DAYS, THE
WITHDRAW OF AMERICAN TROOPS.
CURRENTLY US HAS 12,000 TROOPS
IN AFGHANISTAN.
THAT WILL COULD BE REDUCED TO
8600, WITHIN JUST MONTHS.
>>> CLOSING ARGUMENTS WRAPPED
UP TODAY IN THE HARVEY
WEINSTEIN RAPE TRIAL.
PROSECUTORS ARGUED WEINSTEIN
THOUGHT HE WAS SO POWERFUL HE
COULD GET AWAY WITH TREATING A
CENTS S ASPIRING ACTRESSES IN
DEGRADING WAY THAT INCLUDED
SEXUAL ASSAULT.
DEFENSE WEINSTEIN'S LAWYERS,
THEY ARGUED THAT THE
PROSECUTION IS CREATING A
ALTERNATE UNIVERSE IN WHICH
WOMEN ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR
THEIR OWN ACTIONS.
THE JURY IS TAKING THE WEEKEND
OFF.
DELIBERATION ALSO BEGIN NEXT
WEEK.
>> WELL, THOSE DARN PHONES, IT
IS A SERIOUS ISSUE, AND I'M
SURE WE'RE ALL BEEN GUILTY AT
SOME POINT OR ANOTHER BUT LOTS
OF PEOPLE IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY
PEOPLE ARE THINKING ABOUT THE
TICKETS THEY GOT TODAY.
CRACKDOWN BIG ONE ON DRIVERS
USING THEIR PHONES, IN THEIR
CAR, AND IT HAPPENED NEAR THE
INTERSECTION OF 270 AND COPPER
DRIVE.
STATE AND LOCAL POLICE ARE
WORRIED ABOUT THE NUMBER OF
DEADLY RECOMMENDATION ON THE
ROAD WHICH HAVE BEEN AVERAGING
ABOUT 200 A YEAR IN MARYLAND.
THE COUNTY SAYS HALF OF THE
SERIOUS CRASHES INVOLVE SOME
KIND OF DISTRACTED DRIVING.
>> A SUBSTITUTE TEACHER IS OUT
AFTER JOB AFTER IN IS HEAD
SCRATCHER GIVING LAP DANCES TO
FOURTH GRADERS.
NOT SURE HOW THEY JUSTIFIED
THIS, BUT STUDENTS AT HAIL
THORPE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
BALTIMORE COUNTY COMPLAINS TO
PARENTS AND SCHOOL LEADERS
EARLIER THIS WEEK ABOUT
INAPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR BY THE
WOMAN IN CLASS, ONE PARENT
SAYS SOME OF THE TEN YEAR OLD
WERE EVEN KISSED ON THE FACE
BY THE TEACHER.
>> YA, I'M THINKING OH, MY
GOD, HOW LONG HAS THIS LADY
BEEN A SUBSTITUTE AT THE
SCHOOL, DID SHE EVER
SUBSTITUTE MY KID, I DON'T
EVEN KNOW THE FIRST NAME AT
THIS POINT.
>> I'M NOT EVEN SURE WHAT
LESSON WOULD YOU WORK A LAP
DANCE INTO.
BUT POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING
THE INCIDENT.
SO FAR NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED AGAINST THE WOMAN.
SHE HAS BEEN REMOVED, THOUGH,
FROM THE POOL OF SUBSTITUTE
TEACHERS.
>> LET'S HOPE IT WAS A DANCE
CLASS?
NOW TO STOP STORIES CAUGHT ON
CAMERA MOMENTS, MAN IN
CALIFORNIA SAY TESTING HITS
LUCK AFTER HE WAS CAUGHT ON
CAMERA STEALING LOTTO TICKETS.
SECURITY CAMERA FOOTAGE SHOWS
THIS IS IN A LIQUOR STORE,
SHOWS THE MOMENT THE MAN RAN
OFF WITH MORE THAN $1,000
WORTH OF SCRATCH-OFFICE.
NOW, THE THIEVES ACTUALLY
DISTRACTED THE CASHIER BY
POINTING TO AN ITEM BEHIND THE
COUNTER, YOU KNOW, I GOT YOU
MOMENT.
YA, THEN HE GRABS THE LOTTERY
TICKETS, RUNS OFF.
POLICE STILL HAVEN'T TRACKED
HIM DOWN.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S DUMB ABOUT
THAT, THOUGH, THEY HAVE TO BE
ABLE TO TRACE THE SERIAL
NUMBERS TO SEE WHICH WERE THE
LAST ONES LEGITIMATELY SOLD AT
THE LOCATION.
>> DISCREDIT THEM ALL.
>> ALL RIGHT, BAGHDAD, IRAQ,
SAW ITS FIRST SNOWFALL IN OVER
A DECADE THIS WEEK.
LOOK AT THAT.
THIS WEATHER MAN WAS OUT
REPORT BEING THE STORM, HE
FOUND HIMSELF IN THE MIDDLE OF
SNOWBALL FIGHT.
GROUP OF GOOD NATURE
BYSTANDERS BEGAN PELTING HIM
WITH SNOWBALLS.
>> WHY DOES HE LOOK LIKE
CHARLIE CHAPLAIN?
ALL RIGHT, HERE IS PROOF THAT
YOUR DOG WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
EVEN IF YOU LEAVE THE PLANET
FOR NEARLY A YEAR.
YES, THE PLANET, ASTRONAUT
CHRISTINA COOK POSTED THIS
VIDEO TO TWITTER AFTER
SPENDING 328 DAYS IN SPACE.
YOU CAN SEE HER DOG, BESIDE
HIMSELF, WHEN RETURNS HOME IT
IS HARD TO TELL WHO IS MORE
EXCITED FOR THE REUNION, COOK
BROKE THE RECORDS FOR THE
LONGEST SINGLE SPACE FLIGHT BY
A WOMAN.
ALWAYS SO FUN TO SEE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOTS OF PEOPLE
PLAY THE LOTTERY.
I LOVE SCRATCH OFFICE.
I NEVER WON MORE THAN $20.
JOSEPH HEAT ON, THOUGH, FROM
VIRGINIA THEIR TELL YOU DREAMS
DO COME TRUE.
HE SPENT $30 ON SCRATCH-OFF
TICKET, AT A GAS STATION IN
MEN AND -- MANASSAS, TO HIS
SURPRISE THE TICKET SAID HE
WON $10 MILLION.
HE COLLECTED THAT PRIZE TODAY,
RECOUNTED WHAT HAPPENED WHEN
HE TURNED IT OVER TO THE STORE
CLERK AFTER HE WON.
>> AND I WENT OVER AND
SCRATCHED IT OFF AND I WALKED
BACK UP AND I STARTED SMILING
AT HIM.
AND HE SAID WINNER?
>> AND I SAID -- I SAID YES.
HE SAID A NUMBER, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT WAS, MAYBE 5,000 OR
10,000, OR SOMETHING, I SAID
NO, HIGHER.
AND HE KEPT GOING UP AND I
KEPT SAYING HIGHER.
AND FINLEY I JUST SHOWED HIM
THE TICKET.
AND WE BOTH SAW IT WAS
$10 MILLION.
>> WOW.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW SCRATCH
OFF'S WENT THAT HIGH.
INCREDIBLE.
HEAT ON DOES NOT HAVE ANY BIG
PLANS ON WHAT TO DO WITH THE
WINGS YET.
HE WANTS TO WORK FOR THREE TO
FIVE MORE YEARS BEFORE
RETIRING, HE CLEARLY HAS THE
MONEY TO DO IT NOW SO WE'LL
SEE IF THOSE PLANS CHANGE.
>> WHAT A SWEET VALENTINE'S
HE'LL V ALWAYS DREAM ABOUT
THIS, YOU KNOW, BUT IT NEVER
ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
>> I'M HAPPY IF I GET YOU GET
A FREE TICKET, OH, YES.
>> $10, $50, YA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
STILL TO COME:  VALENTINE DAY
LESSON IN THE CLASSROOM.
HOW LOCAL TEACHER IS TURNING A
CRUSHING CHILDHOOD MEMORY, SHE
WAS HOW MANY ILL AGENT
DOLLARS.
RIDICULED IN CLASS ON
VALENTINE DAY.
>> TURNING IT AROUND.
>> BY WHO SHE THOUGHT WAS THE
LOVE OF HER LIFE IN SCHOOL,
AND HE SENT HER A MEAN CARD
BACK.
SHE IS NOW TURNING IT AROUND,
AND IS TURNING IT INTO A WAY
TO SPREAD A MESSAGE OF LOVE
FOR HER STUDENTS?
GOOD FOR HER.
PLUS, SOLDIER'S SURPRISE.
YES, WE LOVE THESE.
IT IS A FITTING STORY FOR THIS
DAY ABOUT LOVE.
WE WILL SHOW YOU THE
HEARTWARMING MONTHS, AND
MARYLAND SOLDIER SURPRISE HIS
YOUNGER SIBLINGS AT SCHOOL.
>> AND ON THIS FRIDAY, LET'S
TAKE LIVE LOOK AT TRAFFIC
AROUND THE DMV AS RUSH HOUR
RAMPS UP.
NOT TOO BAD.
THE SUN IS OUT.
THE ROADS ARE DRY.
STAY SAFE.
SAFE.
>> THROUGHOUT THE SHOW WE WILL
BE SHARING YOUR VALENTINE DAY
PICTURES, HERE IS ONE, SENDING
THEM TO US FROM OUR VIEWERS,
WITH THE HASHTAG FOX5
VALENTINE.
WE HOPE YOU'RE HAVING A NICE
HOLIDAY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
BACK.
OK, network inspection.
OK.
Connected to WiFi,
protected from threats.
Thermostat -
connected, protected.
Speaker, space vacuum...
Connected, protected. Shh.
Eh, this is not
connected or protected.
But, that's a family heirloom.
And, it's a family security
breach. It's gotta go.
With Xfinity xFi, if it's
connected, it's protected.
Pull the truck around.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Get started with
Xfinity Internet for
$39.99 a month
for 12 months.
Plus, ask about enhanced
network security
for all your
connected devices.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
MIKE: Anyone hear the slogan,
'Mike Will Get It Done?'
OK, let me tell
you what the 'it' is.
As Mayor,
I expanded healthcare coverage.
As President,
I'll build on Obamacare
because healthcare is a right.
I created nearly
500,000 jobs in New York City.
As President,
I'll build an economy
that delivers good jobs
with higher wages.
I'll take on the gun lobby
and save lives.
And I will stop Trump's assault
on women's reproductive rights.
I've got a record
of doing things.
I've got the resources
to take on this fight.
As mayor,
I held myself
accountable for results.
As President,
I'll offer common sense plans
and I will get it done.
So let's stay on the offensive,
and let's win.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> A SOLDIER SURPRISED HIS
YOUNGER SIBLINGS, ONE IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, THE OTHER
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL.
>> THE SOLDIER RETURNING HOME
FROM DEPLOYMENT ON THE USS
ABRAHAM LINCOLN, FOX5 TISHA
LEWIS IN WALDORF WITH THIS
HEARTWARM BEING STORY, TISHA?
>> THE MESSAGE HERE IS FAMILY,
FRIENDS AND LOVE.
BASS IS BACK HOME AFTER A 11
MONTH DEPLOYMENT, AND HIS
YOUNGER SIBLINGS HAD NO IDEA,
UNTIL NOW.
>> YOU GOING TO SIT THERE?
>> OH.
>> VALENTINE DAY ONE FOR THE
BOOKS.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> DID I GET YOU?
SOLDIER BASS SURPRISING HIS
YOUNGER SISTER, 12 YEAR OLD
SASHA, AND BROTHER, 11 YEAR
OLD RASAN AFTER NEARLY A YEAR
AWAY.
>> MISSING ALMOST EVERY TYPE
OF HOLIDAY THERE IS, JUST TO
SEE HER REACTION, IT IS
LIKE -- IT IS THE BEST FEELING
I CAN IMAGINE RIGHT NOW.
>> BASS IN THE MIDDLE EASON
WHAT WE'RE TOLD WAS THE
LONGEST DEPLOYED SHIP.
NOW HE'S HOME.
HERE AT DAVIS, EMBRACING THE
YOUNG HEARTS, WHO KEEP A
MOTIVATED.
>> BOTH YOUNGER SIBLINGS WERE
IN CLASS DURING THE SURPRISE
VISIT.
BOTH, NEVER SAW IT COMING.
>> I WAS JUST LIKE SURPRISED,
WOE ACTUALLY COME MARRY SAINTS
ERS SAID IT TOOK HER TWO
MONTHS TO PULL IT ALL OFF AND
SHE DID WITHOUT A HITCH.
AFTER PLANNING ALMOST THREE
MONTHS FOR THIS, AND QUIETLY
PLOTTING, NOT TELLING MY
HUSBAND, NOT TELLING MY KIDS,
NONE OF MY FRIENDS EVEN KNOW
YET.
>> THEY WILL NOW, BUT I
JUST -- IT IS AN AMAZING
FEELING.
>> FROM HERE BASS SAID I'LL
TAKE THE FAMILY TO DAVE AND
BUSTER'S WHERE SOME GOOD OLD
FUN AND THEN HE DEPLOYS AGAIN
NEXT MONTH.
BACK TO YOU.
>> WEIGH SALUTE THEM, ALWAYS
WARMS OUR HEART, THANK YOU.
WELL, MORE LOVE IN THE AIR,
AND OVER AGAIN AT DC SUPERIOR
COURT, 14 COUPLES SAID THEIR
VOWS TODAY, FULL SLATE ON THIS
VALENTINE DAY, THESE COUPLE
HADS TO SIGN UP ACTUALLY
MONTHS IN ADVANCE TO HAVE
THEIR DATE AT THE WEDDING
CHAPEL ON THIS SPECIAL DAY,
ONE COUPLE WANTED TO GET THEIR
MARRIAGE LICENSE TODAY TO
CELEBRATE 30 YEARS TOGETHER.
>> THE THE MAN OF MY DREAMS.
>> IT FEELS GREAT.
IT IS BETTER THAN WINNING
2 BILLION-DOLLAR.
>> MONEY, BETTER THAN MONDAY.
>> I WAIT.
SHE SAID HOLD ON A SECOND.
>> OKAY, EXCUSE ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW, BLAKE,
$2 MILLION?
>> EVERYONE HAS A PRICY GUESS
ACCORDING TO THAT WOMAN.
IN THE BUILDING AND VOLUNTEERS
DO THIS ON VALENTINE DAY.
>> AND LET'S TAKE ANOTHER LOOK
AT YOUR PHOTOS THIS ONE COMING
IN.
YOU CAN SHARE THEM WITH US, IT
IS IMPORTANT TO USE THE
HASHTAG, IF YOU WANT TO SEE
THEM ON OUR AIR, BECAUSE
THAT'S HOW WE WILL FINDS THEM.
SO USE THE HASHTAG FOX5
VALENTINE AND KEEP YOUR PHOTOS
COMING, WE WOULD LOVE IT SEE
IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, CAITLIN ROTH,
LOVE IS IN THE AIR.
LETS GUESS TO OUR ENGAGED
FORECASTER.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
OUR ENGAGED ANKLE WORE ME,
TOO, OF TWO US PLANNING.
>> PLANNING A WEDDING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
AID THOUGHT, THOUGH, I WAS
LIKE YOU KNOW THE COURTHOUSE,
SAVE US A LOT OF TIME AND
MONEY.
>> CAITLIN?
>> IT IS KIND OF LIKE, YOU
KNOW WHAT, THEY'RE ONTO
SOMETHING.
>> DOT WEDDING THERE, IF YOU
WANT TO THROW A BIG PARTY
AFTERWARD GLUCK TAKE A BIG
HONEYMOON, CAITLIN, WHAT WERE
WE ANYTHING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, I TOLD
MYSELF, DON'T DO IT, AND I DID
IT ANYWAY.
OH, WELL, NEXT TIME.
JUST KIDDING.
YES, WE DO LOVE EVERYONE WHO
DID GO TO THE COURTHOUSE
TODAY, THAT WAS WONDER FOUL
SEE, LOVER IS IN THE AIR.
ALSO COLD AIR IS IN THE AIR,
AS WE SEE OUR CAMERA SHAKING
BEHIND US HERE.
THE AFTERNOON COMMUTE IS
STARTING, AND SEEING SUNSHINE,
SO IT IS BEAUTIFUL LOOKING BUT
IT IS COLD, IT IS BLUSTERY.
TONIGHT TEMPERATURES WILL FALL
TO PROBABLY THE LOWEST NUMBERS
WE'VE SEEN IN A WHILE.
SEEING 22 FOR DC.
THAT WOULD TAKE YOU BACK TO
DECEMBER.
WE HAD SOME COLD MORNINGS IN
JANUARY.
BUT NOTHING IN FEBRUARY.
SO, IT HAS BEEN AT LEAST
COUPLE OF WEEKS SINCE WE'VE
HAD SUCH COLD NIGHT WHICH WE
WILL HAVE AHEAD INTO SATURDAY.
IT WILL BE SUNNY CHILLY ONE
START OFF THE WEEKENDS.
TEMPERATURES REBOUNDS BY THE
SECOND HALF OF THE WEEKENDS SO
SUNDAY ALREADY TAPPING BACK
INTO SOME THAT FAR MORE MILDER
AIR.
THIRTY-SEVEN IN WASHINGTON
OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW.
LOOK, ONLY 25 IN BOSTON, 13 IN
BUFFALO, 34 IN CINCINNATI, 34
NASHVILLE.
COLD VALENTINE DAY FOR THE
EASTERN HALF OF THE COUNTRY,
ACTUALLY, MAJORITY OF THE
COUNTRY.
LOOK AT THE NUMBERS 15 IN
CHICAGO, 14 MINNEAPOLIS, 24
SAINT LEWIS, BACK TO THE
ROCKIES, 39 DENVER.
YES, PRETTY CHILLY.
VERY FIB-LIKE.
ALSO QUIET, HIGH PRESSURE
OVERHEAD A LOFT SUNSHINE
COAST-TO-COAST.
WE WILL HAVE MORE THAT FAR
SUNSHINE FOR TOMORROW HIGH
PRESSURE SLIGHTLY OFF SHORE
STILL GOING TO GET THE CHILLY
WINDS COMING THROUGH, WINDS
WILL DIMINISH, WON'T BE NEARLY
AS GUSTY BUT STILL GOING TO BE
STRAIGHT UP COLD DAY.
>> FORTY'S, TO MAYBE 50'S AREA
WIDE, BUT STILL DRY WEEKEND
OVERALL PRETTY NICE WEEKEND.
THERE IS 38 FOR THE HIGH
TEMPERATURE SATURDAY.
FEW AFTERNOON CLOUDS.
SUNDAY MORE CLOUDS THAN SUN.
BUT, IF YOU'RE NOT WANTING TO
BE OUTSIDE SUNDAY YOUR DAY FOR
IT, TEMPERATURE TRENDS TO HEAD
UPWARD.
FIFTY-ONE SUNDAY, LOOK AT
THIS, 53 MONDAY PRESIDENT'S
DAY, NICE THREE DAY WEAKEN FOR
YOU THERE.
SIXTY, BY TUESDAY.
SO, WE ARE RIGHT BACK TO WHERE
FEBRUARY WANTS TO BE, MORE
SPRING, THAN WINTER.
WE WILL LET YOU KNOW HOW LONG
THAT LAGS CENTS, THOUGH, COULD
BE MORE COLD AIR IN THE SEVEN
DAY FORECAST STILL AHEAD.
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST STAY
INCH DOES FOR THE COLD, RIGHT?
>> CAITLIN, I DIDN'T SHOW YOU.
>> OH, LOOK AT YOU.
>> REAL COLD THERE.
>> I LOVE IT.
I LOVE IT.
ALL RIGHT, STILL TO COME, LOVE
IS IN THE AIR.
EXCEPT FOR MAYBE WEST
VIRGINIA.
WE'RE REVEALING THE MOST
GOOGLE QUESTIONS ABOUT LOVE
AND BREAKING IT DOWN STATE BY
STATE.
>> AND LET'S TAKE LIVE LOOK
ALONG THE BELT WAY AT THE
AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE THIS
AFTERNOON.
YOU KNOW WHAT, IT IS CROWDED
BUT IT IS MOVING.
THAT'S THE MOST YOU CAN HELP
FOR ON THAT STRETCH OF
ROADWAY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
Jessica?
She's been in there for days.
Ever since Cody broke
up with her?
Ladies. Pause her
WiFi. Smoke her out.
We can do that?
With the Xfinity xFi app.
Don't overthink it.
Guys, I think the WiFi's out.
Hi!
Only Xfinity xFi lets you
take control of your WiFi.
I'm not much of a hugger.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get this great offer
from Xfinity.
You'll get double the speed
and save over $250
compared to Fios
in your first two years.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
(upbeat whistling music)
(couple sighs)
- Ah!
- All buckled up,
let's go!
- Tuition Monster,
how are you here already?
She's only two days old!
- And that means
there's only
6,720 days until she's
off to college.
But it is a bit snug
back here,
so next time I'll be
calling shotgun.
(baby giggles)
Vroom vroom!
- [Narrator] Tame the
Tuition Monster
with a Virginia529
savings account.
Learn how at
virginia529.com
OK, so maybe we're
new to home improvement,
with a Virginia529
but we're determined.
We got an insider tip on the
ultimate flooring destination.
Whoa. Floor and
Decor is amazing.
Look at us.
We're shopping alongside
real-life designers
and contractors.
I love this tile.
And this one.
And, these prices!
Look at this... durable
and water-resistant.
We should do
the kitchen next!
Oh, yeah, we
found where the pros go.
Now, we're unstoppable.
Explore Floor and Decor
in person or online
at flooranddecor.com
>> A LOOK AT WHAT'S TRENDING
NOW, CAT LYNN, FIRST UP IN
HONOR OF VALENTINE DAY
COMPLETE ADD LIST OF EACH
STATE'S MOST GOOGLE
RELATIONSHIP.
>> OH, THIS IS INTERESTING.
>> YES.
>> MARYLAND, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON IN MARYLAND.
MOST GOOGLE QUESTION, AM I IN
LOVE?
>> IF YOU HAVE TO GOOGLE, THE
ANSWER IS NO.
>> GOOGLE CAN'T TELL YOU
EVERYTHING, LITERALLY, I KNOW
IT TELLS AWE LOT.
>> I ACTUALLY GOOGLED THIS
BEFORE THE SHOW TODAY.
>> THERE ARE SO MANY QUESTIONS
YOU KNOW, LIKE HOW CLOSE YOU
FEEL TO THAT PERSON, ARE YOU
THINKING ABOUT YOUR EX, YOU
KNOW?
QUIZ, TAKE A QUIZ.
>> YOU ARE ENGAGED IN A.
>> IT WOULD BE VERY BAD SIGN
BEFORE THE MARRIAGE.
>> NO, FOR THE PURPOSE OF THE
SHOW.
>> IN THE DISTRICT EVERY
VIRGINIA THEIR QUESTION WAS
HOW TO GET A DATE.
WEST VIRGINIA THE TOP QUESTION
HOW TO BREAK UP.
>> BREAKING UP CAN BE
AUTHORITIES DO.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES DO YOU NEED
SOME ASSISTANCE, I LIKE
PENNSYLVANIA, MY HOME STATE.
WHEN TO TEXT BACK.
>> WHAT'S THE ETIQUETTE?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT LOVE AND
MARRIAGE, JUST TEXTING.
>> MOVING ON UP, LOOKS LIKE
NEWLYWEDS WANT TO KEEP THE
PARTY GOING ALL NIGHT LONG,
MORE AND MORE COUPLES KEEP
THIS IN MIND BOTH PLANNING
WEDDINGS, MORE AND MORE
COUPLES ARE HOSTING WEDDING
AFTER PARTIES.
SO, VERSE FIRST THE WELD, THEN
THE RECEPTION, THEN AFTER
PARTY FOR THOSE STILL GOING.
ON AVERAGE THE AFTER PARTY
TAKES PLACE AROUND TWO HOURS
AFTER THE RECEPTION ENDS.
ABOUT 50 GUESSES, MORE CASUAL
SETTING AFTER PARTY POPULAR.
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
THIS?
>> WELL, NO, I HAVEN'T GOTTEN
THAT FAR.
STILL TRYING TO WRAP MY MINDS
AROUND THE WHOLE CEREMONY
THING, RIGHT?
BUT I HAVE BEEN AT WEDDINGS
WHERE THIS HAPPENS, BECAUSE A
LOT OF THESE VENUES OR THESE
SPACE THAT IS RENT SHUTDOWN AT
11:00 THEN WELL NO ONE WANTS
TO STOP THE PARTY AT
11:00 P.M.
SO BOTH MIDDLE EASTERN,  IT
WILL BE PRETTY BIG WEDDING BUT
WE LIKE TO STAY UP AND JUST
LIKE YOU SAID, I HAD TO FIND A
VENUE THAT GOES UNTIL
2:00 A.M.
SO OKAY.
>> SO STAYING AT THE VENUE?
>> WE WILL BE STAYING AT THE
VENUE UNTIL 2:00 A.M.
THEN IF PEOPLE WANT TO PARTY
BEYOND THAT THERE IS A BAR
WITHIN THE HOTEL.
>> I'M GOING WEDDING IN
BALTIMORE IN THE FALL.
THEY HAVE AFTER PARTY ALREADY.
>> ALREADY SCHEDULED.
>> THE HOTEL BAR OF THE HOTEL.
>> YES?
>> BUT THEY HAVE AN AREA
CORDED OFF THAT EVERYONE WHO
WANTS TO STAY UP.
>> THAT'S NICE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, PROBABLY
ANOTHER MONEY GRAB IN SOME
WASTE BUT ALSO A MORE CASUAL
WAY TO DO IT.
>> AND YOU DON'T -- HERE IS
THE KEY.
I DON'T THINK THE BRIDE AND
GROOM HAVE TO PAY FOR THAT.
I DON'T THINK HAS TO BE OPEN
BAR AT THAT POINT.
>> THIS IS WHAT I WANT TO
HEAR.
>> JUST GO CASUAL.
>> I WOULD EXPECT TO PAY FOR
MY OWN DRINKS.
>> GOOD.
>> YO, ALL GO TO THE AFTER
PATH, YA.
>> STILL TO COME HERE AT
4:00 EVERY VALENTINE DAY LOCAL
TEACHER MAKES IT HER MISSION
TO SPREAD LOVER AND KINDNESS
IN HER CLASSROOM.
HEAR WHAT INSPIRED HER
MESSAGE.
IT WAS ACTUALLY AN
EMBARRASSING MOMENT FOR HER IN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL ON VALENTINE
DAY, AND IT INSPIRED HER TO
MAKE IT A MORE POSITIVE
EXPERIENCE.
>> SHE HELD ON TO THAT FOR
QUITE SOME TIME.
I HAVE ONE TO SHARE, TOO.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, MAKES US
STRONGER, RIGHT?
>> WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ACCUSED OF ROBBING TWO
BANKS, JUST DAYS APART,
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY HAVE
EVIDENCE LINKING ANGELA FITSU
HILL TO BANK ROBBERIES ON
FEBRUARY 8TH AND 1 YESTERDAY.
NO ONE WAS HURT DURING THE
HOLDS-UPS.
>> BIG NEWS REDSKINS PARK IT,
LOOKS LIKE JOSH NORMAN WILL
NOT BE PART OF RON RIVIERA'S
NEW REGIME IN WASHINGTON
REDSKINS RELEASING THE VETERAN
QUARTERBACK, SAVING THEM
$12.5 MILLION IN CAP SPACE.
THE TEAM ALSO RELEASED THREE
OTHER PLAYERS INCLUDING
RECEIVER PAUL RICHARD SON, WHO
WILL SAVE THEM $6 MILLION IN
DEBT CAP SPACE, THE REDSKINS
SIGNED HIM TWO YEARS AGO BUT
ENDED BOTH SEASONS ON INJURED
RESERVE.
>> UPDATE ON THE DOUGLAS
FREDERICK BRIDGE ABOUT HALFWAY
DONE NOW, WILL SOON REPLACE
THE SOUTH CAPITOL BRIDGE IN
SOUTHEAST NEAR NAVY YARD.
THE NEW BRIDGE, WILL MAKE IT
EASIER FOR PEDESTRIAN,
CYCLISTS AND DRIVERS TO MAKE
IT ACROSS THE RIVER SAFELY.
IT IS THE LARGEST ROAD
IMPROVEMENT IN D.C. HISTORY
AND CREATED MORE THAN 200
JOBS.
>> WELL, DO YOU REMEMBER AS A
KID, EX CHARGING VALENTINE'S
IN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN SUPER
CUTE.
YOU GOT THE LITTLE CANDIES,
THEY HAD THE CUTE SAYINGS,
WITH CARTOON CHARACTERS, AND
SUPERHEROS, BUT A LOCAL HIGH
SCHOOL TEACHER WAS CRUSHED BY
HER FIFTH GRADE CRUSH WHETHER
HE GAVE HER VALENTINE CALLING
HER,  THIS IS SO MEAN, THE
UGLIEST GIRL IN THE CLASS.
>> WHAT?
>> YES, RIGHT?
WHO DOES THIS?
SHE HAS TURNED THAT NEGATIVE
ENERGY INTO VERY POSITIVE
ENERGY OVER THE LAST 20 YEARS,
PHOTO JOURNALIST, NELSON
JONES.
>> DO ANY OF YOU HAVE YOURS TO
HAND OUT, BRYCE, DO YOU?
OKAY.
KEVIN, DO YOU HAVE YOURS?
>> I THINK PROBABLY ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT HAS BEEN MOST
STRIKE TO GO ME ABOUT THIS
EXPERIENCE IS THAT THE
STUDENTS ACTUALLY WELCOME THE
OPPORTUNITY TO BE KIND TO ONE
ANOTHER.
IT IS LIKE I'M GIVING THEM PER
NOTION DO SOMETHING THAT, YOU
KNOW, I THINK ALL OF US HAVE
AN INCH STING TO DO IS TO BE
GOOD TO OTHER PEOPLE.
VERY NICE, GLAD YOU'RE IN MY
CLASS THIS YEAR.
>> I THINK YOU'RE VERY UNIQUE,
YOU'RE COOL, YOU'RE SO SWEET
AND CARING AND FUN, THANK YOU,
ELLIE.
>> INSTEAD OF US KIN OF JUST
WRITING NOTES TO PEOPLE THAT
WE ONLY KNOW, WE IT FOR
EVERYONE, AND I FELT LIKE THAT
WAS REALLY SPECIAL.
AND PLENTY KIND THING FOR HER
TO DO, NOT A LOT OF TEACHERS
DO THAT.
>> NONE OF US KNOW WHAT IS
GOING ON IN ANOTHER PERSON'S
MIND WE MAY THINK WE KNOW
SOMEONE BUT THEY MAY BE CARING
AROUND BURDENS, AND THIS IS A
CHANCE TO LIFT PEOPLE UP AND
TO SAY SOMETHING KIND TO THEM.
>> YOU'RE A PRETTY MELLOW AND
FRIENDLY PERSON.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE THAT
DOESN'T LIKE YOU.
SO THAT SHOWS YOU YOU'RE A
GOOD PERSON.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
>> I PER -- RECEIVED EMAILS
FROM KIDS THIS MORNING JUST
THANKING ME FOR DOING IT,
BECAUSE IT MADE THEM FEEL
BETTER.
>> PRETTY LAID BACK PERSON,
YOU LET ME REST MY FEET ON
YOUR CHAIR, MOST PEOPLE GET
ANOINTS BY THAT, SO IT IS
COOL.
>> RAISE YOUR SELF-ESTEEM,
MAKES YOU FEEL GOOD YOURSELF.
SOMETHING THAT I DEFINITELY
NEEDED.
>> I THINK DIRECTING THEM TO
THINK ABOUT HOW TO BE
THOUGHTFUL TO PEOPLE RATHER
THAN JUST -- IT IS IMPORTANT.
>> I LOVE THAT SO MUCH.
RIGHT?
>> SO GREAT.
GIVING PEOPLE PERMISSION.
>> YES.
>> TO SAY SOMETHING KIND TO
ONE ANOTHER.
>> AND LIKE TEACHING THEM
KINDNESS AND HOW WORDS MATTER,
RIGHT?
>> THAT'S GREAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, STILL TO COME:
IT IS NOT TOO LATE TO BUY SOME
FLOWERS FOR VALENTINE DAY.
BEFORE DO YOU, THOUGH, LISTEN
UP.
YOU WOULD THINK RED ROSE, BUT
THAT'S WHAT WE SHOULD ALL BE
BUYING, RIGHT?
LOCAL FLOUR ILLS, THOUGH, SAYS
THAT MAY NOT BE THE FLOWERS
WOMEN REALLY WANT.
>> WHAT DO WE REALLY WANT?
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THIS.
>> WHAT DO WOMEN WANT?
A WHOLE MOVE BYE THAT.
>> THAT'S A LOT.
>> LET'S FOCUS ON FLOWERS, AND
WE'LL HAVE THE ANSWER AFTER
THE BREAK.
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
>> ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN,
LISTEN UP, TALKING FLOWERS
THIS VALENTINE DAY, FIRST OFF
IT IS NOT TOO LATE TO FIX THEM
UP.
BUT BEFORE YOU DO YOU MAY BE
SURPRISED BY WHAT WOMEN REALLY
WANT WATCH DO WE REALLY WANT,
RIGHT?
COMPLICATED QUESTION?
>> THAT'S A RIDDLE.
>> BUT FOX5'S WISDOM MARTIN
STOPPED BY HELEN OLIVIA
FLOWERS TO ASK ALL OF THE
IMPORTANT QUESTIONS.
>> SO WHAT'S THE MOST POPULAR
FLOWER?
IF I'M OUT ME BEING LAST
MINUTE MANNY THINK ROASTS,
JUST GO GET SOME ROSES IS THAT
CORRECT THE MOST POPULAR
FLOWER?
>> MEN ALWAYS THINK RED ROSES,
ALL OF THE DESIGNERS ACTUALLY
DON'T LIKE RED ROSE.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> WE SURVEYED OUR INSTAGRAM
FOLLOWERS WOULD YOU PREFER RED
ROSES ON VALENTINE DAY OR
BEAUTIFUL MIXED BOUQUET?
94% OF PEOPLE SURVEYED LIKE
THE MIXED BOUQUET.
SO, FOREMEN, DEFINITELY SWITCH
IT UP THIS YEAR YOU.
>> GOT THAT, MEN, MAKE SURE TO
SWITCH IT UP.
I WAS GOING TO THINK SWITCHING
IT UP, BUT NOW THAT YOU
CONFIRM MY THOUGHTS I THINK
WE'RE ALL GOOD.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK THERE IS
NOTHING WRONG WITH RED ROSES.
>> IT IS REALLY THE THOUGHT,
RIGHT?
BUT I GUESS IF WOMEN HAVE A
CHOICE?
>> EXACTLY, OR IF YOU KNOW
THEY LIKE PINK THOUSANDS, BE
THOUGHTFUL, BE LISTENING,
RIGHT?
THERE GO, IF YOU ALREADY
BOUGHT RED ROSES MAYBE FILE
THIS INFORMATION AWAY FOR NEXT
YEAR OR ASK YOUR SIGNIFICANT
OTHER.
>> NO ONE WILL BE UPSET.
>> NO, NO, SUCH A SWEET
GESTURE.
>> WHY PEOPLE NOW, YOU GOT
EMMA WATSON, ALL OF THESE
STARS, I'M DATING MYSELF, AH,
LIKE THE COOL THING.
>> GALENTIE DAY OH, ONLY THE
BEST DAY OF THE YEAR.
>> ANGIE, MAY BE OFFER TODAY
BUT NEVER FAR AWAY.
NEW EPISODE OF HER POD CAST
THE OH, MY GOFF SHOW IS OUT.
IF YOU ARE THINKING OF GIVING
UP ON LOVE, DATING COACH JEST
MCCANN SAYS TACK GOOD LOOK AT
YOURSELF FIRST.
THE AUTHOR OF CURSED RECENTLY
SAT DOWN WITH ANGIE TO TALK
ABOUT HIDDEN HABITS, THE
SABATAGE RELATIONSHIPS.
>> I KEPT HEARING I'M CURSED,
LIKE I KEEP HAVING THIS
PATTERN, AND THE PATTERNS IS
VARIED.
IT WAS A PATTERN MAYBE OF, YOU
KNOW, DATING SOMEONE FOR THREE
MONTHS, THEN THAT PERSON
GHOSTING, OR THE PATTERN WAS
DATING FOR A YEAR, AND THEN
THE PERSON BREAKING UP, AND
MOVING ON, AND MARRYING THE
NEXT PERSON THAT THEY DATED.
FINALLY I THOUGHT I NEED TO
FIGURE OUT WHY DO SOME PEOPLE
HAVE THESE PATTERNS?
THERE IS A COMMON THREAD.
DEEPER THAN JUST THE GO TO
PHRASE, LIKE SHE JUST CHOOSES
THE WRONG GUY, OR HE JUST
CHOOSES THE WRONG GIRL.
>> THERE IS COME UPON END OF
CHOOSING THE WRONG PERSON BUT
THE QUESTION REALLY IS WHY?
THERE ARE FIVE MAIN SABATAGE
HABITS.
AND THEY'RE HABITS OF THE
MINDS.
AND I KNOW WE ALL KNOW THAT
JUDGING IS NOT HABIT TO HAVE,
AND IN THIS CULTURE THE
DIGITAL CULTURE REALLY LENDS
ITSELF TO JUDGING.
BE PRESENT AND AWARE IS THE
NUMBER ONE CURE.
THERE ARE FIVE CURES.
BUT THE FIRST THING DO YOU
HAVE DO IS LEARN TO BE
MINDFUL, LEARN TO BE PRESENT.
>> I CAN LISTEN TO THIS ALL
DAY.
OKAY, WE GOT TO JUDGING WATCH
ARE THE OTHER FOUR HABITS THAT
WE'RE ALL DOING WRONG?
>> YES, JESS SAYS MEDITATION
IS ONE WAY TO APPROACH HOW YOU
JUDGE DATING, WATCH THE FULL
INTERVIEW ON THE OH, MY GOFF
SHOW ON YOUTUBE OR DOWNLOAD IT
WHERE EVER YOU GET YOUR POD
CASTS.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK SOCIAL
MEDIA ALSO HASN'T HELPED IN A
WAY, SO MANY OPTIONS, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHEN YOU FIND THAT PERSON, I
THINK THE BEST THING YOU CAN
DO IS DO A SOCIAL MEDIA DETOX.
>> I AGREE, JUST FOCUS IN, YA.
>> MY SISTER AND HER HUSBAND,
IT IS ALL LOCKDOWN, ALL
PRIVATE.
NOT POSTING FOR OTHER PEOPLE
WHO THEY DON'T KNOW.
>> NICE.
>> WHICH ONLY CREATES
PROBLEMS.
>> TILL TO COME, THE YOUNG
TOAST EVER RECORD A JAMES BOND
THEME SONG.
WE WILL GET TO HEAR FROM BILLY
EILISH NEW TREK FOR THE
UPCOMING PHIL GRAHAM THEIR GUY
CAUGHT ON CAMERA PUNCHING A
WOMAN ON A PLANE, LIT UP THE
INTERNET.
SHE NEARLY GOT TOSSED OFF THE
FLIGHT BECAUSE OF IT, SHE DID.
>> WOW.
>> NOW SHE IS THREATENING
LEGAL ACTION.
>> OH, COME-ON.
>> "TMZ" ACTUALLY SPOKE WITH
HER AND THEY'LL BE JOINING US
LIVE NEXT TO TELL US WHAT'S
GOING WON HER, CAITLIN.
>> OH, MY GOSH, FLYING ISN'T
STRESSFUL ENOUGH.
MAKES ME NOT EVEN WANT TO GET
ON AN AIRPLANE.
CRAMPED SPACES CAN JUST BRING
OUT THE WORST IN PEOPLE.
HOPEFULLY TODAY BRINGING OUT
THE WORST IN YOU WHERE EVER
YOUR PLANS TAKE YOU ON THIS
VALENTINE DAY NIGHT.
IT WILL BE CALLED BUNDLE UP
WEATHER TO START OFF THE
WEEKENDS, YOUR FULL SEVEN DAY
COMING UP WHEN FOX5 RETURNS.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Lo necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month,
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Plus, you can get up to $200 in
Visa Prepaid Cards.
Mix and match your perfect
Fios plan.
Only on Verizon.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
>> IF YOU TOSS AND TURN AT
NIGHT AND CAN'T SLEEP WE HAVE
SOME GOOD NEWS.
>> WITH WHAT'S COMING UP IN
THE NEXT HOUR, SARAH?
>> FORGET MELETONIN AND ALL OF
THE OTHER SLEEP AIDS.
EXPERTS ARE SAYING THEY'VE
FOUND THE KEY TO GETTING A
BETTER NIGHT SLEEP AND THE
BEST PART IT WILL NOT LEAVE
YOU FEELING DROWSY IN THE
MORNING.
HIDDEN TREASURES SHOW YOU WHAT
THE NATIONAL MUSEUM OF
AFRICAN-AMERICAN HISTORY AND
CULTURE IS DOING TO HELP
PEOPLE LEARN ABOUT THEIR OWN
FAMILY HISTORY, ALL COMING UP
NEXT AT 5:00.
GUYS?
>> I SAW THAT MUSEUM, STILL
NEED TICKETS?
I HAVE TO LOOK ON LINE.
THANK YOU, SARAH.
>> SINGER BILLIE EILISH
RELEASED HER NEW UPCOMING
SONG, NO TIME TO DIE.
SHE IS THE YOUNGEST PERSON TO
WRITE AND RECORD A JANES BONDS
THEME SONG, PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
EIGHTEEN YEAR OLD WROTE THE
SONG WITH HER BROTHER, THE
BONN FILM SET TO BE RELEASED
IN APRIL.
>> AMAZING LET'S LISTEN REAL
QUICK.
>> I WAS LOOK CENTS JUST HER
AND HER BROTHER.
>> SO YOUNG BUT HER VOICE SO
UNIQUE, KIND OF FITS THE
THEME, HAS MYSTERY TO IT.
>> VERY DARK.
>> SO FIRST TOLD BUT THE STORY
EARLIER IN THE WEEK, WOMAN ON
THE AIRPLANE STARTED FILMING
WITH PASSENGER BEHIND HER GOT
WAY OUT EVERY CONTROL, STARTED
TREATING HERACY LIKE PUNCHING
BAG BECAUSE SHE WAS RECLINING,
HIS SEAT DIDN'T RECLINE,
BECAUSE AS YOU CAN SEE HE WAS
AT THE BACK OF THE PLANE.
SO HE WAS MORE ANNOYED ABOUT
THAT, AS WOMEN.
THE INCIDENT HAS SPARKED LEGAL
BATTLE.
THE CEO OF DELTA AIRLINES
TODAY SPOKE OUT.
THIS IS WHAT TOWED SAY.
>> I THINK IF SOMEONE KNOWS
THERE IS A TALL PERSON BEHIND
THEM, AND THEY WANT TO RECLINE
THEIR SEAT, I THINK THE
LIGHTNING WOULD BE TO MAKE
CERTAIN IT WAS OKAY.
>> WHAT?
>> SO IF I WANT IT RECLINE MY
SEAT, HEY, DO YOU MINDS?
YOU AGREE?
DELTA, DELTA, LET'S -- LAUREN
LAROSA, I DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU
ARE ON THIS SUBJECT BUT I WANT
TO SAY THAT CEO, TALK ABOUT
DEFLECTION.
>> NO,  THIS IS SO CRAZY.
>> HE NEEDS TO BE A FLIGHT
ATTENDANT, I USED TO DO FLIGHT
ATTENDANT FOR DELTA.
>> NOW YOU CAN SPEAK OUT
AGAINST YOUR OWN COMPANY.
RIDICULOUS, SQUEEZE US ALL
BACK IN THE PLANE AND HE WANTS
TO BLAME THE PASSENGERS FOR
RECLINING THEIR SEAT?
NO, NO, NO MAKE WIDER SEATS.
>> WELL, I THINK AS CEO,
SITTING WHERE HE SITS, NO PUN
INTENDED LIKE HE HAS TO KIND
OF SAY SOMETHING THAT HE FEELS
LIKE WON'T BE CONTROVERSIAL
FOR EVERYONE.
HOW CAN YOU INCLUDE EVERYBODY
IN THIS RIDE?
ALLOWING HER TO RECLINE HER
SEAT BACK BUT ALSO BE
CONSIDERATE OF THE PERSON
BEHIND YOU.
I DON'T GET ON THE PLANE AND
ASK THE PERSON BEHIND ME CAN I
RECLINE, I PAID FOR MY SEAT,
DOW WHAT I WANT TO DO.
BUT IN THIS SITUATION, WENDY
WILLIAMS VERY UPSET.
IN THE VIDEO SHE RECORD YOU
SEE THE MAN CONTINUOUSLY TAP
HER CHAIR, TAP HER CHAIR, TAP
HER CHAIR.
SHE SAID SHE HAS BEEN
CONSIDERING GOING TO THE
F.B.I. AND FILING OFFICIALS
CHARGES BECAUSE NOW IT IS TO
THE POINT WHERE SHE IS HAVING
TO GET X-RAYS DONE, SHE IS
HAVING HEADACHES, BECAUSE SHE
ALREADY SUFFERED A BACK PAIN,
AND THIS JUST MADE IT WORSE,
AND SHE WANTS THE AIRLINE TO
PAY FOR THOSE MEDICAL BILLS.
SHE A TEACHER AND THESE THINGS
ARE EXPENSIVE.
THIS IS NOT INCONVENIENCE,
THAT SHE LOOKED FORWARD TO
HAVING JUST BY DECIDE TO GO
BUY A FLIGHT ON, THAT I MEAN,
BUY TICKET MOORE FLIGHT THAT
DAY JUST HAPPENED TO HAPPEN
THAT WAY BECAUSE SHE WAS
INCONVENIENCED.
>> I'VE BEEN ROWING COMMENTS
ON LINE D SHE TALK ABOUT THE
PEOPLE CRITICIZING HER, FOR
RECORDING IT, MAYBE INCH IS
THAT GATING IT?
DID SHE SAY?
>> SHE DID NOT SPECIFICALLY
SHE TALKED ABOUT THE FACT SHE
DIDN'T KNOW HOW FIGURE WOULD
GET.
DIDN'T KNOW, SHE LITERALLY
SAYS I DIDN'T KNOW I WON'T UP
ON "TMZ."
FOR HERSHEY WAS RECORDING IT
HAD SHE HAD PROBABLY WENT TO
FILE A COMPLAINT OR WHATEVER
THIS THEY PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
BUSHED IT OFF.
BUT WHEN YOU SEE THE REPEATED
HITTING OF THE SO, YOU KIND OF
GET THE SENSE OF WHY SHE WAS
SO UPSET, SO ANNOYED.
BUT SHE DIDN'T NECESSARILY
COMMENT DIRECTLY TO US, SHE
DID TALK ABOUT HOW THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANT ACTUALLY THREATENED
TO GET HER MOVED OFF THE
FLIGHT ONCE THEY LANDED FOR
RECORDING, AND WHAT I THINK
SHE MEANT IS THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANT MUST HAVE THOUGHT
THAT SHE RECORDED HER, BECAUSE
YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO RECORD
THE FLIGHT ATTENDANTS OR
FLIGHT CREW IN ANY
CIRCUMSTANCE ON THE PLANE.
JUST FOR SAFETY REASONS, YOU
KNOW, SO MAYBE THAT'S WHAT THE
FLIGHT ATTENDANT THOUGHT.
BUT WENDY WILLIAMS TOOK IT AS
THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT TELLING
HER TO LEAVE THIS VIDEO OF
THIS INCIDENT HAPPENING, SHE
WAS VERY UPSET ABOUT THAT.
>> LAUREN WE ARE OUT OF TIME
BUT SINCE WE HAVE AN EXPERT
HERE YOU'RE FORMER DELTA
FLIGHT ATTENDANT SHOULD I COME
TO YOU IF THIS HAPPENS?
DO WE INVOLVE THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANT?
>> OH, DON'T COME TO ME.
I WORK AT TMZ.COM, OKAY, GO TO
YOUR NEAREST CORPORATE PRESS
RUMOR SOMETHING LIKE.
>> NO, ON THE FLIGHT, DO YOU
GO TO THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT?
>> OH, YA, NO, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO GO TO THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT.
IF YOU GET INTO ALTERCATION
WITH SOMEONE ON THE FLIGHT
THEN THEY CAN THROW YOU OFF
TOO.
I WOULD DEFINITELY RING THAT
BELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO TO THE INSTA POLL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, LAUREN,
GLAD WE HAVE EXPERT ON THIS,
FORMER DELTA FLIGHT ATTENDANT.
THE INSTA POLL DO YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD HAVE TO ASK
PERMISSION TO RECLINE YOUR
SEAT ON AIRPLANE.
>> I'M IN THE MAJORITY NO.
IF THE SEAT RECLINES YOU
SHOULD BE ABLE TO RECLINE IT,
THE AIRLINES FAULT FORAY
THAWING SEAT TO RECLINE INTO
SOMEONE ELSE'S PERSONAL SPACE
SO MUCH THAT THEY'RE PUNCHING
THE BACK OF THE SEAT.
CRAZE.
>> I DEPENDS ON HOW LONG THE
FLIGHT S IF THIS IS LIKE HOUR
FLIGHT, AND TALL GAY, HI, BE
COURTEOUS.
>> COURSE, AND I RARELY
RECLINE MY SEAT FOR THAT
REASON, BUT IF YOUR SEAT
RECLINES, YOU PAY FOR THE
SEAT, YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO
RECLINE THE SEAT.
>> JUST BE NICE, PEOPLE
PUNCHING THE SEATS?
>> I THINK BOTH AT FAULT HERE,
ALL RIGHT, LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE.
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL NIGHT.
>> DECEIVING, DECEIVING.
>> THIS CRISP ARCTIC AIR IT,
DOES MAKE FOR REALLY CLEAR
BEAUTIFUL NIGHTS.
>> SURE DOES, GOOD PICTURE
TAKING, GUYS, BEAUTIFUL LIVE
LOOK OUT THERE RIGHT NOW AT
NATIONAL HARBOR, YA, IT IS
COLD, BUT IT IS NICE AND
CLEAR, AND I THINK SEE THE
SUNSHINE, BEEN PRETTY GLOOMY
WEEK FULL OF RAIN, I THINK
OVER 2 INCHES OF RAIN HERE IN
D.C. THROUGH THE WEEK.
BUT NO MORE RAIN IN THE
FORECAST AT LEAST IN THE
SHORT-TERM.
WEEKEND, YES, STARTING OFFER
COLD.
BUT BELIEVE IT OR NOT IT WILL
ENDS PRETTY MILD BY THE TIME
WE GET TO THE SECOND HALF OF
SUNDAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURES TODAY, REACH
SHORTLY AFTER MIDNIGHT FALLING
EVERY SENSE, 44 REAGAN, 40
DULLOS, 42 AT THE BWI.
TEMPERATURES OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW
MAINLY IN THE 30'S, ALTHOUGH
ALREADY SEEING SOME 20'S SHOW
UP OUT ALONG EIGHT; 28
WINCHESTER, 29 IN MARTINSBURG,
24 CUMBERLAND, 37 THERE IN
CULPEPER, 37 IN D.C., 36
ANNAPOLIS, 34 IN BALTIMORE.
QUITE THE DROP OFF COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY.
WE IN THE UPPER 50'S, NEAR
06 DEGREES IN SO MANY SPOTS,
AND NOW, 15 TO 20, TO 20 PLUS
DEGREES, COLDER, SO THAT IS A
BIT OF A CHANGE.
AND YOU'RE PROBABLY DRESSED
FOR HAD TO BREAK OUT THE
WINTER GEAR TODAY.
WIN GUSTS REMAIN OVER 20 MILES
PER HOUR HERE REAGAN,
ANNAPOLIS, OUT WEST CASINO
EVERY GUSTY THROUGH THE
EVENING HOURS, SEE WINDS
DIMINISH OVERNIGHT.
IF IT IS DATE NIGHT FOR THIS
EVENING BUNDLE UP WET 33RD BY
7:00 P.M.
FALLING BELOW FREEZING BY 9:00 Y
11:00 P.M.
WATCH THOSE TEMPERATURES
CONTINUE TO TUMBLE INTO
TOMORROW MORNING.
TWENTY'S TO START THE DAY.
NOT AS GUSTY BUT JUST STRAIGHT
UP COLD.
WITH HIGH PRESSURE RIGHT OVER
US FOR YOUR SATURDAY.
TEMPERATURES PEAK IN THE MID
TO UPPER 30S, BUT BY SUNDAY,
WE ARE NOT GOING TO DEVIATE
TOO MUCH FROM THAT.
SO WE WILL START OFF AT
FREEZING IN NOT ABOVE.
THEN LOOK AT THAT WARM UP, UP
TO 50 DEGREES THEREBY 4:30 IN
THE AFTERNOON.
A LOT OF SUNSHINE AGAIN
TOMORROW.
THIS IS 4:00 P.M. SATURDAY
FUTURE CAST, NOT MUCH TO SEE,
CLOUDS INCREASE BIT AS THE
WARMER AIR ROLLS IN 9:00 A.M.
SUNDAY LITTLE LIZ SUNSHINE,
AND PROBABLY HAVE MORE CLOUDS
THAN SUN AS WE GO THROUGH YOUR
SUNDAY AFTERNOON.
THERE IS YOUR SEVEN DAY THREE
DAY WEEKEND FOR SO MANY OF US,
A THREE, MOSTLY CLOUDY MONDAY
LOOKS GREAT.
SIXTY BY SUNDAY, SHOWERS ROLL
IN, AND THEN BACK TO SOME
COLDER WEATHER.
SO YES, IT GETS MILD AGAIN,
BUT THEN IT GETS COLD.
HIGH TEMPERATURES ONLY IN THE
30'S NEXT THURSDAY, FRIDAY.
THAT'S A LOOK AT YOUR SEVEN
DAY, BLAKE, OVER TO YOU.
>> STILL TO COME:  TO HER
FANS, CARRIE UNDERWOOD MAY AND
COUNTRY SUPERSTAR BUT HER
YOUNG SON SEES HER DIFFERENTLY
ACCORDING TO HIS HILARIOUS
RESPONSES ON SCHOOL
ASSIGNMENT.
>> ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
[ fast-paced drumming ]
>> WELCOME BACK.
WE WANT TO THANK YOU FOR ALL THE
PHOTOS YOU'VE BEEN SENDING IN.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE HERE FOR US
ON THIS VALENTINE'S DAY.
HOW ADORABLE, RIGHT?  TIP TO
SHARE THEM WITH US.
MAKE SURE TO USE THE HASHTAG
FOX5 VALENTINE.
>>> SINGER CARRIE UNDERWOOD IS A
SENIOR CITIZEN IN THE EYES OF
HER FOUR YEAR OLD SON.
UNDERWOOD POSTED A PICTURE ON
INSTAGRAM OF HER SON'S CLASS
ASSIGNMENT CALLED ALL ABOUT MY
MOM.
EVERYTHING SEEMED SPOT ON EXCEPT
FOR THE AGE SECTION WHERE ISAIAH
SAID HIS MOM WAS 70 YEARS OLD.
HE ALSO THOUGHT SHE DID LAUNDRY
FOR A LIVING.
>> THAT IS REALLY SWEET.
HOW CUTE IS THAT.
>>> A KOALA IS IN COMPLETE BLISS
WHILE HE RECEIVES A BELLY RUB.
HOW CUTE.
A HEART WARMING SIGHT.
>> THAT'S A KOALA.
>> LOOKED LIKE A DOG AT FIRST.
HEART WARMING SIGHT AFTER SO
MANY ANIMALS HAD TO BE RESCUED
FROM AUSTRALIA'S BUSH FIRES.
MANY NEEDED URGENT CARE THIS
GUY'S WELL ON THE WAY TO
RECOVERY.
>> HE'S LIVING THE LIFE AFTER A
ROUGH FEW MONTHS.
>> DOES HE GET CO-WRITING
CREDIT?
>> ROYALTIES?
>> YEAH.
THIS VIDEO POSTED ON TWITTER BY
GA STAR ININSTRUMENTALIST TRENCH
WHO POSTED VIDEOS WITH HIS DOG
MAPLE.
THIS TIME MAPLE WANTED TO CHIME
IN.
THE DUO MAKES BEAUTIFUL MUSIC
TOGETHER.
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT NOTE
TOGETHER?  THAT WAS POWERFUL.
>> SHE GETS HALF THE ROYALTIES
TO ME, SHE MAKES THE SONG.
>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US.
>> YOUR NEWS AT 5:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 5:00, MURDER
MYSTERY.
NEW DETAILS IN THE CASE OF THE
LOCAL HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
ACCUSED OF KILLING A YOUNG
COUPLE, BUT MANY QUESTIONS
REMAIN.
>>> AND A SCHOOL SCANDAL.
>> I'M THINKING, OH, MY GOD, HOW
LONG HAS THIS LADY BEEN A
SUBSTITUTE.
>> PARENTS OUTRAGEDEN A A POLICE
INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY AFTER A
SUBSTITUTE TEACHER IS ACCUSED OF
GIVING LAP DANCES AT A MARYLAND
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
AND THEN
♪
MORE THAN A DOZEN COUPLE
CELEBRATE VALENTINE'S DAY BY
TYING THE KNOT AT A LOCAL
COURTHOUSE.
FOX5 WAS THERE AND WILL BRING
YOU THE LATEST.
YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
♪
>>> FIRST AT 5:00 DEVELOPING
RIGHT NOW NEW INFORMATION ABOUT
THE MURDERS OF A YOUNG COUPLE IN
SOUTHERN VIRGINIA.
>> AND WE NOW KNOW HOW THEY WERE
KILLED AND WE'RE LEARNING SOME
MORE ABOUT THE 18 YEAR OLD
ALEXANDRIA HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
WHO IS CHARGED WITH THEIR
KILLINGS.
FOX5'S STEPHANIE RAMIREZ IS LIVE
AT TV WILLIAMS HIGH SCHOOL
TONIGHT WITH MORE ON THIS CASE.
STEPHANIE?
>> Reporter:
>> GUYS RIGHT OFF THE TOP WE CAN
TELL YOU THE DEPARTMENT OF
HEALTH FOR VIRGINIA STATE THERE,
THEY'RE TELLING US THE TWO
VICTIMS