OF RAIN RIGHT THERE.
BUT BIG PICTURE WE HAVE SHOWERS
MOVING IN AND THEY COULD BE
AROUND FOR THE MORNING COMMUTE.
OR EVENING COMMUTE.
SORRY.
THEY SHOULD BE OUT OF HERE FOR
THE MORNING COMMUTE TOMORROW SO
WASHINGTON SEEING LIGHT RAIN.
WE EXPECT TEMPERATURES WHICH
HAVE BEEN VERY PLEASANT AND IN
THE 50S MOST OF THE DAY TO KIND
OF FALL INTO THE 40S OVERNIGHT
AND THEN TOMORROW WE'LL START
OFF WITH CLOUD COVER THAT WILL
GIVE WAY TO CLEARING SKIES AS WE
GO THROUGH THE REST OF THE DAY.
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE I CAN SHOW YOU
MUCH MORE ON RADAR BUT WE'LL TRY
TO FIX THAT FOR YOU GET YOU
SOMETHING ELSE FOR A VISUAL I'LL
BE BACK IN A BIT WITH MORE ON
THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME JUST A COUPLE
SHOWERS FOR THE EVENING.
>> WE DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE
CAITLIN.
>>> A DRAMATIC DAY IN COURT
TODAY A MARYLAND JUDGE HEARD A
MOTION TO DISMISS CHARGES
AGAINST CATHERINE HOGGLE, THE
MONTGOMERY COUNTY MOTHER ACCUSED
OF MURDERING HER TWO CHILDREN IN
2014.
>> SHE WAS THE LAST PERSON TO BE
SEEN WITH HER AND STEPHANIE
RAMIREZ JUST GOT OUT OF THE
COURTHOUSE.
STEPHANIE, ANY DECISION TODAY?
>> Reporter: YEAH, MARINA, THE
UPDATE IS THERE IS NO DECISION.
THE JUDGE HEARD ABOUT AN HOUR'S
WORTH OF ARGUMENTS, AN EMOTIONAL
STATEMENT FROM THE CHILDREN'S
FATHER TROY TURNER AND AFTER ALL
OF THIS HE DECIDED HE IS GOING
TO GIVE A WRITTEN OPINION WE MAY
NOT SEE UNTIL LATER THIS WEEK OR
NEXT WEEK.
BEFORE THE HEARING, THE 1:30
HEARING TODAY, THE CHILDREN'S
FATHER, FAMILY AND SUPPORTERS
GATHERED OUTSIDE OF THE
COURTHOUSE TO PRAY.
INSIDE TROY TURNER TOLD THE
JUDGE CATHERINE HOGGLE ROBBED
THE CHILDREN SARAH AND JACOB OF
EVERYTHING THEY WOULD
ACCOMPLISH.
HE ALSO SAID IF SHE CAN GET AWAY
WITH THIS, THEN THERE IS NO
JUSTICE.
THIS STATEMENT WAS IN RESPONSE
TO THE ATTORNEY CALLING FOR THE
MURDER CHARGES AGAINST CATHERINE
HOGGLE TO BE DROPPED.
NOW, NOTHING IS CERTAIN, BUT THE
IDEA IS, IF MURDER CHARGES WERE
DROPPED SHE COULD BE ORDERED TO
CIVIL COMMITMENT WHERE SHE COULD
SPEND THE REST OF HER TIME AT A
PSYCHIATRIC FACILITY BUT THEN
THERE'S THE QUESTION OF COULD
THEY RELEASE HER.
HOGGLE'S ATTORNEY FILED THE
MOTION SAYING THERE IS A FIVE
YEAR LIMITATION HOLDING SOMEONE
CONSISTENTLY FOUND INCOMPETENT
TO STAND TRIAL HE SAID THAT
STARTED IN 2015 T STATE'S
ATTORNEY ARGUED IT'S TOO EARLY
TO TALK ABOUT THIS BECAUSE THEY
BELIEVE THAT 5-YEAR PERIOD
STARTED WHEN HER CHARGES WERE
ELEVATED TO FELONY MURDER
CHARGES IN 2017.
GUYS, THIS WAS THE CHILDREN'S
FATHER, TROY TURNER, JUST BEFORE
GOING INTO THAT COURTROOM TODAY.
>> A LOT OF LOVE MISSING MY
KIDS.
ONE OF THE THINGS I WAS PRAYING
SILENTLY FOR IS THE ABILITY TO
FORGIVE BECAUSE MY UNDERSTANDING
IS THAT GOD CAN'T WORK THROUGH
HATE.
SO I DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO
FORGIVE AND HOPE GOD CAN WORK
THROUGH ME TO BRING JUSTICE TO
MY CHILDREN.
>> Reporter: AND THE OTHER THING
HEAVILY ARGUED TODAY WAS
HOGGLE'S STATUS.
SO OVER AND OVER AGAIN HOGGLE
WAS FOUND INCOMPETENT TO STAND
TRIAL BUT RESTORABLE.
WELL, TODAY IN COURT THEY SAID
THAT ACCORDING TO THE MOST
RECENT REPORTS, SHE WAS FOUND
INCOMPETENT TO STAND TRIAL AND
NOT RESTORABLE.
SO THE JUDGE TODAY VOICED
CONCERNS ON WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF
HE DID HOLD HER, HE DIDN'T
DISMISS CHARGES AND SHE WAS
STILL FOUND TO BE NOT
RESTORABLE.
I CAN TELL YOU TURNER TALKED
ABOUT THIS AFTERWARDS.
HE SAID REGARDLESS OF WHAT
HAPPENS, HE BELIEVES THAT
CATHERINE HOGGLE DID IT, THAT
SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE'S DOING.
HE SAID HE'S GOING TO CONTINUE
TO FIGHT FOR HIS CHILDREN AND
EXPRESSED APPRECIATION THE JUDGE
IS TAKING THE TIME TO MAKE THIS
VERY IMPORTANT DECISION.
GUYS, BACK TO YOU.
>> STEPHANIE WE KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THIS FIGURATIVE CLOCK THAT
THE TIME IS RUNNING OUT THE FIVE
YEARS SHE'S BEEN FOUND
INCOMPETENT.
NOW YOU'RE SAYING IT MEANS SHE'S
NON-RESTORABLE WHICH MEANS WHEN
THE DECISION COMES DOWN IN THE
NEXT TWO WEEKS IS THERE A
POSSIBILITY THAT CATHERINE
HOGGLE WALKS FREE.
>> Reporter: NO, I'M GOING TO
SAY NO RIGHT AWAY.
THAT WAS A DISCUSSION THAT WAS
HAD.
SO BASICALLY EVEN IF THE CHARGES
ARE DROPPED, BOTH SIDES THINK
SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
WALK AROUND IN THE COMMUNITY
RIGHT AWAY.
THERE IS GOING TO BE A DECISION
THAT'S GOING TO HAVE TO BE MADE
ABOUT HER TREATMENT.
BUT I CAN TELL YOU THE STATE'S
ATTORNEY WERE LOOKING AT OTHER
PREVIOUS CASES AND IN ONE CASE A
MURDERER IN SILVER SPRING THE
STATE'S ATTORNEY SAID IT TOOK
EIGHT YEARS FOR THE PERSON TO BE
RESTORED.
SO THEY ARE USING THE TOOLS THEY
HAVE COULD ERRING TO THE STATE'S
ATTORNEY TO TRY TO GET HER
THERE.
BUT AGAIN THE FATHER BELIEVES
THAT THIS IS AN ACT AND HE SAYS
HE'S GOING TO KEEP FIGHTING NO
MATTER WHAT.
>> CERTAINLY A LENGTHY PROCESS.
STEPHANIE RAMIREZ LIVE TONIGHT
FROM MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
>>> REACTION COMING IN THIS
AFTERNOON AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP
ISSUED PARDONS AND COME STATIONS
FOR SOME CONVICTED WHITE COLLAR
CRIMINALS TOP AMONG THEM ROB
BLAGOJEVICH.
HIS 14 YEAR SENTENCE HE SERVED
EIGHT YEARS ON A PLAY TO PAY FOR
BARACK OBAMA'S SENATE SEAT.
AND THREE OTHER MEN, FORMER SAN
FRANCISCO 49ERS OWNER FORMER
POLICE COMMISSIONER AND VECHLT
BANKER MILKEN.
DIBARTOLO CONVICTED BUT NEVER
SERVING TIME.
THE OTHER WAS FOR LYING TO
OFFICIALS WHILE MILKEN SERVED
TIME FOR SECURITY FRAUD AND
CONSPIRACY.
>>> MORE FIREWORKS OVER ROGER
STONE BUT WILL STILL BE SENSER
SENTENCED THURSDAY, DESPITE
CRIES FROM HIS DEFENSE TEAM AND
THE PRESIDENT THE WHOLE PROCESS
HAS BEEN UNFAIR.
STONE CONVICTED ON SEVERAL
COUNTS IN NOVEMBER INCLUDING
LYING TO CONGRESS ABOUT HIS ROLE
IN THE 2016 TRUMP PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN AND ITS TIES TO RUSSIA.
>> SO THE PARDONS MAY NOT BE
OVER.
>>> JURY DELIBERATIONS UNDERWAY
IN THE CASE OF HARVEY WEINSTEIN.
INJURY WILL DECIDE ON TWO SEXUAL
ASSAULT CHARGES, HE'S ACCUSED OF
RAPING A WOMAN IN 2013 AND
PERFORMING ANOTHER TO PERFORM
ORAL SEX IN 2006.
WEINSTEIN CONTENDS IT WAS
CONSENSUAL AND NO WRONGDOINGS
TOO PLACE.
HE FACES LIFE IN PRISON AND
AFTER THESE CHARGES IN NEW YORK
HE GOES TO CALIFORNIA FOR NEW
CHARGES THERE.
>>> THE BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA
FILING FOR BANKRUPTCY THE
ORGANIZATION DEALING WITH
MASSIVE COMPENSATION COSTS TIED
TO SEVERAL SEXUAL ABUSE
LAWSUITS.
THAT COMPENSATION FUND COULD
SURPASS A BILLION DOLLARS AND
SOME ARE SPECULATEING THAT THE
GROUP WILL NOW HAVE TO SELL SOME
OF ITS PROPERTIES WHO PAY
THOUSANDS OF MEN WHO CLAIM THEY
WERE ABUSED BY SCOUT LEADERS T
ORGANIZATION TRYING TO KEEP FROM
FOLDING.
>>> NASCAR DRIVER RYAN NEWMAN IS
NOW AWAKE AND SPEAKING WITH
FAMILY AND DOCTORS.
VERY GOOD NEWS AFTER THIS
VIOLENT CRASH ON THE FINAL LAP
OF THE DAYTONA 500 LAST NIGHT.
THE 42 YEAR OLD'S CAR FLIPPED,
ROLLED, AND WAS HIT ON THE
DRIVER'S SIDE BY ANOTHER CAR
BEFORE IT SLID ACROSS THE FINISH
LINE UPSIDE DOWN.
THE CAR BRIEFLY CAUGHT ON FIRE
BEFORE IT WAS PUT OUT BY TRACK
PERSONNEL.
NEW MAN WAS TAKEN TO A HOSPITAL
AND IS EXPECTED TO BE OKAY,
AGAIN UP AND TALKING NOW, DENNY
HAMLIN WON THE DAYTONA 500 BUT
NASCAR SCRAPPED THE VICTORY LANE
PARTY AS A RESULT OF THE CRASH.
>>> NOW TO THE LATEST ON
CORONAVIRUS.
AT THIS HOUR THERE ARE MORE THAN
73,000 CONFIRMED CASES
WORLDWIDE.
MAJORITY OF THOSE CASES ARE IN
MAIN LAND CHINA AND HEALTH
OFFICIALS SAY CASES ARE
INCREASING BY ABOUT 2,000 EACH
DAY.
MORE THAN 1800 PEOPLE HAVE DIED
FROM THE ILLNESS.
>>> AMONG THOSE VICTIMS IS THE
HEAD OF THE CHINESE HOSPITAL AT
THE EPICENTER OF THE
CORONAVIRUS.
DR. LOU ZMING DIED THIS MORNING
AFTER LEADING THE FIGHT AT THE
HOSPITAL TO CONTAIN THE DEADLY
VIRUS.
THE DIRECTOR IS AT LEAST THE
SEVENTH HEALTH WORKER TO DIE OF
THE DISEASE.
>>> AND LET'S TAKE A LOOK
INSIDE.
THIS IS INSIDE A QUARANTINE ROOM
THAT ONE AMERICAN WHO EVACUATED
FROM THE DIAMOND PRINCESS CRUISE
SHIP IS STAYING IN, OUR FIRST
LOOK INTO THE AREA.
THE TRAVELLER AND SEVERAL OTHERS
ARE LODGED ON BASES IN JAIL AND
TEXAS, TOMORROW THOUSANDS OF
PASSENGERS ON THAT WILL END A
TWO WEEK QUARANTINE.
TWO FLU TO THE US AND TESTED
POSITIVE FOR THE CORONAVIRUS
LEAVING PEOPLE WONDERING IF IT
WAS EFFECTIVE.
>>> DC POLICE SEARCHING FOR A
LOCAL RESTAURANT THE OWNER OF
THE SHRIMP BOAT SAYS A GROUP OF
THIEVES BROKE IN LAST NIGHT AND
TRIED TO STEAL AN ATM.
HERE'S THE VIDEO.
YOU SEE THEM HAVING SEVERAL
FAILED ATTEMPTS.
ONE SUSPECT JUMPING BEHIND THE
COUNTER GRABBING THE SAFE.
IT IS NOT THE FIRST TIME THIS
BUSINESS HAS BEEN HIT.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO CAPTURING TWO
SUSPECTS STEALING AN ATM FROM
THE RESTAURANT BACK IN DECEMBER.
>> THEY TRIED TO GET THE ATM,
BUT WE BOLT IT GOOD SO THEY
COULDN'T MOVE IT.
SO THEY TRIED TO GET ANOTHER
STUFF, THEY LOOK AT OUR SAFE AND
THEY TOOK OUR SAFE.
WHICH IS REALLY SAD, BECAUSE, I
MEAN, YOU TRY TO CHANGE A
NEIGHBORHOOD, AND MAKING PLACE
LOOK NICE AND AT THE END OF THE
DAY, THE HARD WORK MANY WORKERS
THERE AND WHEN YOU LOSE IT, IT'S
SAD.
IT'S REALLY SAD.
>> THE OWNER AT THE TIMES FOX5
OTHER SMALLER INCIDENTS HAVE
HAPPENED AT THAT RESTAURANT BUT
THEY'VE NOT REPORTED THEM TO
POLICE.
>>> NOW TO SOME UNUSUAL MOMENTS
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
CHECK OUT THIS RARE WEATHER
PHENOMENON KNOWN AS AN ICE
VOLCANO.
IT HAPPENED SUNDAY ALONG THE
LAKE MICHIGAN SHORELINE.
NOT A REAL VOLCANO.
AN ICE VOLCANO FORMS NEAR A
LARGE FLOATING PLATFORM OF ICE
WHEN WAVES HIT THE SHORELINE IT
CAN FORCE WATER UP THROUGH THE
CONES OF ICE MAKING IT LOOK LIKE
A VOLCANO.
>> COOL SIGHT.
>>> THIS GUY DESERVES A GOOD
TIP.
THIS WAITER IN ENGLAND CARRYING
FOUR PLATES TO A TABLE, YOU SEE
HIM THERE, HE SLIPS, SPILLED
SAUCE, FALLS STRAIGHT TO THE
GROUND, HANDS THE PLATE THERE TO
THE WAITRESS OR WAITER AND
DIDN'T DROP A THING.
HE THEN HANDS THAT PLATE OVER
AND YOU SEE APPARENTLY THE ONLY
THING THAT HE LOST THERE WAS
SAUSAGE AND A FEW PEAS.
GOOD FOR HIM.
>> HE COULDN'T DO THAT AGAIN IF
HE TRIED.
>> ONE TIME THING.
>> RIGHT.
>>> CHECK OUT THIS YOUNG DOLPHIN
LEARNING HOW TO JUMP.
MICHELLE DICKINSON WAS IN
CALIFORNIA ON A BUSINESS TRIP
WHEN SHE CAPTURED THIS GUY
ENTHUSIASTICALLY JUMPING OUT OF
THE WATER BUT LOOK, BELLY FLOP
RIGHT IN.
THE BABY ENDED YOU HAVE MOSTLY
DOING BELLY FLOPS BUT DID KEEP
TRYING.
>> LOOKS LIKE ME WHEN I DIVE
INTO A POOL.
>>> GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY TODAY,
AN ASSISTANT FOOTBALL COACH
THANKS SOME OF PEOPLE WHO HELPED
SAFE HIS LIFE.
LAST SEPTEMBER TRAY ANDERSON
SUFFERED A HEART ATTACK ON THE
FIELD, BY STANDSERS JUMPED IN TO
HELP ADMINISTER CPR BEFORE HELP
ARRIVED AND TODAY HE HANDED OUT
CLOSE TO A DOZEN CARDIAC SAFE
COINS AS A TOKEN OF HIS
APPRECIATION.
>>S AND I SAID WHY NOT.
WHY SHOULDN'T I STAND UP HERE IN
FRONT OF EVERYBODY AND GIVE THEM
THE JOY OF ME BEING HERE, THE
HARD WORK OF THIS GREAT TEAM
OVER HERE, THE TEAM OVER HERE TO
COME TOGETHER AND BRING ME BACK.
SO THAT I CAN BE HERE AND STAND
BEFORE YOU TODAY.
>> DC FIRE AND EMS PROUD OF THE
WITNESSES WHO STEPPED IN JUST
LAST YEAR WASHINGTON, DC MATCHED
THE NATIONAL AVERAGE OF 40% OF
BYSTANDERS WHO JUMP IN TO HELP
IN SITUATIONS LIKE THIS.
THAT IS ROUGHLY 20% UP FROM
2015.
SO THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
>>> HEADS UP PARENTS, THE ON
LINE LOTTERY FOR FREE TICKETS TO
THIS YEAR'S WHITE HOUSE EASTER
EGG ROLL OPENED AT TEN CLOCK
THIS MORNING SO YOU CAN SIGN UP
NOW.
IT WILL TAKE PLACE APRIL 13TH
THE DAY AFTER EASTER THIS YEAR.
YOU HAVE UNTIL MONDAY,
FEBRUARY 24TH TO ENTER, AND THEN
THE WINNERS WILL BE NOTIFIED BY
E-MAIL IN MARCH.
>> THAT IS A HOT TICKET IN TOWN.
>> UH-HUH.
>> A LOTS OF PEOPLE TRYING TO
GET THEM.
>>> STILL TO COME SPACEX HAS
STRUCK A DEAL WITH A NORTHERN
TOURISM AND WILL A TAKE TOURISTS
HIGHER THAN THEY'VE GONE BEFORE
PLUS GET YOUR PHONES OUT THIS IS
OUR FOX5 INSTAPOLL QUESTION OF
THE DAY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE THE FIRST
TO BE ON THOSE FLIGHTS, I KNOW
PEOPLE ARE CLAM ORG BUT I'M
GOING TO WAIT.
>>> HOW A BUILDING DEMOLITION
ATTEMPT LOOK AT THIS
ACCIDENTALLY CREATED AMERICA'S
NEWEST VIRAL TOURIST SPOT.
IT WAS A BIG FAIL ON THE
DEMOLITION BUT NOW EVERYBODY'S
GOING TO TAKE PICTURE.
>> AND HERE'S A LIVE LOOK AT
TRAFFIC ACROSS OUR AREA, THINGS
LOOK LIKE THEY'RE MOVING PRETTY
SLOWLY AS RUSH HOUR RAMPS UP.
FIVE AT 4:00 P.M. WILL BE RIGHT
BACK.
♪
RIGHT
BACK.
♪♪
It's been reported that
there's a cycyberattack
on business every 39 seconds.
Ouch.
I don't even want
to think about it.
Comcast Business has a solution.
We go beyond fast with a
cloud-based security system
that automatically updates,
so you always have
the latest protection.
Phishing. Malware.
Risky sites.
It can help block all of that.
It's one less thing
for us to worry about.
Comcast Business SecurityEdge
automatically protects
all the devices on your network.
Call 1-800-501-6000 today.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
♪
>> SPACE TRAVEL HAS ALWAYS BEEN
AT THE FOREFRONT OF OUR
IMAGINATION, NOW FOR THE FIRST
TIME AND FOR A HEFTY PRICE
PRIVATE CITIZENS WILL SOON BE
ABLE TO FLY AROUND THE EARTH IN
A SPACE CRAFT.
>> FOX5 IKE EJIOCHI IS IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA WITH HOW ALL
OF THIS IS POSSIBLE.
IKE, SPACE ADVENTURES IS A
COMPANY IN VIENNA OUTS THERE?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
BLAKE.
SPACE ADVENTURES AND SPACEX HAVE
FORMED TOGETHER TO WHAT THEY SAY
IS TO TRY TO EXPAND SPACE
TRAVEL.
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW.
WHENEVER WE TALK ABOUT SPACE
TRAVEL, A LOT OF US ALWAYS SHOOT
TO THIS.
THIS IS THE SPACE SHUTTLE
DISCOVERY.
IT'S THE LONGEST SERVING AND
MOST ACCOMPLISHED SPACE SHUTTLE
IN THE WORLD WITH OVER 39 EARTH
OR ABOUT ITTAL MISSIONS, IT'S
BEEN IN OUTER SPACE A GRANDS
TOTAL OF ONE YEAR.
BUT THE ACTUAL CAPSULES IN WHICH
THE TRAINED ASTRONAUTS LOOK LIKE
THIS, THE SMALLER CAPSULES YOU
USUALLY SEE THE ASTRONAUTS ARE
INSIDE.
SPACEX HAS THE DRAGON CRAFT, THE
NEW EFFORTS ONE THEY'VE BEEN
USING IT FOR YEARS, AND THAT
DRAGON X CAPSULE IS WHAT SPACE
ADVENTURE IS INTERESTED IN.
IN THIS NEW PARTNERSHIP THEY'LL
HAVE ANYBODY, ANY PRIVATE
CITIZEN WHO CAN AFFORD IT TO
ACTUALLY BUY A SEAT ON THAT
DRAGON X SPACESHIP AND TRAVEL
AROUND THE WORLD SEVERAL TIMES.
IT'S A TRIP THAT CAN TAKE UP TO
A WEEK, EVEN LONGER.
SO IT'S A BRAND NEW PARTNERSHIP,
SOMETHING THEY'RE EXCITED ABOUT
AND EVENTUALLY COULD EXPAND
SPACE TRAVEL FOR EVERYONE.
>> SO, IKE, JUST LOOKING AT IT,
I ALREADY KNOW WE CAN'T AFFORD
IT, BUT HOW MUCH DOES IT COST TO
GET A SEAT ON THAT?
>> Reporter: WELL, HERE'S THE
THING.
I SPOKE TO SPACE ADVENTURES AND
THEY SAID THEY DON'T REALLY
DISCLOSE THE PRICE.
>> THAT SHOWS YOU IT'S REALLY
EXPENSIVE THEN.
>> REPORTER: YEAH, BUT THEY DID
SAY IT FALLS IN LINE WITH OTHER
SIMILAR EXPERIENCES.
I LOOKED UP THE NUMBERS, AND A
TRIP LIKE THIS CAN COST ANYWHERE
BETWEEN 30 AND $50 MILLION.
>> WHAT?
>> WOW.
>> Reporter: IT'S A PRETTY PENNY
HOWEVER THEY SAY EVENTUALLY OVER
TIME WHEN SOMEONE LIKE YOU OR I
COULD AFFORD IT WILL ACTUALLY BE
POSSIBLE IF STUFF LIKE THIS
CONTINUES TO HAPPEN AND THE
TECHNOLOGY GETS BETTER AND MORE
AFFORDABLE.
>> IT HAS TO START SOMEWHERE.
CARS WERE A BIG LUXURY AT ONE
POINT AND NOW EVERYBODY HAS ONE.
>> Reporter: I KNOW.
>> THANKS IKE.
>>> SPACE TOURISM IS FOX5
INSTAPOLL OF THE DAY, WOULD YOU
TRAVEL INTO SPACE IF MONEY WAS
NO OBJECT.
YOU CAN VOTE ON FOX5DC.COM ON
OUR NEWS APP AND IT'S PRETTY
EVENLY SPLIT THERE, YEAH, ON THE
NOSE, 50/50.
>> STILL, YOU KNOW WHEN THEY
DON'T SHED THE PRICE TAG, LIKE A
STORE, WHEN THERE'S NO PRICE
TAG, WE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
>> THE ONLY TWO WE CAN SEND ARE
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG AND DONALD
TRUMP, THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES
WITH MONEY.
>>> ASTRONAUTS AT THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION ARE
WAITING FOR A DELICIOUS
DELIVERY, A CARGO SHIP GETTING
READY TO DOCK TODAY.
BESIDES THE USUAL DRIP THEY HAVE
CHEESES, FRESH FEW, VEGABLES,
CHOCOLATE AND CANDIES, THEY HAVE
THE MUNCHIES IN SPACE.
NASA SAID THE ASTRONAUTS
SPECIFICALLY REQUESTED SKITTLES,
HOT TAMALES AND MIKE AND IKE'S.
>> MAYBE I'M CHANGING MY
DECISION NOW, MAYBE IT IS WORTH
GOING.
HOW WIDEY IT TO TOYEDY SPACE
FLIGHT.
>> VERY COOL THIS IS NOT A LIVE
PICTURE OF OUR WEATHER BECAUSE
IT'S PRETTY CLOUDY.
>> I LIKE THAT QUALITY CHOICES.
THEY HAVE CHOCOLATE BUT THEY
HAVE ALL THE FRUITY SUGARS
COVERED, TOO.
>> I GUESS THAT'S THE ULTIMATE
IMAX ACTUALLY BEING UP THERE AND
SEEING IT AND THAT'S WHAT YOU
WOULD EAT LOOKING OUT AT THE
SCREEN.
>> THERE YOU GO, CATCH SOME SORT
MUCH BUZZ SOMEHOW WHEN YOU'RE UP
THERE, THE SUGAR RUSH.
>> WHERE'S THE WINE, THOUGH.
>> PROBABLY NOT ALLOWED, I
GUESS.
>> YEAH.
>> ALCOHOL ON THE INTERNATIONAL
SPACE STATION I THINK IS A BAD
IDEA.
>> NOT AS RON MY UNDER THE
INFLUENCE.
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW
THOSE CLOUDS HAVE CERTAINLY
FILLED IN.
YES, IT WAS A NICE SUNNY FIRST
HALF OF THE DAY, BEAUTIFUL,
TEMPERATURES REALLY JUMPED, BUT
WITH THE CLOUDS COVER WE ARE
WAITING ON SOME SHOWERS, VERY
LIGHT WANE THAT'S BEEN PUSHING
THROUGH THE AREA.
WE'LL HAVE SHOWERS COME AND GO
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
NOTHING HEAVY BUT YOU MIGHT NEED
THE UMBRELLA IF YOU'RE STEPPING
OUT TONIGHT.
56 DEGREES OVERCAST SKIES AND
YOU SEE THAT REFLECED AT THE
AIRPORT RIGHT NOW.
WINDS LIGHT OUT OF THE SOUTH BUT
OVERALL PRETTY MILD AND WE SAW
TEMPERATURES PEAK IN THE UPPER
50 INS THE METRO.
WE HIT 50 IN FREDERICKSBURG, 57
RIGHT NOW IN LEONARDTOWN, 57 IN
STEVENSVILLE, 59 AT DULLES,
THAT'S NICE, 55 WINCHESTER AND
58 UNTIL CULPEPER.
HERE'S RADAR RIGHT NOW.
IT LOOKS LIKE A LOT.
YOU CAN SEE A LOT OF GREEN
MOVING ACROSS THE OHIO VALLEY,
THE MIDWEST INTO THE SOUTH, BUT
THE HEAVIER SHOWERS LOOK TO BE
DOWN ACROSS THE NORTHERN GULF
COAST STATES TRAVELING THROUGH
ATLANTA INTO THE CAROLINAS.
FOR US, WE'LL HAVE A FEW SHOWERS
AROUND BUT IT LOOKS FAIRLY
BROKEN OVERHEAD AND FUTURECAST
SHOWS THAT.
WE HAVE A LITTLE STUFF RIGHT
NOW, AND THAT'S REALLY ALL WE'RE
GOING TO GET FOR THIS EVENING,
7:00 O'CLOCK, A FEW SHOWERS.
IT LOOKS A LITTLE STEADIER LATER
TONIGHT AND THIS IS WHERE SOME
ENHANCEMENT IS SOUTH AND EAST OF
US.
SO AT 11:00 O'CLOCK, THERE'S
NOTHING GOING ON IN DC AND
POINTS NORTH AND WEST, REALLY
CENTRAL MARYLAND AND THE EASTERN
SHORE THAT WILL SEE A
CENTEREDIER REIGN, 2:00 A.M., SO
FROM 11 TO 45 A.M. THEY GET
STEADY SHOWERS WE COULD SEE
NOTHING IN THE METRO.
RAPPED CLEARING WILL OCCUR
TOMORROW MORNING.
THIS IS 7:00 A.M., LINGERING
CLOUD COVER BUT THEN QUICKLY
START TO BUILD IN MORE SUNSHINE.
IT WILL TURN INTO A BRIGHT,
BEAUTIFUL LOOKING WEDNESDAY.
KIND OF COOL WITH THOSE WINDS
OUT OF THE NORTH, TEMPERATURES
WILL BE IN THE 40S TO AROUND 50
DEGREES BUT I THINK WITH DID
CLOUDS QUICKLY DISSIPATING, IT
WILL BE NICE AND SUNNY.
SO THERE'S YOUR FORECAST FOR
TOMORROW.
ANY SHOWERS THAT WE HAVE
OVERNIGHT ARE LONG GONE BY
8:00 A.M., 42 DEGREES, CHILLY
THERE WITH THE CLOUD COVER
BREAKING INTO SUNSHINE BY THE
NOON HOUR, 50 POOH FOR THAT
DAYTIME HIGH LATER ON.
THAT IS A LOOK AT TOMORROW.
WE'LL HAVE A PEEK AT THE WEEKEND
AND THE COLD AIR HEADED OUR WAY
PRECEDING THAT.
THAT'S STILL AHEAD IN YOUR FULL
SEVEN DAY.
MARINA?
>>> ALL RIGHT, WATCH THIS.
THERE SHE GOES.
SORT OF.
A BUILDING IMPLOSION IN DALLAS
DIDN'T QUITE GO AS PLANNED OVER
THE WEEKEND.
THE OUTSIDE OF THE BUILDING CAME
DOWN JUST FINE BUT IT WAS THE
INTERIOR OF THE TOWER THAT IS
STILL STANDING, AND ALTHOUGH IT
IS LEANING, IT'S LEANING
SIGNIFICANTLY SO OF COURSE THE
TOWER HAS NOW BECOME AN INTERNET
SENSATION DUBBED THE LEANING
TOWER OF DALLAS.
MULTIPLE PEOPLE HAVE POSTED ON
SOCIAL MEDIA POSING NEXT TO THE
TOWER.
CREWS DO PLAN TO KNOCK THE REST
OF IT DOWN LATER THIS WEEK.
THAT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
>> GO GET YOUR PICTURES NOW.
>>> STILL TO COME BREAKUPS ARE
NEVER EASY AND STUDIES SHOW
SOCIAL MEDIA MAKES IT EVEN
WORSE.
WE TALK ABOUT THAT COMING UP.
>> FOR SURE.
>>> HERE'S A LIVE LOOK AT THE
BELTWAY ALONG THE AMERICAN
LEGION BRIDGE THERE.
TRAFFIC AS USUAL.
IT IS TUESDAY, MY FRIENDS.
ALL RIGHT.
STAY WITH US, FIVE AT 4:00 WILL
BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
Can my side be firm?
And my side super soft?
Yes. With the Sleep Number 360
smart bed, on sale now,
you can both adjust your comfort
with your sleep number setting.
Can it help me
fall asleep faster?
Yes, by gently
warming your feet.
But can it help
keep me asleep?
Absolutely, it intelligently
senses your movements and
automatically adjusts to
keep you both comfortable.
So, you can really
promise better sleep?
Not promise... Prove.
Don't miss the final days of the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event,
Save 50% on the Sleep Number
360 Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus 0% interest for 24 months
on all smart beds. Ends Sunday.
>>> TIME FOR A LOOK AT WHAT'S
TRENDING, CAITLIN ROTH JOINING
US FOR THESE.
FIRST UP THE GROCERY STORE
DEBATE.
NEW RESEARCH SAYS A LOTS OF
GENERIC ARE AS GOOD AS NAME
BRONZE.
CONSUMER COMPARED PRICES AND
FOUND IT CAN REDUCE YOUR BILL BY
30%.
THE COMPANY ALSO TASTE TESTED
NEARLY 60 STORE BRAND FOODS AND
FOUND ALMOST HALF WERE AS GOOD
AS THEIR NAME BRAND ARRIVALS.
THE MOST POPULAR INCLUDING
FROZEN FOODS, MILK, JUICE, OVER
THE COUNTER PAIN RELIEVERS AND
CLEANING PRODUCTS.
>> THAT'S INTERESTING.
I'M PRETTY FRUGAL WHEN IT COMES
TO THAT STUFF.
>> THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS.
INTERESTING CLEANING PRODUCTS
BECAUSE I FIND THAT'S THE ONE
THING I NOTICE THE DIFFERENCE.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO DETERGENT I
BUY NAME BRANDS.
I THINK THE COMMERCIALS CONVINCE
ME I NEED IT.
>> I GET THAT IT IS ECONOMICAL
AND ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY SAY
COMPARES TO KLEENEX, WHATEVER,
YOU'RE LIKE, OKAY, THEY MIGHT BE
RIGHT.
>> ESPECIALLY WITH GENERIC.
IBUPROFEN YOU'RE SAVING LIKE
$10, MIGHT AS WELL.
>> SOME ARE BIG SAVINGS.
>> AND THE MEDICINE'S AT LEAST
REGULATED WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
>> YEAH, ALLEGEDLY.
>> YOU KNOW YOU SHOULD BE
GETTING WHAT THEY SAY.
>> MOVING ON TO RESEARCHERS AT
THE UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO WHICH
SAY MODERN BREAKUPS ARE MORE
DIFFICULTY THAN EVER.
THEY STUDIED PEOPLE UNDERGOING
UPSETTING BREAKUPS IN THE LAST
18 MONTHS THEY FOUND IT
DIFFICULT TO ESCAPE PEOPLE WHEN
YOU UNFRIEND THEM BECAUSE OTHER
FRIENDS CONTINUE PASSING ON
SHARED MEMORIES.
RESEARCHERS SUGGEST SOCIAL MEDIA
DESIGNERS NEED TO CREATE MORE
EFFECTIVE WAYS TO HELP USERS
HIDE OLD PAINFUL POSTS THEY'D
RATHER NOT SEE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE SOLUTION IS?
DON'T POST IT.
>> RIGHT, DON'T OVER-SHARE ON
SOCIAL MEDIA TO BEGIN WITH THAT
YOU HAVE ALL THESE POSTS COMING
OUT.
>> IF YOU DON'T PUT IT OUT THERE
IT'S NOT COMING BACK.
>> IT'S INTERESTING TO SEE THAT
AS A BLOW BACK.
SOCIAL MEDIA HAS RAMPED UP THAT
PEOPLE PUT THEIR WHOLE LIVES OUT
THERE BUT WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
BREAK UP.
>> WE JUST WENT THROUGH
VALENTINE'S DAY.
EVERYBODY WAS POSTED THEIR LOVEY
DOVEY FACEBOOK POSTS.
>> HOW LONG WILL THEY LAST.
>> ALL THE LIFE MOMENTS LIKE
GETTING MARRIED AND HAVING KIDS,
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU GET
DIVORCED.
THESE ARE LIKE, IT'S ALL STILL
OUT THERE, EVERYTHING YOU PUT ON
LIVE WILL LIVE FOREVER IF YOU
WANT IT TO.
>> THAT'S LIKE THE OLD SLEDDING
PICTURES, DO YOU SLED THEM OR
KEEP SOME.
>> UNTIL THEY'RE MARRIED INTO
THE FAMILY YOU KEEP THEM ON THE
EDGE OF THE FAMILY, SO YOU CAN
CARVE THEM OUT.
>> USED TO BE DIGITALLY.
>> BREAK SOUNDS LIKE AN EXPERT.
>> I'M NOT A RELATIONSHIP EXPERT
BUT I'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT OF
BREAKUPS.
>>> THE DOUBLE MURDER IN
FAUQUIER COUNTY, THE SUSPECT'S
FATHER IS MAKING HIS FIRST
PUBLIC COMMENTS SINCE THIS
HAPPENED.
WE'LL HAVE THAT COMING UP.
♪
♪♪
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
Looking around here I see
tablets, laptops,
printers, smartphones.
They're all connected
to the internet.
They're all connected.
Can your network handle
all those devices?
Sometimes.
Comcast Business
runs on the nation's
largest Gig-speed network.
So you can get the
bandwidth you need
to power all of your devices
at peak performance.
If all of my devices could
have that kind of speed,
I would be dancing!
Get fast, reliable
Internet and Voice
for just $99.99
per month.
Act now and get a
speed upgrade
for one year
at no additional
charge.
Call Today.
>>> HERE'S A LOOK AT SOME OF THE
TOP STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING.
FIRST UP, A WORKING SMOKE
DETECTOR COULD HAVE SAVED THE
LIFE OF AN ELDERLY WOMAN IN THE
DISTRICT.
FLAMES BROKE OUT THIS MORNING IN
THE 4800 BLOCK OF TENTH STREET
NORTHEAST.
FIRE FIGHTERS RESCUED THE WOMAN
FROM THE SECOND STORY OF A
DUPLEX.
SHE LATER DIED AT THE HOSPITAL.
NO WORD YET ON A CAUSE FOR THIS
FIRE.
.
>> THOSE WERE GUNSHOTS THAT KICK
STARTED A VANDALISM VEHICLES IN
SILVER SPRING.
EIGHT CARS SHOT ALONG EATON
ROAD, SAY BROOK AVENUE AND WIRE
AVENUE ON FEBRUARY 8TH AND 12TH.
DETECTIVES HOPING SOMEONE
RECOGNIZES THAT CAR INVOLVED IN
THOSE SHOOTINGS.
THEY SAY NO ONE WAS INJURED.
>>> AND FEDERATED CHARITIES IS
SEEKING HELP TO REPAIR ITS DOG
STATUE.
THE STATUE OF CHARITY THE DOG
STANDS AT THE BUILDING ON MARKET
STREET IN DOWNTOWN FREDERICK.
FOR NOW THE DOG IS WEARING
TEMPORARY BOOTIES TO COVER THE
RUST ON ITS FEET.
REPAIRING THEM WILL PROBABLY
COST THE NONPROFIT $12,000.
THEY SET UP A GoFundMe FOR
DONATIONS AND RAISED ABOUT A
THOUSAND DOLLARS SO FAR.
>> EXPENSIVE.
>>> THE FATHER OF THE FAUQUIER
COUNTY TEEN-AGER ACCUSED OF
MURDERING HIS MOTHER AND BROTHER
WRITING HIS FIRST PUBLIC
COMMENTS WRITING JOSH NORWOOD
REVEALED THE MINUTE HE ARRIVED
AT THAT TIME MIDLAND VIRGINIA
HOME THEY SHARED LAST FRIDAY.
FOX5'S PAUL WAGNER HAS BEEN
EXAMINING THOSE COMMENTS AND
JOINS US LIVE FROM THE NEWS ROOM
WITH THOSE DETAILS.
PAUL?
>> Reporter: HEY MARINA.
JOSH NORWOOD SAYS EVERY PIECE OF
HIS HEART AND SOUL DIED FRIDAY
NIGHT AFTER FINDING HIS WIFE AND
SIX YEAR OLD SON DEAD INSIDE
THEIR HOUSE.
IN A POST WRITTEN ON THE WEB
SITE'S COMMENTS SECTION, NORWOOD
SAYS HE ARRIVED HOME WITH HIS
FLOWERS FOR HIS WIFE AND GIFTS
FOR HIS TWO BOYS WHEN HE WAS
SUDDENLY SHOT.
FIRST WE WANT YOU TO LISTEN TO
WHAT THE FAUQUIER COUNTY
DISPATCHER TELLS DEPUTIES
RUSHING TO THE SCENE.
TAKE A LISTEN.
.
>> Reporter: JOSH NORWOOD THEN
WRITES, I OPENED MY DOOR, AND
BEFORE MY WORK BAG HIT THE
FLOOR, I WAS SHOT IN THE HEAD.
NOT REALIZING WHAT HAPPENED
UNTIL I SAW BLOOD POURING OUT.
I THEN SEARCHED FOR MY FAMILY
AND FOUND JEN AND WYATT DEAD.
THE MURDERER I CALLED A SON
UNTIL THAT ACT MUST HAVE RAN
ONCE HE HEARD ME YELL AS HE KNEW
HIS AMBUSH SHOT FAILED.
FAUQUIER COUNTY INVESTIGATORS
SAY LEVI NORWOOD POSSIBLY ARMED
WITH A NINE MILLIMETER PISTOL
KILLED HIS MOTHER AND BROTHER
BEFORE SHOOTING HIS FATHER AND
RUNNING FROM THE HOUSE.
INVESTIGATORS SAY.
HE THEN WALKED TEN MILES BEFORE
STEALING A TOYOTA CAMRY THAT HAD
THE KEYS INSIDE AND A FULL TANK
OF GAS.
THE 17 YEAR OLD WAS ARRESTED THE
NEXT DAY AT A TARGET STORE IN
DURHAM NORTH CAROLINA WHERE
POLICE SAY HE WAS ATTEMPTING TO
SHOP LIFT HAIR DIANE OTHER
ITEMS.
HE'S WAVED HIS RIGHT TO AN
EXTRADITION AND IS BACK, SHOULD
BE BACK IN VIRGINIA SOMETIME
THIS WEEK.
THE MOTIVE IS STILL UNCLEAR BUT
WRITING ALSO ON FAUQUIER NOW
NORWOOD ADDRESSED ANOTHER CLAIM
THAT LEVI NORWOOD MAY HAVE MADE
THREATS AT THE HIGH SCHOOL HE
ATTENDED.
NO.
THE MURDERER THAT WAS ONCE MY
SON WAS NOT INVESTIGATED FOR
THREATS.
HE WAS NOT KNOWN AS A TROUBLE
MAKER AND NO RED FLAGS FOR US AS
PARENTS TO KNOW OTHERWISE THIS
COULD HAVE BEEN PREVENTED.
HE WENT ON TO SAY JEN WAS AN
AMAZING WIFE AND MOTHER WHO
LOVED HER BOYS MORE THAN
ANYTHING.
AND WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR THEM
TO HELP THEM AND PROTECT THEM.
NOW, A SPOKESPERSON FOR THE
FAUQUIER COUNTY SHERIFF'S OFFICE
SAYS THEY HAVE NO INFORMATION
LEVI NORWOOD WAS EVER
INVESTIGATED FOR MAKING THREATS
AT THE SCHOOL WHERE HE ATTENDED,
AND THEY ARE CONTINUING TO
INVESTIGATE THE MOTIVE.
DETECTIVES HAVE SO FAR BEEN
UNABLE TO QUESTION LEVI NORWOOD
BECAUSE OF STATE RULES REGARDING
JUVENILES IN NORTH CAROLINA.
ONE OTHER NOTE.
NORWOOD WRITES, ALSO, THAT A
SERVICE WILL BE HELD FOR HIS
WIFE AND SON THIS COMING SUNDAY.
WE'RE NOW TRYING TO CONFIRM
THAT.
BACK TO YOU UPSTAIRS.
>> SUCH A SAD AND BIZARRE CASE,
PAUL WAGNER REPORTING.
>>> STILL TO COME HOW A LOCAL
AUCTION FEATURING DC SPORTS
MEMORABILIA HELPING HONOR KOBE
BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER.
>> PLUS RUMOR HAS IT NEW ADELE
MUSIC IS ON THE WAY.
WHAT ADELE HERSELF IS SAYING
ABOUT IT.
>> FINALLY.
>> MARCH MARINA'S BEEN TALKING
ABOUT THIS SINCE THE HOLIDAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HEAR FROM HER
HERSELF.
BEFORE WE GO A LIVE LOOK ALONG
95 IN ALEXANDRIA, THINGS THERE
LOOK PRETTY GOOD BEFORE THE RAIN
COMES IN ON THIS TUESDAY
AFTERNOON.
STAY WITH US.
♪
When we were looking
for a roommate,
he wanted someone super quiet.
Yeah, and he wanted someone
to help out with chores.
So, we got Jean-Pierre.
But one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with renters insurance.
♪♪
Yeah, GEICO did make it easy
to switch and save.
♪♪
Oh no. There's a wall there now.
That's too bad.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy
saving on renters insurance
can be.
Here's one you guys will like.
Show me Making It.
Oh! I got one.
The Best of Amy Poehler.
Amy, maybe we could
use the Voice Remote
to search for something
that you're not in.
Show me Parks and Rec.
From Netflix to
Prime Video to live TV,
Xfinity lets you
find your favorites
with the Emmy award-winning
X1 Voice Remote.
Show me The Best of
Amy Poehler, again.
This time around...
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
for $79.99 a month
for two years.
Plus, for a limited time,
get $100 pre-paid card.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
♪
>> STUDENTS FROM AROUND THE
WORLD ARE USING THEIR MINDS TO
TRY TO SOLVE SOCIETY'S MOST
IMPORTANT ISSUES.
THEY GATHERED AT THE 28TH ANNUAL
FUTURE CITY COMPETITION IN
NORTHWEST DC.
THIS YEAR THE TWO-DAY
COMPETITION CHALLENGED THE
MIDDLE SCHOOL AGE KIDS TO DESIGN
CITIES THAT COMBAT A WATER
CRISIS FOLLOWING A NATURAL
DISASTER.
SOME LOCAL STUDENTS FROM RESTON
VIRGINIA WERE AMONG THE
COMPETITORS.
>> THESE TEAMS HAVE BEEN WORKING
SINCE AUGUST OR SEPTEMBER WHEN
THEY WENT BACK TO SCHOOL OR
THEIR AFTER SCHOOL PROGRAMS AND
COMPETE FIVE DELIVERABLES
RANGING FROM A VIRTUAL CITY
SLIDE SHOW SHORT IS A THE MODELS
PRESENTATIONS AND A PROJECT
PLAN.
>> A TEAM FROM INDIANA WON
$7,500 FOR THE TEAM'S STEM
PROGRAM AND A TRIP TO U.S. SPACE
CAMP IN HUNTSVILLE, ALABAMA.
>>> MONUMENTAL SPORTS ARE
HONORING THE LATE KOBE BRYANT
AND HIS DAUGHTER GIANNA WITH A
SPECIAL AUCTION FEATURING
CAPITALS AND WIZARDS
MEMORABILIA.
>> OUR GREER MCGRADY AT CAPITAL
ONE ARENA WHERE THE AUCTION IS
NOW UNDERWAY.
HEY, GARY.
>> Reporter: YES, WE ARE
DEFINITELY IN AN EMPTY HOUSE, NO
DOUBT, WITH OUR LITTLE TABLE BUT
OUR LITTLE TABLE HAS A LOT TO
OFFER HERE.
THIS IS VERY, VERY UNIQUE WHAT
IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO BRING IN LIZ PACE A
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER OF MONUMENTAL
SPORTS.
THANKS FOR HAVING US OUT.
LISTEN THIS IS A GREAT THING BUT
YOU HAVE TO TELL US ABOUT IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
>> WE HAVE AN AUCTION UP RIGHT
NOW.
>> Reporter: ON LINE.
>> ON LINE AUCTION, ANYONE CAN
BID.
IT'S OPEN FOR THE PUBLIC AT HAND
BID.COM AND WE'RE AUCTIONING OFF
THESE JERSEYS THAT ALEXANDER
OVECHKIN AND WIZARDS PLAYER JOHN
WALL, BRADLEY BEAL, LOUIE WORE
AT THE END OF JANUARY IN HONOR
OF KOBE BRYANT.
>> THEY WORE THEM IN WARMUPS BUT
THAT'S STILL PRETTY COOL.
AND I WANT TO SAY, TOO, THIS WAS
OBI'S IDEA WASN'T IT?  ANOTHER
GREAT OBI IDEA.
>> THIS WAS SOMETHING OBI
DECIDED HE WANTED TO HONOR KOBE
SO HE GOT THIS JERSEY MADE, WORE
IT ON THE 29TH IN THE GAME
AGAINST NASHVILLE.
WE FOUND OUT THE WIZARDS WERE
WEARING JERSEYS THE NEXT NIGHT
AT THEIR GAME ON THE 30TH.
SO WE TOLD THEM THEY WANTED TO
DO THIS AUCTION AND THEY WERE
ALL IN.
THEY WERE SO EXCITED TO HONOR
KOBE, TO REMEMBER HIM IN A
SPECIAL WAY AND HELP RAISE MONEY
FOR CHARITIES THAT WERE
IMPORTANT TO HIM.
>> Reporter: SO AN ON LINE
AUCTION, SO YOU CAN REAL QUICKLY
GIVE US THE ADDRESS, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE IT UP HERE, TOO, TO KIND
OF SHOW, BUT THE YOU CANS A IS
LIVE RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU GO TO THIS AND THEN
HOW LONG DO WE HAVE TO BID.
>> WE'VE ALREADY RAISED CLOSE TO
$6,000.
>> Reporter: WOW.
>> SO HOPEFULLY WE KEEP GETTING
THAT NUMBER UP, IT'S AT HAND
BID.COM.
SEARCH FOR MONUMENTAL AND OUR
AUCTION WILL POP UP.
IT'S OPEN UNTIL SUNDAY
AFTERNOON.
IT WILL CLOSE AT THE END OF THE
SECOND INTERMISSION DURING THE
CAPS GAME AGAINST THE PENGUINS.
>> Reporter: LIZ WAS GREAT
ENOUGH TO BRING THIS OUT RIGHT
HERE.
THERE IS MORE MEMORABILIA AND
WE'LL REVEAL THIS REST OF IT,
NOT THE REST BUT A LOT MORE.
LIZ IS GOING TO BE ON TOMORROW
MORNING ON GOOD DAY DC DURING
THE 10:00 O'CLOCK HOUR, AND
YOU'RE GOING TO BRING LIKE A
WHOLE CAR LOAD OF STUFF AREN'T
YOU.
>> YEAH, I'M GROWING TO BRING A
WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF.
VIEWERS ARE GOING TO LOVE IT.
IT'S REALLY COOL.
ALL THE PROCEEDS GO TO THE MAMBA
AND MAMBA SEAT A SPORTS
FOUNDATION ALONG WITH THE MAMBA
ON THREE FUND.
SO GREAT CAUSES AND WE REALLY
WANT YOU TO BE ABLE TO TAKE
THESE HOME.
>> Reporter: ABSOLUTELY.
THANKS FOR HAVING US OUT, LIZ.
GREAT AUCTION FOR A GREAT CAUSE.
I'LL SEND IT BACK TO YOU GUYS IN
THE STUDIO.
THANKS LIZ, APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE WILL RAISE A LOT OF MONEY
FOR THAT BIG MEMORIAL NEXT
MONDAY.
>> YEAH.
>>> STILL TO COME, TAYLOR
SWIFT'S DAD FORCED TO FIGHT OFF
A BURGLAR INSIDE HIS OWN HOME.
HOW THIS ALL PLAYED OUT.
>> PLUS IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A
SWEET TRIBUTE TO HIS SON BUT
DIDN'T TURN OUT HOW IT PLANNED.
WHY ACTOR ORLANDO BLOOM IS
LIKELY REGRETTING.
>> IF YOU DO SOMETHING IN A
DIFFERENT LANGUAGE OR SYMBOLS
YOU'RE USED TO USING HAVE
SOMEONE FACT CHECK IT FIRST.
>> THE QUESTION IS WHAT DOES IT
SAY.
>> GUYS THERE'S SO MUCH REGRET
THAT CAN COME WITH A TATTOO AND
THEN YOU START GETTING INTO
DIFFERENT LANGUAGES.
>> RIGHT, YOU WANT A MANDARIN
TATTOO, MY HEART WOULD BE
BEATING OUT OF MY CHEST THAT I
DID IT RIGHT.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO FACT CHECK
ANYTHING IN LIFE, RIGHT?  LIKE
ANYTHING.
>> THAT'S THE ONE THING.
>> MAYBE DO THE THING THAT IS
THE MOST PERMANENT SECOND TO
KIDS OR EVEN MAYBE MORE SO
TATTOOS.
THAT'S COMING UP AS WELL AS YOUR
FULL SEVEN-DAY FORECAST.
A FEW SHOWERS TONIGHT, ANOTHER
COLD BLAST ON THE WAY TO END THE
WEEK.
THAT'S AHEAD.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
♪
AFTER THIS.
♪♪
Here's one you guys will like.
Show me Making It.
Oh! I got one.
The Best of Amy Poehler.
Amy, maybe we could
use the Voice Remote
to search for something
that you're not in.
Show me Parks and Rec.
From Netflix to
Prime Video to live TV,
Xfinity lets you
find your favorites
with the Emmy award-winning
X1 Voice Remote.
Show me The Best of
Amy Poehler, again.
This time around...
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get this great
offer from Xfinity.
You'll get double the speed
and save over $250
compared to Fios.
Plus, get $100 back.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
I WORK HARD AND I WANT MY
MONEY TO WORK HARD TOO.
SO I USE MY FREEDOM
UNLIMITED CARD.
EVEN WHEN I'M SPENDING,
I'M EARNING 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING I BUY.
EARNING ON MY FAVORITE SOUP...
GOT IT.
EARNING ON THAT ECLAIR.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT YET.
LET ME GET THE BIG ONE.
NOPE.
THIS ONE?
NO.
LET ME GET THEM ALL.
I'M GONNA GET THEM ALL.
IT'S JUST THE BASICS.
CAN YOU DOUBLE BAG
THIS RIGHT HERE?
EARN 1.5% CASH BACK
ON EVERYTHING YOU BUY
WITH FREEDOM UNLIMITED.
CAN YOU ALSO TELL ME WHAT IT IS?
CHASE.
MAKE MORE OF WHAT'S YOURS.
>>> YOU MIGHT THINK ABOUT A JOB
CHANGE WITH A NEW LIST THAT'S
OUT.
>> SARAH SIMMONS HAS MORE ON
THAT AND WHAT ELSE IS COMING UP
IN THE NEXT HOUR.
HEY SARAH.
>> COMING UP AT 5:00 SEVERAL
LOCAL COMPANIES JUST MADE
FORTUNE'S 100 BEST COMPANIES TO
WORK FOR LIST, ONE IS RANKED AT
THE VERY TOP.
WE'LL HAVE THAT.
PLUS MIKE BLOOMBERG REPORTEDLY
CONSIDERING A LOCAL LAWMAKER AS
A POSSIBLE RUNNING MEAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND OUT WHY.
AND TRENDING TONIGHT, IMAGINE
SITTING NEXT TO THIS IN FIRST
CLASS.
WE ARE HEARING FROM THE WOMAN
WHO BROUGHT A SERVICE HORSE ONTO
A FLIGHT, AND WHAT SHE WANTS
FROM THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
THAT'S NEXT AT 5:00.
>> AND I DON'T THINK THEY GIVE
YOU AN EXTRA SEAT EVEN AT FIRST
CLASS, SO THIS IS JUST SHARING
THE SPACE.
>> I GUESS AT HER FEET.
>> DOES THE PONY GET TO RECLINE?
THAT'S THE BIG QUESTION.
>> THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY WANTS
TO KNOW.
>> THAT'S LAST WEEK'S ARGUMENT.
THIS IS THIS WEEK'S ARGUMENT.
>>> TAYLOR SWIFT'S FATHER FOUGHT
OFF A BURGLAR INSIDE HIS
$4 MILLION PENT HOW IN SAINT
PETERSBURG FLORIDA IN JANUARY.
ACCORDING TO THE TAMPA BAY TIMES
THE SUSPECT 30 YEAR OLD TERRANCE
HOVER USED EMERGENCY ESCAPE
STARES TO CLIMB UP 13 FLOORS AND
BREAK INTO SCOTT SWIFT'S HOME.
SWIFT REPORTEDLY CAME HOME AND
SAW HOOVER BROWSING THROUGH
STUFF.
THEY FOUGHT BRIEFLY BEFORE
HOOVER RAN OFF.
SWIFT LATER PICKED HOOVER OUT OF
A PHOTO LINEUP AND POLICE
ARRESTED HIM ON MONDAY.pI DO WA
A SERIOUS STORY, BUT IT'S SWIFT
AND HOOVER.
♪
SPEAKING OF TAYLOR SWIFT SHE
JUST RELEASED A MUSIC VIDEO FOR
HER SONG THE MAN.
IT WAS CREATED FROM HER LIVE
PERFORMANCE OF A SONG DURING A
CONCERT IN PARIS LAST SEPTEMBER.
IN IT SHE PLAYS ACOUSTIC GUITAR
AND THE AUDIENCE SINGS ALONG TO
THE WORDS.
IT IS THE FOURTH SINGLE FROM HER
LOVER ALBUM.
>>> MEANTIME, ADELE ANNOUNCING
WAY DURING A FRIEND'S WEDDING
WHICH SHE OFFICIATED OVER THE
WEEKEND.
ADELE TOLD GUESTS TO EXPECT HER
NEXT ALBUM IN SEPTEMBER.
RUMORS ABOUT NEW MUSIC HAVE BEEN
CIRCULATING OVER THE PAST
SEVERAL MONTHS AND JUST LAST
MONTH HER MANAGER SAID A
FOLLOW-UP TO HER LAST ALBUM MAY
BE COMING SOONER THAN WE THINK.
AND SHE JUST RECENTLY GOT
DIVORCED AND SHE WRITES A LOT OF
HER OWN MUSIC SO A LOT OF
MATERIAL THERE.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT STORIES FOR MARINA IN
THE NEWSCAST TODAY.
SHE'S LIKE, HAVE YOU SEEN THE
VIDEO.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR IT ON
LINE.
>>> HEALTH PROBLEMS HAS FORCED
OZZY OSBOURNE TO CANCEL HIS
NORTH AMERICAN TOUR.
HE HAD SURGERY LAST YEAR AND
LAST MONTH ANNOUNCED DIAGNOSED
WITH PARKINSON'S DISEASE.
HE SAID HE'S UNDERGOING
TREATMENT IN SWITZERLAND.
THE TOUR WAS SCHEDULED TO START
IN MAY BUT HE SAID HE DIDN'T
WANT TO HAVE TO START A TOUR AND
HAVE TO CANCEL AT THE LAST
MINUTE.
HE HAS A NEW ALBUM COMING OUT
FRIDAY AND SAYS HE WILL
RESCHEDULE WHEN HE'S HEALTHY.
ORIGINALLY THEY MOVED IT BACK
AND NOW HE'S CANCELLED.
>> WISH HIM THE BEST BUT CAN'T
BELIEF HE'S STILL TOURING,
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
>>> ORLANDO BLOOM'S HEART IN THE
RIGHT PLAYS WHEN HE GOT A NEW
TATTOO IN HONOR OF HIS SON
FLYNN.
ONE ISSUE, HIS NAME APPARENTLY
MISSPELLED.
SHOWING OFF HIS NEW INK CAN YOU
GUESS WHO?  IT IS IN MORRIS CODE
AND SUPPOSED TO SAY FLYNN BUT
SAID FREN.
TWO POSTED SAYING IT'S JUST A
MINOR ERROR AND CAN BE FIXED.
>> I NEVER HEARD OF MORES CODE
TATTOOS IS THAT THE NEW TREND
WE'LL BE WATCHING OUT FOR?
>> YEAH.
NOT PUTTING ONE ON MYSELF
ANYTIME SOON, SO.
>> JUST DO IT IN ENGLISH AND
YOU'LL BE FINE.
>> I'M GOING TO WRITE BLAKE.
>>> LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AT THE
U.S. CAPITOL.
PRETTY DREARY OUT THERE ALTHOUGH
IT WAS PRETTY NICE EARLIER TODAY
CONSIDERING THE TEMPERATURES.
> THE CLOUDS HAVE MOVED IN
QUITE QUICKLY CAITLIN.
>> THEY HAVE.
WE HAVE A COUPLE SHOWERS OUT
THERE BUT NOT A BIG DEAL.
WE ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT A LOT
OF RAIN.
IF YOU ARE HEADING OUT TONIGHT
WOULDN'T HURT TO HAVE A RAIN
COAT OREM BRAILLE, SOUTH AND
EAST WE'LL HAVE STEADIER SHOWERS
DURING THE OVERNIGHT HOURS BUT
HONESTLY WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
A LOT OF RAIN JUST A FEW SHOWERS
THROUGHOUT THE EVENING HOURS AND
THEN WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK TO DRY
QUIET CONDITIONS.
SO WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW GOING
FORWARD.
THOSE SHOWERS WILL BE AROUND
TONIGHT, AND THEN FOLLOWING
THAT, WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK TO
SOME DRY CONDITIONS TOMORROW.
SUN COMES OUT, LOOKS LIKE A MUCH
NICER DAY AND THEN ANOTHER COLD
BLAST COMING.
THAT IS GOING TO ARRIV ON
THURSDAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURES TODAY, LET'S
TAKE A LOOK AT THEM.
59 AT REAGAN, 60 AT DULLES AND
62 AT BWI.
WOW, THAT'S REALLY REALLY NICE.
IT WAS AMAZING WHAT THAT
SUNSHINE DID, REALLY WARMED
THINGS UP.
56 OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW, WE'RE
LOOKING AT 54 IN ANNAPOLIS, 58
IN MANASSAS, 59 AT DULLES, 55 IN
WINCHESTER AND 58 IN CULPEPER.
REGIONALLY THERE IS COLD AIR OUT
THERE BACK ACROSS THE MOUNTAINS
PROPER YOU REMEMBER IN
CINCINNATI, 38 IN DETROIT, 37 IN
CHICAGO.
pSO IT'S SPILLING SOUTHWARD
ACROSS THE CANADIAN PRAIRIES
INTO THE NORTHERN PLAINS.
THAT'S WHERE THE REAL COLD IS.
YOU SEE EIGHT IN FARGO, 20 IN
MINNEAPOLIS, LINCOLN, THE
BEGINNINGS OF ANOTHER ARCTIC
HIGH PRESSURE SYSTEM WHICH WILL
EVENTUALLY REACH US.
SATELLITE RADAR YOU HAVE SHOWERS
OUTSIDE, KIND OF BROKEN LINE OF
THEM MOVING ACROSS THE MID SOUTH
AND THE MID ATLANTIC.
LOCALLY, AS WE ZOOM IN ON RADAR,
IT'S REALLY JUST DRIBS AND
DRABS, NOTHING REALLY OVER THE
METRO RIGHT NOW.
A LITTLE BIT OF LIGHT RAIN BY
THE MASON DIXON LINE A LITTLE TO
THE SOUTH ZOOMING IN YOU CAN'T
REALLY SEE MUCH.
PLANNING FORECAST FOR TONIGHT
MOSTLY A CLOUDY ONE, BETTER
CHANCE OF SOME SHOWERS LATER
THIS EVENING BETWEEN 9:00 AND
11:00 P.M. AND MOST WILL BE
SOUTH AND EAST OF DC.
TEMPERATURES IN THE 50S.
IT WILL GET KIND OF CHILLY LATE
TONIGHT.
WE'LL FALL BACK TO 42 IN THE
DISTRICT, EVEN 30S NORTH AND
WEST.
REMEMBER, NORTH AND WEST OF US
THEY'RE NOT GETTING THE RAIN.
THEY'RE GOING TO SEE SOME
CLEARING.
SO IT WILL BE COLD TO START THE
DAY TOMORROW.
SOUTH AND EAST OF US YOU HAVE
MORE CLOUDS AND SHOWERS,
TEMPERATURES WILL STAY IN THE
40S.
WE'LL HIT PROBABLY A HIGH
TEMPERATURE AROUND 50 BRIEFLY
TOMORROW KIND OF TURNING INTO A
NICE, CRISP AFTERNOON.
I MENTIONED ANOTHER ARCTIC
BLAST.
THAT IS COLD AIR COMING IN FROM
THE NORTH.
WE EXPECT HIGH PRESSURE WILL
BRING SOME SUNSHINE TOMORROW.
AND THEN TENS AND 20S FOR LOWS,
30S FOR HIGHS.
A LOT LIKE LAST FRIDAY AND
SATURDAY, IT WILL BE COLD BUT A
BRIEF COLD SNAP.
TEMPERATURES HEADING DOWNWARD,
50 TOMORROW, 41 ON THURSDAY, 39
ON FRIDAY, 50, THOUGH, ON
SATURDAY.
SO, AGAIN, THIS ARCTIC BLAST NOT
THAT CRAZY COLD AND ALSO VERY
SHORT LIVED.
WINTER'S JUST COME IN VERY SMALL
DOSES THIS YEAR.
CHECK OUT THE EURO, CLOUDIER ON
THURSDAY AS THE SYSTEM STAYS TO
OUR SOUTH BRINGING RAIN AND SNOW
SHOWERS BUT THIS SHOULD STAY
JUST FAR SOUTH ENOUGH TO HAVE
VERY LITTLE IMPACT ON US MEANING
NO PRECIPITATION.
THERE'S YOUR SEVEN DAY BECOMING
SUNNY TOMORROW AFTERNOON, 50.
41 WITH MORE CLOUD COVER
THURSDAY, BRIGHT SUNSHINE, 39 ON
FRIDAY.
BEAUTIFUL WEEKEND.
THAT LOOKS GREAT ALREADY.
50S AND SUNSHINE AS WE LOOK
AHEAD.
THAT IS YOUR SEVEN DAY.
BLAKE, BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> CAITLIN, STILL TO COME, A
MARYLAND WAL-MART EMPLOYEE IS
TAKING SOCIAL MEDIA BY STORM AND
PEOPLE ARE HEADING TO THE STORE
JUST TO MEET HER.
WE'LL SHOW YOU WHY COMING UP.
>> I LIKE HER ALREADY.
♪
KE HER ALREADY.
♪♪
We made USAA Insurance for
members like Martin.
An Air Force veteran made of
doing what's right,
not what's easy.
So when a hailstorm hit, USAA
reached out
before he could even inspect the
damage.
That's how you do it right.
USAA insurance is made just the
way Martin's family needs it -
with hassle-free claims, he got
paid before
his neighbor even got started.
Because doing right by our
members, that's what's right.
USAA. What you're made of, we're
made for.
USAA
.
>>> ANOTHER QUICK LOOK AT THE
INSTAPOLL, WOULD YOU TRAVEL INTO
SPACE IF MONEY WAS NO OBJECT?
OK, SEEMS LIKE MORE PEOPLE
LEANING TOWARDS KNOW.
>> UNLESS IT'S AN ESCAPE CAN
CAPSULE BECAUSE THE EARTH IS THE
LAST DAY.
>> YOU STILL THINK ABOUT THE
MONEY, BUT STILL GIVE OTHER
PEOPLE.
>> MONEY IS AN OBJECT.
>> YES, THIS IS TRUE.
>>> FOX 5 NEWS WHERE YOU CAN
VOTE ON OUR FOX 5 DC WEBSITE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND UNINVITED GUEST INVADED A
SOCCER MID MATCH.
THIS HAPPENED IN IN STAND BUG.
HE TRIED TO HOLD ON TO IT.
THE DOG CHASED IT.
BUT THEN RETURNED JUST AS PLAY
RESUMED.
>> HE'S LIKE WAIT, I'M SUPPOSED
TO FETCH.
RIGHT.
>> YOU'VE BEEN TEACHING THIS MAY
WHOLE LIFE.
SHOW ENDED WHEN ONE OF THE
PLAYERS WAS ABLE TO GET HIS ARMS
AROUND THE DOG.
>> THE DOG IS PRETTY GOOD TOO,
BY THE WAY.
SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
>>> SPEAK OF SOCCER, AN IRISH
STRIKER THOUGHT HE HAD SCORED
THE GOAL.
HE'S COMING UP.
HERE GOES.
NOT KWIECHLT APPARENTLY BOUGHT
GOT STUCK IN THE MUD RIGHT
BEFORE IT CROSSED THE GOAL LINE.
HE'S CONVINCED HE GOT IT.
LUCKILY HIS TEAM MATE WAS THERE
AND PUT IT INTO THE BACK OF THE
NET.
THE TEAM HAD A LAUGH AFTERWARDS
BUT YOU GOT TO WAIT.
FOLLOW THROUGH.
NOT QUITE.
>>> THIS MARYLAND WAL-MART
EMPLOYEE IS A HUGE HIT.
HER NAME IS CHARLENE AND EACH
DAY, THE STORE SHOWCASES ITS
PRODUCT OF THE DAY.
THEY'VE BECOME SUCH A HIT,
PEOPLE ARE JUST GOING INTO THE
STORE TO TAKE A PICTURE WITH
CHARLENE.
>> SHE'S MY ALTER EGO.
I LOVE SHE'S A LOCAL CELEBRITY.
GO GET YOUR PICTURE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US AT 4:00.
>>> NEWS A THE 5:00 START NOW.
>>> AT 5:00, MARYLAND MOTHER
ACCUSED OF MURDERING WHO TWO
YOUNG CHILDREN BACK IN COURT.
>>> MANY PEOPLE DISAGREE WITH
THE SENTENCE.
THE DEMOCRATIC HE'S NOT HAD A
REPUBLICAN.
>> WHY THE PRESIDENT COMMUTED
HIS CORRUPTION SENTENCE AND THE
OTHER PARDON.
>> THIS NORTHERN VIRGINIA
COMPANY JUST FORMED A NEW
PARTNERSHIP WITH SPACE X.
IT'S A PARTNERSHIP THEY HOPE
WILL SEND YOU TO NEWER HEIGHTS.
WE'LL EXPLAIN COMING RIGHT UP.
>> NEWS STARTS NOW.
>>>  A MARYLAND HEARD HEARD A
MOTION TO DISMISS CHARGES
AGAINST CATHERINE HOGGLE.
ACCUSED OF MURDERING HERE TWO
YOUNG KIDS NEARLY SIX YEARS AGO.
STEPHANIE RAMIRIZ WAS IN THE
COURTROOM.
WHAT WAS THE DECISION THAT CAME
DOWN?
>> GUYS, THE UPDATE IS NO
DECISION TODAY, CIRCUIT COURT
JUDGE ROBERT GREENBERG, HE
CALLED THIS A MOMENTOUS
DECISION.
OF HE SAID HE'S GOING TO REVIEW
EVERYTHING ARGUED IN COURT AND
COME UP WITH A WRITTEN OPINION
WE MAY NOT SEE UNTIL LATER THIS
WEEK, OR NEXT WEEK.
BUT I CAN TELL YOU, IN THE
COURTROOM TODAY, A VERY
EMOTIONAL HEARING ON A CASE
THAT'S BEEN GOING ON AT LEAST
THE PAST FIVE YEARS WITH LITTLE