SECURITY CAMERAS.
IT'S A BIG PROBLEM AND BACK IN
THE HEADLINES THIS WEEK AFTER
THIS CHILLING VIDEO WENT
VIRAL.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND.
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT
RIGHT NOW.
>> THE STEPS YOU CAN TAKE TO
PREVENT THIS FROM HAPPENING.
A TECH EXPERT JOINS US LIVE.
CAFFEINE CRAZE.
COLA MEETS COFFEE.
THE NEW LIQUID CREATION
HITTING STORE SHELVES WITH A
BIG ENERGY BOOST.
FOX5 MORNING AT 7:00 A.M.
STARTS NOW.
>> ♪
>> 7 O'CLOCK.
GOOD MORNING IF YOU'RE JUST
WAKING UP LET'S TAKE A LIVE
LOOK ACROSS THE AREA RIGHT
NOW.
THERE YOU SEE MGM ON THE LEFT LT
AND THE RADAR MAP ON THE
RIGHT.
TEMPERATURES SOME OF THE
COLDEST WE'VE SEEN THIS
SEASON.
MIX THAT IN WITH THE RAIN AND
YES, THAT MEANS SOME FREEZING
CONDITIONS SO BE EXTRA CAREFUL
WHEN YOU HEAD OUT THE DOOR
THIS MORNING.
>> THAT'S NOT VERY
HOLIDAY-LIKE TUCKER BARNES BUT
DUE TO THIS FORECAST LOUDOUN
COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE CLOSED.
SEVERAL OTHER DISTRICTS IN THE
AREA ARE DELAYED TWO HOURS.
YOU'LL FIND A COMPLETE LIST AT
THE BOTTOM OF YOUR SCREEN ON
THE FOX5 WEATHER APP WHICH YOU
SHOULD HAVE HANDY ON YOUR
DEVICES AND ON OUR WEB SITE
FOX5DC.COM.
>> STACEY IS TRACKING THE
ROADS.
TUCKER IS ON TOP OF THE
PORNOGRAPHY.
>> FEW 100THS OF AN INCH OF
ICE AND THAT'S ALL IT TAKES.
DON'T WANT TO HIT THE SIDEWALK
AND GO FOR A SLIP.
I'LL GIVE YOU MORE DETAILS.
SEE THE PINK.
THAT'S THE POTENTIAL AREA OUT
TO THE WEST, SOUTH AND WEST AT
THIS HOUR AND EVENTUALLY NORTH
AND WEST WHERE WE CAN GET SOME
FREEZING RAIN OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE HOURS.
IT WILL TRANSITION TO RAIN FOR
MOST EVERYBODY LATER THIS
MORNING AND FOR MOST OF US IT
WILL BE JUST A RAIN EVENT.
I'LL HAVE DETAILS IN JUST A
FEW.
STACEY GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
WE HAVE A CRASH ON NORTH
CAPITOL STREET.
THIS IS IF YOU'RE HEADING
NORTHBOUND RIGHT AT NEW YORK
AVENUE.
THE TWO LEFT LANES ARE BLOCKED
RIGHT NOW.
I WILL GIVE YOU ALL THE
DETAILS AS WELL AS A COMPLETE
LOOK AT THE DMV COMING UP.
>> ♪
>> STACEY, THANKS.
7:02 RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE SOME BREAKING NEWS IN
UPPER MARLBORO MARYLAND WE'VE
BEEN SHOWING YOU THIS HOUSE
FIRE THAT HAS BEEN BURNING FOR
SEVERAL HOURS IN THE 6200
BLOCK OF CONNAUGHT COURT.
IT DOES NOT APPEAR ANYBODY WAS
INSIDE OF THAT HOME.
SO FAR NO WORD ON ANY
INJURIES.
SKYFOX OVERHEAD.
FIREFIGHTERS NOW BACK TO
PUTTING SOME WATER ON THERE
TRYING TO CONTAIN THAT BUT THE
HOME A LOSS.
>>> ALSO DEVELOPING THIS
MORNING, JUST A TRAGEDY IN
BETHESDA.
A NINE-YEAR-OLD GIRL DID IS
AFTER BEING HIT BY A SCHOOL
BUS IN HER BETHESDA
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> NOW A COMMUNITY IS IN
MOURNING.
FOX5's MELANIE ALNWICK IS
LIVE FROM THAT BETHESDA
NEIGHBORHOOD WITH THE VERY
LATEST.
JUST A TRAGEDY MEL.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: IT REALLY IS
JUST EVEN IMPOSSIBLE TO
COMPREHEND.
YOU KNOW, A GIRL GETS OFF OF
HER OWN SCHOOL BUS RIGHT HERE
AT TANGLEWOOD DRIVE.
THIS IS WHERE PEOPLE TELL US
THE BUS DRIVER ALWAYS LET'S
PEOPLE OFF PUTS OUT THE STOP
ARM.
THE PARENTS ARE USUALLY PARKED
DOWN ON TANGLEWOOD AND THE
CHILDREN ALWAYS WALK BEHIND
THE SCHOOL BUS.
SO, PEOPLE WE'VE TALKED TO
THIS MORNING ARE KIND OF
PUZZLED AS TO WHY THE GIRL WAS
CROSSING MILLWOOD ROAD HERE
WHEN THE BUS TURNED UP THE
STREET.
POLICE HAVE NOT RELEASED THE
NAME OF THE NINE-YEAR-OLD GIRL
YET AND THE PRINCIPAL OF
BRADLEY HILLS ELEMENTARY IS
ASKING THE COMMUNITY TO GIVE
HER FAMILY PRIVACY TO GRIEVE.
SCHOOL BUS NUMBER 13037
REMAINED PARKED ON MILLWOOD
ROAD MOST OF THE NIGHT AS
MONTGOMERY COUNTY
INVESTIGATORS DOCUMENTED THE
SCENE OF THE COLLISION.
THE BUS WAS CARRYING THE
STUDENTS FROM BRADLEY HILLS
ELEMENTARY AND DROPPED SEVERAL
OFF.
THE DRIVER A 53-YEAR-OLD FROM
SEVERN MARYLAND TURNED RIGHT
ONTO MILLWOOD ROAD AND FOR
REASONS STILL UNDER
INVESTIGATION STRUCK THE
FOURTH GRADER.
A NEIGHBOR THIS MORNING TOLD
US THAT HE ALWAYS SEES THE
DRIVER WATCHING CAREFULLY AS
THE STUDENTS ARE LET OFF THE
BUS.
>> I MEAN, I THINK THE BUS
DRIVER'S -- IS BEING LOOKED
LIKE A TERRIBLE PERSON BUT IT
NEVER HAPPENS.
IT'S THE OTHER CARS THAT CUT
THROUGH HERE.
IT'S A CUT THROUGH LANE:  IT
RIGHT.
>> THIS WHOLE AREA IS A CUT
THROUGH.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
>> Reporter: AND HE WAS
TALKING THERE ABOUT MILLWOOD
ROAD.
HE SAYS IS USUALLY WHERE CARS
ARE CUTTING THROUGH.
NOW, THE GIRL WAS TAKEN BY
AMBULANCE TO CHILDREN'S
NATIONAL MEDICAL CENTER.
IT WAS JUST BEFORE 4:00 P.M.
AT 8:45 LAST NIGHT MONTGOMERY
COUNTY POLICE NOTIFIED THE
COMMUNITY THAT THE GIRL DID
NOT SURVIVE HER INJURIES.
AS YOU CAN IMAGINE THERE WILL
BE EXTRA COUNSELING STAFF AT
BRADLEY HILLS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL TODAY.
CRASH INVESTIGATORS ON THE
SCENE WE WANT TO LET YOU KNOW
TOLD FOX5 THAT THE DRIVER DID
NOT APPEAR TO BE IMPAIRED.
THE DRIVER WAS NOT IMPAIRED.
BUT THE COLLISION AND THE
DETAILS OF EXACTLY WHAT
HAPPENED THAT IS STILL UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>> MEL, THANK.
7:04.
LET'S CHECK SOME OTHER TOP
STORIES.
THE SEARCH CONTINUES IN NEW
YORK CITY FOR SUSPECTS WHO
STABBED TO DEATH A COLLEGE
STUDENT FROM VIRGINIA.
TWO TEENS HAVE BEEN QUESTIONED
BUT BOTH CLEARED AS SUSPECTS.
THAT STUDENT 18-YEAR-OLD TESSA
MAJORS A FRESHMAN AT BARNARD
COLLEGE IS FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
SHE WAS WALKING IN A PARK IN
UPPER MANHATTAN WHEN SHE WAS
STABBED BY ONE OF THE THREE
SUSPECTS WHO HAD BEEN
DEMANDING MONEY.
>> A CLOSE CALL FOR TWO
VOLUNTEER POLICE OFFICERS IN
THE DISTRICT AFTER THEY WERE
SHOT WHILE -- SHOT AT I SHOULD
SAY WHILE SITTING IN A
CRUISER.
A SUSPECT IS IN CUSTODY.
POLICE SAY THE MAN WAS HIDING
IN A WOODED AREA NEAR HAWAII
AVENUE WHEN HE OPENED FIRE
JUST BEFORE 4:00 YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON.
NO WORD ON A MOTIVE.
>> ALSO IN THE DISTRICT A
WOMAN RECOVERING AFTER SHE WAS
ASSAULTED DURING A FIGHT
INVOLVING A GROUP OF TEENAGERS
ON THE METRO.
THIS HAPPENED DURING THE
EVENING RUSH HOUR AT THE
TENLEYTOWN STATION NORTHWEST
D.C.
TWO TEENAGERS WERE TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY.
>> ♪
>> 7:05.
GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
>> GOOD MORNING.
HAPPY FRIDAY.
>> HAPPY FRIDAY TO YOU.
>> YES, OKAY, LET'S REALLY
EMPHASIZE HERE MOSTLY A RAIN
EVENT FOR THE GREAT MAJORITY
OF US.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BUT WE GOT LOTS OF VIEWERS OFF
TO THE NORTH AND WEST AND IT'S
OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST
WHERE YOU CAN GET A LIGHT
GLAZE OF A FREEZING RAIN IN
THE NEXT COUPLE HOURS.
>> WHICH IS JUST ENOUGH --
>> TO CAUSE --
>> TO CAUSE CHAOS.
>> DELAYS CANCELLATIONS AND
ALL KINDS OF PROBLEMS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> MORNING FREEZING RAIN NORTH
AND WEST.
FOR THE REST OF US JUST RAIN
SHOWERS AND RAIN FOR EVERYBODY
LATER THIS AFTERNOON AND
TONIGHT AND AND THE REAL STORY
THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS
UNFORTUNATELY WILL BE MORE
GLOOMY CONDITIONS BE MORE RAIN
SHOWERS SO TAKE THE UMBRELLA
AND CERTAINLY IF YOU'RE NOT
GETTING SHOWERS EARLY THIS
MORNING, WHEN YOU'RE HEADED
HOME FROM SCHOOL, HEADED HOME
FROM WORK WE'LL HAVE SHOWERS
AROUND LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
THAT'S WASHINGTON.
THAT'S BALTIMORE.
SO 95 CORRIDOR IN THE CLEAR
HERE AS FAR AS THE ADVISORIES.
YOU GOT TO GET UP INTO LOUDOUN
COUNTY FREDERICK COUNTY, PARTS
OF FAUQUIER COUNTY AND OUT TO
THE WEST AND LISTEN, I KNOW A
LOT OF YOU ARE DEALING WITH
THIS THIS MORNING OUT TOWARDS
MARTINSBURG AND HAGERSTOWN AND
WINCHESTER AND FRONT ROYAL AND
CERTAINLY THE POTENTIAL WITH
THIS WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
IN EFFECT THROUGH 3 O'CLOCK
THIS AFTERNOON THAT YOU COULD
ENCOUNTER SOME LIGHT FREEZING
RAIN HERE AT THE ONSET OF THE
EVENT.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE SATELLITE
PICTURE AND THE RADAR IN JUST
A SECOND.
NOTICE OUR AREA OF -- I
CANNOT SAY THIS.
OUR AREA AIRPORTS ARE ABOVE
THE FREEZING MARK EARLY THIS
MORNING.
REAGAN NATIONAL AT 36 DEGREES,
35 IN BALTIMORE.
SO WE'RE GOING TO BE OKAY
HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO GET JUST RAIN
BUT YOU CAN SEE A LOT OF PINK
ON THE MAP.
IT'S ALREADY TRANSITIONING TO
GREEN WHERE IT'S FALLING, IT'S
JUST RAIN BUT THIS WILL BE
RAIN THAT WILL FREEZE ON
CONTACT OR AT LEAST
POTENTIALLY FREEZE ON CONTACT
IN POCKETS WHERE THE
TEMPERATURE REMAINS BELOW 32.
SO, AGAIN, THE NEXT COUPLE
HOURS FOR YOU GUYS OFF TO THE
NORTH AND WEST COULD BE TOUCH
AND GO AND YOU COULD
EXPERIENCE FREEZING RAIN.
THINGS WILL IMPROVE.
AS THE ATMOSPHERE CONTINUES TO
WARM AND WE WARM THE SURFACE
LEVELS WE GOT TO CONTEND WITH
ALL THAT.
IT WILL BE MOSTLY RAIN SHOWERS
LATER THIS AFTERNOON AND THIS
EVENING.
HERE'S YOUR FORECAST.
45 FREEZING RAIN.
CHANGING TO ALL RAIN FOR
EVERYBODY LATER TODAY.
I'LL HAVE THE DETAILS ON THE
WEEKEND FORECAST AND WE CAN DO
IT ALL OVER AGAIN.
WINTRY MIX BY MONDAY.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT.
STACEY.
>> THANKS, TUCKER.
WELL, WE ARE KEEPING YOU UP TO
DATE ON THE ROADS THIS
MORNING.
LET'S START WITH NORTH CAPITOL
STREET.
IF YOU'RE HEADING NORTHBOUND
RIGHT AT NEW YORK AVENUE,
WE'VE GOT A CRASH THAT'S
BLOCKING THE TWO LEFT LANES.
TAKE CARE THERE.
295 SOUTHBOUND, HOWEVER, LOOKS
OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS
OF TRAFFIC THIS MORNING.
BUT WHEREVER YOU'RE HEADED IF
YOU'RE ON 295 SOUTHBOUND
YOU'LL GET THERE ON TIME,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
SUITLAND PARKWAY ALSO LOOKS
RELATIVELY CLEAR.
FOR YOUR MARYLAND DRIVE, THE
OUTER LOOP HAS YOUR USUAL
POCKETS OF TRAFFIC AS YOU CAN
SEE A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE ON THE
ROAD BUT WE DON'T HAVE ANY
REPORTS OF INCIDENTS JUST YET.
AND ALSO THE
BALTIMORE-WASHINGTON PARKWAY
LOOKS LIKE IT'S ALSO AT SPEED.
270 SOUTHBOUND FROM FREDERICK
TO THE BELTWAY LOOKS PRETTY
CLEAR AND 66 EASTBOUND FROM
MANASSAS TO THE BELTWAY ALSO
LOOKS GOOD.
ALLISON, STEVE.
>> ♪
>> LET'S GET TO CAPITOL HILL
THIS MORNING.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
IS EXPECTED TO APPROVE TWO
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT
AGAINST PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THEY WILL VOTE BUT DIDN'T
HAPPEN LAST NIGHT.
>> EVEN AFTER THE COMMITTEE
GIVES THE GREEN LIGHT, THE
PROCESS IS FAR FROM OVER.
AND IS ALMOST CERTAIN TO
CONTINUE INTO THE NEW YEAR.
MAUREEN JOINS US IN THE
NEWSROOM WITH THE LATEST
DETAILS.
IT'S LIKE YOU INT I NEED A ROAD.
>> YOU DO.
THE EMOTIONAL DEBATE LASTED 14
HOURS YESTERDAY BUT IT WAS THE
HEARING'S SUDDEN END THAT
CAUSED THE B BIGGEST UPROAR.
>> I WANT THE MEMBERS ON BOTH
SIDES OF THE AISLE TO THINK
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED OVER THESE
LAST TWO DAYS TON SEARCH THEIR
CONSCIENCES BEFORE WE CAST OUR
FINAL VOTES.
>> AT 11:15 P.M. JUDICIARY
CHAIRMAN JERRY NADLER SAID
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH BUT
REPUBLICANS STILL WANTED MORE.
>> THE COMMITTEE IS IN RECESS.
>> MR. CHAIRMAN.
THIS IS THE KANGAROO COURT
THAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS.
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
>> THROUGHOUT THE HEARING THE
GOP SUGGESTED AMENDMENT AFTER
AMENDMENT INCLUDING DISMISSING
THE ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT
ALTOGETHER.
BUT THE DEMOCRATIC MAJORITY
SHOT THEM DOWN.
>> YOU HAVE A RIGGED AND
RUSHED PROCESS WHEN YOU CAN'T
ACCEPT THE WILL OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES REACHED OUT TO A
FOREIGN POWER AND ATTEMPTED TO
DRAG THEM INTO CORRUPTING OUR
ELECTIONS TO HELP HIM CHEAT
AND WIN IN THE ELECTION IN
2020.
>> HERE'S WHAT TO EXPECT NEXT.
THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE WILL
LIKELY APPROVE TWO ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT THIS MORNING.
ABUSE OF POWER AND OBSTRUCTION
OF CONGRESS.
THE ARTICLES WILL HEAD TO THE
RULES COMMITTEE AND FINALLY
MOVE TO THE FULL HOUSE FOR A
VOTE NEXT WEEK.
THERE WILL BE A SENATE TRIAL
NEXT YEAR TO DETERMINE IF
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS TO GO.
BUT SENATE MAJORITY LEADER
MITCH McCONNELL ALREADY
SEEMS CERTAIN OF THE OUTCOME.
>> THE CASE IS SO DARN WEAK
COMING OVER FROM THE HOUSE WE
ALL KNOW HOW IT'S GOING TO
END.
THERE'S NO CHANCE THE
PRESIDENT'S GOING TO BE
REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
>> AND TODAY'S HEARING COULD
LAST BETWEEN 45 MINUTES AND
TWO HOURS.
THE FULL HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES COULD VOTE ON
THE ARTICLES NEXT WEDNESDAY OR
PERHAPS THURSDAY.
STEVE AND ALLISON BACK TO YOU.
>> MO THANKS.
FROM THE U.S. TO THE UK THE
RESULTS ARE IN.
BORIS JOHNSON RETURNING TO
DOWNING STREET THE PRIME
MINISTER AND HIS CONSERVATIVE
PARTY SECURING THE VAST
MAJORITY DEFEATING THE LABOR
PARTY.
THE SWEEPING VICTORY MARKS THE
BIGGEST CONSERVATIVE MAJORITY
IN DECADES IN BRITAIN AND PUTS
BREXIT FIRMLY BACK ON TRACK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETING LAST
NIGHT HIS CONGRATULATIONS TO
JOHNSON SAYING "BRITAIN AND
THE UNITED STATES WILL NOW BE
FREE TO STRIKE A MASSIVE NEW
TRADE DEAL AFTER BREXIT.
THIS DEAL HAS THE POTENTIAL TO
BE FAR BIGGER AND MORE
LUCRATIVE THAN ANY DEAL THAT
COULD BE MADE WITH THE EU ."
>> RECOVERY EFFORTS IN NEW
ZEALAND WILL CONTINUE.
THEY'LL PICK BACK UP TODAY.
CREWS RETRIEVED SIX OF THE
EIGHT VICTIMS ON WHITE ISLAND
FOLLOWING MONDAY'S VOLCANIC
ERUPTION.
TWO PEOPLE BELIEVED TO BE A
TOUR GUIDE AND THE CAPTAIN OF
THE BOAT STILL HAVEN'T BEEN
FOUND.
MILITARY SPECIALISTS WORE
PROTECTIVE CLOTHING AND
BREATHING MASKS TO PROTECT
THEMSELVES AGAINST TOXIC GASES
ON THAT ISLAND.
>> SCARE FOR FORMER NBA
COMMISSIONER DAVID STERN WHO
IS RECOVERING THIS MORNING
FROM EMERGENCY SURGERY AFTER
COLLAPSING AT A NEW YORK CITY
RESTAURANT YESTERDAY.
THE LEAGUE LATER ANNOUNCED
THAT STERN SUFFERED A SUDDEN
BRAIN HEMORRHAGE.
STERN WAS COMMISSIONER FOR 30
YEARS.
HE STEPPED DOWN IN 2014
TURNING THE REINS OVER TO ADAM
SILVER.
>> HISTORY LAST NIGHT IN THE
NFL.
YOU SAW IT ON FOX.
LAMAR JACKSON THROWING FIVE
TOUCHDOWN PASSES.
HE ALSO RAN FOR 86 YARDS 86 YAR.
LAMAR JACKSON IN HIS FIRST
FULL SEASON AS A STARTER SETS
THE SINGLE SEASON RECORD FOR
YARDS RUSHED BY A QUARTERBACK
IS YOUR PASSING MICHAEL VICK.
BALTIMORE ON PACE TO BE THE
TOP SEED.
TUCKER COMING UP WITH YOUR
FORECAST THIS MORNING.
IT IS PROVING TO BE A LITTLE
DIFFICULT FOR SOME OUT THERE
SO YOU'LL WANT TO STAY TUNED.
>> PLUS THE SEARCH CONTINUES
IN MARYLAND FOR A MONEY WHO --
MAN WHO KIDNAPPED AND ROBBED A
WOMAN IN WALDORF.
BOB HAS THOSE DETAILS NEXT.
I'm LáDeia, and there's
more to me than HIV.
There's my career...
my cause...
and creating my dream home.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO is for
adults who are starting
HIV-1 treatment and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines dolutegravir
or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2 medicines
in 1 pill
to help you reach and
then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day
with food
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if you're
allergic to any of its
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,
liver problems, and
liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash and
other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,
including hepatitis B or C.
Don't use DOVATO if you plan
to become pregnant
or during the first 12
weeks of pregnancy
since one of its ingredients may
harm your unborn baby.
Your doctor should do a
pregnancy test
before starting DOVATO.
Use effective birth control
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache,
diarrhea, nausea, trouble
sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment
with DOVATO is right
for you.
>> 7: 15.
WE'RE STARTING TO SEE THE
FLAMES DIE DOWN A LITTLE BIT
IN THIS HOUSE FIRE IN UPPER
MARLBORO.
DID GET ONE UPDATE.
WE DID HEAR FROM FIREFIGHTERS.
THEY WANTED TO STRESS THE FACT
THEY'RE NOT LETTING THE HOUSE
BURN THEY JUST DON'T HAVE ANY
HYDRANTS IN THE AREA.
THEY HAVE TO KEEP TRUCKING
WATER SUPPLIES IN TO GET
ENOUGH WATER TO PUT ON THIS
HOUSE WHICH WE SAW BURNING OUT
OF CONTROL.
>> LOOK HOW CLOSE IT IS TO
THAT OTHER HOME.
>> THEY WANT TO MAKE SURE THEY
KEEP EVERYTHING PROTECTED.
FIREFIGHTERS HAVE BEEN THERE
FOR SEVERAL HOURS.
APPARENTLY THE WATER SUPPLY IS
NOT AS STRONG WITHOUT THE
HYDRANTS THERE.
THEY'RE DOING WHAT THEY CAN
BUT THAT FIRE WAS JUST BURNING
WAY TOO HOT FOR TOO LONG TO BE
ABLE TO SAVE THAT STRUCTURE.
7:16 RIGHT NOW.
>> GOODNESS.
OKAY.
NO REPORTS OF ANY INJURIES.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW IF THAT
CHANGES AT ALL.
TUCKER GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, ALLISON.
YES, IT'S FRIDAY AND WOULDN'T
YOU KNOW IT, SEEMS LIKE IT'S
BEEN AN ACTIVE WEEK OF
WEATHER.
DOING IT AGAIN.
36 HERE IN WASHINGTON.
WE'VE GOT THIS LIGHT FREEZING
RAIN EVENT AT LEAST THE THREAT
OF IT OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST AND TEMPERATURES JUST
DOING TO BE VERY CRITICAL
HERE.
I WANT TO EMPHASIZE MOST OF
THE AREA RIGHT ALONG THE BAY
WE'RE ABOVE FREEZING,
LEONARDTOWN 36 DEGREES, YOU
GUYS IN SOUTHERN MARYLAND HAVE
NO CONCERNS.
IN AND ALONG 95  95 WE'RE ABOVE
32.
WINCHESTER 32, FREDERICK 32.
CUMBERLAND 28.
THERE COULD BE SOME POCKETS
OUT HERE WHERE THE
TEMPERATURES REMAIN BELOW
FREEZING AS WE'VE GOT MOISTURE
WORKING IN AND PERHAPS A LIGHT
GLAZE OF FREEZING RAIN
EXPECTED IN SOME OF THESE
MOUNTAIN COMMUNITIES OFF TO
THE NORTH AND WEST.
YOU CAN SEE THAT THERE.
YOU SEE THE PINK IT'S OUR
RADAR ESTIMATING THAT THE
POTENTIAL IS THERE THAT YOU'RE
GETTING FREEZING RAIN OFF TO
THE WEST EARLY THIS MORNING.
ALREADY TRANSITIONING TO RAIN
HERE AND FOR MOST OF US FOR
MOST OF THE DAY IT'S GOING TO
BE A LIGHT RAIN, SOME SHOWERS
THIS AFTERNOON.
WE'LL GET RAIN AGAIN TONIGHT
INTO YOUR DAY ON SATURDAY AND
IT WILL BE JUST A RAIN EVENT.
IN FACT I'LL SHOW YOU THE
BIGGER PICTURE HERE.
WE GOT TO SLOG THROUGH A BIG
MESS OFF TO OUR SOUTH AND WEST
DOWN TOWARDS ATLANTA.
AREA OF LOW PRESSURE DOWN HERE
AND ALL THIS CLOUDINESS AND
MOISTURE IS GOING TO GET PUSH
UP AN ACROSS OUR AREA LATER
THIS AFTERNOON.
BRIEF PERIOD OF FREEZING RAIN
TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
WE SHOULD SEE THINGS START TO
TRANSITION PRETTY QUICKLY TO
JUST RAIN AND A RAINY
AFTERNOON A RAINY EVENING FOR
US.
ALL RIGHT.
OUR COMPUTERS ARE FORECASTING
ONE, TWO, 100THS OF AN INCH
TOWARDS WINCHESTER AND
CHARLESTOWN.
CUMBERLAND PERHAPS YOU GET A
LITTLE MORE AND SOME OF THOSE
MOUNTAIN COMMUNITIES WELL OFF
TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
HITTING THE ROADS AROUND 95
DON'T BE CONCERNED ABOUT
ICING.
YOU'RE GETTING IT.
WE'LL KICK OFF THE WEEKEND
WITH RAIN SHOWERS AND CLOUDS
AROUND.
THEN SUNDAY LOOKS GOOD BY
AFTERNOON FOR THE REDSKINS
GAME.
PERHAPS ANOTHER ROUND OF
WINTRY MIX ON MONDAY.
THIS COULD BE A PROBLEM
ESPECIALLY TO THE NORTH AND
WEST DURING THE DAY ON MONDAY.
THIS TOO WILL TRANSITION TO
ALL RAIN, CHANGE TO A RAIN
BEFORE ENDING ON TUESDAY.
I'LL BE TWEETING ABOUT THAT
THIS WEEKEND.
SOMETHING TO LOOK FORWARD.
YAY! STACEY HOW IS IT GOING.
>> IT'S GOING TUCKER ITS BEEN
A RELATIVELY QUIET MORNING IN
THE DMV BUT NOW THINGS ARE
PICKING UP SO I WANT TO TELL
YOU A FEW THINGS TO WATCH OUT
FOR.
STARTING WITH THE INNER LOOP.
WE HAVE A VEHICLE FIRE DUE TO
A CRASH.
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER MARYLAND 4
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
THAT'S DEFINITELY GOING TO
CAUSE SOME DELAYS THIS
MORNING.
TAKING A LOOK AT THAT CAMERA,
YOU CAN SEE THAT IT'S ALREADY
CAUSING DELAYS AND I
ANTICIPATE THOSE DELAYS
LASTING FOR AWHILE.
SO, TAKE CARE IF YOU'RE IN
THAT AREA.
MONG ON TO THE INNER LOOP AT
123, WE ALSO HAVE A CRASH
THAT'S BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE
CAUSING A LITTLE BIT OF A SLOW
DOWN THIS MORNING.
95 NORTHBOUND FROM DALE CITY
TO THE BELTWAY, HOWEVER, LOOKS
OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR USUAL POCKETS
OF TRAFFIC BUT OVERALL IT'S A
SMOOTH RIDE.
AND AS WE LOOK AT THE GEORGE
WASHINGTON PARKWAY, IF YOU'RE
HEADED SOUTHBOUND, WE ALSO
HAVE A CRASH RIGHT BEFORE 123
THAT'S BLOCKING THE RIGHT
LANE.
THAT'S ANOTHER THING TO WATCH
OUT FOR.
NORTH CAPITOL STREET
NORTHBOUND AT NEW YORK AVENUE
HAS A CRASH THAT'S BLOCKING
THE TWO LEFT LANES RIGHT NOW.
HOPEFULLY THEY'LL HAVE THAT
CLEARED UP MOMENTARILY.
AND 295 SOUTHBOUND LOOKS OKAY
THIS MORNING.
YOU'VE GOT AN EASY RIDE ON
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE AND THE
SUITLAND PARKWAY.
BACK TO YOU AT THE DESK.
>> BIZARRE CASE OUT OF CHARLES
COUNTY WHERE A KIDNAPPING
ODYSSEY ENDS WITH A
SPECTACULAR CRASH AND THE
KIDNAPPER ON THE RUN.
>> BOB BARNARD IN STUDIO WITH
MORE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GUYS.
YES, THE VICTIM IN THIS CASE
IS A WOMAN WHO WAS EVENTUALLY
LEFT ON THE SIDE OF A ROAD IN
ACCOKEEK AFTER A MAN FORCED
HER TO DRIVE AROUND TO A
NUMBER OF ATM'S TO TAKE OUT
MONEY.
INVESTIGATORS SAY AFTER
LEAVING THE WOMAN ON THE SIDE
OF THE ROAD THAT MAN THEN
SMASHED HER CAR INTO THE FRONT
DOORS OF THE AMF BOWLING ALLEY
IN WALDORF.
THIS IS SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OF
THAT.
SHERIFF'S INVESTIGATORS SAY HE
WAS BREAKING INTO THE BOWLING
ALLEY TO STEAL MONEY FROM ITS
ATM BUT APPARENTLY THAT
MACHINE WAS EMPTY.
YOU'LL SEE HERE IN A MOMENT
THE MAN THAT THE AUTHORITIES
ARE NOW LOOKING FORGETS OUT OF
THE CAR AND GOES INTO THE
BOWLING ALLEY LOOKING FOR MORE
CASH.
BUT AGAIN, HE DIDN'T GET ANY
THERE.
POLICE SAY THIS FRIGHTENING
CRIME STARTED WEDNESDAY NIGHT
IN WALDORF WHEN THE VICTIM
CAME HOME TO FIND THE SUSPECT
INSIDE.
SHE SAYS HE THEN FORCED HER
OUTSIDE AND INTO HER CAR ON
THE HUNT FOR MONEY.
CHARLES COUNTY SHERIFF'S
INVESTIGATORS ARE NOW ASKING
FOR YOUR HELP THIS MORNING.
THERE'S THE OUTSIDE OF THE
BOWLING ALLEY.
THEY'VE SENT US THIS PICTURE
WHICH IS OF THE MAKE AND MODEL
OF THE KIDNAPPING VICTIM'S
CAR.
THIS IS NOT THE ACTUAL CAR.
IT IS STILL MISSING ALONG WITH
THE KIDNAPPING SUSPECT.
IF YOU CAN HELP DETECTIVES
CCATCH THIS GUY PLEASE GIVE
THEM A CALL OR HIT THEM UP ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> BOB THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: YOU BET GUYS.
>> A SPLIT DECISION HANDED
DOWN BY A JURY FOR THE
MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE
OFFICER WHO SLAMMED A SUSPECT
INTO THE GROUND THIS PAST
SUMMER.
HE WAS HANDCUFFED THE SUSPECT
WAS ON THE GROUND ALREADY WHEN
THE OFFICER KEVIN MORRIS
PUSHED HIS FACE DOWN INTO THE
CONCRETE AT A McDONALD'S IN
ASPEN HILL.
MORRIS' TRIAL ENDED WAY SPLIT
VERDICT ON THE TWO CHARGES HE
WAS FACING.
THAT OFFICER FOUND GUILTY OF
ASSAULT BUT NOT GUILTY OF
OFFICER MISCONDUCT.
HERE'S WHAT THE BROTHER OF THE
VICTIM HAD TO SAY.
>> MY BROTHER IS A YOUNG MAN
WHO MADE A MISTAKE.
HE'S NOT PERFECT.
AND ULTIMATELY IT LED TO WHAT
I BELIEVE WAS POLICE BRUTALITY
AND I THINK THAT, YOU KNOW,
THERE NEEDED TO BE AN EXAMPLED
MADE OUT OF KEVIN MORRIS.
I THINK WHAT HE DID WAS
HORRIBLE.
>> OFFICER MORRIS WILL BE
SENTENCED IN FEBRUARY.
>>> 7:21 RIGHT NOW ON A FRIDAY
MORNING AND THE PRESIDENT BUSY
ON TWITTER POSSIBLY BREAKING A
RECORD.
>> BACK AT IT AGAIN THIS
MORNING, ALREADY, TOO.
PLUS HOW OFTEN DO YOU BUY
LOTTERY TICKETS?  THE SHOCKING
NUMBER THE AVERAGE PERSON
SPENDS A YEAR JUST TESTING
THEIR LUCK HOLDING OUT HOPE.
IT'S 7:22.
>> ♪
>> ♪♪
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately to
severely active Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed relief
and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house needs
or recently had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how Janssen can help
you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start with
STELARA®.
Every year,
air medical services save
hundreds of thousands of lives.
But after the emergency,
time and again,
insurance companies
deny coverage,
second guessing doctors,
nurses and first responders...
Now "big insurance"
is lobbying congress.
Asking for restrictions
on air medical services.
Eliminating patients'
access to life-saving care
and destroying jobs
all in exchange for bigger
profits for insurance companies.
Tell Congress,
put patients first,
not big insurance.
>> ♪
>> 7:25.
A NEW SURVEY SAYS THE AVERAGE
AMERICAN SPENDS HOW MUCH ON
LOTTERY TICKETS?  MORE THAN A
THOUSAND DOLLARS A YEAR.
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
THE AVERAGE AMERICAN.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE STUDY SAYS.
SOUND OUTLANDISH DOESN'T IT?
THIS DESPITE THE ODDS OF
HITTING THE JACKPOT BEING
INCREDIBLY SLIM.
THE ODDS ARE YOU'RE MORE
LIKELY TO BE ATTACKED BY A
GRISLY BEAR THAN WIN THE MEGA
MILLIONS.
WHY DO PEOPLE STILL PLAY.
>> WHY NOT.
>> PSYCHOLOGICAL EXPERTS SAY
WE ARE NATURALLY OPTIMISTIC
WHEN IT COMES TO THE
PROBABILITY OF WINNING.
>> WE WANT TO ALL BETTER OUR
CIRCUMSTANCES QUICKLY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THIS BREAKS
DOWN TO AND HOW THEY CAME TO
THAT NUMBER.
>> TO AVERAGE.
>> BREAKS DOWN TO $20 A WEEK
THAT YOU WOULD SPEND ON
LOTTERY TICKETS.
>> YOU THINK THE AVERAGE
PERSON SPENDS 20 BUCKS A WEEK.
>> I DON'T.
>> I THINK THAT'S A HIGHEST
MATE.
>> AVERAGE PERSON THAT SEEMS
HIGH.
>> MAYBE THE AVERAGE LOTTERY
PLAYER.
>> I DO HAVE ONE OF THESE
LOTTERY TICKET AND I HAVE AN
UNRATIONAL PERHAPS HOPE THAT I
WILL WIN.
>> ALLISON YOU MIGHT.
>> I HOPE YOU WIN.
>> YOU GOT TO PLAY TO WIN AM I
HOPE I HEARD THAT.
>> IF I WIN HERE, EVERYBODY
WINS.
>> YOU'RE TALKING TO A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
>> EVERYBODY IN HERE WINS.
>> I SEE.
>> STEVE I WANT TO KNOW MORE
ON THE GRISLY BEAR RESEARCH AS
WELL.
>> NEVER SEEN A GRIZZLY BEAR.
36 IN WASHINGTON.
CLOUDY SKIES TO START YOUR
DAY.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD BY NOW THIS
THREAT OF 14, THAT'S THE PINK
YOU SEE ON THE MAP OFF TO THE
NORTH AND WEST.
I DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME NOW
BUT THE POTENTIAL IS THERE FOR
A LIGHT GLAZE.
THIS IS GOING TO TRANSITION OR
CHANGE VERY QUICKLY TO RAIN
FOR EVERYBODY LATER THIS
MORNING AND DURING THE
AFTERNOON HOURS AND AGAIN, IF
YOU'RE IN THE IMMEDIATE
WASHINGTON AREA, SOUTH, SOUTH
AND EAST, EVEN NORTH AND WEST
INTO PARTS OF MONTGOMERY
COUNTY AND LOUDOUN COUNTY I
DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
GET ANYTHING MORE THAN RAIN
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE A WET
AFTERNOON WET EVENING AND WET
SATURDAY.
QUICK LOOK AT THE SEVEN-DAY.
MONDAY WE COULD HAVE A WINTRY
MIX THAT CHANGES RAIN.
YOU'LL HAVE TO WATCH MONDAY
MORNING TO FIND OUT WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
READY TO JAM THAT CAM, STACEY.
>> I'M READY FOR IT.
WE HAVE GOT SOME MAJOR DELAYS
ON THE INNER LOOP DUE TO A
CRASH INVOLVING A VEHICLE
FIRE.
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
AS YOU CAN SEE, TRAFFIC IS
REALLY AT A SLOW PACE THIS
MORNING.
YOU MAY WANT TO LEAVE EARLIER
IF YOU'RE IN THAT AREA.
ON THE INNER LOOP AT 123, WE
ALSO HAVE A CRASH.
THIS IS BLOCKING THE LEFT
LANE.
THAT'S ALSO A JAM CAM.
LOOK AT THE BRAKE LIGHTS
THERE. IT'S A REALLY SLOW
COMMUTE AS YOU MAKE YOUR WAY
AT 123.
95 NORTHBOUND DALE CITY TO THE
BELTWAY, HOWEVER, TRAFFIC IS
RUNNING AT SPEED AND AS WE
LOOK AT THE GEORGE WASHINGTON
PARKWAY WE'VE GOT THAT CRASH
RIGHT BEFORE 123 BLOCKING THE
RIGHT LANE.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C. ON
TWITTER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
FOX5 MORNING NEWS.
>> ♪
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
America has an
education problem.
The old system isn't
working anymore.
35 million Americans have
put their college
education on hold.
Who's going to do
something about it?
We are.
Strayer University wants
you to graduate.
90% of transfer
students say Strayer
was the right choice for
finishing their degree.
♪
>>> 7:30 ON THIS FRIDAY MORNING.
FRIDAY THE 13th BY THE WAY.
BACK WITH UPDATE ON THIS HOUSE
FIRE IN UPPER MARLBORO,
MARYLAND.
YOU CAN SEE A LOT OF THE FLAMES
ARE BEING PUT OUT AT LEAST
CONTROLLED A LITTLE BIT NOW.
THIS HOUSE BEEN BURNING FOR
SEVERAL HOURS NOW.
DOES NOT APPEAR ANYBODY WAS
INSIDE THE FLAMES VERY STRONG A
SHORT TIME AGO.
YOU CAN SEE IN THE BOTTOM RIGHT
THERE A FIREFIGHTER STILL
PUTTING A STREAM OF WATER
THROUGH THE WINDOWS OF THAT HOME
BUT VERY LARGE HOME.
THE DAMAGE QUIET SEVERE BUT THE
GOOD NEWS HERE, IT DOES NOT
APPEAR ANYBODY WAS HOME, AND NO
ONE HAS BEEN INJURED.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
HEARING RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED IN WE HEAR
OTHERWISE.
AL?
>>> THANKS, STEVE.
>>> STRANGE VOICES IN YOUR HOME
CONTINUING COVERAGE THIS MORNING
ON THOSE TERRIFYING VIDEOS IN
THE NEWS JUST THIS WEEK ALONE.
HOME SECURITY CAMERAS HACKED AND
TAUNTING CHILDREN.
HERE'S A LOOK AT TWO EXAMPLES
AGAIN FROM THIS WEEK ALONE.
>> MOMMY!
>> I'M SANTA CLAUS.
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE MY BEST
FRIEND?
>> WHAT YOU WATCHING?  HEY, WHAT
SHOW IS THAT?
>> SO IN THAT LAST CLIP THE
HACKER TALKING YOUNG GIRL
WATCHING TV HER DAD COMES INTO
THE ROOM AND CONFRONTS THE
HACKER.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO TO PREVENT
THIS?  JOINING US TECH EXPERT
OUR GOOD FRIEND PETE ERICKSON
CEO OF AND PRODUCER OF VOICE
SUMMIT WHICH IS THE TOP
CONFERENCE ON AI AND ALL THINGS
VOICE RELATED.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO BE HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHETHER IT'S
BECAUSE I'M A MOM OR A PERSON
WHO LIKES SOME OF THESE TECH
DEVICES OR NOT BUT I WAS
HORRIFIED TO SEE THAT VIDEO
ESPECIALLY THE FIRST ONE WHERE
THE CHILD IS SCARED OUT OF HER
MIND.
>> VERY DISTRESSING.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
>> WELL, THE INTERNET IS BASED
ON AN ALL TECHNOLOGY THAT'S
NOT -- OLD TECHNOLOGY THAT'S NOT
VERY SECURE.
AS DEVICES COME IN OUR HOMES AND
LEVERAGE THOSE INTERNET THOSE
DEVICES ARE NOT VERY SECURE.
NOW THERE ARE SECURITY PROTOCOLS
AND THINGS STACKED ON TOP OF ALL
THESE DEVICES, BUT WHAT HAPPENED
HERE HACKERS FIND A WAY TO GET
AROUND THEM, AND THERE'S, YOU
KNOW, THERE'S GOOD NEWS AND BAD
NEWS HERE, RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> BAD NEWS THE INTERNET WAS
BASED NOT VERY SECURITY
TECHNOLOGY.
GOOD NEWS THERE ARE THINGS
PEOPLE CAN DO ABOUT IT TO
PREVENT THINGS LIKE THIS FROM
HAPPENING.
>> PETE, I ALSO HEARD WHEN WE
PRESENTER THE STORY AND WE SAID
BUT HERE'S WHAT YOU CAN DO, YOU
CAN CHANGE YOUR PASSWORDS.
YOU CAN --
>> RIGHT.
>> ISN'T THE ONUS ON THESE BIG
BUSINESSES REALLY I MEAN THESE
THEM SECURITY CAMERAS THAT'S ALL
WE'RE HEARING ABOUT NOW.
SHOULDN'T THE ONUS BE ON THEM.
>> THE REALLY IS ABOUT EDUCATION
AND ENCOURAGING PEOPLE TO DO
VERY SIMPLE THINGS LIKE TWO
FACTOR AUTHENTICATION IN ORDER
TO GET INTO YOUR HOME NETWORK
NEW YORK CITY YOUR DEVICE, INTO
YOUR APPLICATIONS.
A LOT OF US ARE VERY USED TO
THAT WITH BANKING APPS.
>> SURE.
WE USE TWO FACTOR AUTHEN
AUTHENTICATION.
HOWEVER WITH THINGS LIKE SECURE
DOOR BELLS AND SMART THINGS IN
OUR HOME WE MAY NOT BE USING
THEM THERE.
BUT I THINK IT'S TIME FOR
EVERYBODY TO REALLY TAKE THAT
NEXT STEP TO SECURE YOURSELF AND
THE ONUS ON THE COMPANIES IS
REALLY BE A SOURCE FOR RESOURCE
FOR EDUCATION, HOW TO TURN ON
TWO FACTOR AUTHENTICATION.
HOW TO MAKE THINGS LIKE YOUR
WI-FI ROUTER IN YOUR HOUSE MORE
SECURE.
>> IS THAT WHY WITH LIKE THE
WI-FI JUST, YOU KNOW, I KNOW THE
ROUTER IS A DIFFERENT THING, WHY
IN THE WORLD WOULD WE HAVE LIKE
26 NUMBERS AND LETTERS WHEN WE
TRY TO GO ON TO OUR WI-FI.
IS THAT A PART OF IT?  LIKE
COMPLICATED PASSWORDS AND ALL OF
THAT.
>> YEAH.
YOUR WI-FI ROUTER COMES AND THEY
GIVE YOU A VERY SECURE PASSWORD,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S AN UNUSUAL
STRING OF CHARACTERS.
BUT THEY'RE DOING THAT BECAUSE
THEY'RE TRYING TO SHOW YOU
WHAT'S CALLED GOOD PASSWORD
HYGIENE.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT IS TO USE A PASSWORD
THAT IS REALLY UNIQUE AND A
CROSS OUR DEVICES I KNOW IT'S
REALLY HARD TO USE DIFFERENT
PASSWORDS.
WE ALL SUFFER FROM THE SAME
CHALLENGE OF WHAT'S THE PASSWORD
ON THIS DEVICE VERSUS THAT
DEVICE.
>> RIGHT.
>> THERE ARE PASSWORD MANAGERS
OUT THERE LIKE LAST PASS AND
OTHER THAT IS YOU CAN USE TO
HELP MAKE IT EASIER.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY IT IS
UP TO US TO MAKE OURSELVES MORE
SECURE.
TO PROTECT OURSELVES.
>> SO ARE ALL OF THESE SORT
DEFINITE ADVICES SECURITY
CAMERAS ALL THESE OTHER THINGS
ARE THEY ALL VULNERABLE IN THE
SAME WAY?
>> EVERYTHING THAT'S CONNECTED
THROUGH THE INTERNET IS
VULNERABLE.
THAT IS THE TRUTH.
THAT IS JUST A FACT, AND IT IS A
CAT AND MOUSE GAME WITH HACKERS.
THEY'RE ALWAYS TRYING TO FIND
THE WAY IN.
>> UM-HMM.
SO HE HAVE WE HAVE TO BE
VIGILANT.
WE HAVE TO USE THINGS LIKE TWO
FACTOR AUTHENTICATION.
I MAY NOT PUT A SECURITY CAMERA
THAT'S CONNECTED TO THE INTERNET
IN A BEDROOM, FOR EXAMPLE.
>> RIGHT.
>> JUST BECAUSE HACKERS ARE
ALWAYS TRYING TO OUTWIT AND
OUTSMART AND I BROUGHT EXAMPLES.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS IS A RING DOORBELL.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS IS A BATTERY POWERED
ONE.
WE CAN PUT IT ANYWHERE.
>> UM-HMM.
SO THIS IS THE TYPE THAT COULD
GO INSIDE.
THIS IS A SMART PLUG LOOKS LIKE
A NORMAL PLUG.
BUT IT'S CONNECTED TO THE
INTERNET.
>> OKAY.
>> THESE ARE REALLY CONVENIENT
THINGS TO HAVE AND OF COURSE THE
ULTIMATE SMART CONNECTED DEVICES
OUR PHONES NOW.
SO WE ARE IN A CAT AND MOUSE
GAME WITH HACKERS.
IT'S A PART OF THE REALITY OF
THE CONNECTED WORLD WE'RE IN.
>> THESE TWO LIKE THEY CAME
RIGHT INTO THE HOUSE.
THAT ONE GENTLEMAN HE'S OF AGE
STILL SCARING THE BEIJI SUSS OUT
OF HIM SOMEBODY SAYING WHAT ARE
YOU WATCHING FIRST OF ALL.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THE FUTURE OF THESE SORT
OF DEVICES, IS IT SAFE, WILL WE
CONTINUE TO SEE DIFFERENT
GENERATIONS OF THESE IN HOME
SECURITY CAMERAS?
>> JUST LIKE WE HAVE BREACHES
AND THERE ARE BIG, YOU KNOW,
TROPHIES OF DATA GET STOLEN,
THIS IS THE REALITY THAT WE'RE
IN.
WE LIVE IN THE CONNECTED WORLD.
I CALL IT SORT OF THE POST
PRIVACY ERA.
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE OUR DATA IS BEING
SOUGHT AFTER AND BEING STOLEN.
SO BE VIGILANT.
TWO FACTOR AUTHENTICATION, USE
STRONG PASSWORDS.
>> TWO FACTOR AUTHENTICATION
JUST MEANS YOU'RE IN ONE WAY BUT
THEN YOU NEED ANOTHER LAYER OF
SECURITY HAVE THAT ALREADY SET
UP AND IN PLACE.
>> YOU'LL GET E-MAIL OR TEXT
MESSAGE OR SOMETHING TO PROVE
THAT IT'S YOU.
>> A CODE.
>> TRYING TO GET IN.
>> IT'S SIMPLE THING TO DO BUT T
>> ALL RIGHT.
>>> PETE ERICKSON YOU ALWAYS
HELP US TOO.
I FEEL A LITTLE MORE SECURE.
>> LITTLE BIT.
>> A LITTLE BIT.
OKAY.
>> UP TO YOU.
>> OKAY.
THE ONUS IS ALWAYS ON US.
PETE IS CEO OF MODEV.
ALL RIGHT.
TUCKER, OVER TO YOU.
>> GREAT SEGMENT, ALLISON.
LET'S HOP ON IN.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY NORTH
AND WEST.
LET'S SHOW YOU THE MAPS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE ME.
WANT TO SEE THE MAPS.
THERE THEY ARE.
NORTH AND WEST LOUDOUN COUNTY
PARTS OF FREDERICK COUNTY,
WASHINGTON COUNTY ALL UNDER A
FREEZING RAIN OR WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORY FREEZING RAIN IS A
CONCERN HERE THROUGH 3:00 P.M.
THIS AFTERNOON HONESTLY HERE
THIS IS GOING TO BE A LIGHT
GLAZE AND MOST OF US ARE GOING
TO GET JUST PLANE RAIN LOOK AT
YOUR TEMPERATURES REAGAN
NATIONAL 36 DEGREES.
DULLES 34.
BWI MARSHALL 35.
IF YOU'RE WATCHING THIS MORNING,
IN AROUND THE IMMEDIATE
WASHINGTON AREA, DO NOT BE
CONCERNED.
FREEZING RAIN WILL NOT IMPACT
YOU IT'S OUR FRIENDS OUT TO THE
WEST AND YOU CAN SEE THE LIGHT
PINK OUT THERE.
THAT'S VERY LIGHT RAIN THAT'S
FALLING BUT THAT IS SORT OF
WORSE CASE SCENARIO FALLING INTO
TEMPERATURES THAT ARE AT OR
BELOW FREEZING BECAUSE THE RAIN
WILL FREEZE ON CONTACT ON THE
SURFACE, AND CAUSE LIGHT GLAZE.
WE HAVE HAD REPORTS OF THAT INTO
SOUTHWEST PARTS OF VIRGINIA
EARLY THIS MORNING.
SO CERTAINLY A POSSIBILITY.
FOR THE REST OF US, CLOUDY
SKIES, A COOL DAY ONLY IN THE
40S, AND FREEZING RAIN WILL
TRANSITION TO RAIN FOR EVERYBODY
BY LATE MORNING EARLY AFTERNOON.
TAKE THE UMBRELLA HERE.
AFTER WORK, AFTER SCHOOL
EVERYBODY WILL HAVE RAIN SHOWERS
AROUND LATER TODAY.
THIS EVENING SOME RAIN SHOWERS.
MUCH OF SATURDAY RAIN SHOWERS.
WEEKEND FORECAST AND EARLY NEXT
WEEK COMING RIGHT UP.
STACEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
I HAVE A FEW UPDATES REGARDING A
FEW INCIDENTS ON THE ROAD.
LET'S START WITH THE INNER LOOP.
WE HAVE A CRASH THIS IS RIGHT AT
BRADDOCK ROAD.
THE TWO LEFT LANES ARE BLOCKED.
TWO RIGHT HOV LANES ARE BLOCKED
AS WELL AS YOU CAN SEE IN OUR
VDOT SHOT, REALLY TYING YOU UP
THIS MORNING.
IT LOOKS LIKE POLICE AND
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS ARE ON SITE
DOING THEIR BEST TO CLEAR THAT
UP FOR YOU.
BUT STILL IT'S GOING TO BE A
SLOW RIDE IF YOU ARE IN THAT
AREA.
LOOKING AT THE INNER LOOP AT
123, WE ALSO HAVE ANOTHER CRASH
THAT'S CAUSING SOME MAJOR DELAYS
WITH SPEEDS DOWN TO ABOUT
20 MILES PER HOUR IN THE THICK
OF THINGS.
THIS IS ALSO BLOCKING THE LEFT
LANE.
MOVING OVER TO THE INNER LOOP AT
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE, WE HAVE
ANOTHER CRASH INVOLVING A
VEHICLE FIRE THE DELAYS ARE
SIGNIFICANT HERE WITH SPEEDS
DOWN TO FOE MILES PER HOUR.
SO IT'S A SLOW COMMUTE THERE AND
FINALLY 95 NORTHBOUND FROM DALE
CITY TO THE BELTWAY, TRAFFIC IS
AT SPEED.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT YOU WOULD
EXPECT FOR THIS TIME OF THE
MORNING.
ANY QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C.
ON TWITTER.
ALLISON?
>> HEADS UP IF YOU HAVE TRAVEL
PLANS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> ALSO SOME GOOD NEWS FOR
COFFEE FANS.
MAYBE.
YOUR CAFFEINE FIX COULD GET A
LITTLE BIT SWEETER.
PEPSI IS TRYING THIS OUT.
DO YOU AGREE?  WE'LL GET THE
DETAILS COMING UP.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ Blow a kiss into the sun ♪
♪ We need someone to lean on ♪
♪ All we needed
somebody to lean on ♪
First payment is on us
when you lease the new XC90.
Starting at $529 a
month for 36 months
with $4350 due at signing.
>>> THERE'S A NEW PROPOSAL IN
VIRGINIA TO MAKE COMMUNITY
COLLEGE TUITION FREE FOR LOW AND
MIDDLE INCOME STUDENTS WHO
PURSUE CAREERS IN HIGH-DEMAND
INDUSTRIES LIKE HEALTH CARE,
PUBLIC SAFETY, EDUCATION.
GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM IS ASKING
FOR $145 MILLION OVER TWO YEARS
TO MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP OUT DID
HIMSELF ON TWITTER YESTERDAY.
HE BROKE HIS OWN RECORD FOR THE
MOST TWEETS IN A DAY SINCE
TAKING OFFICE.
IT WAS A RECENT RECORD TOO BUT
YESTERDAY THE PRESIDENT TWEETED
123 TIMES.
THE MAJORITY OF THEM CAME IN THE
MORNING WHEN HE CRITICIZED THE
IMPEACHMENT HEARINGS AND ALSO
TEENAGED CLIMATE ACTIVIST GRETA
THUNBERG TIMES PERSON OF THE
YEAR.
>>> UP NEXT WE'RE TALKING COFFEE
INFUSED SODA.
>> PLUS, HOW CAN YOU HELP TO
HONOR OUR FALLEN VETERANS THIS
WEEKEND?  WE'RE LIVE AT
ARLINGTON NATIONAL CEMETERY WITH
THE DETAILS.
IT'S COMING UP AFTER THE BREAK.
♪
Every year,
air medical services save
hundreds of thousands of lives.
But after the emergency,
time and again,
insurance companies
deny coverage,
second guessing doctors,
nurses and first responders...
Now "big insurance"
is lobbying congress.
Asking for restrictions
on air medical services.
Eliminating patients'
access to life-saving care
and destroying jobs
all in exchange for bigger
profits for insurance companies.
Tell Congress,
put patients first,
not big insurance.
GET A QUICK CHECK ON BUSINESS
NEWS.
PACK YOUR PATIENCE IF YOU'RE
TRAVELING OVER THE HOLIDAYS.
JOINING US FROM THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK TRACEE CAR ROSCO.
HOW ARE YOU?  HOPEFULLY YOU'LL
HAVE SAFE TRAVELS.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'LL HAVE A LOT OF
COMPANY IF YOU DO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MIGHT HIT SOME TRAFFIC ON THE
WAY BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO BE
115.6 MILLION TRAVELERS THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
THAT IS ACCORDING TO AAA.
THEY SAY THIS IS THE HIGHEST
NUMBER OF PEOPLE TRAVELING
THEY'VE SEEN DURING THE HOLIDAY
SEASON SINCE THEY START THE
KEEPING TRACK ABOUT 20 OR SO
YEARS AGO.
THE BIG MAJORITY OF THOSE WILL
BE DRIVING ABOUT 104 MILLION.
THERE'S ALSO GOING TO BE ABOUT
7 MILLION PEOPLE FLYING SO
DEFINITELY BE PATIENT.
NOW THE BUSIEST DAY IF YOU ARE
GOING TO BE DRIVING ANYWHERE
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE BEFORE
CHRISTMAS BUT AFTER ON
DECEMBER 26th.
ALL OF THIS DESPITE GAS PRICES
BEING HIGHER THIS YEAR BY ABOUT
17 CENTS ON AVERAGE.
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT.
>> SEE HOW MANY PEOPLE MAKE THE
WEEK OF IT OR TRY TO EXTENT THE
HOLIDAY HOWEVER THEY CAN.
ALL RIGHT.
WHEN IT COMES TO GETTING THAT
CAFFEINE FIX I LIKE MY COFFEE.
I ADMIT IT.
I USED TO DRINK SODA NOT SO MUCH
ANY MORE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I LIKE THE
COMBINATION OF THE TWO, TRACEE.
>> WELL, PEPSI IS WILLING TO
GIVE EIGHT SHOT TO SEE MAYBE IF
YOU WILL LIKE IT.
THEY'RE COMING OUT WITH
SOMETHING CALLED PEPSI CAFE.
THEY'RE CALLING IT A COLA
INFUSED WITH COFFEE.
THERE ARE TWO FLAVORS ORIGINAL
AND VANILLA THE ORIGINAL IS
GOING TO BE MORE OF LIKE A
RICHER BLACK COFFEE.
THE VANILLA WILL BE A LITTLE
SWEETER BUT THEY SAY ONE CAN OF
THIS WILL HAVE DOUBLE THE AMOUNT
OF CAFFEINE AS REGULAR CAN OF
PEPSI.
NOW THIS IS THE FIRST TIME WE'VE
SEEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
COCA-COLA HAS SOMETHING IN
INTERNATIONAL MARKETS A COKE
INFUSED WITH COFFEE BUT PEPSI
BACK IN 1986 -- '96 RATHER THEY
CAME OUT WITH PEPSI CONA THAT
WAS SOMETHING VERY SIMILAR.
SO WE WILL SEE IF IT TAKES OFF
THIS TIME AROUND.
I IMAGINE BACK IN 1996 MIGHT NOT
HAVE BUN SO WELL THAT'S WHY IT
IS STILL NOT AROUND.
>> IF AT FIRST YOU DON'T SUCCEED
WAIT 23 YEARS AND TRY IT AGAIN
WITH A DIFFERENT CAN.
>> TRY AGAIN.
>> EVERY TIME I SEE THOSE SKINNY
CANS, TRACEE, ALL I THINK OF
LESS PRODUCT AND IT'S GOING TO
COST ME A LOT MORE MONEY.
>> MAYBE THEY WANT TO YOU THINK
OF LIKE A RED BULL EXACTLY.
>> I THINK OF A RED BULL LIKE AN
ENERGY DRINK.
MAYBE THEY WANT YOU TO HAVE THAT
SORT OF IMAGE.
ENERGY DRINK IN THE SUNNIER CAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL SEE.
>> TRACEE, WE'LL SEE IF YOU TRY
IT, LET US KNOW HOW IT IS.
WE'LL DOT SAME.
IN THE MEANTIME HAVE A GREAT
WEEKEND.
WE'LL SEE YOU MONDAY MORNING.
>> YOU, TOO.
BYE-BYE.
>> GET OVER TO TUCKER.
GOOD MORNING.
>> I TRIED THE 23 YEAR PLAN WITH
A WOMAN I DATED IN COLLEGE I
TRIED 23 YEARS LATER AND SHE
STILL WASN'T INTERESTED.
>> YEAH?
>> YES.
>> GOOD PLAN, THOUGH.
>> DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
>> THANKS, TUCK.
>> I'M GLAD I COULD SHARE.
ICING NORTH AND WEST.
THAT'S BIG THREAT HERE THIS
MORNING.
RAIN SHOWERS FOR THE REST OF US,
AND TRULY WANT TO EMPHASIZE MOST
OF US GETTING PLANE RAIN HERE.
VIEWERS TO THE WEST AND NORTH
AND BIGGEST RISK OF ICE ARE TO
THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
GOING TO RAIN MOST OF THE DAY ON
SATURDAY CLEAR IT OUT SUNDAY.
SUNDAY WILL BE FINE IF GOING TO
THE REDSKINS GAME SUNDAY
AFTERNOON THE POTENTIAL FOR
ANOTHER EVENT HERE ON MONDAY.
WHAT WE CALL OVERRUNNING SO THE
POTENTIAL FOR WINTRY MIX AROUND
HERE ON MONDAY AS WELL.
SHOW YOU THAT ON THE SEVEN DAY.
36 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
OKAY.
95 SOUTH AND EAST EVERYBODY WELL
ABOVE FREEZING SO WHEN IT
ARRIVES IT WILL BE JUST RAIN.
GAITHERSBURG 32 DEGREES.
WANT TO SHOW YOU IN THE
MOUNTAINS WE'RE NOW GETTING IT
ABOVE 32.
SO ANY RAIN WE GET THAT FALLS AS
FREEZING RAIN SHOULD BE KIND OF
TOUCH AND GO HERE OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE OF HOURS AND THEN THINGS
WILL IMPROVE VERY QUICKLY.
FREDERICKSBURG BOUNCED BACK TO
34.
THAT'S A GREAT SIGN.
THE RADAR IS INDICATING THE
POTENTIAL THAT YOU SEE THE PINK
HERE THAT SOME OF THIS IS
FALLING AS FREEZING RAIN, AND
WE'LL HAVE TO CONTEND WITH TO
FOR A FEW MORE HOURS BUT
ATMOSPHERE WILL GRADUALLY WARM
WE'RE EXPECTING DAYTIME HIGHS
HERE IN WASHINGTON IN THE LOW
40S.
SO THIS WILL NOT BE AN ALL DAY
ICING EVENT.
IN FACT THIS IS GOING TO BE KIND
OF TOUCH AND GO FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF HOURS.
THEN AS MENTIONED WE SHOULD
TRANSITION CHANGE OVER PRETTY
QUICK TOLL PLANE RAIN FOR
EVERYBODY LATER THIS MORNING.
TAKE THE UMBRELLA.
LOOK AT ALL THIS MESS WE HAVE
OFF TO OUR SOUTH.
WORKING THROUGH OUR REGION LATER
THIS AFTERNOON.
TONIGHT IF YOU'RE GOING OUT
YOU'LL NEED THE UMBRELLA, AND
WE'LL HAVE SLICK ROADWAYS
BECAUSE IT WILL BE RAINING OUT
THERE AND UNFORTUNATELY MUCH OF
TOMORROW AS THAT AREA OF LOW
PRESSURE JUST KIND OF VERY
SLOWLY MOVES OFF TO OUR NORTH,
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP THE CLOUDS
AROUND WITH POTENTIAL FOR FEW
SHOWERS AROUND HERE AS WELL ON
SATURDAY.
THOSE ARE YOUR POTENTIAL ICE
ACCUMULATIONS YOU CAN SEE THAT'S
VERY LIGHT ICING EVENT BUT WE
ALL KNOW IT ONLY TAKES A LITTLE
BIT OF ICE TO CAUSE A LOT OF
PROBLEMS.
SO WE'LL THROW THAT OUT THERE.
HERE'S FUTURE CAST AT NOON.
NOT GOING TO RAIN ALL AFTERNOON.
THERE WE ARE AT 3:00 O'CLOCK BUT
THE RAIN STARTS TO FILL IN LATER
THIS EVENING.
GOOD STEADY RAIN OVERNIGHT MAYBE
HEAVY AT TIMES TOWARDS DAY BREAK
KEEP RAIN SHOWERS AND COOL TEMPS
IN THE FORECAST FOR THE DAY ON
SUN SATURDAY.
SUNDAY LOOKS GOOD.
PERHAPS ANOTHER WINTRY MIX ON
MONDAY.
THAT TOO WILL BECOME RAIN.
MAYBE AT THE ONSET WINTRY MIX.
WATCH VERY CAREFULLY THE
FORECAST MONDAY.
I'LL BE HERE MONDAY MORNING TO
GIVE YOU THE LATEST.
STACEY?
>> ALL DAY ICING EVENT AN WET
GLAZE.
IT REALLY DOESN'T SOUND THAT
BAD, TUCKER, WHEN YOU SAY IT
THAT WAY.
I'M TELLING YOU IT SOUNDS
DELICIOUS.
WE'VE GOT TO OPEN OUR MINDS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A CRASH ON THE INNER
LOOP AT BRADDOCK ROAD.
THE TWO LEFT LANES ARE BLOCKED
BECAUSE OF THAT.
IT'S SLOWING YOU DOWN A BIT THIS
MORNING.
SOMETHING TO WATCH OUT FOR.
ALSO, ON THE INNER LOOP AT 123
WE'VE GOT A CRASH THAT'S
BLOCKING THE LEFT LANE.
REALLY CAUSING SOME DELAYS THIS
MORNING.
SLOWING YOU DOWN TO ABOUT
20 MILES PER HOUR IN THE HEAT OF
THINGS.
AGAIN, ON THE INNER LOOP, RIGHT
AT PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE, THERE IS
ANOTHER CRASH AS YOU CAN SEE IN
THIS LIVE SHOT IT LOOKS LIKE
POLICE AND EMERGENCY RESPONDERS
ARE ON SITE BUT BECAUSE OF THAT
CRASH, SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO JUST
ABOUT FIVE MILES PER HOUR SO YOU
MAY WANT TO HEAD OUT A LITTLE
EARLY THIS MORNING.
95 NORTHBOUND, HOWEVER F DALE
CITY TO THE BELTWAY LOOKS GOOD.
TRAFFIC IS AT SPEED.
AND NORTH CAPITOL STREET IF
YOU'RE ON NORTH CAPITAL
NORTHBOUND RIGHT AT NEW YORK
AVENUE THE TWO LEFT LANES ARE
BLOCKED.
YOU'VE GOT SOME MAJOR DELAYS
THERE.
AND FINALLY ON 295 SOUTHBOUND,
NO PROBLEM THERE.
HOWEVER, 50 IS A LITTLE BIT
CONGESTED THIS MORNING.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
ALLISON, STEVE?
>> STACEY, THANKS VERY MUCH.
7:51.
A DEADLY FUNGUS FORCED A POPULAR
CHRISTMAS TREE FARM IN LOUDOUN
COUNTY TO CLOSE FOR THE SEASON.
MIDDLEBURG CHRISTMAS TREE FARM
SAYS IT'S EXPERIENCING A
SHORTAGE OF CERTAIN TREES LIKE
DOUG LIST FIRS AND COLORADO BLUE
SPRUCE.
OWNER SAYS HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO
BURN ALL OF THE DEAD TREES IN
HOPES OF PREVENTING THE SPREAD
OF FUNGUS.
THE WARMER WINTERS THE HOT AND
HUMID SUMMERS LIKELY TO BLAME
AND HE HATE TO HEAR ABOUT THAT
ESPECIALLY THIS TIME OF YEAR
WHEN FOLKS ARE LOOKING FOR THEIR
TREES.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> THAT'S HESS LIVELIHOOD.
OKAY.
>> SPEAKING OF WREATHS.
REMEMBER, HONOR AND TEACH
TRADITION ROLLING INTO THE
DISTRICT TODAY.
KARA VAN OF WREATHS THAT WILL BE
PLACED ON EVE GRAVESTONE AT
ARLINGTON NATIONAL CEMETERY.
>> HAPPENING TOMORROW.
FOR MORE DETAILS HOW YOU CAN
HELP MAJOR JEREMY TILLEY JOINS
US LIVE THE OPERATIONS OFFICER
AT ARLINGTON NATIONAL CEMETERY.
WHAT A SPECIAL DAY ON TAP FOR
TOMORROW.
GOOD MORNING, SIR.
CAN YOU SPEAK ABOUT WHAT WE WILL
SEE IN THE AREA TOMORROW?
>> HI, GOOD MORNING TO YOU BOTH.
YEAH.
SO TOMORROW IS WREATHS ACROSS
AMERICA EVENT HERE IN ARLINGTON
NATIONAL CEMETERY.
IT'S A DAY WHERE ANY VISITOR CAN
COME INTO THE CEMETERY.
PICK UP A WREATH FROM A
VOLUNTEER AND PLACE IT AT ANYONE
OF THE HEADSTONES THROUGHOUT THE
CEMETERY.
>> BY THE END OF THE DAY WE'LL
HAVE PLACED OVER -- GO AHEAD.
>> GO AHEAD.
I'LL LET YOU FINISH YOUR
THOUGHT.
THAT WAS THE QUESTION HOW MUCH
WORK IS ACTUALLY INVOLVED HERE
BECAUSE WE KNOW EVERY YEAR YOU
KNOW THE VOLUNTEERS COME OUT BY
THE HUNDREDS IF NOT THOUSANDS.
>> THAT'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
UM, SO ALL IN ALL WE'LL PLACE
OVER 250,000 WREATHS TOMORROW SO
IT'S QUITE AN EVENT, AND IT'S A
LOT OF WORK FOR EVERYBODY
INVOLVED.
>> SADLY, WE ARE LOOKING AT SOME
RAIN IN THE FORECAST BUT WE HAVE
SEEN IN THE PAST WEATHER DOES
NOT DETER THE GOOD FOLKS WHO
COME OUT TO FINISH THIS DEED FOR
ALL OF THESE HEADSTONES.
BUT HOW DOES THAT COMPLICATE IT,
THIS RAIN WE'RE EXPECTED TO SEE?
>> WELL, SO WE'RE ASKING ALL OF
OUR VISITORS WHO PLAN TO ATTEND
TO KEEP AN EYE ON THE FORECAST
AND TO DRESS FOR THE WEATHER
RAIN, COLD WHATEVER THE CASE MAY
BE.
UMBRELLAS ARE OKAY OBVIOUSLY.
AND ALSO TO JUST PLEASE FOLLOW
THE DIRECTIONS OF OUR SAFETY AND
SECURITY PERSONNEL BOTH BEFORE
YOU COME INTO THE CEMETERY AND
GO THROUGH SCREENING AND THEN
ALSO AS YOU MOVE ABOUT THE
CEMETERY.
>> MAJOR I KNOW THAT YOU
OBVIOUSLY YOU HAVE YOUR JOB TO
DO AS OPERATIONS MANAGER AT THE
CEMETERY WHICH IS A VERY
ESTEEMED POST TO HAVE.
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING WE DO
REALLY TO HONOR ALL OF THESE
FALLEN HEROES.
FOR YOU AND OTHERS WHO ARE
SERVING NOW, THE SIMPLE ACT OF
VOLUNTEERING TO PUT A WREATH ON
A STONE, WHAT DOES THAT DO, WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN FOR YOU AS
SOMEONE WHO IS SERVING NOW?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN TOMORROW IS ALL ABOUT
REMEMBERING.
IT'S ABOUT TAKING TIME, LITTLE
BIT OF TIME OUT OF THE HOLIDAY
SEASON TO REMEMBER THE SERVICE
AND THE SACRIFICE OF ALL OF
THOSE THAT ARE INTERRED HERE AT
ARLINGTON.
SO IT'S VERY SPECIAL.
>> AND FOR THOSE WHO MIGHT BE
NEW TO SEEING THIS, WHEN IT'S
ALL SAID AND DONE AND THE
WREATHS ARE ON THE HEADSTONES,
WHAT DOES THAT PICTURE LOOK
LIKE?  WHAT DOES THAT INSPIRE
WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT?
>> WELL, IT'S AN HONOR TO WORK
HERE AND IT'S AN HONOR TO BE A
PART OF THE EVENT.
I THINK EVERYBODY -- THE GOOD
THING ABOUT ARLINGTON EVERYBODY
CAN COME HERE AND HAVE THE
EXPERIENCE THEY WANT TO HAVE,
WHETHER IT'S PERSONAL OR WITH A
GROUP OF PEOPLE AND SO EVERYONE
IS WELCOMED TO COME AND HAVE
THAT EXPERIENCE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE FINAL THING JUST FOR FOLKS
WHO WANT TO COME DOWN MAYBE
THEY'RE WATCHING TODAY THEY'VE
NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE.
IF THEY JUST HOP OFF METRO JUST
COME IN THROUGH THE VISITOR
CENTER DO THEY NEED TO KNOW
ANYTHING BEFORE THEY COME DOWN?
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
SO BASED ON THE LARGE CROWDS
THAT WE'RE EXPECTING AND THE
ROAD CLOSURES THAT WE NEED TO DO
TO KEEP EVERYBODY SAFE, WE
STRONGLY ENCOURAGE EVERYBODY TO
USE PUBLIC TRANSPORTATION
TOMORROW AND SO FORTUNATELY
THERE'S THEE METRO STOPS THAT
ARE IN CLOSE PROXIMITY YOU CAN
HOP OFF AT ROSLAND AND WALK DOWN
NORTH MED STREET TO THE OLDER
WET SELL GATE OR GO TO THE
ARLINGTON CEMETERY METRO STOP
AND THEN GO TO THE MAIN ENTRANCE
OF THE CEMETERY OR YOU CAN ALSO
USE PENTAGON AND THEN YOU CAN
USE COLUMBIA PIKE TO GET TO THE
SOUTH GATE ENTRANCE OF THE
CEMETERY.
>> GOOD TO KNOW.
>> ALL THREE ARE A SHORT 15
MINUTE WALK.
>> GOOD TO KNOW ALL THE GATES
WILL BE ACCESSIBLE TOMORROW FOR
FOLKS THAT WANT TO COME OUT.
MAJOR, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE I
HOPE EVERYTHING GOES WELL
TOMORROW.
I'M SURE IT WILL.
WE'VE SEEN THIS OBVIOUSLY IN THE
PAST ALLISON WHEN WE'VE HAD
RAINY CONDITIONS OUT THERE.
YEAH.
>> YOU SEE FOLKS WHO STILL JUST
COME OUT TO MAKE SURE THAT ALL
THOSE WREATHS GET PLACED WHERE
THEY BELONG.
>> SACRED AND HOLLOWED GROUND
FOR SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LET'S GET OVER TO TUCK AND
GET A CHECK ON THE FORECAST.
HOW YOU DOING.
>> 37 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD FREEZING RAIN
THREAT NOT HERE IN THE IMMEDIATE
WASHINGTON AREA THIS WILL BE
NORTH AND WEST.
I KNOW WE GOT DELAYS AND
CANCELLATIONS OUT THERE.
SO FAR NOT GETTING REPORTS BUT
PLEASE TWEET ME IF YOU'RE
GETTING ICE AT YOUR HOUSE LET ME
KNOW.
WE'RE EXPECTING JUST RAIN
SHOWERS HERE AROUND THE
IMMEDIATE WASHINGTON AREA LATER
THIS MORNING AND THE RAIN WILL
CONTINUE FOR THE START OF YOUR
WEEKEND AS WELL.
OKAY.
SATELLITE/RADAR SEE THE PINK OUT
THERE.
THAT'S WHERE IT IS POSSIBLY
FALLING AS A LIGHT RAIN THAT IS
FREEZING ON THE SURFACE AND
THEREFORE FREEZING RAIN.
THAT THREAT WILL CONTINUE FOR A
FEW MORE HOURS.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY IN
EFFECT FOR THAT REGION UNTIL
3:00 O'CLOCK THIS AFTERNOON.
THERE'S A QUICK LOOK AT OUR
EXPECTED ICE ACCUMULATIONS.
I'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT COMING UP
BUT YOUR FORECAST AGAIN FREEZING
RAIN TRANSITIONING TO RAIN FOR
EVERYBODY THIS AFTERNOON.
THAT RAIN THREAT WILL CONTINUE
TONIGHT INTO YOUR DAY ON
SATURDAY AND THEN WE'LL CLEAR IT
OUT ON SUNDAY.
I'LL HAVE MORE ON THE FORECAST
IN JUST A MINUTE.
STACEY, GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, TUCKER.
WELL, WE HAVE UNFORTUNATE
ACCIDENT TO TELL YOU ABOUT THIS
MORNING IN ROCKVILLE.
WE HAVE AN ACCIDENT INVOLVING A
PEDESTRIAN.
THIS IS RIGHT ON MONTROSE ROAD
AT BAR GATE COURT.
THE GOOD NEWS EMERGENCY
RESPONDERS ARE TAKING THAT
PEDESTRIAN TO THE HOSPITAL.
SO I HOPE THAT PERSON IS OKAY.
BUT JUST WANTED TO GIVE YOU
HEADS UP THERE.
ON THE INNER LOOP, WE ALSO HAVE
A CRASH THIS MORNING THAT HAS
BEEN CLEARED AT BRADDOCK ROAD.
HOWEVER, RESIDUAL DELAYS REMAIN.
ALSO, ON THE INNER LOOP AT 123,
YOU'VE GOT TWO LEFT LANES
BLOCKED DUE TO A CRASH.
REALLY TYING YOU UP WITH SPEEDS
DOWN TO ABOUT 50 MILES PER HOUR
IN THE THICK OF THINGS AND
FINALLY ON THE INNER LOOP AT
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE WE HAVE
ANOTHER CRASH INVOLVING A
VEHICLE FIRE.
SPEEDS ARE DOWN TO JUST ABOUT
2 MILES AN HOUR.
WE'LL HAVE MORE FOX5 MORNING
NEWS AT 8:00 A.M. COMING UP.
♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Tuition goes up each
year ♪
♪ 5% so I hear ♪
♪ I really can't do math ♪
♪ But that's a lot,
I fear ♪
♪ And room and board ♪
(laughs)
- [Narrator] Invest529
gift cards make great gifts.
Learn more at
Invest529.com
- Ooh! (blows air)
I love that song.
(laughs)
Mmm, it tastes blue!
♪
>>> 8:00 O'CLOCK ON THIS FRIDAY
MORNING.
WE ARE ON WEATHER WATCH TODAY.
AREAS WEST OF D.C. WILL SOON BE
UNDER A WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY.
SOME AREAS WILL SEE SOME
FREEZING RAIN THIS MORNING WHICH
COULD MAKE FOR ICY CONDITIONS.
>> THAT LITTLE TASTE OF SOME
WINTER WEATHER PROMPTING SOME
SCHOOL CLOSINGS AND DELAYS AND
THE COMPLETE LIST SCROLLING
ALONG THE BOTTOM OF YOUR SCREEN
ON THE FOX5 WEATHER APP AND ALSO
ON OUR WEBSITE FOXDC.COM.
>> MAKE SURE TO DON'T LOAD THE
FOX5 WEATHER APP IF YOU DON'T
HAVE TUCKER BARNES IN YOUR LIFE,
WE FORTUNATELY DO, LET'S GET
RIGHT TO HIM FOR A FIRST CHECK
OF THE FORECAST.
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
YOU MENTIONED THE WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORY.
IT IS OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
HERE WE ARE IN WASHINGTON,
BALTIMORE AROUND THE IMMEDIATE
WASHINGTON AREA THERE'S NO
ADVISORY OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST PARTS OF LOUDOUN COUNTY,
FREDERICK COUNTY, OUT IN
WINCHESTER ALONG I-81.
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY IN
EFFECT FOR A COUPLE MORE HOURS.
THE THREAT IS FREEZING RAIN.
YOU WON'T GET ANY SLEET OR SNOW
WITH THIS ONE.
JUST FREEZING RAIN.
YOU CAN SEE THAT REFLECTED THIS
MORNING ON OUR STORM TRACKER
RADAR THAT PINK.
SO I'LL HAVE PLENTY MORE DETAILS
WHAT WE CAN EXPECT HERE BUT THE
GOOD NEWS IS, THIS TRANSITION TO
RAIN FOR MOST EVERYBODY LATER
THIS MORNING.
STACEY, HOW IS IT LOOKING,
STEVE, SOMEBODY ELSE.
STACEY, HI.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TOUGH COMMUTE ON THE INNER LOOP
AND PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE THIS
MORNING.
WE HAVE A CRASH INVOLVING A
VEHICLE FIRE.
SO AS YOU CAN SEE, TRAFFIC IS AT
A STAND TILL DOWN TO A MILE PER
HOUR IN THE THICK OF THINGS.
I WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED AS
THINGS PROGRESS, OF COURSE GIVE
YOU FULL LOOK AT THE DMV COMING
UP.
ALLISON, STEVE?
>> THANKS STACEY.
>>> LET GET RIGHT INTO OUR
HEADLINES THIS HOUR.
BREAKING OVERNIGHT IN PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY A MASSIVE HOUSE
FIRE IN UPPER MARLBORO.
THIS WAS THE SCENE EARLIER AND
THOSE FLAMES NOT JUST SHOOTING
THROUGH THE ROOF THEY COMPLETELY
BURN THE ROOF OFF.
IT IS STILL SMOLDERING THIS
HOUR.
THIS THE 6200 BLOCK OF CAN NOT
COURT.
EVERYBODY EVERYBODY WAS ABLE TO
GET OUT SAFE.
THERE WERE NO INJURIES.
FIREFIGHTERS HAVING A TOUGH TIME
BECAUSE THERE ARE NO HYDRANTS IN
THE AREA THEY HAD TO TRUCK IN
ALL THE WATER IT LOOKS TO BE A
TOTAL LOSS FOR THAT STRUCTURE.
>>> DEVELOPING THIS MORNING,
NINE-YEAR-OLD GIRL IS DEAD AFTER
BEING HIT BY HER OWN SCHOOLBUS
IN BETHESDA NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> NOW AS THE COMMUNITY MOURNS
THE TRAGEDY THERE ARE QUESTIONS
ABOUT HOW THIS POSSIBLY COULD
HAVE HAPPENED.
MELANIE ALNWICK OUT THERE IN THE
ENABLED THIS MORNING.
NO ANSWERS YET, MEL, THAT'S THE
UNFORTUNATE PART BUT A LOT OF
QUESTIONS.
>> Reporter: A LOT OF
QUESTIONS, AND I'M SURE A LOT OF
PARENTS ALSO JUST WONDERING HOW
THEY EXPLAIN THIS TO THEIR KIDS
ESPECIALLY THE KIDS THAT WERE
ALSO ON THAT SCHOOLBUS
YESTERDAY.
SO THIS WHERE THE BUS NORMALLY
STOPS.
IT'S HERE AT TANGLE WOOD AND
MILLWOOD, AND THE BUS LET'S
PEOPLE -- LET'S THE KIDS OFF AT
TANGLE WOOD AND WE'RE TOLD THE
KIDS NORMALLY WALK DOWN TANGLE
WOOD TO WHERE THEIR PARENTS
OFTEN WAIT IN THE CARS AND THEN
THE SCHOOLBUS TURNS HERE.
YOU CAN SEE HERE THAT THESE ARE
THE MARKINGS WHERE THE REAR
TIRES AND THE FRONT TIRES OF THE
BUS CAME TO REST.
NOW, POLICE HAVE NOT RELEASED
THE NAME OF THE NINE-YEAR-OLD
GIRL YET.
THE PRINCIPAL OF BRADLEY HILLS
ELEMENTARY IS ASKING THE
COMMUNITY TO GIVE HER FAMILY
PRIVACY TO GRIEVE.
SCHOOLBUS NUMBER 13037 REMAINED
PARKED ON MILLWOOD ROAD MOST OF
THE NIGHT AS MONTGOMERY COUNTY
INVESTIGATORS DOCUMENTED THE
SCENE OF THE COLLISION.
THE BUS HAD JUST LEFT BRADLEY
HILLS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND HAD
DROPPED OFF SEVERAL STUDENTS ON
TANGLE WOOD DRIVE.
THE DRIVER A 53-YEAR-OLD FROM
SEVERN MARYLAND TURNED RIGHT ON
TO MILLWOOD AS THE DRIVER US
USUALLY DOES AND FORINTS STILL
UNDER INVESTIGATION STRUCK THE
FOURTH GRADER.
NEIGHBORS THIS MORNING TOLD US
THAT THEY ALSO SEE THE DRIVER
WATCHING CAREFULLY AS THE
STUDENTS ARE LET OFF THE BUS.
>> THE BUS PULLS UP.
USUALLY ALL THE PARENTS ARE
ALREADY HERE, SO IT'S LIKE I
CAN'T GET MY CAR OUT OF THE
GARAGE, AND THE BUS PULLS UP,
PUTS OUT THE ARM, ALL THE CARS
DRIVE PASSED IT THEY DON'T EVEN
STOP WHICH MAKES NO SENSE, AND
THE BUS DRIVER DOES EVERYTHING
RIGHT.
ALL THE KIDS USUALLY GO LEFT.
>> Reporter: NOT GIRL WAS
TAKEN BY AMBULANCE TO CHILDREN'S
NATIONAL MEDICAL CENTER.
IT WAS JUST BEFORE 4:00 P.M.
8:45 LAST NIGHT POLICE NOTIFIED
THE COMMUNITY THAT THE GIRL DID
NOT SURVIVE HER INJURIES.
AS YOU CAN IMAGINE THERE EXTRA
COUNSELING STAFF AT BRADLEY
HILLS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TODAY.
CRASH INVESTIGATOR DID TELL FOX5
ON THE SCENE THAT THE DRIVER WAS
NOT IMPAIRED.
AGAIN THEY'RE STILL LOOKING INTO
EXACTLY WHERE THE BUS WAS GOING,
WHERE THE GIRL WAS GOING, AND
ALL OF THIS COMES AS MONTGOMERY
COUNTY IS HAVING A MEETING
TOMORROW ON ITS VISION ZERO
THAT'S TRYING TO REDUCE
PEDESTRIAN DEATHS AND COLLISIONS
TO ZERO.
THAT WAS PREVIOUSLY PLANNED.
COUNCIL MEMBERS SAYING THERE
HAVE BEEN 11 DEATHS AND 579
COLLISIONS BETWEEN VEHICLES AND
PEDESTRIANS OR BICYCLISTS JUST
THIS YEAR.
>> MEL, THANKS VERY MUCH.
TRAGIC STORY INDEED.
LET'S GO FROM MONTGOMERY COUNTY
DOWN TO CHARLES COUNTY.
TRY TO FOLLOW ALONG ON THIS
BIZARRE STORY.
SEARCH CONTINUES FOR THE MAN WHO
KIDNAPPED A WOMAN FROM HER HOME,
FORCED HER TO GET INTO HIS CAR
AND WITHDRAWAL MONEY AT SEVERAL
ATM'S.
THIS WAS IN WALDORF WEDNESDAY
NIGHT.
THEN AFTER LEAVING HER IS IT A
TREAT CORNER HE DROVE INTO A
BOWLING ALLEY WITH HIS VEHICLE
TO TRY TO BREAK INTO AN ATM.
WAS NOT ABLE TO DO SO.
LEFT EMPTY HANDED.
POLICE ARE STILL LOOKING FOR
HIM.
♪
>>> 8:05 RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GET TO SOMETHING WE CAN
UNDERSTAND.
>> FRIDAY.
>> THE SCIENCE BEHIND THE
WEATHER.
>> OH YEAH.
>> IT'S FRIDAY.
>> LET'S DIVE INTO THE WEATHER.
OBVIOUSLY YOU PROBABLY HEARD THE
FREEZING RAIN THREAT IS A REAL
ONE.
OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
THE GOOD NEWS IS, THIS WILL NOT
BE ALL DAY EVENT.
>> GOOD.
>> THIS WILL CHANGE TO RAIN EAR
QUICKLY FOR MOST EVERYBODY BUT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU WON'T
ENCOUNTER OR COULDN'T ENCOUNTER
AN ICY SPOT IN THE NEXT COUPLE
OF HOURS.
REAGAN NATIONAL NOW 37.
NOTICE ALL THREE AREA AIRPORTS
ABOVE FREEZING.
THAT'S A GREAT SIGN IT IS GOING
TO BE A COOL DAY.
LISTEN FOR MOST OF US IT'S GOING
TO BE A RAINY DAY SO TAKE THE
UMBRELLA HERE AS YOU HEAD OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
THE EXCEPTION NORTH AND WEST
THAT'S WHERE THE RAIN COULD TURN
TO FREEZING RAIN, AND WHEN
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE SKY IT
LOOKS LIKE RAIN FALLING WHEN IT
HITS A SURFACE AT OR BELOW 42 IT
FREEZES ON CONTACT THAT'S WHY WE
HAVE A WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
NORTH AND WEST UNTIL
3:00 O'CLOCK THIS AFTERNOON.
IT DOES INCLUDE COUNTIES IN
CLOSE AS FREDERICK COUNTY, PARTS
OF LOUDOUN COUNTY, FAUQUIER
COUNTY AND MUCH OF NORTHERN
VIRGINIA, WEST VIRGINIA UNDER
THAT WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY.
ALL RIGHT.
LIVE LOOK AT YOUR STORM TRACKER
RADAR AND AREA SHADED IN PINK
PERHAPS ALONG 81 THERE WE'RE
GETTING SOME LIGHT RETURNS THAT
COULD INDICATE SOME LIGHT
FREEZING RAIN.
SO REALLY BE CAUTIOUS IF YOU'RE
OFF TO THE NORTH AND WEST.
THE BIG PICTURE WE'RE GOING TO
WARM UP THE ATMOSPHERE HERE AS
WE GET A LOT OF MOISTURE MOVING
IN FROM THE SOUTH.
MOST OF THE DAY FOR MOST OF THE
REGION IT'S GOING TO BE JUST
PLANE RAIN.
ON AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN SHOWERS
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
IF YOU GOT PLANS YOU'RE GOING
OUT THIS EVENING, RAIN SHOWERS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> ALLISON YOU WANT TO GO OUT
TOMORROW.
>> UH-HUH.
>> RAIN SHOWERS.
>> MORE ON THE WEEKEND FORECAST
COMING RIGHT UP BUT WITH A
TEMPERATURE AT 45 WE'RE ONLY
CONCERNED WITH WHAT?
>> FREEZING.
>> RAIN SHOWERS THIS AFTERNOON.
>> OH YEAH.
>> FREEZING RAIN.
>> SO MANY MIXED MESSAGES.
THANKS.
>> WEEKEND FORECAST COMING UP.
>> HI, STACEY.
>> HI.
THAT'S A TOUGH FORECAST, AND
IT'S PRETTY TOUGH ON THE ROADS
AS WELL THIS MORNING.
ON THE OUTER LOOP, WE'VE GOT A
CRASH THIS IS RIGHT BEFORE RIVER
ROAD BECAUSE OF THAT CRASH THE
TWO RIGHT LANES ARE BLOCKED.
YOU CAN SEE IN THIS CAMERA THAT
YOU SEE THOSE LIGHTS FLASHING IT
LOOK LIKE WE HAVE POLICE AND
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS ON SIGHT.
BUT THAT WILL DEFINITELY SLOW
YOU UP THIS MORNING.
MOVING OVER TO ROCKVILLE, WE
HAVE REPORTS THAT A PEDESTRIAN
WAS STRUCK THIS MORNING.
THIS WAS RIGHT ON MONTROSE ROAD
AT BAR GATE COURT.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT PEDESTRIAN
IS ON HIS OR HER WAY TO THE
HOSPITAL.
SO WE HOPE THEY ARE OKAY.
BUT JUST SOMETHING TO BE AWARE
OF THIS MORNING.
MOVING OVER TO THE INNER LOOP AT
BRADDOCK ROAD, WE HAD A CRASH
EARLIER.
IT HAS BEEN CLEARED.
BUT WE DO HAVE SOME RESIDUAL
DELAYS.
AS WE LOOK AT THE INNER LOOP AT
123, WE'VE GOT TWO LEFT LANES
BLOCKED DUE TO A CRASH.
THIS IS SLOWING DOWN TO ABOUT
8 MILES PER HOUR IN THE THICK OF
THINGS.
ALSO, AFFECTING 66.
66 IS ALSO DOWN TO 20 MILES PER
HOUR WHERE THEY CONNECT.
I'LL GIVE YOU A COMPLETE LOOK AT
THE DMV COMING UP.
ALLISON, STEVE?
>> STACEY, THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> NOW HAPPENING TODAY, SOME
COURT APPEARANCES FOR SOME OF
THE FORMER NFL PLAYERS ACCUSED
OF BY FEDERAL AUTHORITIES NOW IN
A MASSIVE HEALTH CAR FRAUD.
THAT INCLUDES THIS GUY, CLINTON
PORTIS.
TWO FORMER WASHINGTON REDSKINS
PLAYERS AMONG 10 RETIRED NFL
PLAYERS ACCUSED OF.
CLINTON PORTIS AND CARLOS ROGERS
THE FORMER REDSKINS NOW FACING
FEDERAL CHARGES THIS MORNING.
ACCUSED OF SCHEMING TO RIP OFF
THE LEAGUE'S HELL CARE PROGRAM
FOR RETIRED PLAYERS.
IT'S A SYSTEM THAT REIMBURSES
THE MEN AND THEIR FAMILIES FOR
MEDICAL EXPENSES NOT COVERED BY
INSURANCE.
THE FORMER PLAYERS ACCUSED OF
SUBMITTING FAKE CLAIMS FOR
EXPENSIVE MEDICAL EQUIPMENT THEY
NEVER PURCHASED.
A LAWYER FOR CLINTON PORTIS DID
ISSUE A STATEMENT CLAIMING THE
RETIRED RUNNING BACK HAD NO
KNOWLEDGE THAT HIS PARTICIPATION
IN WHAT HE BELIEVED TO BE AN NFL
SANCTIONED MEDICAL REIMBURSEMENT
INSURANCE PROGRAM WAS ILLEGAL.
♪
>>> NEW SUICIDE PREVENTION
HOTLINE WILL SOON MAKE SEEKING
HELP FOR MENTAL HEALTH
EMERGENCIES ANN AS EASY AS
DIALING 911.
THIS AS FEDERAL REGULATORS ARE
CREATING A NEW THREE DIGIT
SUICIDE HOTLINE NUMBER.
BOB BARNARD HAS MORE FOR US THIS
MORNING.
GOOD MORNING, BOB.
>> Reporter: ALLISON, GOOD
MORNING TO YOU.
THE CURRENT SUICIDE PREVENTION
HOTLINE IS A RANDOM 800 NUMBER.
ONCE IN PLACE THE NEW LIFELINE
WILL BE SIMILAR TO CALLING 911
FOR EMERGENCIES OR 311 FOR CITY
SERVICES.
ACCORDING TO THE WORLD HEALTH
ORGANIZATION, APPROXIMATELY
1 MILLION PEOPLE DIE FROM
SUICIDE EACH YEAR.
GLOBALLY THAT'S ONE DEATH EVERY
40 SECONDS AND THE AGE SEE
PREDICTS THE NUMBER WILL
INCREASE TO ONE EVERY 20 SECONDS
NEXT YEAR.
TO TRY TO PREVENT THIS GROWING
EPIDEMIC, THE FEDERAL
COMMUNICATIONS COMMISSION VOTED
THURSDAY TO ESTABLISH A THREE
DIGIT PHONE NUMBER 988 TO HELP
THOSE IN DISTRESS.
>> ANYONE WHO CALLS 988 WOULD BE
ROUTED TO THE ESTABLISHED
NATIONAL SUICIDE PREVENTION
LIFELINE THEY COULD BE ASSISTED
BY TRAINED COUNSELORS.
>> Reporter: CURRENTLY THE
NATIONAL SUICIDE PREVENTION
LIFELINE USES A 10 DUST NUMBER
WHERE LAST YEAR 2.2 MILLION
CALLS WERE ROUTED TO 163 CRISIS
CENTERS.
SOON, CALLING 988 WILL BE AS
EASY AS DIALING 911.
>> I BELIEVE 988 COULD HELP.
IT HAS AN ECHO OF 911 A NUMBER
WE ALL KNOW AND AWARENESS OF
THIS RESOURCE SHOULD MAKE A REAL
DIFFERENCE WHEN THOSE IN CRISIS
NEED A LIFELINE.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL
REGUREGULATORS ARE HOPING ONCE
IMPLEMENTED THE NEW DEDICATED
NUMBER WILL NOT ONLY BE EASIER
TO REMEMBER BUT HELP REDUCE THE
STIGMA ASSOCIATED WITH MENTAL
HEALTH.
>> I THINK THAT IT WILL HAVE A
MAJOR DIFFERENCE BECAUSE IT WILL
NORMALIZE IT.
IT WILL SAY THAT JUST LIKE WE
TREAT ANY OTHER EMERGENCY, WE
SHOULD BE TREATING THE
EMERGENCIES OF THE MIND.
>> Reporter: NOW THE PROCESS
OF STABBING THE 988 SYSTEM IS
EXPECTED TO TAKE MONTHS WITH THE
FCC PROPOSING TO GIVE SERVICE
PROVIDERS 18 MONTHS TO
ACCOMMODATE THE NEW NUMBER.
WE SHOULD NOTE 988 WILL NOT BE
AVAILABLE BY TEXT.
GUYS?
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, BOB.
>>> STILL AHEAD A LOT OF FOCUS
ON HOME SECURITY CAMERAS
RECENTLY AS MORE PEOPLE SHARE
CREEPY STORIES OF THE DEVICES
BEING HACKED BUT THIS MORNING,
ONE APP IS ENCOURAGING PARENTS
TO SPY ON A BABYSITTER OR NANNY.
SO DOES IT GO TOO FAR?
>> PLUS, SEXIST STRIP CLUB?
THINK ABOUT THAT ONE.
TWO WOMEN ARE SUING A STRIP CLUB
BECAUSE THEY CANNOT GET INSIDE.
LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE AS WE HEAD TO
BREAK.
WEATHER AND TRAFFIC COMING UP ON
THE 5'S NEXT IT'S 8:12.
♪
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately to
severely active Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed relief
and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house needs
or recently had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how Janssen can help
you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start with
STELARA®.
>>> HOPEFULLY YOU'RE READY FOR
THE HOLIDAYS.
THE LIGHTS LOOK PRETTY.
>> GORGEOUS.
>> IN GAITHERSBURG.
SO PRETTY THE TREE AT RIO.
>> THE TRIO.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
SPEAKING OF TRIOS HERE'S THE
THREE OF US.
>> AWE.
>> THE THREE AMIGOS.
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> ON FRIDAY THE 13th.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
LET'S HOP IN I GOT WEATHER TO
>>> ALL RIGHT.
TALK ABOUT.
LET'S HOP IN I GOT WEATHER TO
RAIN SHOWERS FOR MOST OF US,
TALK ABOUT.
TODAY.
RAIN SHOWERS FOR MOST OF US,
THANK YOU I JUST GOT A VIEWER
TODAY.
THAT TWEETED ME OUT IN THE
THANK YOU I JUST GOT A VIEWER
MOUNTAINS MUCH SHE TELLS ME IT'S
THAT TWEETED ME OUT IN THE
33 AND RAINING AT HER HOUSE.
MOUNTAINS MUCH SHE TELLS ME IT'S
>> OKAY.
33 AND RAINING AT HER HOUSE.
>> STAY ABOVE 32 FOR YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> STAY ABOVE 32 FOR YOU.
WE CAN'T CALL IT ALL CLEAR YET
>> EXACTLY.
BECAUSE THE THREAT OF FREEZING
WE CAN'T CALL IT ALL CLEAR YET
RAIN IS THERE FOR A FEW MORE
BECAUSE THE THREAT OF FREEZING
HOURS.
RAIN IS THERE FOR A FEW MORE
NOTICE TEMPERATURES.
HOURS.
THIS IS GREAT NEWS.
NOTICE TEMPERATURES.
37 IN WASHINGTON.
THIS IS GREAT NEWS.
GAITHERSBURG ABOVE FREEZING NOW.
37 IN WASHINGTON.
DULL LET'S, FREDERICK ABOVE
GAITHERSBURG ABOVE FREEZING NOW.
FREEZING.
DULL LET'S, FREDERICK ABOVE
WINCHESTER MARTINSBURG COMER
FREEZING.
LAND STILL HANGING ON TO THE
WINCHESTER MARTINSBURG COMER
FREEZING MARK AND IT IS OFF TO
LAND STILL HANGING ON TO THE
THE NORTH AND WEST WHERE WE HAVE
FREEZING MARK AND IT IS OFF TO
THIS THREAT OF A LIGHT FREEZING
THE NORTH AND WEST WHERE WE HAVE
RAIN EVENT AND YOU CAN SEE THE
THIS THREAT OF A LIGHT FREEZING
STORM TRACKER RADAR SEE THE
RAIN EVENT AND YOU CAN SEE THE
PINKS THERE THAT'S INDICATING
STORM TRACKER RADAR SEE THE
THE POSSIBILITY OF LIGHT
PINKS THERE THAT'S INDICATING
FREEZING RAIN SO CERTAINLY OUT
THE POSSIBILITY OF LIGHT
IN THE MOUNTAINS YOU GUYS HAVE
FREEZING RAIN SO CERTAINLY OUT
THAT POSSIBILITY NEXT COUPLE OF
IN THE MOUNTAINS YOU GUYS HAVE
HOURS AS CLOSE IN AS LOUDOUN
THAT POSSIBILITY NEXT COUPLE OF
COUNTY, PERHAPS PARTS OF
HOURS AS CLOSE IN AS LOUDOUN
FAUQUIER COUNTY, FREDERICK
COUNTY, PERHAPS PARTS OF
COUNTY YOU MIGHT GET A LIGHT
FAUQUIER COUNTY, FREDERICK
GLAZE HERE AS THE ATMOSPHERE
COUNTY YOU MIGHT GET A LIGHT
GRADUALLY WARMS THIS IS ALL
GLAZE HERE AS THE ATMOSPHERE
GOING TO CHANGE OVER PRETTY
GRADUALLY WARMS THIS IS ALL
QUICKLY TO ALL RAIN AND THEN
GOING TO CHANGE OVER PRETTY
WE'LL GOING TO BE IN FOR ON
QUICKLY TO ALL RAIN AND THEN
AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN LATER THIS
WE'LL GOING TO BE IN FOR ON
AFTERNOON AND THIS EVENING AND
AGAIN OFF AGAIN RAIN LATER THIS
SHOWERS WILL LINGER INTO THE DAY
AFTERNOON AND THIS EVENING AND
ON SATURDAY.
SHOWERS WILL LINGER INTO THE DAY
FUTURE CAST THERE WE ARE AT
ON SATURDAY.
11:00.
FUTURE CAST THERE WE ARE AT
NOTICE THERE'S NO LONGER ANY
11:00.
PINK THERE IN OUR FUTURE CAST
NOTICE THERE'S NO LONGER ANY
EXCEPT FOR WELL WELL NORTH AND
PINK THERE IN OUR FUTURE CAST
WEST.
EXCEPT FOR WELL WELL NORTH AND
RAIN FOR JUST ABOUT EVERYBODY AT
WEST.
THAT HOUR.
RAIN FOR JUST ABOUT EVERYBODY AT
AND THEN RAIN SHOWERS FILL IN
THAT HOUR.
LATER THIS AFTERNOON IF YOU'RE
AND THEN RAIN SHOWERS FILL IN
GOING OUT THIS EVENING YOU'LL
LATER THIS AFTERNOON IF YOU'RE
NEED THE UMBRELLA.
GOING OUT THIS EVENING YOU'LL
IT WILL BE COOL AS WELL DAYTIME
NEED THE UMBRELLA.
HIGHS ONLY IN THE MID 40S.
IT WILL BE COOL AS WELL DAYTIME
SO YOU GET A SENSE OF WHAT WE'RE
HIGHS ONLY IN THE MID 40S.
LOOKING ALT THE NEXT COUPLE OF
SO YOU GET A SENSE OF WHAT WE'RE
DAYS.
LOOKING ALT THE NEXT COUPLE OF
>> TOMORROW 52.
DAYS.
RAIN SHOWERS CONTINUE THINGS
>> TOMORROW 52.
SHOULD IMPROVE IN THE AFTERNOON.
RAIN SHOWERS CONTINUE THINGS
SUNDAY WE CLEAR OUT JUST IN TIME
SHOULD IMPROVE IN THE AFTERNOON.
FOR THE REDSKINS WIN.
SUNDAY WE CLEAR OUT JUST IN TIME
THAT'S RIGHT I'M CALLING IT
FOR THE REDSKINS WIN.
EARLY.
THAT'S RIGHT I'M CALLING IT
AND THEN PERHAPS ANOTHER WINTRY
EARLY.
MIX TO KICK OFF NEXT WEEK ON
AND THEN PERHAPS ANOTHER WINTRY
MONDAY.
MIX TO KICK OFF NEXT WEEK ON
SO STAY TUNED FOR THAT FORECAST.
MONDAY.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT LATER
SO STAY TUNED FOR THAT FORECAST.
THIS MORNING.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT LATER
I'LL BE TWEETING ABOUT THAT AS
THIS MORNING.
WELL.
I'LL BE TWEETING ABOUT THAT AS
I'M OUT.
WELL.
STACEY IS IN.
I'M OUT.
>> THANKS, TUCKER.
STACEY IS IN.
>> THE ROADS ARE PICKING UP THIS
>> THANKS, TUCKER.
MORNING FOR SURE.
>> THE ROADS ARE PICKING UP THIS
WANT TO KEEP UPDATED REGARDING A
MORNING FOR SURE.
NEW INCIDENTS.
WANT TO KEEP UPDATED REGARDING A
LET'S FIRST TALK ABOUT THE OUTER
NEW INCIDENTS.
LOOP.
LET'S FIRST TALK ABOUT THE OUTER
WE HAVE ARE A* CRASH BLOCKING
LOOP.
THE TWO RIGHT LANES BEFORE RIVER
WE HAVE ARE A* CRASH BLOCKING
ROAD.
THE TWO RIGHT LANES BEFORE RIVER
AS YOU CAN SEE IN THIS LIVE S
ROAD.
SHOT, REALLY SLOWING DOWN THIS
AS YOU CAN SEE IN THIS LIVE S
MORNING.
SHOT, REALLY SLOWING DOWN THIS
THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT EMERGENCY
MORNING.
RESPONDERS AND POLICE I SHOULD
THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT EMERGENCY
SAY ARE ON SIGHT.
RESPONDERS AND POLICE I SHOULD
LOOKS LIKE THEY ARE DOING THEIR
SAY ARE ON SIGHT.
BEST TO CLEAR THAT ACCIDENT UP.
LOOKS LIKE THEY ARE DOING THEIR
ALSO, SPEAKING OF ACCIDENTS, WE
BEST TO CLEAR THAT ACCIDENT UP.
HAD AN ACCIDENT INVOLVING A
ALSO, SPEAKING OF ACCIDENTS, WE
PEDESTRIAN THIS MORNING.
HAD AN ACCIDENT INVOLVING A
THIS WAS RIGHT ON MONTROSE ROAD
PEDESTRIAN THIS MORNING.
AT BAR GATE COURT BECAUSE OF
THIS WAS RIGHT ON MONTROSE ROAD
THAT THE PEDESTRIAN HAS BEEN
AT BAR GATE COURT BECAUSE OF
TRANSPORTED TO THE HOSPITAL.
THAT THE PEDESTRIAN HAS BEEN
BUT BECAUSE OF THE ACCIDENT AND
TRANSPORTED TO THE HOSPITAL.
THE CRASH INVESTIGATION, THAT
BUT BECAUSE OF THE ACCIDENT AND
FOLLOWED, MONTROSE ROAD IS
THE CRASH INVESTIGATION, THAT
CLOSED BETWEEN MON ROSE PARKWAY
FOLLOWED, MONTROSE ROAD IS
AND JEFFERSON STREET.
CLOSED BETWEEN MON ROSE PARKWAY
SO PLEASE TAKE CARE IF YOU ARE
AND JEFFERSON STREET.
IN THAT AREA AND HOPEFULLY THAT
SO PLEASE TAKE CARE IF YOU ARE
PEDESTRIAN IS OKAY.
IN THAT AREA AND HOPEFULLY THAT
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
PEDESTRIAN IS OKAY.
BACK TO YOU ALLISON AND STEVE.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
>>> I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND.
BACK TO YOU ALLISON AND STEVE.
I'M SANTA CLAUS.
>>> I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND.
>> WE SHOWED YOU THIS
I'M SANTA CLAUS.
FRIGHTENING VIDEO YESTERDAY.
>> WE SHOWED YOU THIS
IT'S A HACKER GAINING ACCESS TO
FRIGHTENING VIDEO YESTERDAY.
A RING SECURITY THAT LITTLE GIRL
IT'S A HACKER GAINING ACCESS TO
YELLING FOR HER MOM THAT WAS IN
A RING SECURITY THAT LITTLE GIRL
A LITTLE GIRL'S BEDROOM.
YELLING FOR HER MOM THAT WAS IN
THE STORY IS RENEWING A DEBATE
A LITTLE GIRL'S BEDROOM.
ABOUT THE SECURITY OF SECURITY
THE STORY IS RENEWING A DEBATE
CAMERAS.
ABOUT THE SECURITY OF SECURITY
BUT THIS MORNING THERE'S AN APP
CAMERAS.
THAT ENCOURAGES PEOPLE TO SPY ON
BUT THIS MORNING THERE'S AN APP
OTHERS SPECIFICALLY FOR PARENTS
THAT ENCOURAGES PEOPLE TO SPY ON
TO KEEP TABS ON A NANNY OR A
OTHERS SPECIFICALLY FOR PARENTS
BABYSITTER.
TO KEEP TABS ON A NANNY OR A
IT'S CALLED STROLLER PATROL IT'S
BABYSITTER.
SET TO ROLL OUT IN NEW YORK CITY
IT'S CALLED STROLLER PATROL IT'S
SOON.
SET TO ROLL OUT IN NEW YORK CITY
NOW THE APP IS FREE.
SOON.
PARENTS AND THE NANNY OR
NOW THE APP IS FREE.
BABYSITTER BOTH CAN SIGN UP FOR
PARENTS AND THE NANNY OR
IT OR TESTIFY TO SIGN UP FOR IT.
BABYSITTER BOTH CAN SIGN UP FOR
APP ALLOWS PARENTS TO SEE THE
IT OR TESTIFY TO SIGN UP FOR IT.
TRACKING TECHNOLOGY.
APP ALLOWS PARENTS TO SEE THE
OTHER APP USERS NEARBY CAN LET
TRACKING TECHNOLOGY.
PARENTS KNOW IF THE NANNY IS
OTHER APP USERS NEARBY CAN LET
MISTREATING A CHILD OR BEING
PARENTS KNOW IF THE NANNY IS
NEGLIGENT.
MISTREATING A CHILD OR BEING
CRITICS OF THE APP SAY IT'S AN
NEGLIGENT.
INVASION OF PRIVACY.
CRITICS OF THE APP SAY IT'S AN
SO LET'S BRING IN OUR FELLOW
INVASION OF PRIVACY.
FOX5 MOMS TO WEIGH IN ON THIS,
SO LET'S BRING IN OUR FELLOW
GOOD MORNING, MO AND HOLLY.
FOX5 MOMS TO WEIGH IN ON THIS,
CLEARLY THIS IS REALLY NOTHING
GOOD MORNING, MO AND HOLLY.
NEW BUT THERE ARE ADDED
CLEARLY THIS IS REALLY NOTHING
ENHANCEMENTS HERE TO BRING OTHER
NEW BUT THERE ARE ADDED
PEOPLE INTO THE EQUATION TO LET
ENHANCEMENTS HERE TO BRING OTHER
YOU KNOW IF YOUR NANNY OR
PEOPLE INTO THE EQUATION TO LET
BABYSITTER IS BEHAVING BADLY.
YOU KNOW IF YOUR NANNY OR
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
BABYSITTER IS BEHAVING BADLY.
THIS.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
THIS.
I THINK IF YOU'RE A GOOD NANNY
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
YOU SHOULDN'T WORRY THAT SOMEONE
I THINK IF YOU'RE A GOOD NANNY
WANTS TO CHECK IN ON YOU OR
YOU SHOULDN'T WORRY THAT SOMEONE
THEIR CHILD.
WANTS TO CHECK IN ON YOU OR
I HAVE SEEN SITUATIONS WHERE
THEIR CHILD.
NANNIES CLEARLY MISTREATING A
I HAVE SEEN SITUATIONS WHERE
CHILD AND I WISHED TO GOD I HAD
NANNIES CLEARLY MISTREATING A
THAT PARENT'S INFORMATION TO
CHILD AND I WISHED TO GOD I HAD
WARN THEM THAT THIS PERSON IS
THAT PARENT'S INFORMATION TO
NOT ON THE UP AND UP.
WARN THEM THAT THIS PERSON IS
I MEAN IT'S HEARTBREAKING WHEN
NOT ON THE UP AND UP.
YOU ENTRUST YOUR CHILD, YOUR
I MEAN IT'S HEARTBREAKING WHEN
LIFE, TO SOMEONE AND THEY
YOU ENTRUST YOUR CHILD, YOUR
MISTREAT THAT PERSON.
LIFE, TO SOMEONE AND THEY
MY GOODNESS ANYTHING YOU CAN DO
MISTREAT THAT PERSON.
TO MAKE SURE THAT THAT DOESN'T
MY GOODNESS ANYTHING YOU CAN DO
HAPPEN.
TO MAKE SURE THAT THAT DOESN'T
I'M ALL FOR IT.
HAPPEN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'M ALL FOR IT.
IT'S YOUR MOST PRIZED POTION YOU
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HAVE IS YOUR CHILD, RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR MOST PRIZED POTION YOU
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HAVE IS YOUR CHILD, RIGHT.
>> THE NANNY HAS TO SIGN UP FOR
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT SO IT'S NOT AN INVASION OF
>> THE NANNY HAS TO SIGN UP FOR
PRIVACY BECAUSE IT'S NOT SOME
IT SO IT'S NOT AN INVASION OF
SECRET THING LIKE THEY DON'T
PRIVACY BECAUSE IT'S NOT SOME
KNOW THEY'RE BEING WATCHED, AND
SECRET THING LIKE THEY DON'T
THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE PROBLEM
KNOW THEY'RE BEING WATCHED, AND
BEING WATCHED, AND OTHER PEOPLE
THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE PROBLEM
BEING ABLE TO WEIGH IN ON IT F
BEING WATCHED, AND OTHER PEOPLE
THEY'RE A PART OF THAT SERVICE
BEING ABLE TO WEIGH IN ON IT F
IS JUST LIKE GOOD OLD-FASHIONED
THEY'RE A PART OF THAT SERVICE
NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH.
IS JUST LIKE GOOD OLD-FASHIONED
>> RIGHT.
NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH.
>> RIGHT?  WE PUT THOSE --
>> RIGHT.
>> NEXT DOOR APPS PEOPLE USE
>> RIGHT?  WE PUT THOSE --
NOW.
>> NEXT DOOR APPS PEOPLE USE
>> YOU PUT THOSE SIGNS HEY,
NOW.
YOU'RE WATCHING OUT FOR OTHER
>> YOU PUT THOSE SIGNS HEY,
PEOPLE'S KIDS, YOU KNOW WHAT, IF
YOU'RE WATCHING OUT FOR OTHER
SOMEONE WAS MISTREATING MY KID,
PEOPLE'S KIDS, YOU KNOW WHAT, IF
I WOULD WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
SOMEONE WAS MISTREATING MY KID,
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I WOULD WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
>> JUST LIKE I THINK ANY PARENT
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WOULD.
>> JUST LIKE I THINK ANY PARENT
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH IT.
WOULD.
>> YUP.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH IT.
>> ALMOST LIKE PREACHING TO THE
>> YUP.
CHOIR.
>> ALMOST LIKE PREACHING TO THE
>> RIGHT.
CHOIR.
>> WITH IT, RIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
>> WITH IT, RIGHT.
>> BECAUSE IF YOU DO SIGN UP AS
>> THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
A NANNY, YOU KNOW THAT YOU'RE
>> BECAUSE IF YOU DO SIGN UP AS
NOT GOING TO -- YOU'RE GOING TO
A NANNY, YOU KNOW THAT YOU'RE
BE ON YOUR BEST BEHAVIOR BUT
NOT GOING TO -- YOU'RE GOING TO
PROBABLY ALREADY REALLY GOOD
BE ON YOUR BEST BEHAVIOR BUT
CAREGIVER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
PROBABLY ALREADY REALLY GOOD
OKAY.
CAREGIVER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SO THIS IS ROLLING OUT AGAIN
OKAY.
IT'S IN NEW YORK CITY.
SO THIS IS ROLLING OUT AGAIN
LADIES, THANK YOU.
IT'S IN NEW YORK CITY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LADIES, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU BRING
>> OKAY.
ME IN FOR THE STRIPPER STORY BUT
>>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU BRING
HERE WE GO.
ME IN FOR THE STRIPPER STORY BUT
TWO WOMEN SUING A FLORIDA STRIP
HERE WE GO.
CLUB BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
TWO WOMEN SUING A FLORIDA STRIP
ALLOWED INSIDE.
CLUB BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
THEY SAY THE PLACE CALLED
ALLOWED INSIDE.
RACHEL'S ORLANDO TURNED THEM
THEY SAY THE PLACE CALLED
AWAY BECAUSE THE CLUB THOUGHT
RACHEL'S ORLANDO TURNED THEM
THEY MAY DRAWS MEN ATTENTION
AWAY BECAUSE THE CLUB THOUGHT
AWAY FROM THE DANCERS.
THEY MAY DRAWS MEN ATTENTION
BOUNCERS WERE WORRIED THE
AWAY FROM THE DANCERS.
HUSBAND WERE LOOKING FOR THAT
BOUNCERS WERE WORRIED THE
ARE HUSBAND AT THE STRIP CLUB.
HUSBAND WERE LOOKING FOR THAT
IT WOULD NOT ALLOW ANY WOMEN NOT
ARE HUSBAND AT THE STRIP CLUB.
ACCOMPANIED BY A MAN.
IT WOULD NOT ALLOW ANY WOMEN NOT
THE PLAINTIFFS HERE NOW ACCUSE
ACCOMPANIED BY A MAN.
THE CLUB OF SEX BASED
THE PLAINTIFFS HERE NOW ACCUSE
DISCRIMINATION.
THE CLUB OF SEX BASED
I DID A LITTLE RESEARCH INTO
DISCRIMINATION.
THIS.
I DID A LITTLE RESEARCH INTO
THE WHOLE SITUATION SEEMS A
THIS.
LITTLE WEIRD.
THE WHOLE SITUATION SEEMS A
FIRST OF ALL, YES, ON THE
LITTLE WEIRD.
SURFACE IT OBVIOUSLY SOUNDS
FIRST OF ALL, YES, ON THE
EXACTLY LIKE WHAT WE JUST
SURFACE IT OBVIOUSLY SOUNDS
PRESENTED, THE ONLY QUESTION I
EXACTLY LIKE WHAT WE JUST
HAVE THE ONE WOMAN WAS A
PRESENTED, THE ONLY QUESTION I
FREQUENT VISITOR OF THIS CLUB.
HAVE THE ONE WOMAN WAS A
>> OKAY.
FREQUENT VISITOR OF THIS CLUB.
>> APPARENTLY SHE WENT ON A
>> OKAY.
WEEKLY BASIS BUT TYPICALLY WITH
>> APPARENTLY SHE WENT ON A
A GUY.
WEEKLY BASIS BUT TYPICALLY WITH
SHE GOES TO THE CLUB.
A GUY.
SHE SEE AS DANCER WHO REMINDS
SHE GOES TO THE CLUB.
HER OF HER FRIEND SO SHE CALLS
SHE SEE AS DANCER WHO REMINDS
HER FRIEND TO MEET HER AT THE
HER OF HER FRIEND SO SHE CALLS
CLUB WHICH HER FRIEND DOES.
HER FRIEND TO MEET HER AT THE
THEY CANNOT GET INSIDE HAD HE
CLUB WHICH HER FRIEND DOES.
CALLED HER FRIEND WHO LIVED IN
THEY CANNOT GET INSIDE HAD HE
ALABAMA 480 MILES AWAY WHO FOR
CALLED HER FRIEND WHO LIVED IN
SOME REASON DROVE 480 MILES TO
ALABAMA 480 MILES AWAY WHO FOR
MEET AT THE CLUB.
SOME REASON DROVE 480 MILES TO
>> NO.
MEET AT THE CLUB.
>> OF WHICH THEY WERE TURNED
>> NO.
AWAY.
>> OF WHICH THEY WERE TURNED
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHAT ALL IS
AWAY.
GOING ON HERE.
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHAT ALL IS
BUT ON THE SURFACE, YES, IT DOES
GOING ON HERE.
SEEM SEXIST TO NOT LET THE LA
BUT ON THE SURFACE, YES, IT DOES
LADINGS INSIDE BECAUSE OF THE
SEEM SEXIST TO NOT LET THE LA
CLUB'S POLICY.
LADINGS INSIDE BECAUSE OF THE
>> SOMEBODY IS RUNNING A GAME
CLUB'S POLICY.
THERE.
>> SOMEBODY IS RUNNING A GAME
THE ALABAMA DROVE -- THE WOMAN
THERE.
FROM ALABAMA DROVE TO SEE HER
THE ALABAMA DROVE -- THE WOMAN
DOP PER GANGER STRIPPER.
FROM ALABAMA DROVE TO SEE HER
>> I ALSO READ A LOT ABOUT IT
DOP PER GANGER STRIPPER.
THE STANDARD RULE IT'S NOT A
>> I ALSO READ A LOT ABOUT IT
SURPRISE TO ANYONE IS THAT IF
THE STANDARD RULE IT'S NOT A
YOU GO TO A STRIP CLUB A LOT OF
SURPRISE TO ANYONE IS THAT IF
STRIP CLUBS HAVE THE RULE THAT
YOU GO TO A STRIP CLUB A LOT OF
THERE HAS TO BE A MAN
STRIP CLUBS HAVE THE RULE THAT
ACCOMPANYING BECAUSE THEY DON'T
THERE HAS TO BE A MAN
WANT THE DRAMA OF A MAD WIFE
ACCOMPANYING BECAUSE THEY DON'T
GOING IN THERE AND CREATING A
WANT THE DRAMA OF A MAD WIFE
PROBLEM.
GOING IN THERE AND CREATING A
IF SHE FINDS HER HUSBAND AND/OR
PROBLEM.
PROSTITUTES GOING IN THERE AND
IF SHE FINDS HER HUSBAND AND/OR
LOOKING FOR JOHNS.
PROSTITUTES GOING IN THERE AND
THIS IS KIND OF LIKE A THING
LOOKING FOR JOHNS.
THAT'S KNOWN AMONG STRIP CLUBS.
THIS IS KIND OF LIKE A THING
>> A MAN SUED BECAUSE HE WAS NOT
THAT'S KNOWN AMONG STRIP CLUBS.
ALLOWED ALSO IN -- SOME KIND OF
>> A MAN SUED BECAUSE HE WAS NOT
A CLUB.
ALLOWED ALSO IN -- SOME KIND OF
IT WENT THE OTHER WAY AS WELL.
A CLUB.
I THINK THIS IS SOMETHING THAT'S
IT WENT THE OTHER WAY AS WELL.
BEEN OUT THERE.
I THINK THIS IS SOMETHING THAT'S
I DON'T KNOW IF LEGALLY IT'S
BEEN OUT THERE.
BEEN SETTLED.
I DON'T KNOW IF LEGALLY IT'S
CLEARLY NOT.
BEEN SETTLED.
YOU CAN BET SOMEONE WITH THIS
CLEARLY NOT.
LAWSUIT PERHAPS WILL SEE THE
YOU CAN BET SOMEONE WITH THIS
COURTS HAVE A SAY AT WHO CAN GO
LAWSUIT PERHAPS WILL SEE THE
ON A STRIP CLUB AND WITH WHOM.
COURTS HAVE A SAY AT WHO CAN GO
>> CERTAINLY A BIZARRE STORY
ON A STRIP CLUB AND WITH WHOM.
INDEED.
>> CERTAINLY A BIZARRE STORY
THANKS FOR WEIGHING IN.
INDEED.
>> OR STAY CLEAR OF STRIP CLUBS.
THANKS FOR WEIGHING IN.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> OR STAY CLEAR OF STRIP CLUBS.
>> THAT'S CRAZY TALK.
I DON'T KNOW.
NEVER MIND.
>> THAT'S CRAZY TALK.
>> THANKS YOU GUYS.
NEVER MIND.
STILL AHEAD MEET THE LOCAL
>> THANKS YOU GUYS.
UNIVERSITY STUDENT OVERCOMING
STILL AHEAD MEET THE LOCAL
HER OWN PERSONAL CHALLENGES AND
UNIVERSITY STUDENT OVERCOMING
IS NOW SWIMMING FOR THE GOLD.
HER OWN PERSONAL CHALLENGES AND
HEAR HER INSPIRING STORY.
IS NOW SWIMMING FOR THE GOLD.
IT'S COMING UP AT 8:30.
HEAR HER INSPIRING STORY.
♪
>>> IT IS 8:25.
>> HANGING OUT WITH ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I NEVER GET ANYBODY TO HANG
OUT WITH ME.
>> AWW.
>> THAT'S KIND OF SAD.
>> IT'S TRUE.
STEVE MOVE IN CLOSER.
YOU WON'T BE SITTING CLOSER TO
THIS.
MOVE IN, STEVE.
MOVE IN, GRAM ANDS, COME ON!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OKAY.
>> COMPETITION.
>> LET'S DO THE FORECAST.
>> LET'S HOP ON IN.
37 NOW.
CLOUDY SKIES.
>> OH, BOY.
>> RAIN FOR MOST OF US LATER
THIS MORNING DURING THE
AFTERNOON.
NOT GOING TO RAIN OF MINUTE
TODAY BUT DEFINITELY BE READY
FOR IT.
AND THAT THREAT OF FREEZING RAIN
CONTINUES FOR A FEW MORE HOURS
NORTH AND WEST.
HONESTLY MOST OF THE
TEMPERATURES ABOVE FREEZING SO I
THINK WE'RE GOING TO -- I DON'T
WANT TO SAY ESCAPE UNSCATHED BUT
THIS WILL NOT BE A MAJOR EVENT
NORTH AND WEST AS IT TRANSITIONS
AND CHANGES OVER TO RAIN THE
NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
THAT'S YOUR FUTURE THERE.
LOOK TO THE SOUTH DOWN TO THE
CAROLINAS A LOT OF RAIN WILL
STREAM NORTH INTO OUR REGION
LATER TONIGHT KEEP THE SHOWERS
IN THE FORECAST TOMORROW.
AND THEN MAYBE WINTRY MIX ON
MONDAY.
THE GOOD NEWS STACEY I'M OUT.
THE SKINS GAME WILL BE IN GOOD
SHAPE SUNDAY AFTERNOON.
>> YOU SCARED ME WITH ALL
ENTHUSIASM.
THERE YOU GO.
>> WELL IT HAS BEEN A TOUGH
COMMUTE THIS MORNING.
LET'S START WITH ROCKVILLE.
WE HAD AN ACCIDENT INVOLVING A
PEDESTRIAN.
THIS IS ON MONTROSE ROAD AT BAR
GATE COURT.
BECAUSE OF THAT, THE CRASH
INVESTIGATION REMAINS RIGHT NOW.
THE PEDESTRIAN HAS BEEN TAKEN TO
THE HOSPITAL.
BUT THE ROAD IS STILL CLOSED.
AGAIN, MOP ROSE ROAD IS CLOSED
BETWEEN MON ROSE PARKWAY AND
JEFFERSON STREET.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UP TO SPEED AS
WE GET UPDATES.
ALLISON, STEVE?
>> STILL AHEAD 8:30 A LOCAL
ATHLETE SWIMMING FOR GOLD.
>> BUT SHE'S HAD TO OVERCOME
BEING LEGALLY BLIND TO DO SO.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT HOW SHE MANAGED
TO BE SUCH A SUCCESS.
HER GOALS FOR THE FUTURE AS
WELL.
73 SHE JOINS US NEXT.
♪
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately to
severely active Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed relief
and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house needs
or recently had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how Janssen can help
you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start with
STELARA®.
For top quality floors
at rock-bottom prices,
come to Floor & Decor.
If you love your wallet,
and you love your home,
you have to go.
Hardwoods, laminates,
tile or stone.
The pros come
here. I come here.
Hands down the best place
for floors. No question.
Floor & Decor.
So you have ten years
experience...
I do.
but no PhD?
I do have a masters in early
childhood development.
you don't mind if I record this,
do you?
Uhh, no!
First Kid.
here's all the numbers, food's
in the fridge,
oh and Lucas likes to pull on
jewelry
so you might want to lose the
nose ring.
By their second kid, parents are
more likely to choose Luvs.
It absorbs 20x its weight
and the Triple Leakguards lock
away wetness
for outstanding leakage
protection.
Live, Learn, and Get Luvs.
♪
>>> OH, MORNING, HATE TO BRING
YOU THIS MORE BREAKING NEWS
RIGHT NOW.
8:30 THIS MORNING.
SKYFOX GIVING US A VIEW OF A
TEENAGER SAID TO BE A
17-YEAR-OLD TEENAGER HAS
LIFE-THREATENING INJURIES AFTER
BEING STRUCK BY A VEHICLE AT
MONTROSE ROAD AND BARGATE COURT
IN THE BETHESDA AREA.
SOUNDS LICKETY COULD BE NORTH
BETHESDA AREA.
WE WILL CONTINUE TO WORK ON THIS
AND GET YOU THE DETAILS.
WE DON'T KNOW THE CONDITION
RIGHT NOW BUT THIS IS HAPPENING,
AGAIN, WE'RE ON A DAY WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT A NINE-YEAR-OLD OR
EXCUSE ME AN ELEMENTARY AGED
SCHOOL CHILD WHO SADLY LOST HER
LIVE BEING HIT BY A VEHICLE.
THERE'S A SCHOOLBUS IN THAT SHOT
BUT I DON'T KNOW THE RELATION TO
THE STORY YET.
WE'RE WORKING ON THE DETAILS.
WE JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW WHAT
WAS GOING ON HERE MANY TRAFFIC
JUST STOPPED RIGHT THERE AS THEY
TRY TO PUT TOGETHER THE PIECES.
TEENAGER IS ALIVE BUT LIFE
THREATENING INJURIES AFTER BEING
HIT AT MONTROSE ROAD AND BARGATE
COURT.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT STORY AS
THE MORNING GOES ON.
>>> SWITCHING GEARS NOW HERE TO
SOME BETTER NEWS 8:31.
SWIMMING FOR THE GOLD.
THAT'S THE MANTRA LOYOLA
UNIVERSITY STUDENT VERY SPECIAL
STUDENT ONLY A FRESHMAN IN
COLLEGE BUT MCLEAN HER POLICE A
WORLD CHAMPION AND NOW A GOAL OF
A GOLD MEDAL IN 2020.
BUT HER SUCCESS IN THE POOL
DOESN'T COME WITHOUT ITS HUR
HURDLES.
MCLEAN IS LEGALLY BLIND.
IN ADDITION TO BEING A MEMBER OF
THE LOYAL HOLA SWIM TEAM SHE'S
TEAM USA PARA OLYMPIC TEAM.
HER SUCCESS CAUGHT THE ATTENTION
OF ANOTHER ACCOMPLISHED MARYLAND
SWIMMER.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> SHE'S ABLE TO GET BACK TO
OLYMPICS AND MEDAL.
THERE'S NOTHING BETTER THAN, UM,
WINNING A MEDAL AND WATCHING
YOUR FLAG RISE, AND I HOPE SHE
HAS THE OPPORTUNITY TO WIN A
GOLD, UM, THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
I WILL MISS FOREVER.
I HAD THE PRIVILEGE TO STAND ON
TOP OF THE PODIUM SO MANY TIMES
AND TO HEAR OUR NATIONAL HASN'T
NEM PLAY.
I HOPE SHE GETS THAT CHANCE.
>> OF COURSE CHAMPION MICHAEL
PHELPS.
ANOTHER MARYLANDSER MC CLAIM WHO
JOINS US THIS MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HOW ARE YOU.
>> I'M DOING WELL.
HOW ARE YOU.
>> YOUR SCHEDULE IS SO BUSY I'M
HONORED YOU HAD TIME TO STOP IN
AND TALK WITH US WITH BLAKE.
>> YES.
>> BLAKE IS HERE AS WELL.
CONGRATS ON ALL YOUR SUCCESS.
WHAT'S IT FEEL LIKE?
>> IT'S JUST SO HUMBLING AND
HONORING THAT I'M ABLE TO DO
SOMETHING THAT I LOVE AND SWIM
AND COMPETE FOR THIS AMAZING
COUNTRY OF THE UNITED STATES,
AND WITHIN MEDALS DOING
SOMETHING THAT I THOROUGHLY
ENJOY.
>> SO I WANT TO GET INTO THIS A
LITTLE BIT BUTT BECAUSE IT MAKES
YOUR STORE EVEN REMARKABLE.
AT WHAT AGE WERE YOU WHEN YOU
STARTED TO LOSE YOUR SITE?
>> MY PARENTS NOTICED AROUND THE
AGE OF TWO THAT I WAS HAVING
TROUBLE SEEING AND AT EIGHT YEAR
OLD MY RETNAS DETACHED
SPONTANEOUSLY BOTH OF MY RETNAS
DETACHED AND WITHIN A SERIES OF
SIX WEEKS I HAD FOUR EMERGENCY
EYE SURGERIES TO TRY TO SAVE MY
VISION AND ONE OF THEM FAILED SO
MY RIGHT EYE IS TOTALLY BLIND
MINE LEFT EYE THEY WERE ABLE TO
KIND OF SALVAGE THE REMAINING
VISION AND I'VE BEEN CROWLEY
PROGRESSIVELY LOSING MY VISION
SINCE EIGHT YEARS OLD.
>> SO THEN YOU DECIDE I'LL START
SWIMMING.
LIKE HOW DOES THIS HAPPEN?  HOW
DID THAT GET I GREATED IN YOUR
LIFE.
>> I ACTUALLY STARTED SWIMMING
AT THE AGE OF FOUR AND AT FOUR
YEARS OLD I TOLD MY PARENTS I
WANTED TO GO TO THE OLYMPICS AND
WITHIN A MEDAL AT THE OLYMPICS
AND THEY KIND OF CHUCKLED
BECAUSE I WAS FOUR.
I DIDN'T KNOW REALLY WHAT I WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AND SO WHEN I WENT BLIND AT
EIGHT YEARS OLD, I HAD TO STOP
SWIMMING WHILE MY EYES HEELED OF
HEALED AND EVERYTHING BUT I
WANTED TO GET BACK IN THE POOL.
WHEN I GOT BACK IN THE POOL I
STARTED HAVING TROUBLES.
I WAS RUNNING INTO THE WALL AND
COULDN'T SEE WHERE I WAS GOING
AND MY PARENTS WERE LIKE MCLEAN
YOU CAN'T -- THIS IS DANGEROUS
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HURT MY
COACH WAS LIKE NO, SHE LOVES
THIS.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
SO WE LEARNED ABOUT THE PARA
OLYMPICS.
I STARTED DOING PARA OLYMPIC
SWIMMING.
>> YOU'RE A CHAMPION.
YOU ARE A SURVIVOR.
BUT WHAT DID IT FEEL LIKE?  CAN
YOU REMEMBER THAT WAS YEARS AGO
NOW.
WHAT DID IT FEEL LIKE TO BE IN
THAT SPACE?  WAS IT FRUSTRATING
WERE YOU ANGRY?  HOW DID THAT
FEEL?
>> IT WAS SCARY.
I MEAN I'VE BEEN SCARED OF THE
DARK FOR AS LONG AS I CAN
RECALL, AND WHEN I WOULD GO IN
THE POOL IT WAS TOTALLY BLACK
AND I COULDN'T SEE ANYTHING AND
I WAS SO AFRAID THAT WHEN I GOT
OUT OF THE POOL IT WOULD STILL
BE BLACK.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO SEE SO I
HAD TO OVERCOME THAT FEAR OF
IT'S OKAY.
IF I GO BLIND WHEN I'M SWIMMING
IT'S OKAY IF I GET OUT OF THE
POOL AND I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
I'LL BE OKAY.
>> YOU'LL BE OKAY.
NOW YOU'RE THRIVING.
YOU'RE INVOLVED MORE.
YOU'RE AT LOYAL HOLA.
HOW IS THAT GOING.
>> I LOVE COLLEGE.
I LOVE THE INDEPENDENCE AND
FREEDOM THAT I HAVE.
I LOVE THAT I CAN GET UP AND GO
WHENEVER I WANT.
I TOOK A TRAIN TO D.C. TODAY BY
MYSELF WITH MY GUIDE DOG BACK
HOME I COULD NEVER DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT INDEPENDENTLY SO I'M
HAVING SO MUCH FUN GETTING TO
MEET NEW PEOPLE AND JUST HAVE
THE SPACE WHERE I CAN BE
CREATIVE AND FREE AND PURSUE
WHAT I LOVE.
>> HOW IS BLAKE ADAPTING?
>> HE LOVES SCHOOL.
HE'S A LADY'S MAN.
>> OKAY.
>> HE LOVES ALL THE ATTENTION HE
GETS.
HE LOVES TO RUN DOWN THE HALLWAY
AND VISIT ALL OF HIS FRIENDS.
>> YEAH.
>> HE LOVES IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AND SCHOOL IS GOING WELL?
>> YES.
SO I HAD A TRANSITION GOING FROM
ONLINE SCHOOL THROUGH DESIRE TO
LEARN GWYNEDD ONLINE CAMPUS BACK
HOME TO A TRADITIONAL CLASSROOM
SETTING SO THAT WAS AN
ADJUSTMENT FOR ME AT% BUT I'M
ABLE TO BE COMMUNICATIONS MAJOR.
>> UM-HMM.
>> I'M MAJORING SOME SOMETHING
THAT I LOVE.
>> AS YOU SHOULD BE
COMMUNICATIONS.
>> COMMUNICATIONS JOURNALISM
MAJOR I'M ABLE TO DO PUBLIC
SPEAKING CLASSES AND MEDIA
WRITING CLASSES AND TIEING
CLASSES AND I ENJOY IT A LOT.
>> WELL, MAN, YOUR STORY WILL
EVEN BE RICHER WHEN YOU MEDAL IN
2020 AT THE PARA OLYMPIC.
WE WISH ALL THE BEST.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHAT A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
TUCKER, OVER TO YOU.
>>> ALLISON, GREAT STORY.
LET'S DO TEMPS.
LISTEN PROBABLY HEARD WE GOT
POTENTIAL FOR FREEZING RAIN OUT
THERE.
LIVE LOOK AT NATIONAL HARBOR YOU
CAN SEE THE CLOUDS.
I'LL BE HONEST GOING TO BE
RAINING FOR MOST OF US FOR MUCH
OF THE AFTERNOON AND THE EVENING
HOURS WE'VE GOT SOME SHOWERS IN
THE FORECAST.
TAKE THE UMBRELLA HERE.
GOING TO BE A COOL ONE TODAY,
ONLY EXPECTED TO BE IN THE MID
40S.
REAGAN NATIONAL 37 DEGREES.
34 DULLES.
36BWI MARSHALL CRIT KELL WE GET
IT ABOVE FREEZING AND WE ARE AT
ALL LOCAL AIRPORTS HERE ABOVE
FREEZING.
IN FACT MOST OF THE AREA ABOVE
FREEZING ALREADY SEEING SOME
SHOWERS MOVE IN THAT'S THE GREEN
ON THE MAP.
UP AND DOWN 95 HERE THROUGH D.C.
AND THEN OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST, THIS IS WHERE THE
POTENTIAL IS SOME OF THIS RAIN
COULD FALL AS FREEZING RAIN SO
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
CONTINUES OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST UNTIL MID AFTERNOON UNTIL
3:00 O'CLOCK.
I'LL BE HONEST MOST MOST OF THE
TEMPERATURES OUT HERE ARE AT OR
ABOVE FREEZING POCKETS OF ICING
WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT THERE TO
THE NORTH AND TO THE WEST LATER
THIS MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
BIG PICTURE GUESS WHAT?  ALL OF
THAT HEADED IN OUR DIRECTION.
SO WE GOT SHOWERS IN THE
FORECAST LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
IF YOU'RE GOING OUT TONIGHT MUCH
OF YOUR SATURDAY HAS SHOWERS IN
THE FORECAST AS WELL.
DETAILS ON OUR WEEKEND FORECAST
COMING UP.
45 THIS AFTERNOON.
CHILLY DAY.
TAKE THE UMBRELLA AND THE, YOU
KNOW, FASHIONABLE RAIN SLICKER.
ALL RIGHT.
STACEY, I KNOW YOU'VE GOT ONE OF
THOSE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I DO TUCKER.
I DO.
I THINK YOU DO TOO, RIGHT?
>> WELL WE ARE KEEPING YOU UP TO
DATE ON THAT ACCIDENT.
FIRST OF ALL ON THE OUTER LOOP.
WE HAD AN ACCIDENT THIS MORNING
THAT HAS BEEN CLEARED TO THE
LEFT SHOULDER.
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER RIVER ROAD.
HOWEVER, WE HAVE MAJOR DELAYS
BECAUSE OF THAT ACCIDENT
RESIDUAL DELAYS THAT WILL
DEFINITELY TIE YOU UP.
ALSO, ON THE INNER LOOP WE HAVE
A CRASH THIS IS RIGHT AT
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE INVOLVING A
VEHICLE FIRE TAKE A LOOK AT THAT
LIVE SHOT TRAFFIC IS AT A CRAWL.
YOU ARE DOWN TO ABOUT 5 MILES
PER HOUR IN THE THICK OF THINGS.
SO TAKE CARE THERE.
ON THE INNER LOOP, YOU'VE GOT
YOUR REGULAR DELAYS FOR THIS
TIME OF MORNING FROM 95 TO 66.
AND AS WE MOVE ON TO 95
NORTHBOUND FROM DALE CITY TO THE
BELTWAY, I'LL END ON A POSITIVE
NOTE.
TRAFFIC IS MOVING AT SPEED.
THAT'S YOUR RIDE.
QUESTIONS STACEY FOX5 D.C. ON
TWITTER.
♪
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD WHY METRO
SMART TRIP CARD MAY BE SO 2019
FOR SOME RIDERS.
>> PLUS THE PRICE OF LUCK.
THE AMOUNT THE AVERAGE PERSON
SUPPOSEDLY SPENDS A YEAR BUYING
LOTTERY TICKETS.
♪
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ Blow a kiss into the sun ♪
♪ We need someone to lean on ♪
♪ All we needed
somebody to lean on ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
Sweden's greetings.
Enjoy your first payment on us
when you lease a new Volvo.
Now through January 2nd.
The good news?
Our protection is guaranteed.
The bad news?
The perfect photo is not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
>>> BACK NOW 8:41.
SMART TRIP CARDS COULD BE A
THING OF THE PAST BECAUSE YOU
MIGHT JUST BE ABLE TO USE YOUR
CELL PHONE.
IN FACT NEXT YEAR YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO UP LOAD YOUR METRO CARD TO
YOUR IPHONE AND APPLE WATCH.
SAME WAY YOU WOULD USE YOUR
PHYSICAL SMART TRIP CARD JUST
TAP AND GO.
GOOGLE SAYS IT IS WORKING TO
ROLL OUT AN ANDROID GOOGLE PAY
SUPPORT APP AS WELL THAT ONE
MIGHT TAKE A LITTLE MORE TIME TO
ROLL OUT.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
>>> NEW SURVEY SAYS THE AVERAGE
AMERICAN SPENDS MORE THAN $1,000
A YEAR ON LOTTERY TICKETS.
ODDS ARE YOU'LL BE MORE LIKELY
TO I LOVE WHEN WE PUT THESE ODDS
ARE THINGS OUT THERE.
YOU'LL BE MORE LIKELY TO BE
ATTACKED BY A GRIZZLY BEAR THAN
WITHIN THE MEGA MILLIONS GRAND
PRIZE.
WHICH WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE
HAPPEN.
100% WOULD SAY GRIZZLY.
>> WE'RE OPTIMISTIC WHEN IT
COMES TO THE PROBABLY WINNING
SOMETHING, WINNING ANYTHING AND,
AL, IF YOU ROUND IT OUT BY $2,
TO $1,040 A YEAR, THAT WOULD BE
20 BUCKS A WEEK ON AVERAGE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE BASICALLY
SAYING.
>> I CAN SEE.
>> AMERICANS ARE SPENDING $20 A
WEEK ON LOTTERY TICKETS.
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY WHO DOES
BUT I'M SURE IT EVENS OUT
PERHAPS.
>> PERHAPS.
GOOD LUCK EVERYBODY IF YOU'RE
PLAYING.
>>> UP NEXT WE'RE GETTING INTO
THE HOLIDAY SPIRIT IN A RATHER
COOL WAY.
THE LARGEST CLEAR ICE MAZE IN
THE NATION, OH, IT'S RIGHT HERE
IN D.C.
AND IT'S ALL FOR A GREAT CAUSE.
STAY WITH US.
♪
♪♪
VO: This guy spends his time
tweeting.
This guy gets things done.
Bloomberg built a global news
and information company by
taking on
the toughest competition -
creating 20,000 jobs.
As New York mayor, he guided a
shaken city
in the wake of 9/11, improving
services,
revitalizing old industrial
sites,
supporting small businesses -
creating 400,000 jobs.
Trump's tweets divide a nation;
Mike's steady leadership will
build an economy
where everyone can get ahead.
BLOOMBERG: I'm Mike Bloomberg,
and I approve this message.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
CHECKING OUT ALL THE PICTURES
RIGHT THERE WHAT'S GOING ON
OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW.
TO YOUR LEFT AND TO YOUR RIGHT.
WHAT'S GOING TO START TO HAPPEN.
THAT PINK NOT FUN TODAY.
>> FRIDAY THE 13th.
IT'S HERE, TUCKER.
THE PRECIPITATION.
>> LISTEN IF ANYBODY ACTUALLY
ENTERS PURPLE REIGN, I NEED TO
KNOW IMMEDIATELY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN THAT'S --
>> SAME KIND OF PURPLE REIGN
THEY MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO LET
YOU KNOW.
>> OKAY.
GOT IT.
>> 37 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
YES.
HOW ABOUT A PINK RAIN, I'LL SHOW
YOU RADAR IN JUST A SECOND.
PINK RAIN INDICATING THE
POSSIBILITY OF FREEZING RAIN TO
THE NORTH AND TO THE WEST.
TEMPERATURES GOING TO BE VERY
CRITICAL HERE OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE OF HOURS.
YOU CAN SEE OUT IN THE MOUNTAINS
WE'RE HANGING ON TO THAT
FREEZING MARK AS BEST WE CAN.
TRYING TO GET RID OF THE
FREEZING MARK BUT IT'S HOLDING
TOUGH HERE NORTH AND WEST.
HAGERSTOWN DOWN TOWARDS
WINCHESTER, FRONT ROYAL STILL
32.
I JUST CHECK.
29 IN CUMBERLAND FOR EVERYBODY
ELSE THE TEMPERATURES ABOVE
FREEZING SO WHAT'S FALLING OUT
THERE IS FALLING AS RAIN, BUT IF
IT'S ENCOUNTERING 32-DEGREE
TEMPERATURES, IT'S POSSIBLY IT'S
GLAZING OVER AND CAUSING WHAT WE
CALL FREEZING RAIN.
SO WE'VE GOT A WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORY IN EFFECT UNTIL
3:00 O'CLOCK THIS AFTERNOON FOR
OUR COMMUNITIES OFF TO THE NORTH
AND WEST.
I KNOW A LOT OF YOU OUT THERE
PLEASE BE CAUTIOUS.
IT DOESN'T TAKE A LOT OF
FREEZING RAIN TO CAUSE A LOT OF
PROBLEMS.
RAIN SHOWERS FOR THE REST OF US.
YOU CAN SEE IN AROUND THE
BELTWAY WE'RE GETTING RAIN
SHOWERS.
DOWN 95 TOWARDS FREDERICKSBURG
AND RICHMOND AT THIS HOW IT'S
RAINING.
AND THEN OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WEST IT'S NOT PURPLE IT'S PINK
BUT YOU CAN SEE ALONG 81 WHERE
THOSE TEMPERATURES RIGHT AROUND
THE FREEZING MARK.
SO AGAIN, THE POSSIBILITY OF
SLIPPERY CONDITIONS OUT HERE FOR
A FEW MORE HOURS.
BIG PICTURE DOING THAT OUT OF
THE SOUTH BECAUSE NOT ONLY WE
GET A BIG SEARCH OF MOISTURE OUT
OF THE SOUTH WE'RE GOING TO GET
WARMER TEMPERATURES AS WELL.
SO EVENTUALLY MID 40S AROUND
HERE LATER THIS AFTERNOON MY
ADVICE TAKE UMBRELLAS FOR
EVERYBODY IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
AFTER SCHOOL, AFTER WORK GOING
OUT FOR DINNER TONIGHT IT'S
GOING TO BE JUST PLAIN OLD RA
RAINING AROUND HERE FOR MUCH OF
THE EVENING AND UNFORTUNATELY
SATURDAY LOOKS WET AS WELL AS
THINGS WILL BE VERY GRADUALLY
IMPROVING HERE THIS WEEKEND.
THERE YOU'RE EXPECTED ICE
ACCUMULATIONS VERY LIGHT AMOUNTS
BUT WE KNOW LIGHT AMOUNTS CAN
SOMETIMES CAUSE MAJOR PROBLEMS.
SO THERE YOU GO.
FUTURE CAST LET ME JUST SHOW YOU
IT WON'T RAIN ALL AFTERNOON BUT
THE SHOWERS WILL FILL BACK IN
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
AND THIS EVENING RAIN MAY EVEN
BE HEAVY AT TIMES OVERNIGHT AND
WE'LL KEEP THIS THING GOING INTO
THE DAY ON SATURDAY.
WON'T RAIN ALL DAY SATURDAY.
I THINK THINGS WILL GET LITTLE
BETTER SATURDAY AFTERNOON BUT
YOU GET THE IDEA KIND OF A GRAY
AND COOL DAY.
52 DEGREES.
BETTER FOR THE SKINS GAME SUNDAY
AFTERNOON.
GO REDSKINS THAT LOOKS BETTER
THEN PERHAPS A WINTRY MIX TO
RAIN.
MOST AL RAIN EVENT ON MONDAY
IT'S POSSIBLE IT'S A WINTRY MIX
JUST LIKE THIS MORNING AT THE
ONSET HAVE TO WATCH THAT TIME
PERIOD CAREFULLY AS WELL.
I'M DONE.
STACEY POTIONS TURN.
>> THANKS TUCKER ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT ABOUT TAKING CARE.
RECIPE FOR DISASTER WHEN YOU
DON'T COMBINE WITH THOSE WET
CONDITIONS AND SPEAKING OF WE
JUST WANT TO KEEP UP TO DATE
REGARDING THAT ACCIDENT IN RO
ROCKVILLE WHERE A PEDESTRIAN WAS
STRUCK THIS MORNING.
THIS WAS RIGHT ON MONTROSE ROAD
AT BARGATE COURT.
THAT PEDESTRIAN IS A TEENAGER
AND WITH LIFE THREATENING
INJURIES.
THAT PEDESTRIAN HAS BEEN
TRANSPORTED TO THE HOSPITAL BUT
THE CRASH INVESTIGATION REMAINS.
SO A PORTION OF MONTROSE ROAD IS
NOW CLOSED.
IT'S CLOSED BETWEEN MONTROSE
PARKWAY AND JEFFERSON STREET.
SO WE DO HOPE THAT PEDESTRIAN IS
OKAY.
MOVING ON TO THE OUTER LOOP, WE
HAVE A CRASH THIS MORNING THAT
HAS BEEN CLEARED AND MOVED TO
THE LEFT SHOULDER RIGHT AFTER
RIVER ROAD.
HOWEVER, YOU'VE GOT MAJOR DELAYS
BECAUSE OF THAT CRASH.
SOMETHING TO LOOK OUT FOR.
ON THE INNER LOOP AT
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE, WE HAVE A
CRASH INVOLVING A VEHICLE FIRE.
AS YOU CAN SEE, REALLY SLOWING
YOU DOWN WITH SPEEDS DOWN TO
ABOUT 5 MILES PER HOUR IN THE
THICK OF THINGS.
THAT'S YOUR TRAFFIC.
BACK TO YOU ALLISON AND STEVE.
>> STACEY, THANKS VERY MUCH.
8:49 RIGHT NOW.
>>> ALL RIGHT IF YOU ARE LOOKING
TO CELEBRATE THE HOLIDAYS IN
LET'S JUST SAY A COOL WAY -- WHY
WOULDN'T WE JOB.
>> KNEW A TRACTION IN D.C. MIGHT
BE YOUR ANSWER.
>> NOT ONLY IS IT THE LARGEST
CLEAR ICE MAZE IN THE NATION,
YOU CAN ALSO HAVE FUN WHILE
GIVING BACK.
SO MICHELLE ROTELLA IS THERE.
SHE'S CHECKING IT OUT LIVE ON
LOCATION D.C.'S CITY CENTER.
ALREADY A COOL SPOT IN D.C.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GUYS.
YEAH.
YOU GOT TO COME OUT HERE AND SEE
IT THE DETAILS ON THIS IS
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
WE'RE TALKING WALLS OF ICE THAT
ARE 7 FEET HIGH, 110,000 POUNDS
OF ICE.
SO MUCH HAS GONE INTO THIS AND
THIS IS GOING ON THIS WEEKEND SO
WITH ME RIGHT NOW I HAVE TIM
LOWRY WITH CITY CENTER D.C.
>> GOOD MORNING.
GOOD MORNING.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE FOR THIS
WEEKEND AND WENT INTO THIS.
>> THIS IS OUR THIRD YEAR OF
DOING AND A ICE ACTIVATION
DURING THE HOLIDAYS.
TWO YEARS AGO WE DID D.C.'S
FIRST IGLOO.
LAST YEAR WE DID THESE LIFE SIZE
12-FOOT REPLICAS OF THE
MONUMENTS.
WHEN THE TEAM STARTED TALKING
ABOUT THIS YEAR WHAT WE WERE
GOING TO DO THIS WHOLE CONCEPT
OF AN ICE MAZE CAME UP.
AND THESE BLOCKS OF ICE EACH
WEIGH 300 POUNDS.
>> WOW.
>> THERE'S AS YOU SAID
110,000 POUNDS IN TOTAL OF ICE
THAT'S BEEN BROUGHT IN.
10 ARTISANS SKULL TOURS IF ANY
ROUND THE U.S. ALL CAME HERE TO
BUILD THE LARGEST CLEAR ICE MAZE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
>> I MEAN THE DETAIL IS TRULY
INCREDIBLE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS.
SO WHAT CAN PEOPLE REALLY EXPECT
OBVIOUSLY WHAT'S DIFFERENT FROM
LAST YEAR TO LIKE THIS YEAR.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO JUST TOP
IT OFF?
>> WELL, LISTEN EVERY YEAR YOU
KIND OF HAVE TO UP YOURSELF DON
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
THIS YEAR WE MORE THAN DOUBLE
THE AMOUNT OF ICE, WE CHANGED
THE EXPERIENCE AND MADE IT
SOMETHING THAT IS VERY
INTERACTIVE SOMETHING THAT'S
IMMERSIVE.
YOU CAN COME IN AND GET LOST.
YOU HAVE TO TURN AROUND A FEW
TIMES.
AND FIND YOUR WAY OUT THE END
NEXT TO OUR BIG HOLIDAY TREE
JUST TO COME AND CELEBRATE THE
HOLIDAYS.
>> I KNOW THIS IS EXTRA SPECIAL
FOR YOU BECAUSE YOU LOVE DOING
THINGS FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
>> WE DO.
>> AND SO THAT IS WHERE I HAVE
AMY BEAR HERE AND YOU GUYS ARE
TEAMING UP TOGETHER WITH
CHILDREN'S NATIONAL SO TELL ME A
LITTLE BIT ABOUT YOUR
INVOLVEMENT WITH THAT AND REALLY
WHAT IT MEANS TO YOU AND WHY?
>> WELL, WE'RE GRATEFUL TO HAVE
THIS PARTNERSHIP.
OUR OLDEST SON WAS BORN WITH
FIVE COULDN'T CENTRAL HEART
DEFECTS HAS HAD MANY HEART
SURGERIES AT CHILDREN'S
NATIONAL, AND TO SHOW OUR
GRATITUDE, TO HAVE A THRIVING
12-YEAR-OLD BOY DOING WELL IN
SPORTS AND ACADEMICS, WE WANT TO
GIVE BACK TO CHILDREN'S NATIONAL
ENCOURAGE OTHERS TO DO THE SAME.
SO THE BEAR -- DR. BEAR GIVING
IS A WONDERFUL WAY TO GET THE
COMMUNITY INVOLVED.
THERE'S 300 LIGHT UP BEARS NOT
ONLY HERE AT CITY CENTER AT
CHILDREN'S NATIONAL AND ACROSS
THE REGION, AND THEY ILLUMINATE
EVERY TIME SOMEONE MAKES
DONATION IT GOES TO TREAT THE
OVER 240,000 PATIENTS THAT ARE
TREATED ANNUALLY AT THE
HOSPITAL.
SO IT GOES TOWARDS THE
INNOVATIVE RESEARCH THAT'S
HAPPENING, PATIENT CARE PRO
PROGRAMS, AND OFFSET THE FEES
FOR THE PATIENTS WITH LESS
DESIRABLE CIRCUMSTANCES.
>> WOW, GUYS THAT IS ABSOLUTELY
INCREDIBLE.
SO THIS IS ACTUALLY ONE OF THE
BEARS THAT LIGHTS UP A LITTLE
BIT WHEN WE COME OVER HERE AND
JUST SEE IT.
IT'S LIGHTING UP RIGHT NOW.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT PEOPLE
WILL COME IN BECAUSE IT IS FREE.
FREE EVENT BUT OF COURSE WE DO
WANT THEM TO GIVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO GIVE BACK, RIGHT.
>> EXACTLY.
SO THEY CAN COME OUT THIS
WEEKEND AND ENJOY THE ICE MAZE.
THEY CAN DONATE TO THE
DR. BEARS, AND IF THEY CAN'T GET
HERE, THEN THEY CAN GO TO
CHILDREN'S NATIONAL.ORG/LIGHTS
AND MAKE A DONATION FROM HOME.
BEAUTIFUL WAY TO GET THE
COMMUNITY COLLECTIVELY GIVE
TOGETHER AND MAKE A DIFFERENCE
WORLD RENOWNED CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL RIGHT HERE IN THE
NATION'S BACKYARD.
>> WOW.
IT IS INCREDIBLE.
YOU GUYS HAVE TO GET OUT HERE
AND CHECK IT OUT FOR YOURSELF.
LET'S QUI QUICKLY LET'S TELL PEE
THE DETAILS OF WHEN THEY CAN
COME AND EVERYTHING THAT GOES
INTO THAT.
I KNOW THERE'S SOME FOOD AND
JUST SOME OTHER THINGS GOING ON
AROUND THE AREA.
>> SURE.
WELL, WE HAVE LOTS OF
RESTAURANTS AND FOOD AND
BEVERAGE OFFERINGS HERE AT CITY
CENTER.
THE ICE MAZE OPENS TODAY AT 4:0.
AND THEN IT WILL BE OPEN
TOMORROW STARTING THE 9:00 A.M.
I THINK THERE'S A BREAK BETWEEN
2:00 AND 4:00 TO KIND OF
REFREEZE EVERYTHING FOR A FEW
MOMENTS.
THEN OPENS BACK UP AT
4:00 O'CLOCK AND GOES TILL
9:00 O'CLOCK.
SAME ON SUNDAY.
OPENS AT 9:00, IT WILL BE OPEN
TILL I THINK 9:00 P.M.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GUYS, YOU GUYS GOT TO GET OUT
HERE AND CHECK IT OUT FOR
YOURSELVES.
COMING UP I MIGHT ACTUALLY PUT
SOME FINISHING TOUCHES ON SOME
OF THIS YOU GUYS WILL HAVE TO
SEE IT FOR YOURSELF.
BACK TO YOU.
>> 8:54 RIGHT NOW.
OKAY.
IT IS MOVIE REVIEW FRIDAY A LOT
OF ENTERTAINMENT WHETHER IT BE
ICE MAZES ARE GOING TO THE
THEATERS IF YOU CHOOSE THE
THEATER OPTION KEV HAS HIS TAKE
ON THE NEW JUMANJI FILM AS WELL
AS RICHARD JEWEL THE STORY OF
THE ATLANTA OLYMPIC BOMBING.
WE'RE BACK IN JUST TWO MINUTES
WITH THAT.
TIME FOR LIGHTS, CAMERA MC KA
KATHY.
>> WHAT SHOULD WE SEE.
>> DECEMBER IS A BIG RELEASE
MONTH STAR WARS IS NEXT MONTH
THE RISE OF SKY WALKER LET'S
START OFF JUMANJI OPENING UP
THIS WEEK.
JUMANJI THE NEXT LEVEL SEQUEL TO
THE FIRST JUMANJI FILM WHICH
BROUGHT IN $963 MILLION
WORLDWIDE AT THE BOX OFFICE.
CLEARLY, YOU MAKE A SEQUEL WHICH
IN MY OPINION BEGS THE QUESTION.
THIS IS SOMETHING I'VE FOUND
INTERESTING WHEN A SEQUEL COMES
OUT, IS IT COMING OUT BECAUSE OF
A BUSINESS DECISION?
>> UM-HMM.
>> OR COMING OUT BECAUSE OF A
STORY DECISION?
>> HMM.
>> I WONDER SOMETIMES LIKE WAS
SEQUEL MADE.
YOU KIND OF HAVE TO FACTOR IN
WHEN YOU SEE A SEQUEL THIS ONE I
BELIEVE IS STILL A FUN FILM BUT
IT'S NOT AS GOOD AS THE ORIGINAL
COUPLE YEARS AGO.
EVEN THOUGH THAT'S NOT EVEN THE
ORIGINAL.
THAT'S ACTUALLY A SEQUEL TOO
BECAUSE THE '90'S VERSION WITH
ROBIN WILLIAMS WAS THE FIRST
ONE.
>> THAT WAS THE FIRST ONE.
>> THEN YOU HAD A COUPLE YEARS
AGO YOU HAD THE ROCK AND KEVIN
HART.
>> IS THAT A REIMAGINING OR
WHOLE ANOTHER ONE.
>> THAT WAS CONSIDERED A SEQUEL.
>> SEQUEL TO ONE.
>> THIS IS THREE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S NOT AS FUNNY AS THE
FIRST ONE.
WHAT STEALS THE IN MANY FOR ME
IS KEVIN HART'S IMPRESSION OF
DANNY GLOVER.
NOW WHEN TENDER JUMANJI KEVIN
HART IS PLAYING CHARACTER WHOSE
AN OLDER VERSION WITH DANNY
GLOVER'S CHARACTER THE REAL
WORLD AND THE ROCK IS PLAYING
DANNY DEVITO'S CHARACTER AN
OLDER VERSION IN THE REAL WORLD
AS WELL.
THE MOVIE HAS SOME LAUGHS AND
SOME GOOD ACTION BUT OVERALL I
DID NOT LOVE IT I THOUGHT IT WAS
FINE.
>> HOW IS JACK BLACK.
>> JACK BLACK IS GREAT.
>> HE IS?  YOU COULD SEE WHEN IT
SWITCHES TO WHO THE CHARACTER HE
IS AND HE'S ALL LIKE --
>> THE PERFORMANCES ARE REALLY
GREAT.
THAT WHAT WORKS.
SOME OF THE JOKES DIDN'T LAND
SOME OF THE ACTION FELT A LITTLE
BIT THE SAME AS THE FIRST ONE.
>> IT WAS A WINNER.
>> THREE OUT OF FIVE.
>> THE SECOND ONE WAS A WINNER.
WHY NOT?
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
YEAH.
>> MONEY DECISION.
>> OKAY.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
>> NEXT QUESTION -- MOVIE
RICHARD JEWELL THIS IS A FILM
WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO DIVE
DEEPER INTO THE CONTROVERSY
SURROUNDING THIS FILM IN GOOD
DAY.
#GOODDAYDC F YOU'RE TO THE
FAMILIAR WITH WHAT'S HAPPENING
WITH THIS MOVIE RICHARD JEWELL
DIRECTED BY MR. CLINT EASTWOOD
IT CENTERS AROUND RICHARD JEWELL
THIS HAPPENED IN '96 THE
SENTENCE PAL PARK BOMBING.
HE SAW A SUSPICIOUS PACKAGE AND
CLEARED THE AREA.
THE FILM FOCUSES ON WHAT HAPPENS
TO HIM SPECIFICALLY HAILED AS A
HERO THE A FIRST AND BECOME THE
PRIME SUSPECT EARLY IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> I REMEMBER IT LIKE YESTERDAY.
>> BULLIED VERY HEAVILY IN THE
MEDIA AND BY THE FBI IN THE FILM
THE CONTROVERSY SURRO SURROUNDIE
FILM AROUND KATHY SCRUGS WHO
PLAYS A JOURNALIST IN THE FILM.
IN THE MOVIE IT EM MIZE SHE
TRADES SEXUAL FAVORS FOR TIPS
FROM THE FBI.
WE'LL DIVE INTO THAT OLIVIA WILD
HAS NOW RESPONDED TO THOSE
ACCUSATIONS AND THE INN ACCURACY
THE ATLANTIC JOURNAL
CONSTITUTION WHO SHE WORK FOR
SAYING IT'S INACCURATE.
I GAVE A 3.5 OUT OF FIVE.
BREAK ALL THAT DOWN #GOODDAYDC.
THIS MORNING WE'LL DIVE INTO
OLIVIA WILD'S RESPONSE.
>> THE NEWS IS KNOT NON-STOP.
GOOD DAY AD89A IN FACT STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
♪
>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, WINTER
WEATHER TO BOOK END THE WEEKEND.
SOME FREEZING RAIN REPORTS IN
PARTS OF THE REGION SHUT DOWN
SCHOOLS THIS MORNING AND MORE
COULD BE ON THE WAY.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT NEXT
SYSTEM THAT COULD HIT JUST IN
TIME FOR THE MONDAY RUSH.
>>> JUST INCOMPREHENSIBLE
TRAGEDY NINE-YEAR-OLD GIRL IS
STRUCK AND