>> GOSH, THIS IS AWESOME.
>> HI, EVERYBODY, AND WELCOME
BACK.
MIKE JOY WITH JEFF GORDON.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN SO EXCITED FOR
THE START OF A 500 AS YESTERDAY
AND NEVER SO DISAPPOINTED WHEN
THE RAINS CAME.
BUT HERE WE GO, WE HAVE 450
MILES LEFT TO RACE, AND, HEY,
THERE IS THE DAYTONA 500.
>> I LOVE WHAT CLINT BOWYER
SAID.
YESTERDAY WAS AWESOME, NEVER
SEEN SO MUCH ENERGY AND
ENTHUSIASM TO GET THE DAYTONA
500 STARTED.
HERE WE ARE, 24 HOURS LATER AND
QUITE A FEW THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
THE SUN IS OUT, THE TRACK IS
GOING TO BE HIGHER, STRATEGIES
COMPLETELY CHANGED.
BUT ONE THING THAT'S DEFINITELY
NOT CHANGED MIKE, IT'S THE
DAYTONA 500, SO WHATEVER YOU DID
AS A COMPETITOR TO GET YOURSELF
READY TO GO IN THE GREAT
AMERICAN RACE, MAKE SURE YOU GO
THROUGH THOSE SAME STEPS BECAUSE
ALL OF THOSE SAME THINGS ARE
STILL ON THE LINE.
>> IN THE 20 LAPS WE HAD
YESTERDAY, RICKY STENHOUSE LED
THEM ALL IN A CHEVROLET.
THE FORDS LINED UP BEHIND HIM TO
SAVE GAS.
THE TOYOTAS ALL DROPPED TO THE
BACK TO RUN AT THROTTLE.
HOW IT TURN OUT?
>> WE WHAT DID IT FEEL LIKE TO
LEAD THE FIRST LAPS OF THE
DAYTONA 500 YESTERDAY?
MORE TO DO TODAY.
>> 180 LAPS.
REALLY AGGRESSIVE EARLY AND I
KNOW THEY'RE LINED UP BEHIND ME
AND I WAS TRYING TO BLOCK AND
KEEP OUR CAMARO UP FRONT.
WE WERE ABLE TO DO THAT.
I FEEL LIKE OUR CAR DROVE REALLY
WELL AND HAD OUR SPEED SINCE WE
UNLOADED HERE, WHICH IS FUN TO
RACE AND FUN TO DRIVE.
HOPEFULLY WE CAN KEEP IT UP LIKE
YOU SAID, WE'VE BEEN LEADING
THIS THING FOR A WHILE NOW, BUT
NO EXTRA LAPS.
HONESTLY, I DON'T CARE IF WE
LEAD ANOTHER ONE AS LONG AS WE
LEAD THE LAST ONE.
THAT'S ALL WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT.
BUT WE HAVE A REALLY GREAT CAR
AND A BEAUTIFUL DAY HERE TO GET
RACING GOING AGAIN.
>> GOOD LUCK TODAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> KYLE BUSCH BACK IN THE PACK A
LITTLE FURTHER THAN WE EXPECTED.
BASED ON THE TIMING OF THE RED
FLAG.
>> NOT A WHOLE LOT DIFFERENT.
WE'RE STILL KIND OF UNDERNEATH
OUR SAME IDEA, OUR SAME STRATEGY
HERE.
WE THINK IT WILL WORK.
WE DON'T KNOW, OBVIOUSLY.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN CAUTIONS ARE
GOING TO FLY AND THAT CAN ALWAYS
DERAIL YOUR PLANS BUT WE'LL
STICK TO THE PLAN.
THE CAMRY HAS BEEN SO GOOD, THE
BALANCE GOOD, OUR CAR IS FINE.
WE DON'T REALLY KNOW ABOUT SPEED
RELATED TO THE REST OF THE GUYS.
WE'RE NOT REALLY HUNTING THAT
RIGHT NOW.
THE SUN BEING OUT, TODAY BEING
HOT, THAT'S WHAT WE WERE LOOKING
FOR AND HOPEFULLY SET UP FOR.
>> GOOD LUCK, KYLE.
>> THANKS, REGAN.
WELL, IT WILL BE THE DAYTONA 450
WHEN THEY WAVE THE GREEN FLAG.
450 MILES TO GO.
LET'S CHECK IN AT THE RACE HUB
STUDIO WITH OUR DRIVER AND
STRATEGISTS, JAMIE McMURRAY AND
LARRY McREYNOLDS.
>> WE'VE ONLY RUN 20 LAPS SO WE
DON'T HAVE TO PIT, BUT I THINK
THE TIME OF THIS CAUTION IS VERY
INTERESTING.
I THINK YOU WILL COME TO PIT
ROAD, YOU WILL MAKE SURE THAT
THING IS FULL OF FUEL BECAUSE
THIS CAN GET YOU TO THE END OF
STAGE ONE.
I THINK IT'S A GREAT TIME TO AT
LEAST GET TWO FRESH TIRES, BUT
JAMIE, I THINK THE BIG THING, A
LOT OF THESE DRIVERS ARE LOOKING
FOR AN ADJUSTMENT RIGHT NOW.
>> I CAN TELL HE WAS UP ALL
NIGHT WORRIED ABOUT STRATEGY.
I WASN'T.
IINER AND A GOOD
NIGHT'S SLEEP.
MY CAR IS GOING TO HANDLE
DIFFERENT.
BIGGEST THING IS I WANT TO KEEP
THIS GUY UPDATED ON WHAT I NEED
TO BE IN WHEN THE BIG TROPHY IS
AWARDED.
>> MY CONCLUSION, I'M THE ONLY
ONE THAT DIDN'T GET ANY SLEEP
LAST NIGHT.
>> HERE'S HOW THEY WILL RESTART
WITH 20 LAPS COMPLETE.
RICKY STENHOUSE LED THEM ALL.
THEN THOSE FIVE FORDS RIGHT
BEHIND THEM BEFORE WILLIAM BYRON
AND JIMMIE JOHNSON.
YOU SEE HOW MUCH THEY GAINED OR
LOST SINCE THE START OF THE
RACE.
>> NOT A LOT OF CHASE ON THAT
FIRST PAGE.
ROW FIVE, LOOK AT THESE BIG
GAINS BY DAVID RAGAN.
ALEX BOWMAN LOST 14 SPOTS.
>> A BUNCH OF SHUFFLING AROUND
IN THIS PART OF THE PACK, ALL
THE WAY BACK TO BUBBA WALLACE,
WHO DROPPED 13 SPOTS.
THEN LOOK ON THE BOTTOM LINE
HERE AT THE TOYOTAS, MARTIN
TRUEX DROPPED BACK 16 POSITIONS.
KYLE BUSCH AND HIS TEAMMATES.
>> WE TALKED ABOUT THE TOYOTAS
DROPPING TO THE BACK.
WE HEARD FROM KYLE BUSCH.
WE'RE ANXIOUS TO SEE WHAT THEIR
STRATEGY IS.
>> LET'S GET LATE-BREAKING
STORIES FROM PIT ROAD BEGINNING
WITH MATT YOCUM.
>> SEVERAL HOURS OF DEBATE THIS
MORNING WITH PIT STRATEGY,
BASICALLY WRITTEN IN PENCIL.
THE FORD CAMP, THEY NEED ABOUT
13 GALLONS SO WHEN JOEY LOGANO
HITS PIT ROAD, LOOK FOR HIS GAS
MAN, NICK HENSLEY TO SIT HIM
WITH A SECOND CAN FOR MAYBE
ABOUT A SECOND AND A HALF.
REGAN?
>> TWO-TIME CHAMPION DENNY
HAMLIN HAD TO START FROM THE
YEAR YESTERDAY AFTER FAILING
PRERACE INSPECTION.
WISDOM WOULD HAVE HIM MOVING TO
THE FRONT QUICKLY, BUT HIS
TEAMMATES DROPPED BACK TO HIM AS
PART OF A TOYOTA PLAN.
TODAY THEY ANTICIPATE GETTING
TRACK POSITION.
INSTEAD THEY'LL HAVE TO
CONSTANTLY PASS CARS AT THE END
OF THIS STAGE.
>> THEY WILL BOTH TELL YOU THIS
IS THE BEST CAR THEY'VE HAD AT
DAYTONA, 20 LAPS YESTERDAY NOT
CHANGING THEIR OPINION.
IN RECENT YEARS, THE ISSUE FOR
HARVICK HAS BEEN GETTING CAUGHT
UP IN SOMEONE ELSE'S MESS, BUT
IF HE CAN KEEP HIS CAR CLEAN, HE
WILL BE A STRONG PICK TODAY TO
PICK UP HIS SECOND DAYTONA 500
WIN.
JAMIE LITTLE?
>> HIS TEAMMATE, CLINT BOWYER,
OPTED TO DROP TO THE BACK IN THE
EARLY LAPS OF THE DAYTONA 500
YESTERDAY.
IT WAS A GOOD OPPORTUNITY FOR
THE TEAM TO GET A READ ON ITS
FUEL MILEAGE, SOMETHING THAT CAN
COME INTO PLAY TODAY, AS EARLY
AS THIS NEXT ROUND OF LAPS, 20,
30 LAPS TO GO.
WATCH FOR THE 14 TO TAKE FOUR
TIRES AND PACK IT AS FULL AS
THEY CAN GET IT WITH FUEL.
MIKE?
>> THANKS, JAMIE.
IN THE PACK STRAIGHTAWAY BEHIND
THE SAFETY CAR AS THEY CROSS THE
START/FINISH LINE.
80-MILE-AN-HOUR FOX DRONE CAM.
WHAT A GREAT VIEW.
ONE YOU CAN'T GET WHEN YOU BUY A
TICKET, ONLY IN FRONT OF YOUR TV
SET.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT TODAY.
WHEN THE SUN IS OUT LIKE THIS
AND THIS TRACK WILL BE SLICK, IT
WILL BE A HANDFUL FOR THESE
DRIVERS.
IT WILL MAKE IT VERY
ENTERTAINING FOR ALL OF US.
>> 75 DEGREES RIGHT NOW.
IT WILL TRAIL OFF TO ABOUT 68
ABOUT THE TIME THIS RACE IS
OVER.
AS THEY COME PAST, PIT ROAD IS
NOT YET OPEN.
THERE WILL BE A GREEN LIGHT
HEADING INTO PIT ROAD WHEN THE
TEAMS ARE ALLOWED TO PIT.
SO WE LISTENED IN ON SEVEN-TIME
SERIES CHAMPION JIMMIE JOHNSON,
RACING IN HIS FINAL DAYTONA 500
TODAY.
HERE'S HIS CREW CHIEF.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU TO ALL THE FANS THAT
CAME OUT YESTERDAY AND THE ONE
WHO IS STAYED OVER FOR TODAY.
A GREAT CROWD OF FANS.
BUCKLE DOWN, FINISH THIS THING
THE WAY WE WANT TO.
>> LARRY Mac, I THINK YOU HAVE
COMPETITION FOR YOUR JOB, CREW
CHIEFS BECOMING BROADCASTERS.
LOOK AT JIMMIE'S HEART RATE
MONITOR.
HIS RESTING HEART RATE IS ABOUT
40 BEATS PER MINUTE, 71 RIGHT
NOW INTO THE CAUTION FLAG.
>> WE TALK ABOUT THE CALM BEFORE
THE STORM.
THIS IS THE CALM BECAUSE AS
JIMMIE JOHNSON'S HEART RATE, I'M
GOING TO BE HONEST, IT DOESN'T
GET VERY HIGH, BUT THIS RACE
STRETCHES YOU OUT MENTALLY.
AS THIS RACE GOES ON, I CAN'T
WAIT TO FOLLOW ALONG WITH HIS
HEART RATE AND BEATS PER MINUTE
AND SEE WHAT AFFECTS THEM AND
WHAT MAKES THEM GO UP OR DOWN.
MAINLY IT WILL BE STRESS.
>> JOHNSON IS LINED UP EIGHTH.
WE EXPECT WHOLESALE CHANGES IN
THIS LINEUP WHEN PIT ROAD IS
OPEN AND THE GREEN LIGHT IS ON.
SO CARS WILL BE ABLE TO PIT THIS
TIME BY.
>> HOW COME WHEN I OPERATE MY
DRONE THE SHOTS DON'T LOOK QUITE
LIKE THAT?
>> THAT IS A GREAT PIECE OF
EQUIPMENT WE'VE GOT THERE AND
VERY CREATIVE USES WE'LL FIND
FOR IT AS THE SEASON GOES ON.
>> A GREEN LIGHT.
THEY COME THROUGH TURNS THREE
AND FOUR NOTING THAT THE PIT
ROAD ENTRY IS GOING TO BE OPEN
THIS NEXT TIME BY.
>> LARRY, IF YOU DON'T PIT NOW,
WHAT'S YOUR STRATEGY?
>> IF YOU DON'T PIT NOW, MIKE,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PIT
PROBABLY WITH ABOUT 15 LAPS TO
GO IN THIS STAGE.
I COULD NOT IMAGINE GOING WITH
THAT STRATEGY.
>> THAT MEANS YOU'RE BANKING ON
SOMETHING.
THE LAST THING YOU WANT TO DO IS
COME DOWN PIT ROAD UNDER GREEN.
>> LOOKS LIKE MORE THAN HALF OF
THE FIELD WILL PIT AT THE FRONT
OF THE FIELD, ALL BUT TWO CARS,
McDOWELL AND CUSTER, COME IN.
>> JOEY LOGANO TAKING FOUR TILES
AND FUEL.
RICKY STENHOUSE JR. INTO HIS
BOX.
WILLIAM BYRON TAKING FOUR TIRES
AND FUEL.
>> JUST ABOUT EVERYONE UP AND
DOWN PIT ROAD WANTS FOUR FRESH
GOODYEARS AND A FULL TANK OF GAS
FOR THIS RESTART.
>> AND THIS TRACK IS GREEN, SO
THEY WANT FRESH TIRES BECAUSE
THEY KNOW THAT YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO USE THESE TIRES UP ON
THIS RUN A LITTLE MORE THAN
NORMAL.
>> SO CARS THAT DID NOT PIT,
MICHAEL McDOWELL, COLE CUSTER,
LAJOIE, BRENDAN GAUGHAN, PREECE,
AND ALL THE TOYOTAS.
>> JOEY LOGANO TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF THAT FIRST PIT STALL IN, PIT
STALL 40, AND COMES OFF PIT ROAD
FIRST.
>> GETTING READY TO RESUME THE
500 IN DAYTONA, HERE'S A QUICK
WORD FROM GOODYEAR.
♪♪
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES, GIRL, LOOK
INSIDE, GIRL ♪
>> READY FOR THE RESTART.
IT WILL BE 24 LAPS COMPLETE WHEN
THEY COME BY.
SCORING RESUMED AS SOON AS THEY
BROUGHT OUT THE YELLOW FLAG AND
THE CARS MOVED AWAY.
GOING TO BE ONE MORE LAP OF
CAUTION.
THOUGHT I SAW THE LIGHTS OFF
ATOP THE SAFETY CAR.
THAT GROUP UP FRONT LED BY
MICHAEL McDOWELL AND COLE CUSTER
TOWARD PIT ROAD.
>> THIS IS HOW CLOSE THEY ARE IN
FUEL MILEAGE.
SOME THAT CAME DOWN PIT ROAD,
JOEY LOGANO, I DON'T KNOW IF HE
HAD AN ISSUE, BUT TOPPING OFF
FUEL AND COMING IN TIME BECAUSE
THEY'RE SO TIGHT ON THEIR FUEL
WINDOW.
>> HERE COME ALL OF THE TOYOTAS
FOR THE FIRST TIME TO PIT ROAD.
FIRST TIME ON PIT ROAD FOR THE
JOE GIBBS MACHINES.
JIMMIE JOHNSON BEING CITED FOR
TOO MANY MEN OVER THE WALL BY
THAT HAWKEYE OFFICIATING SYSTEM
THAT NASCAR USES TO
ELECTRONICALLY PASS ALONG PIT
ROAD VIOLATIONS TO THE
OFFICIALS, THEN MAKE THE CALL.
KEVIN HARVICK'S STOP HERE.
TIME TO KICK OFF BUSCH'S FASTEST
PICKOFF EVER.
FANS WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO
TWEET #SWEET THINGS FOR A CHANCE
TO WIN A NEW SPORTS CAR.
TWEET NOW FOR A CHANCE TO WIN.
BRAD KESELOWSKI'S TEAM CITED FOR
BEING OVER THE WALL TOO SOON.
>> NASCAR WILL HAVE TO FIND A
WAY TO REPOSITION HIM IN THIS
LINEUP BECAUSE THE LIGHTS ARE
OUT ON THE PIT ROAD.
HE'S ON THE FRONT ROW.
>> WE WOULD HAVE RESTARTED
SECOND.
RYAN NEWMAN.
>> KIND OF ANXIOUS TO SEE RICKY
STENHOUSE JR.
HE'S LED THIS WHOLE RACE,
EVERYBODY IN HIS REAR-VIEW
MIRROR.
NOW HE'S GOT A LITTLE WORK TO
DO, BUT I THINK HE'LL BE JUST AS
AGGRESSIVE TRYING TO GET THAT
LEAD BACK.
>> PACE CAR DIVES TO PIT ROAD,
AND HERE THEY COME.
KESELOWSKI WAS NOT THE CAR THAT
WAS CITED.
KESELOWSKI ALIGNED WITH RYAN
NEWMAN ON THE RESTART.
APOLOGIZE FOR BAD INFORMATION
THERE.
>> SEE RIGHT AWAY A LOT OF FORDS
JUMPING DOWN IN THAT INSIDE LANE
GETTING BUMPER TO BUMPER.
GET THAT INSIDE ROW MOVING.
>> THREE WIDE MIDWAY THROUGH THE
FIELD.
UP THE WAY OUTSIDE.
>> YEAH, RYAN NEWMAN JUMPED UP
IN FRONT OF RICKY STENHOUSE JR.
ARIC ALMIROLA GETS A NICE JUMP
FROM HIS TEAMMATE TO MOVE INTO
SECOND PLACE.
>> ONE SLID OFF THE BOTTOM.
JIMMIE JOHNSON GETTING A PUSH
GOING THROUGH THE CENTER.
HARVICK BEHIND HIS TEAMMATE
ALMIROLA IN THE 10.
>> KESELOWSKI MOVING LANES GOES
TO THE OUTSIDE TO BLOCK THAT
OUTSIDE LANE BUT HERE COMES A
BIG RUN ON THE INSIDE.
ARIC ALMIROLA SAID HE HAD A FAST
RACE CAR.
HE'S SHOWING IT RIGHT NOW.
>> HEADS UP DRIVING BY KEVIN
HARVICK BEHIND THE 10 OF ARIC
ALMIROLA.
HE PUSHED THE REAR BUMPER.
HE BACKED OFF TO MAKE SURE
ALMIROLA'S CAR WAS PLANTED INTO
THE BANKING.
>> RICKY STENHOUSE, THE 47, OUR
POLE SITTER A BIT BOXED IN HERE
SITTING IN THIRD ON THE OUTSIDE.
HERE'S VINCE.
>> ARIC ALMIROLA GOT A BIG SHOVE
FROM KEVIN HARVICK.
HE GOT ON THE RADIO AND SAID,
TELL HIM I DON'T NEED IT.
THEY DIDN'T WANT THE BIG PUSH AT
THAT PARTICULAR MOMENT.
HE FEELS LIKE HE'S GOT ENOUGH
SPEED WITHOUT THE BIG BUMP FROM
BEHIND.
>> THIS EARLY INTO THE DAYTONA
500, I DON'T BLAME HIM.
YOU'RE UP FRONT.
YEAH, YOU'D LIKE TO BE LEADING
BUT HOW MUCH RISK DO YOU WANT TO
TAKE DOING THAT.
WE SAW HIM GET A PRETTY BIG BUMP
GOING INTO THE TRI-OVAL IN THE
LAST LAP AND HIS HANDS TURNED TO
THE RIGHT AS THAT CAR ALMOST
JUMPED SIDEWAYS.
>> ALMIROLA'S GAINING.
HE'S GOT THE LEAD INTO TURN ONE
ON THE INSIDE.
>> TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THAT
SHORTER ROUTE ON THE BOTTOM
LANE.
AS THOSE CARS LED BY KESELOWSKI
HAVE TO RUN THAT HIGH LINE.
AS YOU CAN SEE THE MOMENTUM OF
THAT OUTSIDE LANE CARRIES HIM
DOWN THE STRAIGHTAWAYS.
>> FORD MUSTANGS OUT FRONT FOR
BRAD KESELOWSKI AND ARIC
ALMIROLA.
THAT LEAD DRAFT HAS ABOUT 20
CARS, 21 CARS IN IT.
>> BASICALLY NOTHING BUT FORDS.
YOU HAVE STENHOUSE THERE IN
SIXTH IN THE CHEVROLET AND KURT
BUSCH IN TENTH.
>> JIMMIE JOHNSON, HOW ABOUT THE
PENALTY CALLED ON JIMMIE
JOHNSON?
>> WHAT GOT THEM IN TROUBLE WAS
ACTUALLY WHERE THEY'RE PITTING
WITH THAT OPENING IN FRONT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE THE GUYS
JUST STEP OUT ON PIT ROAD.
YOU SEE THEM CIRCLED RIGHT
THERE.
JUST STEPPED OUT ON PIT ROAD
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S NOT A WALL
THERE.
THAT'S COUNTED AS TOO MANY MEN
OVER THE WALL.
>> THANKS, LARRY.
AGAIN, IT WAS 32, CORY LAJOIE.
WE GOT SOME BAD INFORMATION ON
WHOSE CREW WAS OVER THE WALL TOO
SOON.
NOT BRAD KESELOWSKI WHO RUNS IN
THIS FRONT PACK IN THE FRONT
THREE FIRST CAR ON THE OUTSIDE
TO ALMIROLA AND KEVIN HARVICK.
>> JIMMIE JOHNSON GIVE A LITTLE
WAVE.
I THINK IT WAS THE 37 BEHIND HIM
OF RYAN PREECE PROBABLY LET
JIMMIE IN.
JUST SHOWING A LITTLE THANK YOU.
>> JOEY LOGANO RAN SECOND FOR
THE FIRST 20 LAPS OF THIS
DAYTONA 500.
MATT?
>> MIKE N THAT OUTSIDE LANE
LOGANO TOLD SPOTTER T.J. MAJORS
A FEW MOMENTS AGO, YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED TO HELP ME ON THE EXIT
OF TURN FOUR BECAUSE THE SUN IS
SUCH A CHALLENGE.
CAN'T SEE IN MY MIRROR BECAUSE
OF THE ANGLE OF THE SUN.
>> THAT WON'T BE A PROBLEM AT
THE FINISH OF THIS DAYTONA 500.
THE LIGHTS WILL BE ON.
IT WILL BE DARK.
THE SPARKS WILL BE FLYING.
HOPEFULLY JUST FROM UNDER THE
CAR AND NOT BETWEEN BETWEEN
CARS.
>> ONLY GLARE YOU WANT WHEN THIS
RACE ENDS IS FROM FLASHBULBS
GOING OFF IN VICTORY LANE.
>> WHAT A DIFFERENT RACE THOUGH
TODAY, MIKE.
WE SAW THIS RACE TAKE OFF
YESTERDAY AND I THINK A LOT OF
TEAMS HAD A STRATEGY THAT HAD
FUEL INVOLVED.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT FUEL.
THEY'RE SIDE BY SIDE ALL THE WAY
BACK.
BUMP DRAFTING HERE EARLY ON.
HERE'S ALEX BOWMAN WITH A MOVE
AND HIS TEAMMATES LINED UP
BEHIND HIM AND WILLIAM BYRON AND
JIMMIE JOHNSON.
>> KESELOWSKI TAKES THE HIGH
GROOVE TO THE FRONT WITH RYAN
NEWMAN AND STENHOUSE IN TOW.
THEN CUSTER, LOGANO AND MATT
DiBENEDETTO WHO'S NEW TO THE 21
OF THE WOOD BROTHERS THIS YEAR.
NOW GOING TO THE OTHER END OF
THE FIELD IN 36th PLACE, CLINT
BOWYER.
JAMIE?
>> JUST LIKE WE SAW YESTERDAY,
MIKE, CLINT BOWYER BY DESIGN HAS
CHOSEN TO FALL TO THE BACK.
HE JUST FEELS LIKE THAT IS HIS
BEST BET TO BE SAFE AND BE THERE
AT THE END.
IT HAS NOT BEEN NICE TO HIM, THE
DAYTONA 500, THAT IS, OVER THE
LAST FEW YEARS.
HE HAS A HARD TIME FINISHING
THESE RACES.
I TALKED TO HIS CREW CHIEF.
JOHNNY WORKS WITH OUR -- HE'S IN
THIRD NOW.
ARIC ALMIROLA THE LAST TWO
YEARS.
ARIC LIKES TO BE UP FRONT.
WITH CLINT FALLING TO THE BACK
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT DYNAMIC,
SETUP.
YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT DIFFERENT
FUEL MILEAGE NUMBERS BUT HE'S
GOING TO HOLD OUT AND HOPE IT
WORKS FOR HIM TODAY.
>> CLINT TOLD ME I HATE RACING
MY GUTS OUT HERE ONLY TO GET
CAUGHT UP IN SOMEBODY ELSE'S
MESS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE RIGHT
STRATEGY IS, MIKE.
I'VE TALKED TO A LOT OF DRIVERS,
I'VE DONE IT MYSELF WHERE I'VE
PUSHED HARD TO BE UP FRONT TO BE
OUT OF TROUBLE AND YOU STILL GET
CAUGHT UP.
YOU RIGHT AROUND IN THE BACK,
EVEN THEN WHEN IT'S TIME TO GO,
YOU STILL GET CAUGHT UP IN THE
WRECK.
SO THERE IS NO SET STRATEGY THAT
REALLY WORKS.
NO REAL GAME PLAN, YOU'VE JUST
GOT TO GO FOR IT AND STICK WITH
WHATEVER YOUR PLAN IS.
>> WITH 33 LAPS COMPLETE, FORDS
HAVE NINE OF THE TOP TEN SPOTS
AND WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE FROM
DAYTONA, BUT FIRST HERE IS A
SPECIAL MESSAGE FROM WENDY'S.
(Ding)
These are a few of
my favorite things.
Yep, Wendy's is changing
the game from THIS...
To a breakfast that eats other
breakfasts for breakfast.
These are a few of
my favorite things.
Who says you can't have a
Baconator for Breakfast?
Sausage patty piled high
with 6 pieces of bacon.
Six?!
Don't just "grab a coffee..."
Grab a Frosty-ccino instead:
cold brew with our
famous Frosty mix.
And it's only half the calories
of a Starbucks Cafe
Vanilla Frappuccino.
Half?
And forget that
frozen-folded-egg-stuff.
'Cause Wendy's only uses
fresh-cracked eggs on
on ALL our breakfast sandwiches.
ALL OF THEM.
One bite and it'll
be your new favorite.
Guaranteed.
That's right, it's
actually guaranteed.
My favorite things.
These are a few of
my favorite things.
So racing fans, say goodnight
to that old breakfast,
Hello?
And ask yourself,
You Up For This?
♪ Favorite things! ♪
Honey where's our limo?
We're not getting a limo.
I thought you were
going to get a car
that was classy and elegant.
Oh we are.
♪
This one's got over
700 horse power.
Great, 'cause I'm driving.
You're fanatical about NASCAR.
GEICO is fanatical
about saving you money
on car insurance.
Fifteen minutes could save you
fifteen percent or more.
Proud partner of NASCAR.
Fifteen minutes could save you
fifteen percent or more.
Exploring isn't just doing
one thing well.
You need to set a course.
Adjust your speed.
Avoid danger.
Manage multiple terrains.
And cover your blind spots.
All while keeping the
crew happy.
The completely redesigned
2020 Ford Explorer
with available Ford Co-Pilot
360 technology.
The Greatest Exploration
vehicle of all time.
We're off to a good start
from left bead.
but right bead is
cutting him off now,
left bead is making
a bit of contact
OHH we've got a double bead!
going for the inside line!
the left bead! into first place!
WOW!
aaaahhhh. Beautiful.
>>> I HEAR THEY'RE REMAKING A
GREAT RACING MOVIE.
"TOP GUN."
>> GREAT SHOT.
37 LAPS OF 200 COMPLETE THAT
WILL MAKE UP THE 500 MILES HERE
IN DAYTONA.
FORDS ON POINT.
EIGHT OF THE FIRST NINE.
RICKY STENHOUSE 47th.
THE ONLY CHEVROLET IN THAT
GROUP.
THE REST OF THE CHEVYS ARE LINED
UP 8th THROUGH 11th AND THEN A
GAGGLE FROM 34th BACK.
THOSE TOYOTAS WERE WONDERING
ABOUT, WELL, DO WE SIT HERE?
DO WE PULL OUT?
ARE WE GETTING TOO FAR BACK?
HOW ARE WE DOING?
>> I THINK THE 34 NEEDS TO CATCH
UP TO THE TAIL OF THAT OTHER
PACK.
I KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING, BUT
THE GAP'S TOO BIG.
>> MIGHT NEED TO DRIVE AROUND
THEM IF THEY'RE GOING TO FALL
OFF THAT HARD.
>> NO, THEY'RE GOING FORWARD.
DON'T JUMP IT.
WE'RE GOING TO RACE IT AND WE'RE
GOING TO GET STUCK SIDE BY SIDE.
DON'T DO IT.
>> IF THEY'RE WORRIED ABOUT
GETTING SIDE BY SIDE, THAT TELLS
ME THEY'RE IN FULL FUEL CON
VARGS MODE.
>> THE BEST THING THAT'S
HAPPENING FOR THEM IS THAT THEY
ARE SIDE BY SIDE.
AS HE MENTIONED, THE 34, THERE'S
DEFINITELY A BIGGER GAP THAN
WHAT THEY WANTED TO SEE.
WHAT WE'VE TRIED TO DECIPHER ON
WHAT THEIR STRATEGY IS WE
BELIEVER THAT TOWARDS THE END OF
THIS STAGE THEY'RE ACTUALLY
GOING TO TRY TO MAKE A RUN AT
THAT FRONT GROUP AND MAKE UP
SOME POSITIONS BECAUSE THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO STOP AT THAT
STAGE ANYWAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE ADVANTAGE
OF SAVING FUEL WOULD BE RIGHT
NOW.
>> WE'LL FIND OUT.
65 LAPS IS THE END OF STAGE 1.
COMPLETING LAP 39 RIGHT NOW WITH
RYAN NEWMAN OF ROUSH FENWAY
RACING IN THE NUMBER 6 FORD OUT
FRONT.
ARIC ALMIROLA AND BRAD
KESELOWSKI AND IT'S ON FOR THE
LEAD.
HERE COMES ALMIROLA WHO CAME
WITHIN ONE MILE OF WINNING THE
DAYTONA 500 A COUPLE OF YEARS
AGO.
WAS LEADING IN THE BACK STRETCH
AND GOT TURNED AROUND ON THE
LAST LAP.
>> WHAT A FAST RACE CAR HE HAS
TODAY.
HE WAS REALLY EXCITED AND YOU
COULD TELL, HE'S HAD THAT
SWAGGER.
HE HAD THAT CONFIDENCE AND HE'S
SHOWING IT TODAY.
NOW ONE OF THE THINGS HE COULD
HAVE EASILY DONE IS MOVED UP IN
FRONT OF RYAN NEWMAN THERE TO
MAINTAIN THIS LEAD AND CONTROL
WHICH LANE HE WANTED TO STAY IN,
BUT HE'S WORKING WITH HIS
TEAMMATE RIGHT BEHIND HIM KEVIN
HARVICK.
PRETTY CONTENT BEING IN THAT --
NOSE TO TAIL RIGHT NOW.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT ONE CHEVROLET
UP TOWARDS THE FRONT, RICKY
STENHOUSE, OUR POLE SITTER.
VINCE?
>> THEY JUST TOLD RICKY AS YOU
GUYS HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT,
FUEL MILEAGE REALLY IMPORTANT.
TRYING TO GET TO THE END OF THE
FIRST STAGE.
THEY JUST TOLD RICKY, THE
MILEAGE IS NOT GOOD IF YOU'RE
ONE OF THE FIRST TWO CARS IN
LINE.
SO KEEP THAT IN MIND AS YOU SEE
WHERE RICKY STENHOUSE JR. HAS
HIMSELF POSITIONED.
>> HE'S GOT A LITTLE HELP NOW.
THE NUMBER 9 AND 48 CHEVROLETS
OF CHASE ELLIOTT AND JIMMIE
JOHNSON ARE RIGHT UP THERE WITH
HIM.
LARRY?
>> MIKE, I SPENT A LOT OF TIME
LAST NIGHT AND THIS MORNING
TALKING WITH DIFFERENT CREW
CHIEFS AND IT'S AMAZING THE
DIFFERENCE IN THE MILEAGE WHEN
YOU'RE UP THERE LEADING, PULLING
THE PACK OR YOU'RE BACK SINGLE
FILE DRAFTING.
FOR EXAMPLE, IF YOU'RE LEADING,
YOU'RE GETTING 5.2 TO 5.3 MILES
PER GALL.
THAT'S A 39 TO 40 LAP FUEL
WINDOW.
IF YOU'RE SINGLE FILE DRAFTING
YOU'RE GETTING AS MUCH AS 5.8 TO
6 MILES TO THE GALLON WHICH WILL
ADD 2 TO 3 TO 4 LAPS TO WHAT YOU
CAN RUN ON FUEL.
>> SEE RIGHT HERE RIDING ON
BOARD WITH CHRISTOPHER BELL.
HE'S RUNNING ABOUT 60, 70%
THROTTLE.
SO DEFINITELY IN FUEL MODE.
NOW I'M REALLY STARTING TO GET
CONCERNED WITH SOME OF THESE
CARS AT THE FRONT THAT ARE
RUNNING WIDE OPEN AND HAVE BEEN
SIDE BY SIDE.
THEY'RE NOT SAVING ANY FUEL AND
SOME OF THOSE CARS DIDN'T EVEN
TOP OFF, MIKE.
>> HOW ABOUT THE TOYOTAS WAY OUT
BACK.
MATT?
>> MIKE, GO BACK TO PRACTICE ON
FRIDAY.
THE FIVE TOYOTAS WERE ALL IN
LINE.
OVER 20 LAPS THEY WOULD RUN FIVE
LAPS EACH.
THAT WAY THEY COULD HAVE GREAT
INFORMATION FOR WHICH TOYOTA
WOULD HAVE GREAT INFORMATION FOR
BEING A PULLER.
>> THEY'RE HOLDING STATION OUT
BACK.
>> THERE IS A BIG DIFFERENCE IN
THIS GROUP AND THE CUTOFF LINE
IS SIXth.
EVERYBODY ABOVE THE LINE PITTED
AT LAP 23.
EVERYBODY BELOW THIS LINE, NOW
STENHOUSE, PITTED AND TOPPED OFF
AT LAP 24.
THAT ONE EXTRA LAP COULD MAKE A
DIFFERENCE.
>> I THINK IT IS GOING TO MAKE A
DIFFERENCE, OTHERWISE I THINK
SOME OF THESE DRIVERS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO START SAVING A LOT OF
FUEL TOWARDS THE END OF THIS
STAGE.
JAMIE?
>> GUYS, I'M WATCHING.
I'M THINKING THE TOYOTAS, THE
ONLY WAY THIS IS GOING TO WORK
IS IF THEY GET SINGLE FILE IN
FRONT.
THE ONLY WAY THEY CAN ADVANCE IS
IF THEY'RE SINGLE FILE AND THEY
CAN PUSH.
WE SAW HOW FAST THEY WERE
TOGETHER.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
GET TO THE FRONT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY HAVE TO
GAIN THEN.
>> 26 LAPS WE'LL FIND OUT.
THAT'S THE END OF STAGE ONE.
ARIC ALMIROLA IN A FORD IS YOUR
RACE LEADER.
FIRST CHEVY IS RICKY STENHOUSE
IN 6th.
THE FIRST TOYOTA IS MARTIN TRUEX
JR. IN 34th.
35 LAPS COMPLETE IN THE DAYTONA
500.
d the wolf huffed
and puffed.
Like you do sometimes,
Grandpa?
Well, when you have COPD,
it can be hard to breathe.
So my doctor said...
SYMBICORT can help you breathe
better—starting
within 5 minutes.
It doesn't replace a rescue
inhaler for sudden symptoms.
SYMBICORT helps provide
significant improvement
of your lung function.
SYMBICORT is for COPD,
including chronic bronchitis
and emphysema.
It should not be taken more
than twice a day.
It may increase your risk
of lung infections,
osteoporosis,
and some eye problems.
Tell your doctor if you have
a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
SYMBICORT could mean a day
with better breathing.
Watch out, piggies!
Ask your doctor if SYMBICORT
is right for you.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
Allow us to
reintroduce ourselves.
A new retro-inspired look...
...for the great
American lager.
This Bud's For You.
Little Caesars delivery is the
best thing since sliced bread.
Sorry, sliced bread.
Save $5 or more
over other national chains
on delivered pizza.
(Doorbell rings.)
In 1979
Pizza, pizza.
Jiffy Lube changed everything
by providing the first
convenient oil change service.
♪
Millions of
satisfied customers later,
we're still who you trust.
♪
Jiffy Lube.
You can do more in a Jiffy.
>>> BILL ELLIOTT JUAN THE
DAYTONA 500 IN 1985 AND WAS A
PERENNIAL MOST POPULAR DRIVER
CHOICE.
NOW THAT MANTLE FALLS TO HIS SON
CHASE WHOSE HENDRICK CHEVROLET
MOMENTS AGO TOOK OVER THE LEAD
FROM CHRIS BUESCHER.
THE CHEVYS MOVE TO THE FRONT
INCLUDING JIMMIE JOHNSON WHO
RESTARTED TAIL END OF THE FIELD.
>> YEAH.
REMEMBER, HE HAD THAT PENALTY
DURING THE PIT STOP BUT JIMMIE
JOHNSON'S BEEN LOCKED ONTO THE
BUMPER OF EITHER CHASE ELLIOTT,
I THINK WE SAW HIM WORKING WITH
WILLIAM BYRON AND ALEX BOWMAN.
THOSE FOUR CHEVROLETS AT
HENDRICK MOTORSPORTS FEEL LIKE
THEY SAVED ENOUGH FUEL.
THEY SHOWED A LOT OF SPEED IN
QUALIFYING.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN IT PLAY OUT SO
FAR TODAY UNTIL NOW.
>> SO NOW THERE'S A SIX-PACK OF
CHEVYS AT THE FRONT OF THE
FIELD.
CHASE ELLIOTT, JIMMIE JOHNSON,
ALEX BOWMAN, WILLIAM BYRON, THE
HENDRICK CARS, RICKY STENHOUSE
FOR JTG DOHERTY RACING AND TY
DILLON IN THE 13.
LATE AFTERNOON MONDAY HOLIDAY.
48 LAPS COMPLETE.
STAGE BREAK AT LAP 65.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE A GOOD TIME TO
CRANK IT UP.
>> 15 AT THE LINE RIGHT HERE
THIS TIME.
>> TELL ME WHEN I CAN GO WIDE
OPEN AND MAKE IT.
TRYING TO SAVE AS MUCH AS I CAN.
>> 15 LEFT AT THIS STAGE.
>> ONE UP TOP SLOW.
>> DID YOU SAY I CAN GO?
>> 74 GOING BY.
SAVE ON FUEL.
DRAGGING THE WHOLE LINE BACK.
>> LET THEM GO.
>> 15 CARS IN THE LEAD DRAFT OFF
TURN NUMBER FOUR.
THINGS ARE GETTING BUSY THOUGH
BEHIND THEM AS DRIVERS BEGIN TO
JOCKEY FOR POSITION.
KYLE BUSCH JUST SAID ON THE
RADIO, COME ON, IT'S TIME TO GO.
14.
MAKE IT 13 LAPS TO GO IN STAGE
ONE.
>> AS FAR BACK AS THEY ARE, I
DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY'RE GOING
TO GO.
>> HERE'S KEVIN HARVICK'S RADIO.
>> CRAZIEST THING I'VE EVER
SEEN.
>> ALL THOSE GUYS AROUND YOU
WERE RIDING SAVING FUEL.
>> WE DID THAT ON THE BOTTOM.
>> VINCE?
>> YEAH, KEVIN WAS CONFUSED AS
TO WHY THEY ALL WENT TO THE TOP
OF THE TRACK WHEN THEY HAD BEEN
RUNNING AT THE BOTTOM.
HE WAS TOLD THERE WERE ONLY FOUR
FORDS DOWN ON THE BOTTOM SO THEY
ALL WENT TO THE TOP.
KEVIN DIDN'T LIKE THAT STRATEGY
AND THAT LINE OF THINKING.
HE WAS A GOOD TEAM PLAYER, HE
WASN'T TOO PLEASED ABOUT IT.
>> YOU'RE RIDING WITH AUSTIN
DILLON ON THE COCA-COLA CAM.
DILLON WAS CONCERNED THAT
LEADING THAT PACK HE WAS BURNING
TOO MUCH FUEL SO HE'S DRIFTED
BACK OUT OF THE LEAD POSITION
BUT THINGS QUICKLY WENT DOUBLE
WIDE THERE.
IN 12th PLACE, RYAN BLANEY.
HERE'S REGAN.
>> THE REPORT FROM CREW CHIEF TO
DRIVER RYAN BLANEY WAS THAT YOU
HAVE SAVED ENOUGH FUEL.
FEEL FREE TO GO WHENEVER YOU
WANT TO.
YOU'RE GOOD TO GO TO THE END OF
THE STAGE.
THESE CARS AT THE FRONT SOME OF
THEM APPEAR TO BE OKAY WITH FUEL
NOW.
>> I THINK THAT'S WHAT YOU SEE
OUT OF THESE CHEVROLETS LEADING
RIGHT NOW.
THEY CAME A LAP LATER, TOPPED
OFF AND THEN THEY STAGED A
LITTLE BIT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
PACK.
AS SOON AS THE FORDS HAD TO
START SAVING A LITTLE BIT MORE
THEY DROVE RIGHT BY THEM AND
TOOK THE LEAD.
>> IN 11 LAPS WE'LL SEE WHO WINS
STAGE ONE OF THIS YEAR'S DAYTONA
500.
ailer.
Invisible trailer?
And it's not the
trailer right next to us?
This guy?
You don't
believe me?
Hop in.
Good lookin' pickup,
I will say that.
Oh wow.
Silverado offers an optional
technology package with
up to 15
different views -
including one
enhanced view
that makes your
trailer appear invisible.
Wow.
- That's pretty sweet.
- That's cool.
Oooohh!
That's awesome.
Where'd the trailer go?
I love it.
It's magic.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
[ siren ]
I love it.
Give me your hand!
I can save you...
Lots of money with
Liberty Mutual!
We customize your
car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need!
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
I only have as long as
this pit stop takes
to tell you about Busch's
fastest giveaway ever.
All you have to do
is watch Daytona,
tweet #PitForBusch
every time Harvick pits
and you could win
a Busch sports car!
Whew, with a second to spa...
BUSCHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
In 1979
Jiffy Lube changed everything
by providing the first
convenient oil change service.
♪
Millions of
satisfied customers later,
they're changing everything...
again.
Jiffy Lube Multicare.
Brakes, batteries,
spark plugs and more.
You can do more in a Jiffy.
>>> YOU'RE WATCHING THE 15-CAR
LEAD DRAFT FROM THE GOODYEAR
BLIMP.
GOODYEAR, DISCOVER WHAT'S
POSSIBLE.
KEEP MOVING.
GOODYEAR, MORE DRIVEN.
EIGHT LAPS TO GO IN STAGE ONE.
JOEY LOGANO, THE YELLOW CAR IN
THE OUTSIDE LANE TRYING TO MAKE
SOMETHING HAPPEN HERE WITH ARIC
ALMIROLA ON THE OUTSIDE.
>> I FEEL LIKE THEY NOW ARE IN
THEIR FUEL WINDOW.
THEY WANT TO TRY TO GET TRACK
POSITION OR GET THOSE VALUABLE
POINTS THAT ARE GOING TO BE
AWARDED AT THE END OF THIS
STAGE.
>> NOW A QUARTER OF A LAP DOWN.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THE
TOYOTAS.
HERE'S KYLE BUSCH'S RADIO.
>> CAN THE LEAD PACK MAKE IT THE
WHOLE WAY?
>> A BUNCH OF THEM SAVED.
>> IF THEY CAN ALL MAKE IT WE'RE
RACING THE WHOLE PACK.
SO WE EITHER GO UP THERE AND
RACE IT OR HANG OUT HERE AND
FORFEIT.
>> WOW.
I'M AS BAFFLED AS KYLE BUSCH IS
OF WHAT THEIR STRATEGY IS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ANYBODY IS.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE THEY'RE
GOING O PIT BEFORE THIS STAGE
ENDS SO I'M JUST COMPLETELY
CONFUSED.
>> LOOK, I THOUGHT THEY WERE
SAVING GAS OR JUST BEING
CONSERVATIVE TO STAY OUT OF THE
WRECKS.
>> AND THERE IT IS.
ONE CAR GOES SLIDING ACROSS THE
INFIELD GRASS.
WILLIAM BYRON WHO WON HIS
QUALIFYING RACE HERE ON
THURSDAY.
AND THAT WILL CHANGE EVERYTHING.
>> CERTAINLY HAS CHANGED IT FOR
THAT EXAL AT THAT 24.
>> CONTACT WITH RICKY STENHOUSE
PUTS WILLIAM BYRON INTO THE
INSIDE WALL AND A HARD HIT.
>> I BELIEVE HE WAS IN FOURTH
POSITION IN FRONT OF RICKY
STENHOUSE JR.
>> WELL, HE'D LIKE TO DRIVE IT
AWAY BUT HE HASN'T SEEN THE
FRONT END OF THAT.
>> THAT'S -- THAT'S DEFINITELY.
>> ROLL BACTERIAL.
>> NO CHANCES OF WINNING THIS
DAYTONA 500.
>> OFFICIALLY IT IS THE SECOND
CAUTION FLAG OF THE DAYTONA 500.
WATCH THE 47 OF STENHOUSE.
>> THEY HAD JUST GOTTEN A RUN.
THE 10 GETS TO THE REAR BUMPER
OF THE 13.
LITTLE SURGE OF THE 47.
OH, HE GETS TO THE LEFT SIDE OF
THAT REAR BUMPER.
WHEN YOU TRY TO BUMP DRAFT, YOU
NEED TO BE EITHER THE CENTER OR
TO THE RIGHT.
IT ALMOST LOOKED LIKE STENHOUSE
WAS GOING TO POKE OUT AND TRY TO
GO BY HIM AND MAYBE MISJUDGED.
MADE CONTACT AND TURNED WILLIAM
BYRON RIGHT AROUND.
THOSE GUYS HAD SO MUCH
ANTICIPATION AFTER THAT GREAT
DUEL ON THURSDAY.
>> YOU CAN JUST SEE AS RICKY
STENHOUSE JR. MOVED LEFT HE JUST
CAUGHT THAT LEFT REAR OF THE
BUMPER.
>> INTO THE SAFER BARRIER THAT
NOW LINES THE INSIDE OF THE
SPEEDWAY AS WELL AS THE OUTSIDE.
>> HERE'S CHAD KNAUS HIS CREW
CHIEF.
>> YOU WORK SO HARD.
>> WILLIAM IS OKAY.
THAT'S THE AMR SAFETY TEAM
ATTENDING TO HIM OUT THERE ON
THE BACK STRAIGHTAWAY.
HE'LL MAKE THE MANDATORY RIDE TO
THE ADVENT HEALTH CARE CENTER
AND HIS HOPES OF WINNING THE 500
ARE DASHED.
>> YOU JUST WORK SO HARD TO GET
DOWN HERE.
YOU'VE GOT ONE CHANCE EVERY YEAR
TO WIN THE DAYTONA 500 AND THAT
CHANCE IS NOW GONE FOR THAT 24
TEAM.
NOW THEY'RE ON PIT ROAD.
>> FORDS LED BY FORDS OF BRAD
KESELOWSKI, KEVIN HARVICK AND
COLE CUSTER AND ALL THE TOYOTAS
COMING IN TO TOP OFF AS WELL.
JOEY GASE WILL GET THE FREE
PASS, MEANING HE CAN COME AROUND
UNDER CAUTION AND GET BACK ON
THE LEAD LAP.
>> THIS IS ONE AREA YOU SEE
CHRISTOPHER BELL, ONE OF OUR
ROOKIES OVER SHOT HIS PIT, HAD
TO BACK INTO IT.
THAT WILL COST HIM A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME.
SO THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE UP
THOSE STAGE POINTS BY PITTING
NOW.
YOU SEE THEY GO AROUND TO THE
LEFT SIDE.
PUT FOUR TIRES ON THE 18 OF KYLE
BUSCH.
THEY'RE GOING TO GAIN THAT TRACK
POSITION BACK AFTER THOSE OTHERS
PIT WHEN THIS STAGE IS OVER.
>> THERE'S THE RACE OFF PIT
ROAD.
12 DRIVERS TO THE FRONT OF THE
FIELD DID NOT PIT AS WILLIAM
BYRON GETS SENT SLIDING ACROSS
THE GRASS INTO THE INFIELD
BARRIER AND OUT OF THE 500.
KFC's Original Recipe
is made from
a secret blend of 11
herbs and spices.
And now you can get
2 pieces of my
world famous chicken
as a 5 dollar fill up.
A secret you can eat
for just 5 bucks.
KFC
It's Finger Lickin' Good
Dear Jimmie,
A secret you can eat
for just 5 bucks.
My name is Ethan.
I've been a fan of yours
my whole life.
I've been watching you race
my entire life.
Since I was two years old.
You're the best driver
I've ever seen.
You've won so many races.
7 championships
5 in a row?!
Who does that?
♪
Forget about last year,
I have.
♪
But I know you still got it.
If anyone can bring it home,
it's you.
You're not done yet
are you?
Are you?
You're the fastest racer.
G - O - A - T
The GOAT!
The greatest of all time!
It's your last lap!
You got this.
Let's go burn some rubber!
Pedal to the metal.
Turn it up Jimmie!
Let's go!
I believe in you!
Finish strong.
One more lap.
One final time.
♪
♪ Yes I'm stuck in
the middle with you, ♪
No one likes to feel stuck,
boxed in, or held back.
Especially by something
Like your cloud.
It's a problem.
But the IBM Cloud is different.
It's the most open and secure
public cloud for business.
It can manage all your apps
and data from anywhere.
So it can help take on anything,
from rebooking
flights, on the fly
to restocking shelves on demand.
Without getting in your way.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>> THE DAYTONA 500 ON FOX IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY THE ALL NEW
FORD EXPLORER BUILT FORD PROUD.
>> ANOTHER PIT STOP FOR THE
NUMBER 4 CAR MEANS ANOTHER
CHANCE FOR YOU TO WIN A NEW CAR
FROM BUSCH BEER.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TWEET
#PIT4BUSCH AND #SWEEPSTAKES
WHILE HARVICK IS PITTING AND YOU
COULD WIN BIG SO TWEET NOW.
COMING TO THE END OF STAGE ONE
WE'RE GOING TO GET ONE TO GO.
MICHAEL McDOWELL COMES IN TO TOP
OFF, SO DOES TIMMY HILL.
HERE COMES KEVIN HARVICK AND
KYLE BUSCH AND ALL THE REST OF
THE TOYOTAS.
>> I THINK WE'RE STARTING TO NOW
LEARN MORE ABOUT THE STRATEGY BY
THE TOYOTAS.
I THINK THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE UP
TRACK POSITION, GIVE UP STAGE
POINTS AND TRY TO GET THEMSELVES
OUT OF ANY POTENTIAL WRECKS AND
BE IN POSITION TO WIN THE
DAYTONA 500 AT 400 OR 450 MILES.
NOT RIGHT NOW.
>> LARRY, DO YOU AGREE WITH THIS
AS A LONG-TERM PLAN?
>> YEAH, I THINK THEY'RE TRYING
TO GET THEIR TRACK POSITION
RIGHT THERE.
WITH THEIR COMING BACK AND
TOPPING OFF, IT GETS THEM AT THE
BACK OF THE FIELD OUT OF
TROUBLE.
>> WITH TWO LAPS TO GO UNTIL THE
END OF STAGE ONE.
PLAYOFF POINTS AT STAKE FOR THE
STAGE WINNER.
AND POINTS TO BE AWARDED TO THE
TOP TEN WHEN THEY TAKE THE GREEN
AND WHITE CHECKERED FLAG AT LAP
65.
WHERE'S OUR DRONE GOING TO
RESTART?
ANYWHERE HE WANTS, RIGHT?
>> WE KNOW WHAT THE PACE CAR'S
RUNNING.
OUR DRONE IS OUTRUNNING THE PACE
CAR RIGHT NOW.
THAT THING GETS UP AND GOES.
>> 80 VERSUS 70, I BELIEVE.
SO ON POINT, CHEVROLETS.
CHASE ELLIOTT, JIMMIE JOHNSON.
BOWMAN AND STENHOUSE IN CHEVYS.
ARIC ALMIROLA THE LONE FORD IN
THE TOP FIVE.
LOOKS LIKE AN X WING FIGHTER
FROM "STAR WARS."
>> SO COOL.
SO COOL.
YES, I AM A "STAR WARS" FAN.
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M GOING TO BE CURIOUS TO
SEE HOW IMPORTANT STAGE POINTS
ARE TO THESE COMPETITORS RIGHT
NOW BECAUSE IF THEY'RE GOING TO
BE AGGRESSIVE TO GET THOSE
POINTS, THEN AT THE END OF EACH
OF THESE STAGES TODAY WE'RE
GOING O SEE A HECK OF A RACE AND
A BATTLE FOR THEM.
>> NONE OF THE TOP 13 HAVE BEEN
ON PIT ROAD SINCE LAP 24.
EVERYONE FROM 14th ON BACK HAS
JUST PITTED.
TWO LAPS TO RACE TO THE END OF
STAGE ONE AS CHASE ELLIOTT AND
JIMMIE JOHNSON LEAD THEM TOWARDS
TURN ONE.
AND JUST NOW THE TOYOTAS ARE
CROSSING THE START/FINISH LINE
HALF A LAP BACK.
>> REALLY NOT EVEN MOVING AT
FULL SPEED.
SO I THINK THEY FEEL LIKE MAYBE
SOMETHING BIG IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN
IN FRONT OF THEM.
AND THEY'RE SAVING A LOT MORE
FUEL, TOO, DOING THAT.
BIG PUSH FROM THE 88 OF ALEX
BOWMAN TO THE REAR BUMPER OF HER
TEAMMATE CHASE ELLIOTT.
LOOKED LIKE KURT BUSCH WAS GOING
TO POKE TO THE OUTSIDE.
>> HE AND MATT DiBENEDETTO HAD A
LOOK UP HIGH BUT AS THEY COME
OFF OF FOUR IT WILL BE ONE LAP
TO THE END OF STAGE ONE.
>> REMEMBER, THE TOP TEN PAY
POINTS AT THE END OF THIS STAGE.
>> JIMMIE JOHNSON WITH STENHOUSE
LEADING THE OUTSIDE ROW.
AND THE JOE GIBBS CARS ARE
COMING TO THE LINE NOW.
>> I THINK THEY CAN PROBABLY
ABOUT 1/3 THROTTLE IT TO THE END
OF THE STAGE.
>> SOME DECISIONS FOR THOSE
HENDRICKS CHEVROLETS.
ARE THEY GOING TO MOVE UP AND
WORK WITH JIMMIE JOHNSON A AND
THEIR TEAMMATE OR DO THEY HAVE
TO BLOCK THE BIG RUN COMING FROM
THE VERY FAST NUMBER 10 OF ARIC
ALMIROLA.
>> HERE COME THE FORDS, 10 AND
22.
ALMIROLA.
>> TY DILLON, THREE WIDE DOWN TO
THE LINE AND THE STAGE ONE
WINNER, CHASE ELLIOTT OVER ALEX
BOWMAN, ARIC ALMIROLA, JOEY
LOGANO AND JIMMIE JOHNSON.
>> GOOD JOB, BUDDY.
MEANWHILE, HALF A LAP LATER --
>> YEAH, THESE GUYS ARE IN FULL
FUEL SAVING MODE.
>> AND THE REST OF THE FIELD
CROSSES THE LINE.
LET'S CHECK WITH JAMIE.
>> WILLIAM BYRON HAS BEEN
CHECKED AND RELEASED AND HE IS
OKAY.
SO MUCH PREPARATION, SO MUCH
DRAFT PRACTICE ALL TO END LIKE
THAT.
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY GOT HIT IN THE
BACK BUMPER.
I SAW A BRIEF REPLAY OF IT.
SEE IT HERE.
YEAH, I MEAN, HE WAS KIND OF
MOVING WHEN HE HIT ME FIRST AND
PUSHED ME LEFT WITH HIM AND THEN
HE HIT ME OFF CENTER IN THE REAR
AND IT JUST TURNED ME AROUND.
IT WAS JUST ENOUGH -- THE FIRST
HIT WHEN HE WAS SLIDING LEFT ON
MY BUMPER WAS WHAT REALLY MOVED
MY CAR LEFT WITH HIM AND SO,
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST -- IT'S
UNFORTUNATE.
I FEEL LIKE -- I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S REALLY NO
REASON IT'S LAP 45 OR WHATEVER
TO BE THAT AGGRESSIVE MOVING
ACROSS MY BUMPER BUT IT IS WHAT
IT IS.
WE'LL GO INTO VEGAS AND GO TRY
TO WIN THAT ONE.
>> WILLIAM BYRON, FIRST ONE OUT
OF THE DAYTONA 500.
MIKE.
>> THANKS, JAMIE.
LAS VEGAS MOTOR SPEEDWAY BECOMES
THE SECOND RACE OF THE SEASON.
THAT'S WHERE FOX NASCAR COVERAGE
WILL BE THIS WEEKEND AND A HATS
OFF NOT TO JUST OUR CAMERAMAN
AND THE GREAT CAMERA WORK YOU'VE
SEEN AND ALL OF OUR TECHNICIANS,
ALL OF OUR STAFF, MANY OF WHOM
HAVE NOT BEEN HOME FOR 25 DAYS.
THEY WENT TO MIAMI TO DO THE
SUPER BOWL, THEY CAME RIGHT HERE
TO DAYTONA, TWO WEEKS OF
SPEEDWEEKS AND TONIGHT IT ALL
GETS PACKED UP AND ROLLS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY TO LAS VEGAS.
PIT ROAD SHOULD BE OPEN THIS
TIME AROUND FOR THE END OF STAGE
ONE SERVICE.
CHEVROLETS OF ELLIOTT AND
BOWMAN.
THE FORDS OF ALMIROLA AND
LOGANO.
JIMMIE JOHNSON ARE YOUR FIRST
FIVE.
CHRIS BUESCHER GOT THE FINAL
STAGE POINT.
FEBRUARY 28th JOHN CENA IS BACK
JOINING THE SUPER STARS OF
"SMACKDOWN" AS HE RETURNS HOME
TO BOSTON.
A SPECIAL FRIDAY NIGHT
"SMACKDOWN" FEBRUARY 28th, 8
EASTERN, 7 CENTRAL ON FOX.
>> YOU KNOW, I WOULD SAY A LOT
OF THE DRIVERS THAT PITTED ON
THAT LAST CAUTION WILL STAY OUT.
THE ONES THAT DID NOT WILL PIT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE TOYOTAS
ARE GOING TO DO.
>> LARRY, THE WAY THEIR STRATEGY
PLAYED OUT IN THIS FIRST STAGE,
THEY PITTED LATE, THEY KNEW THEY
ONLY HAD TO RACE TWO LAPS AND
THEY KNEW JUST HOW SLOW THEY
COULD GO AND NOT GET LAPPED
BEFORE THE END OF THE STAGE TO
SAVE AS MUCH FUEL AS POSSIBLE.
KIND OF PLAYS OUT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
PIT ROAD'S A BUSY PLACE, MATT.
>> MIKE, CHASE ELLIOTT'S IN.
MOMENTS HE SAYS OFF TURN FOUR HE
DOES EXPERIENCE A LITTLE BIT OF
FREE BUT OVERALL THE CAR IS
GOOD.
THE 22 OF LOGANO GOING ON THE
LEFT SIDE.
FOUR WHEEL DRIFT, AIR PRESSURE
ADJUSTMENT TO TRY TO TIGHTEN HIM
UP, REGAN.
>> 88 OF ALEX BOWMAN.
HE WANTED TO BE AROUND CHEVYS AT
THE END OF THE RACE AND STAGES.
VINCE?
>> ARIC ALMIROLA SAID I'M GOOD.
GIVE ME FOUR TIRES AND A
TEAROFF.
>> BRAD KESELOWSKI WINS THE RACE
OFF PIT ROAD.
THOSE CARS WITH THE GREEN UP
MARKS LIKELY TOOK JUST TWO
TIRES.
>> DENNY HAMLIN OUR LEADER
CURRENTLY.
LET'S DIAL UP OUR STAGE ONE
WINNER CHASE ELLIOTT.
HEY, CHASE, THIS IS JEFF UP IN
THE FOX SPORTS BOOTH.
YOU GOT ME, BUDDY?
HEY, CHASE.
JEFF UP IN THE FOX SPORTS BOOTH.
YOU GOT ME?
TRY HIM AGAIN AFTER THE BREAK.
>> WE'LL CHECK THE FREQUENCY,
KENNETH, AND TRY AGAIN AFTER THE
BREAK.
CHASE ELLIOTT, STAGE ONE WINNER.
With Pizza Hut's new Mozzarella
Poppers Pizza
you can switch between 16 fried
mozzarella bites
and a large pizza.
Pizza, then app. App, then
pizza.
It's your world.
We're just making pizza in it.
Hurry and try it before it's
gone.
No One OutPizzas The Hut.
Try Target's Same
Day Delivery.
At your door, so you
can get more.
♪ Feels so good ♪
Target Run & Done.
[ fast-paced drumming ]
>>> YESTERDAY HERE IN DAYTONA
THE PRESIDENT AND FIRST LADY
PACED THE OPENING LAPS OF THE
DAYTONA 500 IN THE PRESIDENTIAL
LIMOUSINE.
WE GOT 20 LAPS UNDERWAY.
WE'RE NOW AT LAP 68 IN THE 500.
HERE'S YOUR STAGE ONE WINNER.
>> YEAH, LET'S GIVE HIM ANOTHER
TRY.
HEY, CHASE, THIS IS JEFF UP IN
THE FOX SPORTS BOOTH.
YOU GOT ME?
>> YEAH, GO AHEAD.
>> WELL, GREAT WAY TO START THE
DAYTONA 500 WITH A STAGE WIN.
TELL US ABOUT YOUR CAR.
HOW ARE THE CONDITIONS?
HOW'S THE CAR DRIVING?
CERTAINLY SHOWS THAT IT HAS
PLENTY OF SPEED.
>> YEAH, WE'RE HAPPY WITH THE
CAMARO.
I THINK IT'S BEEN PLENTY FAST
ENOUGH.
IT'S A MATTER OF BEING IN THE
RIGHT PLACE.
HOPING THE LANE GOES YOUR WAY.
SO NICE TO GET A PLAYOFF POINT
AND HOPEFULLY WE CAN FINISH OUT
THE DAY JUST LIKE THAT.
>> CERTAINLY SEEN SOME DIFFERENT
STRATEGIES PLAYING OUT.
SOME SAVING FUEL MILEAGE, YOU
GUYS ARE PRETTY AGGRESSIVE
GETTING TO THE FRONT THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HOW EASY IS IT GOING TO BE FOR
YOU TO GET BACK UP THERE THIS
TIME?
>> THAT'S THE QUESTION.
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY WAS DOING
DIFFERENT THINGS THERE FOR THAT
FIRST STAGE, ON DIFFERENT
AGENDAS.
YOU'RE ONLY BATTLING 1/4, HALF
THE FIELD VERSUS LATER ON BEING
BATTLING WHOEVER IS LEFT.
>> THANKS FOR TALKING TO US.
GOOD LUCK THE REST OF THE WAY.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
>>> CHASE ELLIOTT STAGE ONE
WINNER.
THERE'S HIS PIT STOP.
DENNY HAMLIN WILL BE OUT FRONT
FOR THE RESTART WITH COLE CUSTER
FOR STAGE TWO.
You know what's good about this?
Your sign's pointing at my sign,
so people are gonna
look at my sign.
Switch to Progressive
and you can save hundreds.
You know, like the sign says.
Switch to Progressive
and you can save hundreds.
As parents of six,
this network is
one less thing
I have to worry about.
(VO)
Why the Aceves family
chose Verizon.
We all use our phones
very differently.