>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS MONDAY --
A DEADLY WINTER STORM IS ON THE
MOVE, RIGHT AS THE HUGE WEEK OF
HOLIDAY TRAVEL BEGINS.
WINTER STORM WARNING.
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS, FROM
COLORADO TO MASSACHUSETTS IN THE
PATH OF WICKED WEATHER THIS
MORNING.
HEAVY SNOW AND WIND
SENDING CARS AND TRUCKS SLIDING
OFF ROADS, THE STORM EVEN
SPARKING A DEADLY AVALANCHE.
GINGER HERE WITH THE LATEST
TIMING AND TRACK.
>>> ABC NEWS INVESTIGATES
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG.
NEW QUESTIONS THIS MORNING ABOUT
THE DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE, ALLEGATIONS OF
SEXIST REMARKS AND A COMPANY
CULTURE THAT SOME FORMER
EMPLOYEES SAY DEGRADED WOMEN.
>>> URGENT MANHUNT.
THE SEARCH RIGHT NOW FOR THE
KILLER OF COLLEGE FRESHMAN TESSA
MAJORS.
THE 13-YEAR-OLD IN CUSTODY
TELLING POLICE TWO OTHERS ARE ON
THE RUN AS HUNDREDS GATHER AT A
VIGIL OVERNIGHT.
>>> THE NEW VIDEO OF THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS FILM CREW
CAUGHT IMPROPERLY TAPING
AN OPPONENT'S SIDELINE.
>> AND THIS IS A PIECE YOU'RE
FILMING ON YOUR ADVANCED SCOUT?
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON, GUYS.
>> WHAT THE NFL AND TEAM ARE NOW
SAYING.
>>> MISSING THE MARK.
THE HALLMARK CHANNEL REVERSING
ITS DECISION TO PULL A
COMMERCIAL SHOWING TWO WOMEN
KISSING AFTER FACING FIERCE
BACKLASH.
THEIR ABOUT-FACE THIS MORNING.
>>> HOLIDAY SHOPPING ALERT.
HOW FACEBOOK AND RETAILERS
IS TARGETING YOU WITH ADS FOR
ITEMS YOU DON'T EVEN LOOK AT
ONLINE.
THE WAY YOU'RE NOW BEING TRACKED
IN STORES AND HOW TO STOP IT.
♪ MIGHT AS WELL JUMP ♪
>>> AND “BEARLY” MOVING.
THE CAR CAUGHT IN A TRAFFIC JAM
WHEN THIS HAPPENS.
BEHIND THAT SCARY MOMENT.
♪ GO AHEAD JUMP ♪
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
HOPE YOU HAD A BETTER WEEKEND
THAN THE FAMILY IN THAT CAR.
>> TRUE?
WE KNOW IT WAS A GOOD WEEKEND
FOR BUFFALO BILLS FANS.
THEY CLINCHED THE PLAYOFF SPOT
OVERNIGHT.
>> THE FANS WERE OUT IN FULL
FORCE TO CELEBRATE AND TAKE A
LOOK.
THERE THEY ARE, 2:00 A.M.
WELCOMING THE TEAM BACK TO
BUFFALO IN 25-DEGREE WEATHER NO
LESS.
>> WOO!
CERTAINLY FEELING THE COLD
SPEAKING OF 25-DEGREE WEATHER IN
KANSAS.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE CHIEFS GAME.
THEY HAD A PREGAME SNOWBALL
FIGHT THERE.
A LITTLE NAUGHTY AND A LITTLE
NICE.
MADE SOME SNOW ANGELS TOO.
THAT WINTER STORM IS ON THE MOVE
THIS MORNING AS MAJOR HOLIDAY
TRAVEL WEEK GETS UNDER WAY AND
GINGER STARTS US OFF WITH THE
LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, GINGER.
>> GOOD MORNING.
MISSOURI STATE HIGHWAY PATROL
TELLING US THAT JUST YESTERDAY
MORE THAN 550 WEATHER-RELATED
ACCIDENTS IN THEIR STATE ALONE.
THE TROUBLE THIS MORNING SE
STRETCHES ALL THE WAY INTO
INDIANA.
>> HIGHWAY 71 SOUTH.
>> Reporter: NEARLY A QUARTER
INCH OF ICE AND FOOT OF SNOW
FROM KANSAS TO INDIANA.
SLICK ROADS SIDELINING VEHICLES
IN KANSAS TEMPORARILY SHUTTING
DOWN INTERSTATE 135 AND IN
ILLINOIS, THIS CAR LOSING
CONTROL SLIDING INTO A RAILROAD
TRACK.
ITS SIDE DOOR SMASHED IN BUT
THANKFULLY NOBODY HURT.
IN MISSOURI, HIGHWAYS LITTERED
WITH STALLED CARS AND BACKUPS.
>> WESTBOUND HAS FOUR PLOWS
CLEARING THE ROADWAYS.
>> Reporter: AS A FLEET OF S
SNOWPLOWS WORKED, THE CHIEFS
HOSTING THE BRONCOS IN A FRESH
COAT OF SNOW.
UTAH, A DEADLY AVALANCHE TAKING
THE LIFE OF A 45-YEAR-OLD
SNOWBOARDER.
MORE THAN 2 1/2 FEET AFTER A
BRIEF WARM-UP LIKELY CAUSED THE
AVALANCHE.
WARNINGS FROM COLORADO TO NEW
MEXICO AND RHODE ISLAND AND
MASSACHUSETTS.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN THIS LONG
FRONT AND THE LOW ASSOCIATED
WITH IT COULD CAUSE TORNADOES
AND EVEN DAMAGING WINDS BACK
FROM NORTHERN ALABAMA THROUGH
MISSISSIPPI LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
INDIANAPOLIS COULD GET FIVE TO
NINE INCHES OF SNOW.
THAT WILL CERTAINLY IMPACT YOUR
AFTERNOON COMMUTE AND THEN
TOMORROW MORNING, NEW YORK CITY
SHOULD STAY RAIN BUT ICE AND
SNOW UP TO BOSTON.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A PROBLEM
TUESDAY MORNING IF ANYBODY HAS
TRAVEL PLANS TOMORROW, GEORGE.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WE GO TO WASHINGTON NOW.
THE HOUSE IS GEARING UP FOR A
FINAL VOTE ON IMPEACHMENT THIS
WEEK.
THE PRESIDENT ON TRACK TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN HISTORY
IMPEACHED BY THE HOUSE SETTING
UP A SENATE TRIAL FOR EARLY NEXT
YEAR.
OUR SENIOR CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MARY BRUCE ON
CAPITOL HILL WITH THE LATEST.
THE JOCKEYING OVER THAT TRIAL IS
HEATING UP.
>> Reporter: GEORGE, IT
CERTAINLY IS.
AS IMPEACHMENT IS NOW HEADING TO
A TRIAL IN THE
REPUBLICAN-CONTROLLED SENATE,
THE PRESIDENT WILL BE ON
FRIENDLIER TURF BUT THE PARTISAN
BATTLE LINES BEING DRAWN.
REPUBLICANS ARE PROMISING IT'S
NOT GOING ANYWHERE IN THE
SENATE.
>> I WANT TO END IT.
I DON'T WANT TO LEGITIMIZE IT.
I HATE WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE FAIR
PROCEEDINGS AND THEN IT'S NOT
GOING ANYWHERE BECAUSE THE FACTS
AREN'T THERE.
>> Reporter: THE TOP REPUBLICAN
IN THE SENATE, MITCH McCONNELL,
IS ALL BUT GUARANTEEING TO
ACQUIT PROMISING TOTAL
COORDINATION WITH THE WHITE
HOUSE.
DEMOCRATS ARE OUTRAGED.
>> HERE YOU HAVE THE MAJORITY
LEADER OF THE SENATE IN EFFECT
THE FOREMAN OF THE JURY SAYING
HE IS GOING TO WORK HAND IN
GLOVE WITH THE DEFENSE ATTORNEY.
A VIE LIEGS OF THE OATH THEY'RE
ABOUT TO TAKE A COMPLETE
SUBVERSION OF THE CONSTITUTIONAL
SCHEME.
>> Reporter: TRYING TO FORCE
REPUBLICANS TO THE NEGOTIATING
TABLE, DEMOCRATS HAVE RELEASED
THEIR OWN PLAN FOR A TRIAL.
ASKING FOR FOUR WITNESSES, THE
WHITE HOUSE PREVENTED FROM
TESTIFYING IN THE HOUSE,
INCLUDING ACTING CHIEF OF STAFF
MICK MULVANEY AND FORMER TRUMP
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON.
>> MAJORITY LEADER McCONNELL
NEEDS TO SIT DOWN WITH MINORITY
LEADER SCHUMER TO NEGOTIATE WHAT
THE TERMS WILL BE.
AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE THE
RUTH.
>> Reporter: ON IF THE POSSESS
IS DEAD ON ARRIVAL, DEMOCRATS IN
THE HOUSE ARE STANDING BY THEIR
DECISION.
>> IF PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
OVERWHELMINGLY ACQUITTED IN THE
SENATE IS THAT A FAFAILURE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT A FAILURE, AT
LEAST NOT IN THE SENSE OF OUR
CONSTITUTIONAL DUTY IN THE
HOUSE.
>> Reporter: OVERNIGHT THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE RELEASED ITS
FULL 658-PAGE REPORT OUTLINING
THE CASE AGAINST THE PRESIDENT.
THIS VOTE IS GOING TO BE
HISTORIC, GEORGE, BUT IT'S NOT
WITHOUT SOME POLITICAL RISKS FOR
MANY DEMOCRATS.
THE PRESIDENT AND REPUBLICANS
HAVE BEEN PUTTING A LOT OF
PRESSURE ON THOSE MODERATE
DEMOCRATS UP FOR RE-ELECTION IN
DISTRICTS THAT TRUMP WON AND A
HANDFUL OF THEM ARE EXPECTED TO
OPPOSE IMPEACHMENT.
ONE OF THOSE DEMOCRATS,
REPRESENTATIVE VAN DREW OF NEW
JERSEY, IS ACTUALLY PLANNING TO
SWITCH PARTIES JOINING
REPUBLICANS AHEAD OF THE VOTE.
>> YEAH, THE PRESIDENT IS
TOUTING THAT AHEAD OF THE VOTE.
MEANTIME, SOME OF THOSE MODERATE
DEMOCRATS ARE PUSHING TO HAVE A
FORMER REPUBLICAN BE ONE OF
THEIR MANAGERS FOR IMPEACHMENT
IN THE SENATE.
>> Reporter: HIS NAME IS JUSTIN
AMASH, DEMOCRATS ARE HOPING
ADDING HIS CONSERVATIVE VOICE TO
MAKE THEIR CASE AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT WILL HELP THEM APPEAL
TO A BROADER GROUP OF AMERICANS
AND LET THEM MAKE THE CASE THIS
IS A BIPARTISAN EFFORT.
JUSTIN AMASH IS A LIBERTARIAN
AND LEFT THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
EARLIER THIS YEAR, ONE OF THE
MOST CONSERVATIVE VOICES ON THE
HILL AND HE IS AN OUTSPOKEN
CRITIC OF THE PRESIDENT.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> THE RACE FOR THE WHITE HOUSE
AND THE SPOTLIGHT ON MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG AND NEW DETAILS ON
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXISM.
THE BILLIONAIRE ACCUSED OF
MAKING CRUDE REMARKS TOWARD
WOMEN AT HIS COMPANY AND HIS
COMPANY, THE TARGET OF THREE
ONGOING LAWSUITS BY FORMER
FEMALE EMPLOYEES.
OUR CHIEF NATIONAL CORRESPONDENT
TOM LLAMAS HAS MORE ON ALL THIS.
GOOD MORNING, TOM.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU.
A BOOKLET WE BELIEVE HAS NEVER
BEEN SEEN ON TV AND ONE THAT NO
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE WOULD
WANT OUT THERE.
IT'S AN ORIGINAL COPY OF THE
PORTABLE BLOOMBERG, THE WIT AND
WISDOM OF MICHAEL BLOOMBERG.
A COLLECTION OF HIS QUOTES
ASSEMBLED BY ONE OF HIS TOP
STAFFERS IN THE EARLY 1990s AS A
BIRTHDAY GIFT.
BLOOMBERG SAYS HE DOESN'T
REMEMBER MAKING THE COMMENTS BUT
THE QUOTES WE FOUND INSIDE ECHO
CLAIMS IN LAWSUITS ACCUSING
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG OF SEXIST
REMARKS AND FOSTERING A COMPANY
CULTURE THAT DEGRADED WOMEN THEN
AND NOW.
IN THE 1990s AS MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG'S COMPANY WAS TAKING
OFF, ONE OF HIS REGIONAL SALES
MAN
MANAGER'S CAREER WAS ABOUT TO
END.
THE TIPPING POINT CAME SHE SAYS
WHEN SHE TOLD HER BOSS, MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG, SHE WAS PREGNANT.
>> SHE THOUGHT HE WOULD BE
PLEASED THAT SHE WAS PREGNANT.
SHE SAID THAT TO HIM AND HE SAID
TO HER, KILL IT.
>> Reporter: IN HER LAWSUIT,
SEKAI WHO RESIGNED SOON AFTER
HER CHILD WAS BORN SAID SHE
UNDERSTUDED STATEMENT OF MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG TO MEAN I SHOULD HAVE
AN ABORTION TO KEEP MY JOB.
WHEN THE REMARK FIRST SURFACED
HE STRONGLY DENIED SAYING IT BUT
THERE ARE ALLEGATIONS OF OTHER
DISTURBING REMARKS.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH THE NEW
YORK STATE DIVISION OF HUMAN
RIGHTS SHE ALLEGES BLOOMBERG
TOLD HER IF YOU LOOK LIKE THAT,
I WOULD DO YOU IN A SECOND.
GESTURING TO ANOTHER WOMAN.
ANOTHER TIME SAYING, YOUR
EXPLETIVE LOOKS HUGE IN THAT NEW
DRESS.
THAT INCLUDES AN ALLEGATION THAT
BLOOMBERG TOLD A GROUP OF FEMALE
EMPLOYEES HE WANTED TO PERFORM A
SEX ACT ON ACTRESS SHARON STONE.
>> IF MR. BLOOMBERG IS RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT I THINK THE PUBLIC
NEEDS TO KNOW WHAT ACTUALLY
HAPPENED IN HIS BUSINESS.
>> Reporter: ONE OF HER LAWYERS
SAID SHE CAN'T DISCUSS THIS
PERIOD.
HER CASE SETTLED AND SHE SIGNED
A CONFIDENTIALITY AGREEMENT.
BONNIE JOSEPHS FIRST REPRESENTED
HER WHEN SHE SUED MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG AND HIS COMPANY AND
SAID SHE INTERVIEWED A DOZEN
EMPLOYEES AT THE TIME WHO
DESCRIBED A SEXIST ATMOSPHERE
FULL OF RAUNCHY BEHAVIOR.
>> AT THE CHRISTMAS PARTIES OR
OTHER KIND OF PARTIES, THE MALE
EMPLOYEES SOMETIMES PUT PLASTIC
BREASTS ON THEM WHICH SQUIRTED
WATER FROM THE NIPPLES OF THE
PLASTIC BREASTS.
>> Reporter: THE ALLEGATIONS
ECHO WHAT'S FOUND INSIDE THIS
BOOKLET FROM 1990.
THE PORTABLE BLOOMBERG WHICH HAS
DOGGED THE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE FOR DECADES.
IN IT BLOOMBERG IS QUOTED AS
SAYING IF WOMEN WANTED TO BE
APPRECIATED TO ARE THEIR BRAINS
THEY'D GO TO THE LIBRARY INSTEAD
OF TO BLOOMINGDALE'S.
I KNOW FOR A FACT ANY
SELF-RESPECTING WOMAN WHO WALKS
PAST A CONSTRUCTION SITE DOESN'T
GET A WHISTLE WILL TURN AROUND
AND WALK PAST AGAIN AND AGAIN
UNTIL SHE DOES GET ONE.
I WANT AN EXPLETIVE FROM JANE
FONDA.
HAVE YOU SEEN JANE FONDA?
NOT BAD FOR 50.
JUST YESTERDAY ABC NEWS
QUESTIONED BLOOMBERG ABOUT THESE
ALLEGATIONS.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'VE MADE ANY
MISTAKES IN THE WAY THAT YOU
TREATED FEE MEAL EMPLOYEES AT
YOUR COMPANY?
>> I DON'T.
NOT EVERYBODY IS HAPPY BUT WE
HAVE AN ENVIABLE RECORD OF
TREATING PEOPLE THE SAME IN
TERMS OF COMPENSATION AND
PROMOTIONS AND AUTHORITY.
>> WE HAVE INVESTIGATED THE
COMPANY FOR THE LAST FOUR YEARS
AND THE CULTURE IS SUCH THAT
WOMEN ARE NOT VALUED, IN FACT,
THEY'RE OBJECTIFIED.
>> Reporter: ATTORNEY DONNA
CLANCY FILED THREE CASES AGAINST
THEM ONGOING INCLUDING SEXUAL
HARASSMENT AND GENDER INEQUALITY
AND CLANCY SAYS THERE'S A REASON
WHY VOTERS MAY HAVE NEVER HEARD
OF OTHER ALLEGATIONS LIKE THESE.
IT'S BECAUSE BLOOMBERG'S COMPANY
AGREED TO FINANCIAL SETTLEMENTS
WITH NONDISCLOSURE AGREEMENTS
ATTACHED SILENCING THE WOMEN
COMPLAINING?
>> THEY WANT TO KEEP THESE NDAs.
THEY DON'T WANT ANYONE TALKING
ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: NOW A COMPANY
SPOKESPERSON DENIED ALLEGATIONS
OF A CULTURE HOSTILE TO WOMEN
AND HIGHLIGHTED A SERIES OF
REFORMS BLOOMBERG ENACTED WHEN
HE RETURNED TO THE COMPANY IN
2014 INCLUDING EXTENDING PAID
MATERNITY LEAVE.
EVEN SO A BLOOMBERG SPOKESPERSON
SAID, QUOTE, MIKE HAS COME TO
SEE THAT SOME OF WHAT HE HAS
SAID IS DISRESPECTFUL AND WRONG.
>> THANKS, TOM.
>>> TURNING TO THE LATEST ON
THAT CHILLING MURDER OF A
COLLEGE STUDENT HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY.
THE SEARCH STILL ON THIS MORNING
FOR AT LEAST TWO SUSPECTS WHILE
OVERNIGHT A HUGE VIGIL TOOK
PLACE HONORING TESSA MAJORS.
ERIELLE RESHEF HAS THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: OVERNIGHT, HUNDREDS
GATHERING ON THE VERY PARK STEPS
JUST A BLOCK FROM CAMPUS WHERE
POLICE SAY TESSA MAJORS WAS
ATTACKED LAST WEDNESDAY AROUND
7:00 P.M. BY A GROUP OF TEENS
WOULD DEMANDED MONEY BEFORE
LEAVING HER STAGGERING IN VAIN
FOR HELP.
>> NEW YORK SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THERE FOR A PLACE TO LEARN AND
GROW AND INSTEAD IT WAS A PLACE
WHERE HER LIFE WAS STOLEN FROM
US.
>> Reporter: A MANHUNT UNDER WAY
FOR THE KILLER OF THE BARNARD
FRESHMEN.
>> THOSE RESPONSIBLE WILL BE
BROUGHT TO JUSTICE.
>> Reporter: POLICE ARRESTING A
13-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT ON FRIDAY
THEY SAY WAS CAUGHT WITH THE
MURDER WEAPON AND APPEARED TO
MATCH A SUSPECT IN GRAINY
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO.
POLICE CHARGING HIM WITH MURDER,
ROBBERY AND WEAPONS POSSESSION.
NOW BEING HELD WITHOUT BAIL.
POLICE SAY THAT TEEN IS NOT THE
STABBER BUT MADE STATEMENTS
LINKING HIM TO THE GRISLY CRIME
AND IMPLICATED AT LEAST TWO
OTHERS FROM HIS MIDDLE SCHOOL.
>> THEY HAVE ONE IN CUSTODY AND
HE IS THE STORYTELLER.
HE'S THE NARRATORMENT YOU GET
DETAILED INFORMATION AND SEE IF
THAT COINCIDES WITH THE PHYSICAL
EVIDENCE.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING THE
18-YEAR-OLD'S HOMETOWN IN
VIRGINIA ALSO REMEMBERING THE
BUDDING JOURNALIST AND MUSICIAN.
>> WHEN YOU SAW HER, YOU KNEW
THAT THAT'S WHAT SHE WAS MEANT
TO BE DOING.
SHE WAS A GREAT PERFORMER.
>> Reporter: TESSA'S ANGUISHED
FAMILY SAYING WE ARE DEVASTATED
BY THE SENTLESS LOSS OF OUR
BEAUTIFUL AND TALENTED TESS.
WE ARE THANKFUL FOR THE
INCREDIBLE OUTPOURING OF LOVE
AND SUPPORT WE HAVE RECEIVED
FROM ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
AND THE 13-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT HAS
NOW BEEN CHARGED AS A JUVENILE.
HIS CASE BEING HANDLED IN FAMILY
COURT.
HIS AUNT HAS ACCOMPANIED HIM
THROUGHOUT THIS INVESTIGATION
AND SHE IS MAINTAINING HIS
INNOCENCE.
GEORGE.
>> SUCH A HORRIBLY SAD STORY.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WE TURN TO THE INVESTIGATION
AT THE NATION'S TOP MILITARY
ACADEMIES.
STUDENTS FROM BOTH WEST POINT
AND THE NAVAL ACADEMY UNDER
SCRUTINY FOR FLASHING WHAT
LOOKED LIKE A WHITE POWER SYMBOL
ON LIVE TV DURING THE ARMY/NAVY
FOOTBALL GAME AND STEPHANIE
RAMOS IS HERE WITH MORE.
>> Reporter: THE PLAY FROM THE
ARMY/NAVY FOOTBALL GAME IS
GETTING THE BIGGEST REACTION.
OFFICIALS ARE INVESTIGATING THIS
MOMENT RIGHT HERE WHERE KA --
CADETS FLASHED THIS SYMBOL AS AN
ESPN BROADCASTER WAS REPORTING
LIVE.
AT LEAST FOUR CADETS PUT UP THAT
SYMBOL.
WEST POINT IS RELEASING A
STATEMENT SAYING WEST POINT IS
LOOKING INTO THE MATTER.
AT THIS TIME WE DO NOT KNOW THE
INTENT OF THE CADETS.
THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY IS OUT
WITH A STATEMENT SAYING IT IS
ALSO INVESTIGATING AND WILL HOLD
THOSE INVOLVED ACCOUNTABLE.
>> SO THIS SYMBOL, THERE MIGHT
BE A DIFFERENT MEANING AT THE
MILITARY ACADEMIES THAN WHAT WE
NORMALLY SEE OVER THE INTERNET.
>> RIGHT.
THIS IS A FAMILIAR SYMBOL.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE OKAY SIGN BUT
SINCE 2017 ACCORDING TO THE
ANTI-DEFAMATION LEAGUE THE WHITE
NATIONALIST COMMUNITY ADOPTED
THAT SIGN SIGNIFYING WHITE
SUPREMACY SO THE SCHOOLS ARE
INVESTIGATING, THE CADETS NOT
IDENTIFIED SO IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT
THEIR ACTUAL INTENT WAS.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WE TURN TO THAT REVERSAL BY
THE HALLMARK CHANNEL ANNOUNCING
IT WILL RUN A COMMERCIAL SHOWING
TWO WOMEN KISSING AND THAT WAS
IN THE FACE OF FIERCE BACKLASH
FOR PULLING THE AD.
WILL REEVE IS HERE WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
THE AD FROM WEDDING PLANNING
WEBSITE ZOLA FEATURED A LESBIAN
COUPLE KISSING AT THE ALTAR
WHICH DREW THE IRE OF
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS AND HALLMARK
YOU WILL PULLED IT SAYING IT HAD
BECOME A DISTRACTION.
THAT BLEW THE WHOLE THING UP AND
NOW UNDER PRESSURE, HALLMARK IS
APOLOGIZING AND TRYING TO UNMAKE
ITS MESS.
>> DO YOU THINK ZOLA COULD HAVE
MADE PLANNING YOUR PERFECT
WEDDING EASIER?
>> Both: WE DO.
>> Reporter: AFTER IGNITING A
CONTROVERSY BY PULLING ADS FROM
WEDDING PLANNING WEBSITE ZOLA
FEATURING A SAME-SEX COUPLE KISS
AT THEIR WEDDING, THE HALLMARK
CHANNEL IS REVERSING COURSE.
NOW OPEN TO PUTTING THE
COMMERCIALS BACK ON THE AIR.
>> WE HELPED A MILLION CUPS PLAN
THEIR WEDDINGS.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT AND
CEO OF HALLMARK CARDS SAYING IN
A STATEMENT, QUOTE, THE CROWN
MEDIA TEAM HAS BEEN AGONIZING
OVER THIS DECISION AS WE'VE SEEN
THE HURT IT HAS UNINTENTIONALLY
CAUSED.
SAID SIMPLY, THEY BELIEVE THIS
WAS THE WRONG DECISION.
WE ARE TRULY SORRY FOR THE HURT
AND DISAPPOINTMENT THIS HAS
CAUSED.
HALLMARK ADDING THAT IT WILL BE
WORKING WITH ZOLA TO, QUOTE,
RE-ESTABLISH OUR PARTNERSHIP AND
REINSTATE THE COMMERCIALS.
THE HEAD OF THE ADVOCACY GROUP
GLAAD WEIGHING IN OVERNIGHT.
>> THIS IS SO IMPORTANT FOR THE
LGBTQ COMMUNITY WHO TWO DAYS AGO
WERE TOLD THEY WEREN'T WORTHY OF
RUNNING AN ADVERTISEMENT ON THE
HALLMARK CHANNEL.
THE DECISION TO PUT IT BACK ON
THE AIR IS 100% THE RIGHT ONE.
>> Reporter: FAMOUS FOR ITS
ANNUAL COUNTDOWN TO CHRISTMAS
MOVIE MARATHONS FEATURING MADE
FOR TV MOVIES FULL OF COOKIE
BAKING, SKATING AND G-RATED
ROM
ROMANCE, THE HALLMARK CHAPEL
CAME UNDER FIRE AFTER PULLING
THE ADS IN QUESTION IN RESPONSE
TO COMPLAINTS FROM A
CONSERVATIVE ADVOCACY GROUP.
CROWN MEDIA EXPLAINED THEIR
INITIAL DECISION TO ABC NEWS
CLAIMING THE DEBATE ROUNDING THE
COMMERCIALS ON ALL SIDES WAS
DISTRACTING FROM THE PURPOSE OF
OUR NETWORK, WHICH IS TO PROVIDE
ENTERTAINMENT VALUE.
BACKLASH WAS SWIFT AND VIRAL.
THE #BOYCOTTHALLMARKCHANNEL
TRENDING ON TWITTER WITH
CELEBRITIES SUCH AS ELLEN
DeGENERES TWEETING ISN'T IT
ALMOST 2020?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
PLEASE EXPLAIN.
WE'RE ALL EARS.
GLAAD RESPONDING, HALLMARK
CHANNEL'S DECISION TO REMOVE
LGBTQ FAMILIES IN SUCH A BLATANT
WAY IS DISCRIMINATORY AND
ESPECIALLY HYPOCRITICAL COMING
FROM A NETWORK THAT CLAIMS TO
PRESENT FAMILY PROGRAMMING.
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" EVEN
JABBING AT THE CONTROVERSY THIS
WEEKEND.
>> WELL, THAT'S RIGHT, THE TRUE
REASON FOR CHRISTMAS IS HUSBAND,
SO THIS HUSBAND.
I'M EMILY CRINKLE FOR HALLMARK
REMINDING YOU TO STAY STRAIGHT
OUT THERE.
>> AFTER THEIR DECISION TO PULL
THE AD INITIALLY ZOLA SAID THEY
WOULD NO LONGER ADVERTISE ON THE
CHANNEL AT ALL POINTING OUT ITS
NEARLY IDENTICAL ADS WERE DEEMED
OKAY TO RUN ON HALLMARK, THE
ONLY DIFFERENCE BEING THOSE
PORTRAYED HETEROSEXUAL COUPLES
AT THE ALTAR.
>> THEY HEARD A LOT OF FEEDBACK
AND MADE THE CHANGE.
>> TALK ABOUT A DISTRACTION.
>> THANK YOU, APPRECIATE IT.
>>> ALSO, AN INCREDIBLE MOMENT
OF TRIUMPH ON THE FOOTBALL
FIELD.
TAKE A LOOK.
THAT IS NEWTOWN, CONNECTICUT,
HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL TEAM DOING
SOMETHING THEY HAVEN'T DONE
SINCE 1992, WINNING THE STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
SO MUCH CELEBRATION THERE IN THE
FOG, IT LOOKS LIKE.
GUESS WHAT, THAT VICTORY CAME ON
THE SEVENTH ANNIVERSARY OF SANDY
HOOK.
A POWERFUL MOMENT FOR THOSE
PLAYERS, THEIR FAMILIES AND THE
ENTIRE TOWN.
>> GOOD TO SEE THAT.
THANK YOU, AMY.
>>> FOLLOWING A LOT OF OTHER
STORIES INCLUDING THE LATEST ON
THE PATRIOTS AND SPYGATE 2.0.
WHAT THE NEW VIDEO SHOWS.
>>> OUTRAGE AFTER HARVEY
WEINSTEIN REPORTEDLY SAYS HE HAS
DONE MORE PROFESSIONALLY FOR
WOMEN THAN ANY OTHER FILMMAKER
BUT FIRST TO GINGER.
>> SELECT CITIES BROUGHT TO YOU
BY WALGREENS.
>> Veronica: ON WEATHER ALERT ON
THIS MONDAY.
ONCE AGAIN, WE'RE GETTING A
QUICK-MOVING NEW ASSISTANCE
WEATHER SYSTEM -- NUISANCE
WEATHER SYSTEM COMINGHROUGH.
SHOULD BE ALL RAIN BY LATE
MORNING.
TEMPERATURES RISING ABOVE
FREEZING INTO THE MID AND UPPER
30S FOR YOUR LUNCHTIME HOUR.
YOUR AFTERNOON AND EVENING RUSH.
SO HAVE THAT BIG UMBRELLA READY
TO GO, AND MAKE SURE YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING WARM ON AND BUDGET
EXTRA TIME.
WE'VE GOT LINGERING RAIN SHOWERS
FOR YOUR TUESDAY, THE HIGH 49.
COLDER CONDITIONS FROM MID-WEEK
ON THROUGH THE REST OF THE WORK
WEEK.
>>> JUST GETTING GOING HERE ON A
MONDAY.
GOT A LOT MORE COMING UP.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
Some banks, it seems like
they are going at the speed
of yesteryear.
But not here.
This is Capital One.
Where you can open
a new savings account
in about 5 minutes
and earn 5 times
the national average.
This is banking reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
When you've crossed Fruit of
the Loom off your list,
you know your holiday
shopping is complete.
Feel free to
celebrate.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
Dad, we need to talk about
something important.
You don't need to go
anywhere dad,
this is your home.
The best home to be in
is your own.
Home Instead offers
personalized in-home services
for your loved ones.
Home Instead Senior Care.
To us, it's personal.
Welcome back to our
Holiday PJ party.
Home Instead Senior Care.
It's time to gift wrap.
Did someone say gift rap?
♪ Sittin' with my crew all
cozy by the fire ♪
♪ please don't be so jealous
of my holiday attire ♪
Shop up to SIXTY PERCENT
OFF everything!
With sleepwear from EIGHT BUCKS!
That's up to SIXTY PERCENT
OFF everything!
- Are we actually not
wrapping any gifts?
- Now at Old Navy!
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
QUICK UPDATE ON LOCAL SCHOOLS,
HOWARD COUNTY SCHOOLS ARE NOW
CLOSED THIS MORNING.
POLICE ARE RACING TO TRACK DOWN
THIEVES WHO STOLE SEVERAL LUXURY
CARS IN ARLINGTON.
STARTED AROUND 9:00 COLUMBIA
PIKE.
SUSPECT STOLE EIGHT CARS FROM
THERE AND CAUGHT ON SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO AND HEADED TO FREDS WHERE
THEY STOLE TWO VEHICLES.
>> NO WORD ON WHAT CAUSED SUV TO
CRASH INTO A GAS STATION.
OFFICIALS SAY DRIVER OKAY.
BACK WITH A CHECK ON
>> VERONICA: DUSTING OF SNOW OUT
SIDE THE BELTWAY.
YOU CAN SEE ONE OF THE FOOTBALL
FIELDS, THIS IS WOODROE WILSON
HIGH SCHOOL.
ROADS WET.
WE HAVE TO WATCH UNTREATED
ROADS.
WE SWITCH TO RAIN AFTER 10:00.
HIGH TEMPERATURE TODAY, 38-39
DEGREES.
>> JULIE: ALL RIGHT, VJ STILL
MONITORING THIS THREE-CAR PILE
UP OUT BOUND 66 TO NUTLY STREET.
45 MINUTE DRIVE HEADED WEST.
IT WILL SAVE YOU TIME USING
ROUTE 50.
OUT OF TYSONS, EASTBOUND TOLL
ROAD BEFORE WIEHLE AVENUE ON THE
RIGHT SIDE OF THE HIGHWAY.
DELAYS TO AND FROM LAUREL ON
THIS WET PAVEMENT ON THE BW
PARKWAY.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
BACK TO YOU.
>> VERONICA: ALL RIGHT, THANK
We ordered 10,000 units.
That sounds good.
Pretty cool, huh?
They're speaking to Mom in
Japanese, and Mom hears them in
English.
♪
Can you understand me?
Yes, I can understand you.
Okay.
I have a lot of questions.
How do you guys fly? What does
Santa do in the summer?
Is Mrs. Claus a good cook?
Do you guys get presents?
Can you roller skate or ice
skate?
Any Comments Doug?
Yeah. Only pay for what you
need with Liberty Mutual.
Only pay for what you
Con Liberty Mutual solo
pagas lo que necesitas.
Only pay for what
you need...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Yep, it's 1850.
Colonel James, you're under
arrest for drinking co-
♪ ♪ ♪
Oh, this one's been
cut with Starbucks.
It's not pure 1850.
1850 Coffee.
Quality that's Criminal.
♪♪
You try baking a pie.
>>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE,
3P.
O?
>> TAKING ONE LAST LOOK, SIR, AT
MY FRIENDS.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
A LOT OF EXCITEMENT FOR "STAR
WARS: THE RISE OF SKYWALKER."
OPENING THIS FRIDAY.
YOU'LL SEE OUR VERY OFFICIAL
COUNTDOWN CLOCK THERE ON YOUR
SCREEN THREE DAYS, 16 HOUR, 29
MINUTES, 37 SECONDS.
OVER THE WEEKEND A SURPRISE CLIP
FEATURING AGAME OF FORTNITE.
J.J. ABRAMS TEAMED UP WITH THEM
TO UNVEIL IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE IT IN OUR
NEXT HOUR.
>> WE WON'T KEEP THE COUNTDOWN
CLOCK UP THROUGH THE WHOLE SHOW?
>> NO.
>>> 20 STATES ON ALERT AS A
POWERFUL WINTER STORM BARRELS
EAST.
MILLIONS FROM COLORADO TO
MASSACHUSETTS NOW FACING
DANGEROUS CONDITIONS AS THAT
HUGE HOLIDAY TRAVEL WEEK GETS
UNDER WAY.
ALSO WE KNOW THIS IS A BIG WEEK
IN WASHINGTON GEARING UP FOR A
FINAL VOTE ON IMPEACHMENT.
THE PRESIDENT ON TRACK TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN
HISTORY IMPEACHED BY THE HOUSE.
>>> AND TAKE A LOOK AT THIS ONE.
SOMETHING YOU DON'T SEE EVERY
DAY IN CALIFORNIA.
YEAH, THAT'S A BEAR THAT JUMPS
ON THE TRUNK OF THAT CAR.
THANKFULLY IT JUMPED OFF JUST A
FEW SECONDS LATER.
NO ONE WAS INJURED.
>> NOT SURE WHAT I WOULD DO.
>> SCREAM.
I'D SCREAM.
DEFINITELY SCREAM.
>>> WE'LL TURN TO THE LATEST
CONTROVERSY FOR THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS.
THEY CLINCHED A PLAYOFF SPOT
SUNDAY BUT UNDER A CLOUD OF
SUSPICION AFTER ADMITTING ONE OF
THEIR EMPLOYEES IMPROPERLY
FILMED ANOTHER TEAM.
NFL IS INVESTIGATING.
T.J. HOLMES HERE WITH THE STORY.
>> STOP ME IF YOU'VE HEARD THIS
ONE BEFORE, GEORGE, BUT THE
PATRIOTS HAVE BEEN ACCUSED OF
CHEATING.
YES, THE TEAM THAT GAVE US
SPYGATE AND DEFLATEGATE IS BACK
WITH A BRAND-NEW SCANDAL AND
THIS TIME IT APPEARS WE HAVE
SOME VIDEO EVIDENCE TO GO ALONG
WITH THIS NEW CHEATING
ACCUSATION.
THIS IS NEW VIDEO OBTAINED BY
FOX SPORTS THAT HIGHLIGHTS THE
CONFRONTATION BETWEEN A PATRIOTS
VIDEOGRAPHER AND A BENGALS
SECURITY OFFICIAL.
>> AND THIS IS A PIECE YOU'RE
FILMING ON YOUR ADVANCE SCOUT.
>> YES.
>> YEAH?
COME ON, GUYS.
I DON'T SEE THE ADVANCED SCOUT
IN THIS FOOTAGE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
WE WERE TRYING TO GET SOME FIELD
PERSPECTIVE.
THAT'S MY BAD.
>> THAT'S NOT THE FIELD.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN HEAR THE
VIDEOGRAPHER CLAIMING HE'S
FILMING THEIR OWN TEAM'S SCOUT
BUT THE SECURITY GUARD ISN'T
BUYING IT.
THE NEW VIDEO SHOWS THE PATRIOTS
EMPLOYEE CAPTURING EIGHT MINUTES
OF THE BENGALS' SIDELINE
POTENTIALLY CATCHING SIGNALS AND
PLACE OF AN OPPOSING TEAM WHICH
IS AGAINST LEAGUE RULES.
AT ONE POINT IN THE NEW VIDEO A
PATRIOTS CREW MEMBER CAN EVEN BE
HEARD OFFERING TO DELETE THE
VIDEO HE WASN'T SUPPOSED TO
SHOOT.
>> BUT I CAN DELETE THIS RIGHT
HERE FOR YOU.
>> THE DAMAGE IS DONE, MY
FRIEND.
>> NO, IT ISN'T BECAUSE WE CAN
DELETE IT.
>> Reporter: SECURITY APPROACHED
THE CREW WITH THIS VIDEO FOR
THEIR OWN RECORDS AND HANDING IT
OVER TO THE NFL.
THE PATRIOTS WHO HAVE ALREADY
ACKNOWLEDGED THAT THEIR
PRODUCTION CREW ACTED
INAPPROPRIATELY ARE NOW FACING
STEEP PENALTIES AND OVERNIGHT
THE VIDEOGRAPHER OVERNIGHT SPOKE
OUT WRITING IN A STATEMENT, IT
NEVER OCCURRED TO ME THAT MY
ACTIONS AND THE ACTIONS OF MY
CREW WOULD BE MISCONSTRUED.
HE ADDS, I HAD NO INTENTION TO
PROVIDE FOOTAGE TO FOOTBALL
OPERATIONS.
I DID NOT PROVIDE ANY FOOTAGE
AND I WAS NEVER ASKED TO DO SO.
THE PATRIOTS MET THE BENGALS FOR
THE FIRST TIME SUNDAY SINCE THE
INCIDENT.
THIS LATEST INCIDENT COMES JUST
FIVE YEARS AFTER PATRIOTS
QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY WAS
SUSPENDED FOUR GAMES DUE TO THE
DEFLATEGATE CONTROVERSY AN
ALLEGATION THAT THE PATRIOTS HAD
PURPOSELY UNDERINFLATED THE
BALLS IN THE AFC CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME AND IN 25007 THEY WERE
DISCIPLINED FOR VIDEOTAPING
SIGNALS FROM AN UNAUTHORIZED
LOENGZ.
THE VIDEOGRAPHER/PRODUCER HAS
BEEN SUSPENDED.
BELICHICK WAS FINED $500,000 AND
THE TEAM 250,000 AND THE TEAM
FOR DEFLATE GATE FINED A MILLION
DOLLARS AND BRADY SUSPENDED.
YOU CAN EXPECT A PUNISHMENT TO
COME SOON.
>> LET'S TALK TO STEPHEN A.
SMITH.
I WISH I COULD HAVE BEEN NEXT TO
YOU WHEN YOU FIRST SAW THIS
VIDEO.
>> WELL, LISTEN, IT'S INCREDIBLY
INCRIMINATING.
THERE IS NO WAY AROUND THAT THE
FACT OF THE MATTER IT JUST FLIES
IN THE FACE OF COMMON SENSE.
EXCUSE ME, YOU HAVE A
VIDEOGRAPHER, YOU WORK WITH THE
NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS AND HISTORY
OF SPITEGATE IN 2007 AND
DEFLEETGAIT IN 2015 AND THE
THIRD INCIDENT AND YOU'RE SAYING
YOU DIDN'T UNDERSTAND WHEN
YOU'RE CAUGHT ON TAPE ASKING NOT
ONCE OR TWICE FOR THE BENGALS
SECURITY GUY TO LET'S JUST
DELETE IT.
LET'S JUST DELETE IT.
THIS DOESN'T HAVE TO HAPPEN.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN A MISTAKE.
>> I SINCERELY DOUBT IT AND TELL
YOU FOLKS THAT COVER THE NFL
SINCERELY DOUBT IT AND THE
NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE IS
LOOKING INTO THIS AND TAKING
THEIR TIME BECAUSE THEY
UNDERSTAND HOW SERIOUS THIS IS.
YOU HAVE A PLETHORA OF TEAMS IN
THE NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE
THAT HAVE CONSISTENTLY
QUESTIONED THE TACTICS OF THE
NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
YOU HAVE BILL BELICHICK ON THE
RECORD SAYING, EX-KEYS ME, WE'LL
BE COMPETITIVE AND WE'RE GOING
TO PUSH THE ENVELOPE TO SOME
DEGREE.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BREAK ANY
RULES.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT BUT
HE SAID WORDS LIKE THAT AND
THEN, AGAIN, KNOWING HOW
METICULOUS HE IS, THIS IS A TEAM
THAT'S BEEN TO NINE SUPER BOWLS
AND CAPTURED SIX SUPER BOWL
CHAMPIONSHIPS IN THE LAST 19
YEARS AND IN THE PROCESS WITH
THE RECORD COMING INTO
YESTERDAY'S VICTORY AGAINST THE
CINCINNATI BENGALS YOU HAVE AN
ORGANIZATION THAT PEOPLE HAVING
LOOKED AT AND TALKED ABOUT THEIR
LEVEL OF DOMINANCE AND THINK
ABOUT, GO BACK TO SOME OF THE
THINGS THAT WERE WRITTEN ABOUT
IN 2015 WHEN THEY WERE TALKING
ABOUT THE PATRIOTS, THEY SAID,
HEY, IF YOU GO TO A TEAM AND YOU
GET CAUGHT DOING THIS, MAKE SURE
YOU'RE WEARING A MEDIA
CREDENTIAL AND ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT YOU SHOULD SAY IS THAT
YOU'RE FILMING IT FOR KRAFT
PRODUCTIONS.
THESE ARE THE KIND OF THINGS
RECORDED IN THE PAST AND
SUDDENLY THIS IS EXACTLY THE
EXCUSE THAT'S BEING USED SO IT
DOES NOT LOOK GOOD FOR THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS AT ALL.
>> WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
T.J. MENTIONED THE FINE BACK IN
2007 WHICH WAS HUGE.
I MEAN ARE THEY JUST LOOKING AT
ANOTHER FINE?
IT DIDN'T STOP THEM THE FIRST
TIME.
>> BILL BELICHICK WAS FINED
$500,000 AND THE ORGANIZATION
$250,000 AND A FIRST ROUND PICK
WAS CONFISCATED FROM THELE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
THAT'S AN INCREDIBLY SERIOUS
THING TO NFL TEAMS.
DO WE THINK IT WILL GO THIS FAR?
HIGHLY UNLIKELY BUT YOU NEVER
KNOW.
WHEN I SPOKE TO THE NFL OFFICE A
FEW DAYS AGO THEY SAID WE'RE
THOROUGHLY INVESTIGATING THIS
AND WE'RE GOING TO TAKE OUR TIME
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY THEY NEED TO
MAKE SURE THEY GET IT RIGHT AND
IF YOU'RE TAKING THIS MUCH TIME,
THAT MEANS YOU'RE TRYING TO FIND
OUT, IS IT A VIDEOGRAPHER OR DID
ORDERS COME FROM UP TOP?
>> DO THE PATRIOTS PRICE THIS IN
AS THE COST OF DOING BUSINESS.
>> EXACTLY WHAT THEY DO.
THEIR ATTITUDE IS EXCUSE ME, AT
THE END OF THE DAY IF WE'RE
WINNING CHAMPIONSHIPS AND
CERTAINLY I'M NOT TRYING TO
IMPUGN OR SULLY THEIR
REPUTATION, THEY'RE CHAMPIONS AS
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
SIX-TIME CHAMPION.
YOU KNOW WHAT, FIGURE IT OUT.
FIGURE IT OUT WHAT THEY'RE DOING
AND LEARN HOW TO DO IT BUT IN
THE END THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT
ARE LOOKING AT THEM WITH A
RAISED EYEBROW AND THERE IS NO
WAY AROUND THAT.
>> THANKS FOR MANY COULDING IN
THIS MORNING.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE OUTRAGE AT NEW
COMMENTS FROM HARVEY WEINSTEIN.
THE DISGRACED FILM EXECUTIVE
ACCUSED OF SEXUAL MISCONDUCT BY
DOZENS OF WOMEN, GOOD MORNING,
LINSEY.
>> GOOD MORNING.
IN THAT INTERVIEW OVER THE
WEEKENDS 67-YEAR-OLD DISGRACED
FORMER MOVIE MOGUL SAYS HE WANTS
TO BE RECOGNIZED FOR WHO HE WAS
INSTEAD OF WHAT HE'S BECOME BUT
A GROUP OF HIS ACCUSERS ARE
FIRING BACK SAYING THEY REFUSE
TO LET HIM REWRITE HIS LEGACY OF
ABUSE.
REACTIONS ARE POURING IN AFTER
DISGRACED HOLLYWOOD PRODUCER
HARVEY WEINSTEIN BROKE HIS
SILENCE IN AN INTERVIEW WITH
"THE NEW YORK POST."
IN THE ARTICLE POSTED ON SUNDAY,
WEINSTEIN WHO IS ACCUSED BY MORE
THAN 80 WOMEN OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, ASSAULT OR RAPE
PROCLAIMED I FEEL LIKE THE
FORGOTTEN MAN.
THE 67-YEAR-OLD POINTING TO
DECADES SPENT AS A HOLLYWOOD
PRODUCER TELLING "THE POST" I'VE
MADE MORE MOVIES DIRECTED BY
WOMEN AND ABOUT WOMEN THAN ANY
FILMMAKER AND I'M TALKING ABOUT
30 YEARS AGO.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT NOW WHEN
IT'S VOGUE.
I DID IT FIRST.
I PIONEERED IT.
BUT THIS MORNING, A VERY
DIFFERENT REACTION TO THOSE
WORDS FROM 23 WOMEN WHO CAME
FORWARD TO REPORT WEINSTEIN'S
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT INCLUDING
ASHLEY JUDD AND ROSE McGOWAN.
IN A NEW STATEMENT THE WOMEN
CLAIM WEINSTEIN IS TRYING TO
GASP LIGHT SOCIETY AGAIN.
HE WON'T BE FORGOTTEN.
HE WILL BE REMEMBERED AS A
SEXUAL PREDATOR AND AN
UNREPENTANT ABUSER WHO TOOK
EVERYTHING AND DESERVED NOTHING.
WEINSTEIN WHO DENIES HAVING ANY
NONCONSENSUAL SEX JUST LAST WEEK
REACHED A TENTATIVE SETTLEMENT
WITH MOST OF HIS ACCUSERS FOR
$25 MILLION WITHOUT
ACKNOWLEDGING ANY WRONGDOING.
HE SPOKE TO THE POST FROM A NEW
YORK HOSPITAL WHERE HE HAD
SPINAL SURGERY TO ADDRESS
INJURIES FROM HIS AUGUST CAR
CRASH.
ATTORNEY GLORIA ALLRED ADDED
WHINING AT THIS POINT BY
MR. WEINSTEIN IS REVEALING.
HE WHAT IS BEEN RELEASED TO THE
HOSPITAL SET TO GO TO TRIAL IN
JANUARY WHERE HE WILL BE TRIED
ON FIVE CHARGES INCLUDING RAPE
IN THE FIRST AND THIRD DEGREES
THAT COULD PUT HIM IN PRISON FOR
THE REST OF HIS LIFE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LINSEY, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> COMING UP, THE NEW INSTAGRAM
FEATURE ROLLING OUT TODAY TO
STOP BULLYING AND NEXT RIGHT
HERE ON "GMA," WE'VE GOT HOLIDAY
SHOPPING ALERTS FOR YOU.
HOW RETAILERS ARE TEAMING UP
WITH FACEBOOK TO TARGET YOU WITH
ADS EVEN WHEN YOU'VE DONE YOUR
SHOPPING IN STORES, NOT ONLINE.
Delicious high-fiber
Raisin Bran.
You sure you don't want
me to come with you?
I'm very sure.
Because I can.
(laughs)
Make good choices.
You make good choices.
I am.
Fiber is good for
DIGESTIVE HEALTH.
Good choices never
tasted so good.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
(DOG VO)
My Beneful Superfood Blend
has me feeling super healthy.
With salmon, cranberries...
...oh, but we are not done
yet!
Here comes Superfood wet with
beef, salmon, and pumpkin.
It's like a superfood Sundae.
On a Monday.
(AVO)
Beneful Superfood Blend
dry and wet recipes.
["White Christmas" -
performed by The Drifters]
♪
(Dad)
Woah!
What do you think?
[tries speaking Korean]
Pecan Nuts?
(Woman) [yelling in Korean]
Honey, please do it well,
do it well.
(Dad)
Maple Syrup?
(Store Clerk)
No.
(Dad)
Thank you, I appreciate it.
No maple?
Alright, alright. Thank you.
(Daughter)
Come on, slowpoke!
♪
Yes!
(Dad)
Thank you.
Come on, slowpoke.
♪
(Daughter)
Merry Christmas!
(Mom)
Awe, thank you, sweetie.
♪
Find your rhythm.
Your happy place.
YOU
Then break it.
Every Emergen-C gives you a
potent blend of nutrients
so you can emerge your best,
with Emergen-C.
The good news?
Our protection is guaranteed.
The bad news?
The perfect photo is not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
Get to Kohl's for gifts to get
them moving!...
Save 25% on Under Armour fleece
for men...
Save 25% on women's Adidas
apparel...
And save 25% on Nike shoes for
the family.
Plus - get Kohl's Cash!
You'll find new gifts at every
turn - this holiday at Kohl's.
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THAT
HOLIDAY SHOPPING ALERT.
FACEBOOK USERS SAY THEY'RE
NOTICING ADS IN THEIR FEEDS FOR
ITEMS THEY BOUGHT IN BRICK AND
MORTAR STORE, NOT ONLINE AND
THAT IS RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT
HOW YOUR SHOPPING IS NOW BEING
TRACKED.
A STORY WE FIRST SAW IN
"BUSINESS INSIDER" AND OUR
TECHNOLOGY CORRESPONDENT BECKY
WORLEY HAS MORE ON ALL THIS.
GOOD MORNING, BECKY.
>> GOOD MORNING, CECILIA.
WE'VE BEEN AWARE FOR YEARS THAT
WHAT YOU CLICK ONLINE INFLUENCES
THE ADS YOU SEE BUT THE IDEA
THAT YOUR IN-STORE PURCHASES ARE
MARRIED TO YOUR SOCIAL PROFILE
IS CATCHING SOME GIFT GIVERS OFF
GUARD.
'TIS THE SEASON FOR NOT ONLY
PRESENTS AND PACKAGES, BUT ADS
AND WITH CHRISTMAS RIGHT AROUND
THE CORNER YOU'RE LIKELY SEEING
MORE THAN UGLY CHRISTMAS
SWEATERS AND SANTA HATS ON YOUR
FACEBOOK FEEDS.
ACCORDING TO BUSINESS INSIDER
RETAILERS ARE TEAMING UP WITH
THE SOCIAL MEDIA GIANT TO CREATE
TARGETED ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENTS TOWARDS CUSTOMERS
BASED NOT ONLY ON WHAT YOU'RE
CLICKING BUT WHERE YOU'RE
PHYSICALLY SHOPPING.
>> THEY'RE ABLE TO GATHER
INFORMATION ABOUT WHAT YOU BUY
IN PHYSICAL STORES AND OMDAHL
AND LETS BUSINESSES SEND IT
INFORMATION ABOUT WHAT YOU
PURCHASED.
>> Reporter: WHEN YOU STOP BY
MACY'S, YOU'RE LIKELY TO SEE
TARGETED ADS FROM THEM ON YOUR
FEEDS.
I SPOTTED THIS ON MY FEED AFTER
A STOP BY MY LOCAL HOME DEPOT.
A FEW DAYS LATER THERE WAS THIS
AD.
WHEN I CLICKSED WHY AM I SEEING
IN THIS IT SAID HOME DEPOT
UPLOADED MY PURCHASE DATA AND
FACEBOOK MATCHED WIT MY PROFILE.
WE REACHED OUT TO HOME DEPOT.
THEY WERE UNAVAILABLE FOR
COMMENT.
MACY'S TELLING US IT IS A WAY TO
FUEL OUR GROWTH.
>> BUSINESSES CAN ELECT TO SEND
FACEBOOK INFORMATION ABOUT THEIR
CUSTOMERS INCLUDING THEIR NAME,
THEIR EMAILS, AND INFORMATION
ABOUT WHAT THEY PURCHASED.
>> Reporter: FACEBOOK CONFIRMING
THIS PRACTICE SAYING RETAILERS
ARE ABLE TO REACH THEIR
CUSTOMERS WITH ADS ON FACEBOOK
BY SHARING OFFLINE EVENTS LIKE
AN IN-STORE PURCHASE.
ALSO ADDING THAT THIS IS
STANDARD FOR THE INDUSTRY.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE ADS
BASED ON YOUR BRICK AND MORTAR
PURCHASES YOU CAN OPT OUT.
YOU JUST GO TO FACEBOOK ON YOUR
PHONE IN THE LOWER RIGHT-HAND
CORNER.
THOSE THREE LITTLE LINES ARE THE
MENU BAR.
CLICK ON THAT AND GET INTO
SETTINGS FOR ADS, AD
PREFERENCES, YOU CHOOSE AD
SETTINGS, CHOOSE ADS BASED ON
DATA FROM PARTNERS, YOU GOT TO
CONTINUE THROUGH THAT SCREEN AND
THEN THE IMPORTANT PART, YOU
SELECT NOT ALLOWED.
IT'S ROUGHLY THE SAME PROCESS,
MAYBE A LITTLE EASIER IF YOU DO
IT ON YOUR COMPUTER IN A BROWSER
BUT, GUY, I FEEL LIKE IT'S ALSO
NICE TO KNOW HOW THIS IS HAUL
HAPPENING BEHIND THE SCENE.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT SURE IS.
>> KNOWLEDGE IS POWER.
THANKS, BECKY.
>>> COMING UP NEXT THE CROWNING
MOMENT MAKING HISTORY.
IT'S OUR "PLAY OF THE DAY."
STAY WITH US.
♪ I'M WALKING ON SUNSHINE ♪
We didn't have to stop the
movie.
I didn't have to call an
ambulance.
And I didn't have to contact
your family.
Because your AFib didn't cause a
blood clot
that led to a stroke.
Not today.
We'd discussed how your stroke
risk increases over time,
so even though you were
feeling fine,
we chose XARELTO® to help keep
you protected.
Once-daily XARELTO® ...
...significantly lowers the risk
of stroke in people with AFib...
not caused by a heart valve
problem.
In fact, over 96% of people
remained stroke-free.
Don't stop taking XARELTO®
without talking to your doctor,
as this may increase your risk
of stroke.
While taking, a spinal injection
increases the risk of blood
clots,
which may cause paralysis -
the inability to move.
You may bruise more easily or
take longer for bleeding
to stop.
XARELTO® can cause serious,
and in rare cases,
fatal bleeding.
It may increase your risk of
bleeding if you take certain
medicines.
Get help right away for
unexpected bleeding
or unusual bruising.
Do not take XARELTO® if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
Before starting, tell your
doctor about all planned
medical or dental procedures...
...and any kidney or liver
problems.
Be sure you're doing...
...all you can to help protect
yourself from a stroke.
Ask your doctor if it's time for
XARELTO®.
To learn more about cost and how
Janssen can help,
visit XARELTO.com.
(Man)
You take care of yourself.
(Elderly Woman)
Oh, thank you so much.
(Elderly Man 1)
I'll be alright.
(Man)
Ok.
(Elderly Man 1)
(Man)
Ok George, see you again soon.
(Elderly Man 2)
Bye bye.
(Elderly Man 3)
Ah Dell, and you brought the
family this time!
(VO)
It feels good to help those
in need.
You can choose Meals on Wheels
to get two hundred and fifty
dollars from Subaru
when you get a new Subaru,
like the all new Outback.
(VO 2)
Get 0.9% on a new Outback
during the Subaru share the love
event.
She's the one
The one for you
When you know
You just know
Love is her
Love is him
Love is us
♪♪
The Vera Wang LOVE collection
designed for Zales,
the Diamond Store.
♪ I'M WALKING ON SUNSHINE WHOA ♪
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH OUR "PLAY
OF THE DAY."
A MAJOR CULTURAL MILESTONE AND
THE ULTIMATE DISPLAY OF GOOD
SPORTSMANSHIP.
CHECK OUT THIS MOMENT.
IT'S THE MOMENT TONI-ANN SINGH
FROM JAMAICA WAS CROWNED MISS
WORLD MAKING HER THE FIFTH BLACK
WORLD TO HOLD A MAJOR TITLE THIS
YEAR BUT LOOK AT THE WINNING
MOMENT.
THAT'S MISS NIGERIA.
SHE COULD NOT BE MORE EXCITED
FOR MISS JAMAICA.
TWITTER WENT WILD FOR IT.
ONE WRITING I HOPE THE BEAUTY
AND LOVE MISS NIGERIA SHOWED IN
THAT MOMENT PROPELS HER FURTHER
THAN WINNING WOULD HAVE.
ANOTHER, IF OUR FRIENDSHIP IS
NOT LIKE MISS NIGERIA VIBES I
DON'T WANT IT.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
THE CROWNS IN FIVE MAJOR BEAUTY
PAGEANTS NOW ALL HELD BY WOMEN
OF COLOR.
>> A REMARKABLE YEAR IF THANKS,
AMY.
>>> COMING UP INSTAGRAM'S NEW
EFFORT TO STOP BULLYING AND A
SPECIAL HOLIDAY EDITION OF MAKE
YOUR MONDAY FOR SOMEONE WOULD
GIVES EVERYONE A PLACE AT THE
TABLE.
Try that.
Here you go.
I'll put it right here.
(gasps)
J.C. Penney.
Remember the little things.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
HERE'S THE STORY
OF GREEN MOUNTAIN
COFFEE ROASTERS
SUMATRA RESERVE.
LET'S GO TO SUMATRA.
THE COFFEE HERE IS AMAZING.
BECAUSE THE VOLCANIC
SOIL IS AMAZING.
SO WE GIVE FARMERS
LIKE WIN MORE PLANTS.
TO GROW MORE DELICIOUS COFFEE.
WHICH HELPS PROVIDE
FOR WIN'S FAMILY.
ALL, FOR A SMOOTHER
TASTING CUP OF COFFEE.
GREEN MOUNTAIN COFFEE ROASTERS.
Welcome back to our
Holiday PJ party.
It's time to gift wrap.
Did someone say gift rap?
♪ Sittin' with my crew all
cozy by the fire ♪
♪ please don't be so jealous
of my holiday attire ♪
Shop up to SIXTY PERCENT
OFF everything!
With sleepwear from EIGHT BUCKS!
That's up to SIXTY PERCENT
OFF everything!
- Are we actually not
wrapping any gifts?
- Now at Old Navy!
Are the color cartridges
in your printer
ready for another school year?
(beep)
What's "cyan" mean?
It means "cyanara,"
honor roll.
(imitates whooshing, booming)
The ink!
Dad!
I'm so hosed.
Yeah, you are.
(Shaq)
The Epson EcoTank printer.
No more cartridges.
It comes with
an incredible amount of ink
that can save you
a lot of trips to the store.
It comes with
an incredible amount of ink
that can save you
a lot of trips to the store.t.
Get ready
for the Dean's list.
Who's Dean?
The Epson EcoTank.
Just fill and chill!
Available at...
What'd we decide
on the flyers again?
Uh, "Fifteen minutes
could save you 15%
or more on car insurance."
I think we're gonna swap over to
"Over seventy-five
years of savings and service."
What, we're just gonna
swap over?
Yep. Pump the breaks on this,
swap it over to that.
Pump the breaks, and, uh,
swap over?
That's right.
Instead of all this
that I've already-?
Yeah.
What are we gonna do with these?
Keep it at your desk,
and save it for next time.
GEICO. Over 75 years of savings
and service.
Mom, why do we always
come here for the holidays?
How did you find
Great-Grandma's recipe?
We're related to them?
We're Portuguese?
I thought we were Hungarian?
Grandpa, can you tell me
the story again?
Behind every question
is a story waiting
to be discovered.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
THIS IS WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS MOMENT
FROM ILLINOIS.
THAT IS GRAY BELL THE BIRD UP ON
TOP DROPPING CRACKERS AND TREATS
FOR ANNIE, THE DOG.
ISN'T THAT NICE?
IT'S A SYSTEM.
IT CERTAINLY WORKS.
LOOK.
HOW WONDERFUL.
COMING UP, HERE ON "GMA," ACTOR
JAMES VAN DER BEEK IS GETTING
EVEN MORE PERSONAL.
HOW HE AND HIS WIFE ARE HEALING
AFTER THEIR MISCARRIAGE.
>>> ONE YOUNG WOMAN WITH
DIABETES IS ABOUT TO HAVE HER
CHRISTMAS WISH COME TRUE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS IT.
ALL ON "GMA" SOON.
THE SEGMENT, THOUGH, SPONSOR
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY ANCESTRY.
GIVE A GIFT THAT WILL GET THE
WHOLE FAMILY TALKING.
HOPKINS.
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
THE MESSY WINTRY WEATHER STILL
IMPACTING OUR WEATHER THIS
MORNING.
TAKE A LOOK OUTSIDE.
VERONICA, YOU SAY WE ONLY HAVE
TO DEAL WITH IT A LITTLE WHILE
LONGER.
>> VERONICA: THERE IS THE
TRAFFIC IN THE MEDIAN, THAT SNOW
ON THE GRASS YOU CAN SEE IT
HANGING IN THE TREES.
TEMPERATURES, 34 DEGREES BY 9:00
THIS MORNING.
38 BY NOON.
WE SHOULD SEE TEMPERATURES HOLD
STEADY.
RISE A DEGREE OR SO EVENING
HOURS.
CHILLY RAIN.
STAY ON WEATHER ALERT MORNING
HOURS UNTIL NOON.
49 HIGH TEMPERATURE TOMORROW,
RAIN WON'T WRAP UP UNTIL LATE
TUESDAY.
>> JULIE: RAIN CAUSING PROBLEMS
ESPECIALLY FOR THOSE CONTINUING
ACROSS THE BAY BRIDGE.
THIS IS WHERE WE HAD AN INCIDENT
CLEARED SLOW RIDE STEPHENSVILLE
ACROSS THE BRIDGE BACK TO
ANNAPOLIS.
ALSO FIND WE ARE WAITING FOR
DELAYS TO IMPROVE HERE ALONG
EAST CAPITOL STREET.
SHUT DOWN SIXTH AND SEVENTH
STREET NORTHEAST.
SOME IMPROVEMENT THAT IS 66
WESTBOUND LEAVING THE BELTWAY.
37 MINUTE RIDE HEADED FROM THE
BELTWAY.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
>> LINDSEY: I WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOME IMAGES WE ARE GETTING FROM
OUR VIEWERS UP LOADED TO OUR
FACEBOOK PAGE.
CLEAR SPRINGS, MARYLAND.
QUITE A BIT OF SNOW UP THERE.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY EAST GOODY
DRIVE AN HOUR AGO.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE IN
BOWIE.
FINALLY PUPPIES PLAYING IN THE
SNOW.
PHOTOS, SEND THEM OUR WAY,
MELANIE?
>> MELANIE: VERY CUTE.
GET
ANY TIME WITH THE ABC 7 APP.
>> ADRIANNA:
AMERICA" BACK IN TWO MINUTES ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS TWO FOR THE LATEST LOCAL
NEWS ON "GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON."
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
IT'S 8:00 A.M.
WINTER STORM ON THE MOVE THROUGH
THE ROCKIES AND THE PLAINS.
NOW 20 STATES FROM COLORADO TO
MASSACHUSETTS IN THE PATH.
HEAVY SNOW, FREEZING RAIN AND
TORNADO THREATS.
GINGER HERE WITH THE LATEST ON
THE TIMING AND THE TRACK.
>>> SHOWDOWN ON CAPITOL HILL BY
THE END OF THE WEEK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP LIKELY TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT TO BECOME
IMPEACHED.
THE LATEST FROM WASHINGTON THIS
MORNING.
>>> "GMA" EXCLUSIVE.
INSTAGRAM REVEALING THE NEW WAY
IT'S FIGHTING ONLINE BULLYING
RIGHT IN YOUR FEED PUTTING
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE TO WORK.
HOW IT ALL FUNCTIONS.
WHAT YOU SHOULD KNOW AND WILL IT
STOP BULLYING BEFORE IT STARTS?
>>> JAMES VAN DER BEEK AND HESS
WIFE KIMBERLY REVEALING HOW
THEY'RE COPING WEEKS AFTER HER
HISS CARRIAGE.
♪
>>> JUST NINE DAYS TILL
CHRISTMAS AND WE'RE DOUBLING
DOWN ON SECRET SANTA SURPRISES.
A WOMAN LIVING WITH DIABETES
ABOUT TO HAVE HER WISH
FULFILLED.
SHE HAS NO IDEA.
>>> YOU'LL MEET THE RESTAURANT
OWNER SO POPULAR ALL HER
CUSTOMERS JOINED IN OUR BIG
"GMA" SURPRISE.
WHAT OUR VOLUNTEER ELVES PUT
TOGETHER THAT LED TO THIS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> ALL AHEAD AS WE SAY GOOD
MORNING, AMERICA.
♪
>>> AND GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
THANK YOU FOR STARTING YOUR WEEK
WITH US.
>> ALL RIGHT, A LITTLE BRUCE,
ALWAYS GOOD IN THE MORNING,
RIGHT?
AS WE MENTIONED WE'RE JUST NINE
DAYS AWAY FROM CHRISTMAS AND
COUNTING DOWN BY MAKING THE
ULTIMATE CHRISTMAS COOKIES AND
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU TWO HINTS
ABOUT WHAT OUR CHEF IS GOING TO
BAKE FOR US THIS MORNING, RED
VELVET AND PEPPERMINT HOT COCOA.
>>> FIRST THAT WINTER STORM ON
THE MOVE AS A MAJOR HOLIDAY
TRAVEL WEEK GETS UNDER WAY,
LET'S HEAD BACK OVER TO GINGER
TRACKING THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, GINGER.
>> GOOD MORNING.
HUNDREDS OF ACCIDENTS REPORTED
OVER THE WEEKEND.
THAT WAS JUST ROUND ONE.
YOU SEE THE PICTURES COMING OUT
OF KANSAS OF ALL OF THE FLIP,
ROLLOVERS AND THE STOP-UP, THAT
WILL BE THE CASE NOT ONLY FROM
KANSAS BUT THROUGH INDIANA
BECAUSE, AGAIN, A SECOND ROUND
IS COMING AT YOU SO YOU CAN SEE
THE WARNINGS IN PLACE.
THAT'S THE PINK AREA HERE
HIGHLIGHTED FROM ST. LOUIS
THROUGH INDIANAPOLIS.
THAT'S NOT JUST SNOW BUT IT'S
ALSO THE FREEZING RAIN POTENTIAL
AND WANT TO WARN YOU ALL FROM
LOUISIANA RIGHT THROUGH
MISSISSIPPI, REALLY THE SABINE
VALLEY UP THROUGH NORTHERN
ALABAMA, TODAY THE POTENTIAL FOR
DAMAGING WIND AND EVEN A TORNADO
BUT SNOW WITH INDIANAPOLIS
PICKING UP BY THIS AMP, FIVE TO
NINE INCH, TOMORROW BOSTON COULD
HAVE A COUPLE OF FRESH INCH,
RHODE ISLAND, MASSACHUSETTS, THE
SOUTHERN PART THERE RIGHT
THROUGH CONNECTICUT AND THE
SUBURBS OF NEW YORK, NORTH OF
NEW YORK COULD END UP WITH SOME
OF THAT FREEZING RAIN CAUSING
THAT SHEET OF ICE TOMORROW
MORNING.
SO THAT'S GOING TO BE A PROBLEM
AND BY THURSDAY MORNING, DON'T
SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU, THAT'S
WHAT IT WILL FEEL LIKE.
>> YOU DID WARN US, OKAY, THANKS
VERY MUCH.
>>> TO WASHINGTON NOW WHERE THE
HOUSE IS GEARING UP TO ARE A
FINAL VOTE ON IMPEACHMENT THIS
WEEK.
THE PRESIDENT ON TRACK TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN HISTORY
IMPEACHED BY THE HOUSE.
LET'S GO BACK TO OUR SENIOR
CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENT MARY
BRUCE ON CAPITOL HILL.
GOOD MORNING, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
WELL, EVEN BEFORE THE HOUSE
VOTES ON IMPEACHMENT REPUBLICANS
ARE PROMISING IT ISN'T GOING
ANYWHERE.
IN THE SENATE MITCH McCONNELL IS
ALL BUT GUARANTEEING TO ACQUIT
PROMISING, QUOTE, TOTAL
COORDINATION WITH THE WHITE
HOUSE.
DEMOCRATS ARE OUTRAGED.
THEY SAY THAT REPUBLICANS ARE
LETTING THE PRESIDENT PLAN HIS
OWN TRIAL AND DEMOCRATS ARE OUT
THIS MORNING WITH THEIR OWN
OPENING OFFER.
THEY ARE ASKING FOR FOUR
WITNESSES ALL OF WHOM WERE
PREVENTED AND BLOCKED FROM
TESTIFYING IN THE HOUSE
INCLUDING ACTING CHIEF OF STAFF
MICK MULVANEY AND FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON.
NOW, THE HOUSE IS EXPECTED TO
VOTE AND LIKELY IMPEACH THE
PRESIDENT ON WEDNESDAY BUT IT IS
CLEAR ALREADY THAT THE PARTISAN
FIGHT OVER IN THE SENATE WILL BE
JUST AS BITTER AND DIVISIVE.
>> IT SURE S THANKS VERY MUCH.
AMY.
>>> AS THE HOLIDAYS ARE MOVING
INTO FULL SWING HOW ABOUT
SOMETHING TO MAKE YOU SMILE?
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HUGE LINES AT ARLINGTON NATIONAL
CEMETERY OVER THE WEEKEND, SO
MANY PEOPLE TURNING OUT FOR THE
ANNUAL TRIBUTE AT ARLINGTON AND
AT MORE THAN 1600 LOCATIONS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY PLACING
WREATHS ON THE GRAVES OF SERVICE
MEMBERS AS PART OF WREATHS
ACROSS AMERICA.
IT'S ALL PART OF A SALUTE TO
FALLEN HEROES AND A BIG THANK
YOU TO VETS FOR THEIR SERVICE
AND THEIR SACRIFICE THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
THAT CERTAINLY WARMS ALL OF OUR
HEARTS.
>> BEAUTIFUL TRADITION.
>>> COMING UP HERE, EXCLUSIVE
LOOK AT THE NEW FEATURE ROLLING
OUT ON INSTAGRAM.
IT'S DESIGNED TO STOP BULLYING
BEFORE IT STARTS.
>>> PLUS, JAMES VAN DER BEEK'S
PERSONAL MESSAGE.
HOW HE AND HIS WIFE ARE DOING
AFTER THEIR MISCARRIAGE.
>>> CHARLIZE THERON IS HERE LIVE
TALKING ABOUT "BOMBSHELL" AND SO
MUCH MORE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> WAIT, AM I GOING TO BE THE
STORY?
May your holidays glow bright
and all your dreams
take flight.
Lease the C 300 Sedan
for just $399 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Winter Event.
Hurry in today.
Hi Mom. Hi Dad.
Hey.
How's my little princess?
I want to be a movie director.
Oh!
That's great.
♪♪
These are real people,
not actors,
who've got their eczema
under control.
With less eczema,
you can show more skin.
So Roll Up Those Sleeves.
And help heal your skin
from within
with DUPIXENT.
DUPIXENT is the first treatment
of its kind that continuously
treats
moderate-to-severe eczema,
or atopic dermatitis,
even between flare ups.
DUPIXENT is a biologic,
and not a cream or steroid.
Many people taking DUPIXENT
saw clear or almost clear skin.
And, had
significantly less itch.
That's a difference
you can feel.
Don't use if you're
allergic to DUPIXENT.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur,
including anaphylaxis,
which is severe.
Tell your doctor about
new or worsening eye problems,
such as eye pain
or vision changes,
or a parasitic infection.
If you take asthma medicines,
don't change or stop them
without talking to your doctor.
So help heal
your skin from within,
And talk to your eczema
specialist about DUPIXENT.
SFX: [sneezing]
I am not for ignoring
the first sign of a cold.
I am for shortening my cold,
with Zicam!
Zicam is
completely different.
Unlike most other
cold medicines,
Zicam is clinically proven to
shorten colds.
I am a ZiFan for Zicam!
Oral or Nasal.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Well it finally
happened, Zachary.
Somebody burned
down my she shed.
Nobody burned down
your she shed, Cheryl.
Well my she shed's on fire.
Your she shed was
struck by lightning.
Zachary, is my she shed
covered by State Farm?
Your she shed's covered, Cheryl.
You hear that Victor?
I'm getting a new
she shi-er she shed.
She shi-er?
Mhhm.
That's wonderful news.
Home insurance trusted by
more people than any other.
State Farm.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
WELCOME TO OUR VERY CHRISTMASSY
AUDIENCE HERE.
>> YES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ON THIS MONDAY MORNING.
YOU GUYS WANT TO COME BACK
TOMORROW, JAMIE FOXX WILL BE
HERE LIVE WITH A POWERFUL NEW
MOVIE.
LET'S WELCOME HAINES FOR SOME
"POP NEWS."
>> THANK YOU, GEORGE.
GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING.
WE BEGIN WITH SOME BIG BIRTHDAY
CELEBRATIONS OVER THE WEEKEND.
FIRST UP, TAYLOR SWIFT.
THE SINGER RANG IN HER 30th
BIRTHDAY ON FRIDAY AND IT WAS
OUT OF HER WILDEST DREAMS.
FIRST SHE PERFORMED AT
iHEARTRADIO'S JINGLE BALL IN
MADISON SQUARE GARDEN AND AFTER
CELEBRATED WITH JUST A FEW
CELEBRITY FRIENDS LIKE CAMILA
CABELLO, HALSEY, GIGI HADID.
SAME AS PIE BIRTHDAY EVERY YEAR
AND THE GUYS FROM "QUEER EYE"
AND SEAN COMB, AKA DIDDY WAS
BUSY THROWING THE PARTY OF THE
YEAR TO CELEBRATE THE BIG 5-0.
HIS GUEST LIST INCLUDED BEYONCE
AND JAY-Z, KIM KARDASHIAN AND
KANYE WEST.
PHARRELL WILLIAMS AND SO MANY
MORE WHO WERE ALL TREATED TO
SOME DANCE MOVES FROM DIDDY
HIMSELF AS THEY PARTIED ALL
NIGHT.
♪
I LOVE A DANCE SOLO.
WHEN IT'S YOUR PARTY YOU CAN
MAKE PEOPLE WATCH YOU DANCE.
WELCOME TO NEXT YEAR'S PARTY.
OKAY.
>>> AND NOW WE ARE LESS THAN
FOUR DAYS AWAY FROM THE FINAL
CHAPTER IN THE EPIC "STAR WARS"
SAGA.
OVER THE WEEKEND, DIRECTOR J.J.
ABRAMS TEAMED UP WITH THE SUPER
POPULAR VIDEO GAME FORTNITE TO
UNVEIL A BRAND-NEW CLIP OF THE
HIGHLY ANTICIPATED FILM.
NOW THEY'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
SEE THAT GUY TALKING IN THE
BLACK SHIRT?
I CAN'T TELL WHICH ONE HE IS
ACTUALLY.
>> IN THE MIDDLE.
>> THERE'S SOMEONE TALKING IN
THE MIDDLE?
>> OH, THERE HE IS.
THAT'S A VIDEO GAME VERSION OF
J.J. ABRAMS AT, QUOTE, RISKY
REELS WHICH IS THE DRIVE-IN
MOVIE THEATER LOCATION INSIDE
THE FORTNITE GAME.
DID YOU FOLLOW ME?
>> TRYING.
>> THERE'S PROBABLY LIKE THREE
YOUNG PEOPLE IN HERE THAT ARE
LIKE, YES, I GET IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT SO THE NEW CLIP IS CALLED
"JEDI MIND TRICK."
TAKE A LOOK.
♪
>> DROP YOUR WEAPONS.
>> IT'S OKAY THAT WE'RE HERE.
>> IT'S OKAY THAT YOU'RE HERE.
>> IT'S GOOD.
>> DID SHE DO THAT FOR US?
>> SO THE LIVE EVENT WAS SO BIG
WITH PLAYERS TRYING TO GET IN
THAT THE EVENT HAD TO BE PUSHED
BACK AND WE'RE GUESSING THERE
WILL BE JUST AS JUST AS MANY
REAL-LIFE PEOPLE GETTING IN THE
THEATERS WHEN "THE RISE OF
SKYWALKER" IS FINALLY OUT.
I WAS LAUGHING BECAUSE I WAS
LIKE, I CAN IMAGINE SHOWING UP
IN A PHYSICAL PLACE LIKE AN
ELEVATOR THAT HAS A 20-PERSON
CAPACITY.
THERE IS A RISK WHEN YOU OVERDO
IT.
GETTING BLOCKED OUT OF AN A.I.
EVENT, I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
THERE'S A LINE AT THAT.
>> MIND BLOWN.
>> TOO METAPHOR ME BUT AND
FINALLY ONE OF OUR FAVORITE
STORIES OF THE DAY, FOUR
ROO
ROOMMATES ACROSS THE POND REALLY
WANTED TO GET A DOG BUT THEIR
LANDLORD DOESN'T ALLOW PETS.
SO THEY WROTE A LETTER TO THEIR
NEIGHBOR ASKING IF THEY COULD
WALK THEIR NEIGHBOR'S DOG.
SAYING WE'VE ALL GROWN UP WITH
ANIMALS AND THE ADULT LIFE IS A
STRUGGLE WITHOUT ONE.
SINCERELY THE BOYS FROM NUMBER
23.
WELL, THEY DID GET A RESPONSE
FROM THE DOG HERSELF.
WHOSE NAME HAPPENS TO BE STEVIE
TICKS AND WROTE A LETTER
STAMPING IT WITH HER PAW AND
WRITING IN PART I MUST WARN YOU
THE PRICE OF MY FRIENDSHIP IS
FIVE BALL THROWS A DAY AND BELLY
SCRATCHES WHENEVER I DEMAND
THEM.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE THE BOYS AND
STEVIE ARE GETTING ALONG
FAMOUSLY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT'S SO CUTE.
>> ONE OF THE GUYS NAMED JACK
SHARING THIS PHOTO ON TWITTER
SAYING IT'S THE START OF A
BEAUTIFUL FRIENDSHIP.
>> THAT'S REALLY SWEET.
LOVE THAT.
>> THE EMOTIONAL SUPPORT OF
ANIMALS.
>> THEY CAN COME WALK OUR DOGS
ANY TIME.
>> THEY ARE TOO FAR FROM LONDON
FOR THAT.
>> THANKS, SARA.
>>> WE MOVE TO OUR COVER STORY.
AN EXCLUSIVE LOOK AT THE NEW WAY
INSTAGRAM IS TAKING ON BULLYING.
THEY WANT TO BUILD A NEW FEATURE
TO STOP OFFENSIVE COMMENTS AND
TROLLING.
REBECCA JARVIS HERE WITH THAT.
HEY, REBECCA.
>> HEY, GEORGE, GOOD MORNING.
THIS THINK OF IT AS A REALITY
CHECK AND SECOND CHANCE.
IF YOU'RE ABOUT TO POST
SOMETHING INSTAGRAM CONSIDERS
POTENTIAL BULLYING YOU'LL HAVE
THE OPTION TO MAKE A CHANGE
BEFORE DOING SOMETHING
REGRETTABLE.
INSTAGRAM WORKING TO COMBAT
BULLYING ON ITS PLATFORM AND
EMPLOYING ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE TO HELP DO IT.
STARTING TODAY THE SOCIAL MEDIA
GIANT IS ROLLING OUT A NEW
FEATURE TO ITS BILLION PLUS
USERS, NOW IF A USER WRITES A
CAPTION ON A PHOTO OR VIDEO THAT
THE A.I. DEEMS OFFENSIVE LIKE
THIS, THAT USER WILL RECEIVE A
RTING THEM THEIR
LANGUAGE COULD BE CONSIDERED
BULLYING.
GIVING THEM THE CHANCE TO
POSSIBLY CHANGE OR DELETE THEIR
WORDS BEFORE POSTING.
SMITH COLLEGE'S RACHEL SIMMONS
HAS SEEN SOCIAL MEDIA'S IMPACT
ON HER STUDENTS FIRSTHAND.
>> WHEN YOU ARE BEING
CYBERBULLIED IT FOLLOWS YOU 24
HOURS A DAY.
IT'S PUBLIC AND EVERYONE CAN SEE
IT AND SO THAT CAN REALLY MAKE A
KID AFRAID TO GO TO SCHOOL.
IT CAN DISRUPT THEIR SLEEP.
IT CAN MAKE THEM FEEL LIKE
THERE'S NOWHERE THEY CAN BE
WHERE THE BULLYING WON'T BE.
>> Reporter: THE NEW TOOL GIVING
HER HOPE.
>> THIS IS A GREAT STEP IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION.
WE WANT TO SEE SOCIAL MEDIA
PLATFORMS LIKE INSTAGRAM
STOPPING BULLIES BEFORE THEY
START.
>> Reporter: INSTAGRAM
PARTNERING WITH SUICIDE
PREVENTION PROGRAMS TO CREATE
THE PRODUCT.
THE LATEST CHANGE TO THE
PLATFORM COMING AFTER INSTAGRAM
OPTED TO BEGIN REMOVING LIKES
FROM POSTS.
AND INSTAGRAM REALIZES THAT
NEGATIVITY AND BULLYING ARE BIG
PROBLEMS ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
THEY'RE WORKING TO MAKE MORE
CHANGES, GUY, EXPECT TO SEE
ADDITIONAL CHANGES COMING SOON
BUT THIS IS A START AND THE IDEA
HERE IS, MAKE SURE PEOPLE ARE
THINKING WHEN THEY'RE ON SOCIAL
MEDIA.
>> I LOVE THAT IT GOES FOR THE
PERSON WHO MAY BE DOING THE
BULLYING -- I KNOW YOU CAN
RESTRICT OR BLOCK PEOPLE BUT
IT'S MAKING THOSE PEOPLE THINK
TWICE.
>> HAVE A SECOND THOUGHT.
>> THANKS.
>>> THAT PERSONAL REVELATION
FROM "DANCING WITH THE STARS"
JAMES VAN DER BEEK OPENING UP
ABOUT THE HEALING PROCESS AFTER
HIS WIFE'S RECENT MISCARRIAGE
SAYING THEY ARE, QUOTE, STILL IN
REPAIR.
PAULA FARIS IS HERE WITH MORE ON
THIS, GOOD MORNING, PAULA.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
YES, THEY ARE STILL IN REPAIR
AND KEEP IN MIND THIS
MISCARRIAGE WAS JUST LAST MONTH.
JAMES VAN DER BEEK GIVING AN
UPDATE TO HIS MANY FANS WRITING
HEALING, IT HAPPENS AT ITS OWN
PACE AND IT'S NOT ALWAYS THE
PACE THAT WE WOULD LIKE.
ACTOR JAMES VAN DER BEEK SHARING
THIS HEARTWARMING INSTAGRAM
PHOTO OF AND HIS WIFE KIMBERLY
OVER THE WEEKEND SAYING THE TWO
ARE STILL IN REPAIR REBUILDING
THEIR LIVES FOLLOWING A RECENT
MISCARRIAGE LAST MONTH.
WRITING, DISCOVERING THAT
HEALING HAPPENS AT ITS OWN PACE,
NOT THE PACE YOU'D LIKE AND
DEFINITELY NOT THE PACE AT WHICH
THE WORLD KEEPS ON MOVING, BUT
IT HAPPENS.
AND THERE'S BEAUTY IN ALLOWING
YOURSELF TO BE EXACTLY WHERE
YOU'RE AT.
♪ AMEN ♪
>> Reporter: THE "DAWSON'S
CREEK" STAR FIRST SHARED THE
NEWS WHILE COMPETING ON THIS
SEASON OF "DANCING WITH THE
STARS."
>> MY WIFE KIMBERLY AND I WENT
THROUGH EVERY EXPECTANT PARENT'S
WORST NIGHTMARE.
WE LOST THE BABY.
>> Reporter: SHORTLY AFTER THAT
EPISODE KIMBERLY POSTED DETAILS
SURROUND THE TRAGEDY ON HER
INSTAGRAM STORY.
>> IN, YOU KNOW, 48 HOURS WE
LOST OUR BABY BOY AND I ALMOST
LOST MY LIFE.
>> Reporter: THE COUPLE ALREADY
PARENTS TO FIVE CHILDREN HAVE
BEEN THROUGH MISCARRIAGES
BEFORE.
JAMES SAYING BACK IN OCTOBER,
MISCARRIAGE, A WORD THAT NEEDS A
REPLA
REPLACEMENT, NOBODY FAILED TO
CARRY, THESE THINGS SOMETIMES
JUST HAPPEN IS SOMETHING THAT
PEOPLE RARELY TALK ABOUT AND
OFTEN GO THROUGH IN SECRET.
THERE NEEDS TO BE ZERO SHAME
AROUND IT GIVING YOUR TIME AND
SPACE TO GRIEF.
THE FAMILY COMMITTED TO GRIEVING
TOGETHER.
SHE ALMOST LOST HER LIFE BUT SHE
IS TAKING TIME TO RECOVER AFTER
SAYING SHE REALLY OVEREXTENDED
HERSELF.
AS FOR JAMES HE'S BEEN REALLY
OPEN THROUGHOUT THE PROCESS
WHICH HE'S NOT USED TO DOING,
CECILIA, BUT THE ENERGY HE'S
FELT FROM PEOPLE AND SUPPORT AND
PRAYERS HAS HELPED THEM.
SO IMPORTANT NOT TO ISOLATE
YOURSELF IN THOSE MOMENT,
CECILIA.
>> THEY'RE HELPING EVERYBODY BY
TALKING ABOUT THIS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LET'S BRING IN DR. JENNIFER
ASHTON NOW.
IT IS SO IMPORTANT, WE WERE JUST
SAYING, IN TALKING ABOUT THIS.
I KNOW YOU'RE AN OB/GYN.
YOU TALK TO YOUR PATIENTS ALL
THE TIME ABOUT THIS.
WHAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
YOU WANT TO TAKE AWAY WHEN A
COUPLE, A WOMAN, COMES TO YOU
AFTER HAVING A MISCARRIAGE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, IT'S NO ONE'S
FAULT.
THAT'S HUMAN NATURE TO BLAME
OURSELF, TO BLAME SOMEONE OR
SOMETHING ELSE.
NO ONE IS TO BLAME HERE.
NUMBER TWO, IT'S INCREDIBLY
COMMON AFFECTING ABOUT 10% OR
EVEN MORE OF WOMEN WHO ARE
PREGNANT AND COUPLES.
IT IS 100% A PAINFUL LOSS.
IT IS ABSOLUTELY INACCURATE TO
SAY, OH, WELL, IT'S NOT THE SAME
THING AS LOSING A REAL PERSON.
THIS IS A MAJOR LOSS, AND THIS
IS PROBABLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING, THERE IS NO MEDICAL TERM
MISCARRIAGE.
THE MEDICAL TERM IS SPONTANEOUS
ABORTION AND IF YOU REALLY LOOK
AT THE WORD MISCARRIAGE IT
ALMOST IMPLIES BLAME, IMPLIES
FAULT SO WE NEED TO MOVE IN 2020
TO POSSIBLY RENAMING IT WHAT IT
IS WHICH IS PREGNANCY LOSS.
>> JAMES VAN DER BEEK SAID THIS
HAD JUST HAPPENED A MONTH AGO
AND THEY'RE OBVIOUSLY -- THEY'RE
STILL CLEARLY GOING THROUGH
THIS.
IS THERE A TIME FRAME YOU TALK
TO YOUR PATIENTS ABOUT.
>> YES AND NO.
EVERY COUPLE, EVERY WOMAN WILL
PROCEED ALONG THEIR OWN PACE BUT
GENERAL GUIDELINES IN THE WORLD
OF PSYCHOLOGY.
BASICALLY SIX MONTHS AFTER A
LOSS, IF YOU'RE STILL SUFFERING
WITH SEVERE SIGNS AND SYMPTOMS,
WHICH HAPPENS 10% OF THE TIME,
THAT COULD BE SOMETHING CALLED
COMPLICATED GRIEF DISORDER AND
IN THE WORLD OF PSYCHOLOGY,
THERE ARE SOME SIGNS OR
SYMPTOMS.
IF YOU HAVE INTENSE YEARNING FOR
THE PERSON OR THING THAT'S LOST,
YOU HAVE AN INABILITY TO ACCEPT
THAT DEATH OR LOSS, YOU HAVE
PERSISTENT FEELING OF BEING
EMOTIONALLY NUMB.
YOU CAN'T CONNECT WITH PEOPLE OR
THINGS THAT WERE AND ARE
IMPORTANT TO YOU AND PERSISTENT
CONCERNS ABOUT HOW THAT LOSS
OCCURRED.
THAT CAN BE AN INDICATION THAT
YOU'RE SUFFERING FROM PERSISTENT
BEREAVEMENT OR COMPLICATED GRIEF
SYNDROME AND NEED TO GET
PROFESSIONAL HELP FOR THAT.
>> JUST GOOD WE KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THIS SO MUCH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S ALMOST 2020.
WE CAN'T WHISPER ABOUT IT
ANYMORE.
>> GINGER, WE HEAD OVER TO YOU.
>> A "GMA" MOMENT FOR EVERYBODY.
THIS FROM BROOKLYN, NEW YORK.
A 2-YEAR-OLD GIRL JUST FEELING
THE SOUL THIS MORNING.
♪
>> SHE'S SINGING TO MISS PATTI
LaBELLE.
>> OH, YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING THAT ONE.
PLEASE TAKE A MOMENT TO GO TO MY
FACEBOOK PAGE AND DROP YOUR
"GMA" MOMENT SO WE CAN SHA
>> Veronica: ON WEATHER ALERT ON
THIS MONDAY.
ONCE AGAIN, WE'RE GETTING A
QUICK-MOVING NEW ASSISTANCE
WEATHER SYSTEM -- NUISANCE
WEATHER SYSTEM COMING THROUGH.
SHOULD BE ALL RAIN BY LATE
MORNING.
TEMPERATURES RISING ABOVE
FREEZING INTO THE MID AND UPPER
30S FOR YOUR LUNCHTIME HOUR.
YOUR AFTERNOON AND EVENING RUSH.
SO HAVE THAT BIG UMBRELLA READY
TO GO, AND MAKE SURE YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING WARM ON AND BUDGET
EXTRA TIME.
WE'VE GOT LINGERING RAIN SHOWERS
FOR YOUR TUESDAY, THE HIGH 49.
COLDER CONDITIONS FROM MID-WEEK
ON THROUGH THE REST OF THE WORK
WEEK.
>>> NOW TO NEW HOPE FOR THE
NEARLY 500 MILLION PEOPLE LIVING
WITH DIABETES AROUND THE WORLD.
SCIENCE IS MAKING MAJOR NEW
ADVANCES TO TREAT AND MAKE
LIVING WITH THAT DISEASE A
LITTLE EASIER.
THIS MORNING, RESEARCHERS SAY
BETTER TREATMENTS ARE CHANGING
THE LIVES OF TYPE 1 DIABETICS
EVERY DAY.
SOME PATIENTS USE A CLOSED LOOP
PUMP.
TREATMENTS ON THE HORIZON
INCLUDE NEW MEDICATIONS THAT
STOP THE DESTRUCTION OF CELLS
THAT MAKE INSULIN, DIABETIC
ALERT DOGS AND EVEN AN
ARTIFICIAL PANCREAS THAT MAY
SOMEDAY MAKE MANAGING TYPE 1
DIABETES COMPLETELY AUTOMATIC.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN SOME
INCREDIBLE ADVANCEMENTS.
THE TECHNOLOGY IS BETTER.
THE TREATMENTS ARE BETTER.
>> Reporter: THIS GIVES HOPE TO
THE SETTERSTROM FAMILY OF SEVEN.
MIDDLE CHILD EMILY NOW 16 WAS
DIAGNOSED WITH TYPE 1 DIABETES
IN KINDERGARTEN AFTER SHE
SUDDENLY STARTED TO EXPERIENCE
RAPID WEIGHT LOSS.
>> I REMEMBER IT WAS REALLY
SCARY IN THE ER.
>> Reporter: MOM JENNIFER WHO
LOST HER BROTHER TO DIABETES WAS
AFRAID FOR HER DAUGHTER.
>> NORMAL BLOOD SUGAR RANGE
REALLY SHOULD BE BETWEEN LIKE 80
TO 150 AND SHE WAS OVER 800 AND
THEY WERE SAYING, SHE COULD HAVE
DEFINITELY GOT INTO A COMA.
>> Reporter: FOR YEARS EMILY
TOOK UP TO FIVE SHOTS OF INSULIN
EVERY DAY.
NOW SHE'S ON THE PUMP WHICH
GIVES BETTER CONTROL.
EVEN THEN THERE ARE CONCERNS.
A CHANGE IN DIET OR EXERCISE CAN
THROW EVERYTHING OFF BALANCE
PUTTING EMILY'S LIFE IN DANGER.
>> SHE'S HAD LOWS WHERE -- I CAN
TELL LIKE HER EYES WILL GET
GLOSSY AND SHE -- LIKE SHE JUST
DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT.
>> Reporter: EMILY HASN'T LET
HER ILLNESS SLOW HER DOWN.
SHE IS AN AP STUDENT ON THE
VARSITY COLOR GUARD TEAM AND SHE
PLANS TO ATTEND COLLEGE.
>> I'M RESPONSIBLE WITH IT BUT
AT THE SAME TIME IT'S REALLY
SCARY KNOWING SOMETHING COULD
HAPPEN TO ME AND THERE WOULD BE
NO ONE THERE THAT WOULD KNOW HOW
TO TREAT IT OR HELP ME.
>> I WANT HER TO HAVE THAT
EXPERIENCE AND GO TO COLLEGE BUT
WANT HER TO -- HOPEFULLY WE CAN
FIND A SCHOOL SHE CAN STAY
CLOSE.
>> AND EMILY AND HER MOM
JENNIFER JOIN US NOW.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US,
BOTH OF YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND JENNIFER, I WANT TO ASK AS I
MOM HOW DO YOU COPE WITH THE
FEAR OF HAVING YOUR DAUGHTER
LIVING WITH THIS DISEASE?
>> IT'S SCARY.
I MEAN SHE'S A REALLY
RESPONSIBLE KID.
BUT I DO GET SCARED.
ESPECIALLY AT NIGHT, YOU KNOW,
SHE COULD DEFINITELY GO INTO A
DANGEROUS LOW LEVEL WITH HER
BLOOD SUGARS AND THAT'S ALWAYS
BROUGHT ON BY ACTIVITY AND SHE
IS A SUPER ACTIVE KID SO IT IS
DEFINITELY SCARY.
>> EMILY, WHAT IS THE HARDEST
PART?
>> I THINK IT'S JUST REMEMBERING
THAT I HAVE TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL MY STUFF AND I HAVE TO
REMEMBER THAT WHENEVER I GO OUT,
I HAVE TO BRING LIKE MY TEST KIT
FOR MY FINGER AND I HAVE TO LIKE
BRING JUICE AND EXTRA INSULIN
AND STUFF IN CASE ANYTHING
HAPPENS TO ME AND IT'S JUST
KNOWING IF I FORGET SOMETHING
AND SOMETHING BAD HAPPENS IT
COULD BE HORRIBLE.
>> YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO BE
THINKING AHEAD.
WE HAVE SOMEBODY THAT MIGHT BE
ABLE TO HELP WITH SOME OF THIS
NOW.
JOINING US BY FACEBOOK, WE'LL
LOOK UP THERE.
JEANETTE FORREY AND YOU HAVE A
LITTLE HOLIDAY SURPRISE FOR US.
TELL US ABOUT THE SERVICE DOG,
JEANETTE.
>> HI, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
HAVING ME THIS MORNING.
HERE AT FORREY KENNELS WE
SPECIALIZE IN DIABETIC ALERT
DOGS TRAINED TO DETECT LOWS AND
HIGHS FOR THOSE WITH TYPE 1
DIABETES.
DOGS HAVE BEEN PHENOMENAL AT
HELPING THEM STAY IN A HEALTHY
RANGE BUT SO MANY GOES INTO
TRAINING A DIABETIC ALERT DOG.
AT THE CHEMES THEY'RE RAISED ON
A CURRICULUM WITH SCENT
IMPRINTING AND EARLY SCENT
EXPOSURE AND WHEN THEY ARE OLD
ENOUGH WE EVALUATE OUR PUPPIES
TO DETERMINE ONES SHOW THE BEST
APTITUDE AND WHEN WE TARGET
THESE ELITE PUPPIES, THEY ARE
THEN MATCHED WITH SOMEONE VERY,
VERY SPECIAL, SOMEONE THAT NEEDS
THEIR HEART HEALED AND LIFE
CHANGED THROUGH THE POWER OF A
DOG AND TODAY FORREY CHEMES
THROUGH OUR HEALING HEARTS
PROGRAM ANNOUNCE THIS DOG FULLY
TRAINED WILL BE DONATED TO EMILY
AS HER DIABETIC ALERT SERVICE
DOG.
>> I LOVE SEEING THE EMOTION IN
MOM, JENNIFER.
EMILY, WOULDN'T IT BE SO
GREAT -- I'M SURE YOU CAN'T WAIT
TO MEET YOUR DOG IN PERSON.
HOW ABOUT WE DO THAT RIGHT NOW?
JEANETTE, COME ON OUT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> LOOK AT HOW CUTE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> EMILY, CAN YOU TELL US WHAT
YOU'RE FEELING.
>> I'M SO HAPPY.
HE IS ADORABLE.
>> HE IS GORGEOUS.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> FULLY TRAINED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SO HE'S JUST A PUPPY NOW.
HE WILL JOIN DOG TRAINING AND
WILL BE TRAINED SPECIFICALLY FOR
EMILY'S HIGHS AND LOWS AND TAKE
HER SALIVA WHEN BLOOD SUGAR IS
LOW AND HIGH AND HE WILL BE
TRAINED SPECIFICALLY FOR HER.
WHICH WILL TAKE ABOUT A YEAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE THE
LEVEL OF COMFORT YOU'RE FEELING
RIGHT NOW, JENNIFER.
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT YOUR
FEARS EARLIER.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN TO YOU.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS JUST AWESOME.
SHE WANTS TO GO TO COLLEGE AND
IF I'M NOT THERE I'M SO WORRIED,
YOU KNOW.
AT NIGHT, GOING TO CLASSES, OR
ANYTHING AND SHE'LL HAVE THIS,
THIS EXTRA -- OH, MY GOD.
I'M PEACHLESS.
I'M SPEECHLESS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WHAT A SWEET PUPPY.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU GOT TO COME UP WITH A GREAT
NAME FOR HIM.
THANK YOU FOR THAT GREAT
SURPRISE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW, COMMUTERS
DEALING WITH A MAJOR ISSUE ON
METRO, LINDSEY MASTIS AT THE
ALERT DESK WITH DETAILS.
THEY ARE AT THE SCENE,
FRIENDSHIP HEIGHTS.
IT IS AN ABSOLUTE MESS RIGHT
NOW.
THEY ARE SAYING THEY ARE SINGLE
TRACKING FRIENDSHIPS AND VAN
NESS, DOESN'T LOOK LIKE TRAIN
ARE STOPPING IN FRIENDSHIP
HEIGHTS.
STILL WORKING ON GETTING MORE
INFORMATION FROM THEM ABOUT WHAT
IS HAPPENING NEXT.
SINGLING TRACKING IN THE AREA,
DELAYS IN BOTH DIRECTIONS.
BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> JESSOB: 8:27, IT HAS BEEN A
ROLLER COASTER OF A MORNING.
>> VERONICA: LITTLE BIT OF
FREEZING RAIN, HALF INCH HERNDON
AND LEESBURG AND PURCELLVILLE
AND BELTSVILLE, 1.3 INCHES
>> MARKET, MARYLAND.
CLOUDS ALL HANGING LOW WITH SNOW
FALLING AND EVEN RAIN STARTING
TO TAKE OVER THE AREA, JULIE,
MOSTLY RAIN AFTER 10:00 THIS
MORNING, HIGH TODAY, 39 DEGREES
LATE.
>> JULIE: ON THE ROADS THIS
MORNING, HERE IN ARLINGTON LEFT
OF A CRASH, 395 NORTH WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD SQUEEZING THE RIGHT
LANE.
DELAYS NORTH DUKE STREET TO THE
SCENE.
STILL MONITORING THIS CLEAN UP,
IT HAS BEEN THERE SINCE 5:00.
NOW JUST A 14 MINUTE RIDE
BELTWAY TO VIENNA, ALL RIGHT,
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
STAY WITH US, MORE OF "GOOD
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
OUR NEXT GUEST WON AN OSCAR AND
GOLDEN GLOBE AND S.A.G. AWARD.
>> AND GETTING OSCAR BUZZ FOR
HER LATEST ROLE AS MEGYN KELLY
IN "BOMBSHELL."
SO HAPPY TO HAVE CHARLIZE THERON
HERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M SORRY YOU'RE FEELING A
LITTLE UNDER THE WEATHER RIGHT
NOW AND WE'RE VERY HAPPY YOU'RE
HERE DESPITE THAT.
>> OF COURSE.
>> YOU HAVE A LOT TO CELEBRATE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU WERE JUST NOMINATED FOR THAT
GOLDEN GLOBE AND A S.A.G. AWARD
AS WELL.
YOU POSTED A VIDEO BY THE WAY
WHICH WE LOVE WHEN YOU HEARD
THAT THE CAST GOT A S.A.G. AWARD
NOMINATION.
THERE YOU ARE.
I MEAN, YOU WERE REALLY EXCITED.
>> THEN YOU REMEMBER YOU HAVE NO
UNDERPANTS ON.
>> SO THAT WAS YOUR REACTION
WHEN THE CAST GOT NOMINATED.
HOW DID YOU REACT WHEN YOU
PERSONALLY GOT NOMINATED.
>> ALL OF THIS STUFF IS ALWAYS
SO EXCITING BECAUSE I DON'T
THINK ANYBODY MAKES MOVIES FOR
THIS AND SO THE FACT OUR MOVIE
HAS BEEN GETTING THIS NICE BUZZ
HAS BEEN SUCH A REWARD AND THEN
TO GET THIS, I ALWAYS -- I FEEL
LIKE IT'S LIKE GIANT JUICY
CHERRIES ON ALREADY DELICIOUS
CAKE.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY I CAN
DESCRIBE IT.
>> IT IS AN INCREDIBLE
PERFORMANCE.
I WAS WATCHING WITH MY DAUGHTER
LAST NIGHT.
WE LITERALLY GASPED THE FIRST
TIME YOU COME ON THE SCREEN
BECAUSE YOU LOOK AND SOUND SO
MUCH LIKE MEGYN KELLY AND IS IT
TRUE NICOLE KIDMAN DIDN'T
RECOGNIZE YOU WHEN YOU FIRST
CAME ON SET.
>> FOR A SECOND, YES.
FOR A SECOND, I MEAN IT WAS
CHAOTIC THE WAY WE SHOT IT.
JAY ROACH, OUR FILM'S DIRECTOR
WANTED TO SHOOT 360 AT ALL TIMES
AND IT FELT LIKE A REAL NEWSROOM
SO WE WERE ALWAYS SCATTERED IN
THIS REAL NEWSROOM SO I THINK
FOR A SECOND SHE JUST COULDN'T
PUT IT TOGETHER THAT IT COULD BE
ME FROM AFAR.
BUT THE PROSTHETIC WORK, THE
MAKEUP AND HAIR IN THIS FILM IS
REALLY TOP NOTCH.
>> IT'S INCREDIBLE.
>> IT'S INCREDIBLE PEOPLE.
>> WHAT DID YOU LATCH ON TO
MEGYN KELLY THAT FOR YOU MADE IT
WORK?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S A
COMBINATION OF A LOT OF SMALL
LITTLE THINGS.
IT'S THE DEVIL'S IN THE DETAILS
AND I THINK IT'S A COMBINATION
OF TRYING TO UNDERSTAND AS BEST
I COULD WHERE SHE CAME FROM, WHY
SHE SOUNDS THE WAY SHE SOUNDS,
WHY SHE HOLES HERSELF THE WAY
SHE HOLES HERSELF AND IT'S JUST
RESEARCH.
YOU JUST HAVE TO KIND OF SIT
DOWN AND READ AS MUCH AS YOU
CAN, WATCH AS MUCH AS YOU CAN,
LISTEN TO AS MUCH AS YOU CAN AND
PRAY TO THE MOVIE GODS THAT WHEN
YOU SHOW UP ON THAT FIRST DAY
YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO MANUFACTURE
SOMETHING, THAT IT'S UNDER YOUR
SKIN ALREADY.
>> ARE YOU READY TO SEE THIS?
>> YES.
>> -- ASKED ME TEN YEARS AGO.
I HAD TURNED DOWN A LAW FIRM
PARTNERSHIP FOR AN ENTRY LEVEL
JOB HERE AT FOX.
ROGER WOULD CALL ME UP TO NEW
YORK TO DANGLE PROSPECTS.
I WANTED HIS HELP.
>> DID YOU DO ANYTHING?
>> NO.
>> WILL YOU TALK?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MEGYN KELLY ACTUALLY BROKE
HER SILENCE ABOUT THE MOVIE OVER
THE WEEKEND.
HERE'S PART OF WHAT SHE SAID,
QUOTE, WATCHING THIS PICTURE WAS
AN INCREDIBLY EMOTIONAL
EXPERIENCE FOR ME AND FOR THOSE
WITH WHOM I SAW IT.
SEXUAL HARASSMENT IS PERVASIVE
IN THIS COUNTRY.
IT CAN LEAVE SCARS THAT DO NOT
HEAL.
SHE ALSO SAID, QUOTE, SHE ONLY
GOT HER FIRST LOOK AT THE FILM
ONCE IT WAS PAST THE POINT OF
ANY POSSIBLE EDITS THOUGH THERE
ARE CERTAINLY SOME I WOULD HAVE
MADE.
HAVE YOU HEARD FROM HER
DIRECTLY.
>> I MEAN, OF COURSE, I WOULD
PROBABLY WANT TO EDIT EVERYTHING
IF SOMEBODY DID SOMETHING ABOUT
ME.
I THINK SHE WAS INCREDIBLY KIND.
I'VE ALWAYS SAID I HAVE GREAT
EMPATHY FOR ALL OF THE WOMEN
WOULD HAVE TO WATCH THIS FILM
BECAUSE I DO THINK EVEN THOUGHS
THIS THEY A CATHARSIS AROUND IT
IT IS ALSO HAVING TO GO BACK TO
A PLACE AND A TIME IN YOUR LIFE
THAT YOU JUST -- YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE DEFINED BY AND YOU JUST
MAYBE WANT TO PUT IT BEHIND YOU
BUT I THINK WE'RE LIVING IN SUCH
AN INTERESTING MOMENT RIGHT NOW
WHERE WE'RE ACTUALLY HAVING A
REAL CONVERSATION ABOUT SEXUAL
HARASSMENT IN THE WORKPLACE AND
I THINK BECAUSE THAT'S
HAPPENING, A LOT OF THESE WOMEN
ARE JUST FEELING THEY'RE -- THE
IMPORTANCE OF GETTING THE STORY
OUT THERE IS MORE IMPORTANT AND
SO I HAVE GREAT EMPATHY.
OF COURSE IT MUST BE INCREDIBLY
EMOTIONAL TO GO ON THIS JOURNEY
AGAIN AND TO REWATCH IT.
SO I'M JUST GRATEFUL TO ALL OF
THESE WOMEN THAT WE HAVE THIS
STORY.
YOU KNOW, I WISH THIS NEVER
HAPPENED TO THEM BUT I THINK
THIS STORY IS AND WILL BE PART
OF A HISTORICAL MOMENT THAT
REALLY CHANGES THINGS FOR WOMEN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> DID YOUR PERCEPTION -- YOU
KNOW, THIS IS SO UNKNOWN TO SO
MANY PEOPLE.
DID YOUR PERCEPTION OF THE STORY
CHANGE BY DOING THE FILM?
>> MY PERCEPTION OF THE STORY?
>> OF THE MEGYN KELLY STORY, THE
FOX STORY.
>> WELL, YEAH, YOU KNOW, I TRIED
TO NOT THINK ABOUT THE MEGYN
KELLY STORY.
I TRIED TO THINK OF JUST, YOU
KNOW, THIS COMPARTMENTALIZED
MOMENT, THIS YEAR AND A HALF OR
HOWEVER LONG IT WAS THAT WE WERE
PORTRAYING BECAUSE THE MEGYN
KELLY STORY CAN BE VERY
OVERWHELMING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THAT'S A BIG ONE TO TAKE ON SO
THE MORE WE JUST REALLY FOCUSED
ON THAT YEAR AND A HALF, IT
BECAME EASIER TO REALLY KIND OF
TAP INTO THAT STORY AND WHAT WAS
HAPPENING THERE.
I WOULD SAY THE THING THAT
CHANGED FOR ME WAS THAT I FORGOT
A LOT OF THE NUANCE.
I FORGOT A LOT OF THE -- THE
THINGS THAT, YOU KNOW, WERE
EITHER NOT REPORTED OR WERE
REPORTED REALLY QUICKLY AND OR
REPORTED IN A WAY THAT -- IN A
MANNER THAT FELT A LITTLE BIT
SENSATIONALIZED.
I DIDN'T FULLY UNDERSTAND THE
CONSEQUENCES THAT A LOT OF THESE
WOMEN WERE FACING AND SO A LOT
OF IT WAS LIKE, NOBODY'S
STEPPING UP AND PROTECTING
GRETCHEN.
BUT I THINK EVERYBODY HAD A
REALLY COMPLICATED SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES TO DEAL WITH IN
ORDER TO GET TO THAT PLACE AND I
THINK FOR A LOT OF WOMEN IT'S
REALLY HARD TO TAKE THAT STEP
FORWARD KNOWING THAT THERE'S SO
MANY RISKS AND THAT THEY'RE
PROBABLY GOING TO PUT THEMSELF
THIS IS A POSITION WHERE THEY'RE
GOING TO LOSE SOMETHING.
>> YOU GUYS TOLD THE STORY VERY
WELL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> SO POWERFUL.
>> THANKS FOR COMING IN.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> "BOMBSHELL" IN SELECT
THEATERS NOW.
OPENS NATIONWIDE THIS FRIDAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH A SPECIAL
MAKE YOUR MONDAY.
WE ARE TEAMING UP WITH OUR
SPONSORED TELEFLORA WHO
ENCOURAGES EVERYONE TO LOVE OUT
LOUD THIS HOLIDAY BY HONORING
THOSE WHO MAKE A DIFFERENCE IN
OUR LIVES AND GOT THE CHANCE TO
MEET A REMARKABLE WOMAN WHO
GIVES EVERYONE A PLACE AT THE
TABLE.
WITH A SMILE THAT LIGHTS UP A
ROOM, MAGGIE GREETS THE PATRONS
OF HER CAFE CALLED A PLACE AT
THE TABLE IN RALEIGH, NORTH
CAROLINA.
>> HOW WAS THE FOOD?
IS IT GOOD.
>> ALWAYS GOOD.
>> Reporter: BUT THIS IS NOT
YOUR REGULAR RESTAURANT.
THIS IS A PAY WHAT YOU CAN CAFE
WHERE EVERYONE IS INVITED.
>> WE ALL DESERVE TO FEEL LIKE
WE MATTER AND THAT WE ARE
WELCOME.
>> Reporter: CUSTOMERS HAVE
OPTIONS WHEN PAYING FOR THEIR
MEAL.
THEY CAN PAY THE SUGGESTED
PRICE, PAY WHAT THEY CAN AFFORD
OR VOLUNTEER FOR THEIR MEAL AND
THE COMMUNITY IS ENCOURAGED TO
PAY IT FORWARD BY DONATING
TOWARD A MEAL FOR SOMEONE IN
NEED.
>> THE FOOD IS UPSCALE DINING
EXPERIENCE.
THERE'S NO LINES DRAWN BETWEEN
THE MAN IN A BUSINESS SUIT AND
THOSE WOULD CARRIED ALL THEIR
CLOTHES ON THEIR BACK.
>> PEOPLE EXPERIENCING HOMELESS
THIS IS AND EATING IN SOUP
KITCHENS IT LACKS CHOICE.
I DECIDED WE NEEDED TO CREATE A
PLACE WHERE ALL COULD COME
TOGETHER, SIT TOGETHER,
VOLUNTEER TOGETHER AND MAKE THIS
A REALLY TRULY A COMMUNITY CAFE.
>> WE HAVE SANDWICH, WAFFLES.
>> Reporter: THE DELICIOUS FOOD
ISN'T THE MAIN DRAW.
IT'S MAGGIE.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'S HAD A DAY
FOR HERSELF IN THE LAST TWO
YEARS, IN THREE, FOUR, FIVE
YEARS.
>> MAGGIE MAKES EVERYONE AROUND
HER A BETTER PERSON.
>> I CAME IN HERE BROKEN,
HOMELESS AND THEY LOVED ME.
THEY ACCEPTED ME.
I'M OWE GRATEFUL TO MAGGIE FOR
HELPING TO GIVE ME A LIFE AGAIN.
>> Reporter: SO WE'RE PARTNERING
WITH OUR SPONSORED TELEFLORA TO
SURPRISE HER WITH A HUGE THANK
YOU EVENT AND STYLE DIRECTOR
FROM "GOOD HOUSEKEEPING" LORI
BERGAMOTTO IS HERE TO HELP.
>> MAGGIE IS RIGHT AROUND THE
CORNER.
SHE THINKS WE'RE JUST HERE TO DO
A STORY ABOUT THE CAFE.
SHE HAS NO IDEA THAT WE'RE
REALLY HERE TO HONOR HER HARD
WORK AND DEDICATION TO THIS
COMMUNITY.
LET'S GO SURPRISE HER.
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> ARE YOU MAGGIE KANE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M LORI BERGAMOTTO AND I'M
HERE HELPING OUT "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA" AND WE HAVE A SURPRISE
FOR YOU.
SO, MAGGIE, I WANT TO TELL YOU,
YOU ARE AMAZING.
YOU HAVE WORKED TIRELESSLY FOR
THIS COMMUNITY.
YOU'VE PROVIDED THOUSANDS OF
MEALS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TODAY IS ALL ABOUT YOU,
MAGGIE.
MAGGIE, WE'RE GOING TO MAKE YOUR
DAY.
WE HAVE A CAR READY TO TAKE YOU
TO A SPA DAY, A WELL DESERVED
SPA DAY.
WHAT?
>> AND IT GETS BETTER.
THERE'S MORE.
AND WHILE YOU'RE GONE, THESE
AMAZING VOLUNTEERS ARE GOING TO
SPRUCE UP YOUR CAFE FOR THE
HOLIDAYS AND GET IT IN TIPTOP
SHAPE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> CAN WE SEND HER OFF WITH A
BIG CHEER.
[ CHEERS ]
>> HOW ARE YOU TODAY.
>> GOOD.
>> WHILE MAGGIE HITS THE SPA THE
VOLUNTEER ELVES GET TO WORK.
>> LET'S GO DECORATE.
[ CHEERS ]
>> THIS IS GOING TO LOOK GREAT.
>> Reporter: MAKING SURE EACH
TABLE HAS A LITTLE HOLIDAY
MAGIC.
AFTER ALL THAT PAMPERING, IT'S
TIME FOR THE BIG REVEAL.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT THIS ON YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOUR HANDS AND
HERE WE GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, MY GOD.
IT LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> WELL, LET ME SHOW YOU MORE.
LET ME WALK YOU TO THE TREE AND
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW WE MADE
SURE TO ADD A PERSONAL TOUCH AND
THERE'S EVEN MORE AROUND THE
CORNER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DID WE MAKE YOUR DAY?
>> OH, GOD.
YOU CERTAINLY DID.
THANK YOU.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT WAS A GOOD STORY.
MAGGIE IS SUCH A FORCE FOR GOOD
AND LISTEN TO THIS.
SHE HAS PROVIDED ALMOST 20,000
MEALS TO THE COMMUNITY AND
RECEIVED MORE THAN $49,000 IN
PAY IT FORWARD MEALS SO
EVERYBODY DOING THEIR JOB.
YOU ALL CAN GET IN ON THE FUN
TOO.
JUST SHOW YOUR LOVE AND
APPRECIATION WITH A FESTIVE
TELEFLORA ARRANGEMENT AND PLUS
BECAUSE WE'RE ALL ABOUT THE
LOVE, EVERYBODY IN THE STUDIO
AUDIENCE GOING HOME WITH A $100
TELEFLORA GIFT CARD.
>> Veronica: PREPARE EXTRA TIME
IN YOUR COMMUTE ON THIS MONDAY.
WE'RE UNDER A WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORY FOR LOUDOUN COUNTY,
MONTGOMERY AND FAUQUIER COUNTY.
THROUGH YOUR MORNING HOURS,
TEMPERATURES TODAY RISING INTO
THE UPPER 30S.
SHOULD BE LOOKING AT ALL RAINILY
>>> AMY, OVER TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, GINGER, THANK YOU.
I'M HERE WITH OSCAR AWARD
WINNING ACTRESS BRIE LARSON WHO
MANY KNOW AS CAPTAIN MARVEL NOW
STARRING IN A POWERFUL NEW MOVIE
CALLED "JUST MERCY."
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS IS AN INCREDIBLY
POWERFUL MOVIE.
I DISCUSS WATCHED IT LAST NIGHT
AND WITH MY DAUGHTER AND IT IS
THE TRUE STORY.
BASED ON A TRUE STORY OF A
LAWYER WHO GETS WRONGFULLY
CONVICTED PEOPLE SOME JUSTICE.
YOU'RE STARRING ALONG WITH
MICHAEL B. JORDAN, JAMIE FOXX.
TELL ME ABOUT WHAT THE
EXPERIENCE WAS LIKE MAKING THIS
MOVIE.
>> OH, IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
MICHAELS WITH A PRODUCER ON THIS
FILM AS WELL SO HE WAS OUR
LEADER ON AND OFF CAMERA, JAMIE,
HE GOT TO BE IN THE KIND OF
INTERSECTION OF EVERYTHING THAT
HE'S GOOD AT, ENTERTAINER,
MUSICIAN AND ACTOR.
SO IT WASN'T JUST THAT WE WERE
DOING THESE REALLY DEEP SCENES
ON CAMERA.
HE WAS SORT OF LEADING US WITH
MUSIC, WITH STORY, WITH JOKES
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
>> AMAZING.
IN FACT, WE HAVE A SNEAK PEEK OF
THE MOVIE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> HIS ATTORNEY WAS OPENLY IN
FAVOR OF THE DEATH PENALTY.
HE THOUGHT MAD DOGS OUGHT TO
DIE.
>> SHE'S PRETTY STRESSED OUT.
>> I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GIVE UP
WHEN I GOT A CALL FROM A HARVARD
LAWYER SAYING THAT HE HAD JUST
PASSED THE ALABAMA BAR AND HAD
FEDERAL FUNDING TO START A LEGAL
CENTER FOR INMATES ON DEATH ROW.
I WAS IN IT BEFORE YOU EVEN
OFFERED ME THE JOB.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YOU PLAY EVA.
SHE IS THE WOMAN WHO HELPED
FOUND THE EQUAL JUSTICE
INITIATIVE.
YOU SAID SHE'S YOUR REAL-LIFE
HERO.
TELL ME WHY SHE INSPIRES YOU SO
MUCH.
>> I MEAN, WHAT I LOVE ABOUT HER
AND THE DEPICTION OF HER IN THIS
FILM IT SHOWS YOU DON'T JUST
HAVE TO BE A LAWYER TO GET
INVOLVED WITH THINGS INVOLVING
JUSTICE.
SHE WAS A MOM WHO NOTICED THAT
SOMETHING WAS GOING WRONG IN HER
TOWN AND SO SHE JUST TOOK THE
INITIATIVE HERSELF.
SO FOR ANYONE WHO WATCHES THE
FILM OR IS LISTENING NOW LIKE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO THINK THAT THE
SYSTEM IS SO BIG YOU CAN'T GET
INVOLVED.
THERE'S SO MUCH THAT CAN BE DONE
AND I THINK BRINGING THE POWER
FIRST BACK TO OURSELVES AND
RECOGNIZING THAT OUR SYSTEMS ARE
MADE UP OF PEOPLE IS SUCH AN
IMPORTANT THING TO REMEMBER.
>> IT'S AN INCREDIBLE FILM FOR
EVERYONE TO SEE.
I KNOW WE MENTIONED "CAPTAIN
MARVEL" AT THE BEGINNING AND I
HAVE TO ASK YOU A CAPTAIN MARVEL
QUESTION.
FANS ARE WONDERING, OKAY, IF YOU
ARE --
>> UH-HUH.
>> YOUR NEXT MOVIE APPEARANCE,
WE'VE GOT A THROWBACK PHOTO YOU
PUT.
>> THERE'S A PHOTO?
>> YES, THE PHOTO YOU PUT UP.
>> OKAY, WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
>> IS CAPTAIN MARVEL GOING TO BE
IN --
>> I CAN'T ANSWER THAT BUT THAT
WAS SUPERFUN.
>> CAN YOU TELL US ANYTHING
ABOUT "CAPTAIN MARVEL 2."
>> NO, BUT THAT PHOTO IS REALLY
COOL, RIGHT?
>> IT'S A BIG HINT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE HOLIDAYS.
LAST YEAR YOU GOT NEW TAP SHOES
FOR CRAM.
>> I DID.
>> YOU SHOWED EVERYONE THAT ON
SOCIAL MEDIA AS WELL.
THEY WERE ADORABLE.
WHAT'S ON YOUR CHRISTMAS WISH
LIST THIS YEAR.
>> I MEAN THIS SOUPS JUST LIKE
MAYBE IT'S KIND OF LAME BUT I
JUST FEEL LIKE THIS YEAR WAS
SO -- THERE WAS SO MUCH
ABUNDANCE FOR ME SO I'M FOCUSING
ON CHARITABLE DONATIONS SO
EGI.ORG.
IF YOU CAN HELP THESE PEOPLE.
THEY'RE GETTING SO MANY PEOPLE
REACHING OUT TO THEM NEEDING
SUPPORT SO IF YOU HAVE ANYTHING
EXTRA TO GIVE OR IF YOU FEEL
YOUR LIFE IS FULL HELP SOMEBODY
GET LEGAL SUPPORT.
>> I LOVE THAT.
I LOVE THAT.
SPEAKING OF THE FILM WE HAVE
MICHAEL B. JORDAN AND JAMIE FOXX
ON THIS WEEK.
WHAT SHOULD WE ASK THEM?
TELL US SOME QUESTIONS.
>> I WANT TO KNOW IS JAMIE FOXX
ON THE MAST SINGER?
ISN'T THAT A THEORY?
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE KEEP TELLING
ME.
I WANT TO KNOW.
>> WE WILL TRY TO UNCOVER THAT.
>> PLEASE.
>> I DIDN'T DO SUCH A GOOD JOB
WITH YOU IN "CAPTAIN MARVEL" BUT
WE CAN TRY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BRIE LARSON, EVERYONE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND "JUST MERCY" HITS SELECT
THEATERS CHRISTMAS DAY AND OPENS
NATIONWIDE ON JANUARY 10th.
>>> COMING UP, WAIT TILL YOU SEE
THE ULTIMATE CHRISTMAS COOKIES
WE ARE MAKING.
♪
♪ JINGLE BELL ♪
>>> WE ARE BACK AND WE ARE
BAKING FOR OUR ULTIMATE
CHRISTMAS COOKIE SERIES AND THIS
MORNING WE'VE GOT THE AUTHOR OF
"HELLO, COOKIE DOUGH: 110
DOUGHLICIOUS CONFECTIONS"
KRISTEN TOMLAN HERE.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
OKAY, THIS IS A FIRST.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF STUFFED
COOKIES.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
>> COOKIE CUPCAKES THAT ARE
STUFFED.
SO THIS VERSION IS GOING TO BE
OUR RED VELVET.
>> OKAY.
>> DELICIOUS.
WE'VE GOT OUR BUTTER AND OUR
SUGAR IN HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO ADD OUR EGGS
WHICH ARE ROOM TEMPERATURE.
>> THAT'S KEY.
>> KEY.
AND THEN A LITTLE BIT OF FOOD
COLORING TO MAKE IT RED.
>> MAKES IT RED, YES.
>> I'LL HAVE YOU WHISK THESE DRY
INGREDIENTS TOGETHER.
>> WE ALWAYS DO THESE SEPARATE.
>> DRY AND WET SEPARATE.
AND THE TRICK YOU SAY NOT TO MIX
THE DOUGH TOO MUCH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ONCE YOU ADD THE DRY
INGREDIENTS.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GOOD.
>> YEP, YOU DON'T WANT TO
OVERMIX OR COOKIES WILL END UP
LIKE HOCKEY PUCK.
>> NOBODY WANTS THAT.
AFTER THAT YOU THROW THAT --
POUR THAT IN THERE.
>> DEFINITELY, IT HERE.
EXACTLY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THEN THE OTHER PART,
STUFFERING A COOKIE.
I'VE NEVER DONE IT.
>> YES, EXACTLY SO YOU ARE GOING
TO HAVE A RED VELVET DOUGH.
THE PERFECT WAY TO GET YOUR KIDS
INVOLVED.
CREATE AN OPENING IN THE MIDDLE
AND I'LL PIPE IN CLASSIC CREAM
CHEESE FROSTING.
>> CAN'T HAVE THAT WITHOUT CREAM
>> YOU'LL COVER IT UP.
>> FROM THE BOTTOM.
>> LICK MY FINGER.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ALL OF THIS COOKIE DOUGH IS
EDIBLE SO IT'S ALL EDIBLE AND
BAKABLE.
WHEN YOU BAKE IT, IT'S GOING TO
TURN OUT --
>> LIKE A CUPCAKE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AND YOU'RE GOING TO FROST IT.
>> WHEAT INSIDE.
>> YOU COULD STUFF THEM WITH
ANYTHING.
>> NOT JUST CREAM CHEESE.
WHAT ELSE --
>> KNEW TELL.
CHOCOLATE GA GASH, SPRINKLES.
>> YES, HELLO.
>> AND OF COURSE WE HAVE TO ADD
SPRINKLES ON TOP.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> GORGEOUS.
GREAT THING TO TAKE TO SCHOOL.
OR TO THE OFFICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> IF YOU'RE TAKING THEM WITH
YOU --
>> TRAVELING.
>> PICK UP ONE OF THESE NIFTY
CARRIER, THEY'LL'S TURN OUT
PERFECT EVERY TIME.
>> THESE ARE FANTASTIC.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> SO YOU'VE GOT -- BUT, WAIT,
THERE'S MORE.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
>> WE HAVE OUR PEPPERMINT HOT
COCOA BOMBS.
>> PEPPERMINT HOT COCOA BOMBS
TOPPED WITH MARSHMALLOWS,
TOASTED MARSHMALLOWS, CHOCOLATE
GANACHE.
PEPPERMINT PIECES.
>> I KNOW YOU WANT ONE.
>> THESE ARE STUFFED AS WELL.
>> MY GOSH, STUFFED WITH?
>> MARSHMALLOW FLUFF.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THIS IS AMAZING.
>> SO GOOD.
>> WE'LL GIVE YOU SOME, I
PROMISE.
YOU GET THESE RECIPES PLUS OUR
COOKIE GUIDE WITH RECIPES FOR 25
COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITE AND GUESS
WHAT, EVERYONE GETS TO GO HOME
NOT JUST WITH COOKIES WITH A
COPY OF KRISTEN'S BOOK.
>> YES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> STAY WITH US.
>> WE'LL BE BACK.
>> Announcer: TOMORROW, WAKE UP
WITH ANDY GRAMMER LIVE.
♪ SO DON'T GIVE UP ♪
>> Announcer: TOMORROW ONLY ON
"GOOD MORNING AMERICA."
PRESENTED BY CARMAX.
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY STATE FARM.
TALK TO AN AGENT TODAY AT
800-STATE-FARM.
>> NICE START TO THE WEEK.
>> YEAH, WE GOT COOKIES.
THANKS FOR WATCHING, EVERYBODY.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
D.C. MAYOR MURIEL BOWSER 4
MILLION DOLLAR FAMILY'S FIRST
D.C. INITIATIVE AND USED TO HELP
OPEN 10 FAMILY SUCCESS CENTERS.
MAYOR BOWSER WILL MAKE THAT THE
AT 10:30 IN SOUTHEAST.
>> JESSOB: GEARING UP FROM A BIG
CELEBRATION ON GEORGETOWN,
UNIVERSITY.
SOCCER TEAM CELEBRATING NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP, GU BEATING
VIRGINIA IN PENALTY KICKS AFTER
TRIPLE OVERTIME TO BRING HOME
FIRST NCAA MEN'S SOCCER TITLE.
HOSTING AT 3:00 AT HEELLY CENTER
ON CAMPUS.
>> ADRIANNA: VERONICA JOHNSON
TRACKING ALL KINDS OF
TEMPERATURES.
>> WE NOT ONLY HAVE LOW
VISIBILITY SNOW SHOWERS LEFT
LINGERING AND SLICK POCKETS,
MONTGOMERY COUNTY MOUNT LOUDOUN
COUNTY, CHILLY RAIN 38-39
DEGREES.
LOOK INTO YOUR OVERNIGHT PERIOD.
TEMPERATURES STAY HIGH ABOVE
FREEZING.
SCATTERED RAIN SHOWERS, 49
DEGREES HIGH TEMPERATURE
TOMORROW.
COLD AIR, SUNSHINE, WEDNESDAY
41.
THURSDAY, HIGH TEMPERATURE 34
DEGREES.
COLD HERE, WINTRY WEATHER COMING
THROUGH WINDER SOLSTICE DOESN'T
START UNTIL SATURDAY.
AD
>> ADRIANNA: GET TRAFFIC,
WEATHER, AND NEWS ANY TIME WITH
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> JESSOB: WE ARE BACK IN A