>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU ON THIS FRIDAY A
NEW WINTER STORM IS MOVING IN
THREATENING THE HOLIDAY TRAVEL
RUSH.
BITTER BLAST.
MILLIONS HIT THE ROADS AND SKIES
ON WHAT'S EXPECTED TO BE THE
BUSIEST CHRISTMAS SEASON TRAVEL
DAY ON RECORD.
A NEW STORM TAKING AIM WITH
HEAVY SNOW AND RAIN.
>>> IMPEACHMENT SHOWDOWN.
THE LATEST ON SPEAKER PELOSI'S
THREAT TO HOLD UP PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S TRIAL.
ALL THE FALLOUT INSIDE THE WHITE
HOUSE AS ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR
CHRISTIAN MAGAZINES IN AMERICA
BLASTS THE PRESIDENT SAYING HE
SHOULD BE REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
>>> FIERY FACE-OFF.
IN THE MOST HEATED DEBATE YET,
SEVEN DEMOCRATS FACING OFF
OVERNIGHT.
MAYOR PETE, THE TOP TARGET OVER
HIS WEALTHY BACKERS.
>> BILLIONAIRES IN WINE CAVES
SHOULD NOT PICK THE NEXT
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> MR. MAYOR, YOUR RESPONSE.
>> YOU KNOW, ACCORDING TO FORBES
MAGAZINE I'M LITERALLY THE ONLY
PERSON ON THIS STAGE WHO IS NOT
A MILLIONAIRE OR A BILLIONAIRE.
>> AND JOE BIDEN FIGHTING BACK
AFTER BEING MOCKED FOR
STUTTERING.
>>> BREAKING NEWS IN THE CASE OF
THAT MISSING TEXAS MOM AND HER
BABY.
AUTHORITIES SURROUND A HOME IN
HOUSTON RIGHT NOW.
>>> ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
PAT SAJAK SPEAKING OUT IN HIS
FIRST INTERVIEW SINCE HIS
MEDICAL EMERGENCY.
>> YOU GO IN AND THEY DON'T KNOW
IF I'M COMING OUT.
>> WHAT IT WAS LIKE SEEING VANNA
WHITE TAKE CONTROL OF THE WHEEL
AND WHAT HE SAYS ABOUT LEAVING
THE SHOW ONLY ON "GMA."
♪
>>> AND FEELING THE FORCE.
THE STARLINER ROCKET BLASTING
OFF MOMENTS AGO.
>> WE'VE CLEARED THE TO YOUER.
>> THIS AS "STAR WARS" BLASTS
INTO THEATERS.
TROOPS GETTING AN EARLY
SCREENING.
FANS LINING UP ALL NIGHT AND NOW
THE BREAKOUT STAR IS JOINING US
LIVE.
>>> AND GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
HAPPY FRIDAY.
HAPPY HOLIDAY FRIDAY.
HAPPY "STAR WARS" FRIDAY.
THE DAY IS HERE.
"THE RISE OF SKYWALKER" ABOUT TO
HIT THESEERS.
>> CROWDS WERE LINING UP
OVERNIGHT FOR THAT PREMIERE FOR
THE KICKOFF OF THE FILM AND
PEOPLE ALSO LINING UP AT
AIRPORTS THIS MORNING AS THAT
TRAVEL RUSH BEGINS.
>> IT IS ALREADY VERY BUSY OUT
THERE AND THIS IS HAPPENING AS A
NEW WINTER STORM MOVES IN.
THE WEST IS NOW BRACING FOR
SNOW, RAIN AND POSSIBLE
MUDSLIDES.
GINGER STARTS US OFF WITH THE
LATEST.
>> WE'RE ALREADY SEEING
PICTURES.
SNOWALL ECONOMY PASS, INTERSTATE
90 HAVING IMPACTS.
MORE THAN A FOOT OF SNOW.
LOOK AT THIS OUT OF OREGON.
THE LANDSLIDES THAT ARE TAKING
PLACE AFTER YOU GET A COUPLE OF
INCHES OF RAIN QUICKLY.
NOT ONLY COULD YOU SEE THAT
LANDSLIDE BUT THE WHOLE HOLIDAY
TRAVEL PICTURE.
IT'S NOT JUST THE PACIFIC
NORTHWEST AND NORTHERN
CALIFORNIA, SFO IF YOU'RE FLYING
THROUGH THERE COULD HAVE ISSUES,
HOUSTON OVER TO ORLANDO ARE
WATCHING FOR TRAVEL DELAYS
POSSIBLE BECAUSE OF RAIN.
LET ME GIVE YOU A REAL
INDICATION OF WHAT'S ABOUT TO
HAPPEN FROM CALIFORNIA UP
THROUGH THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST.
THERE'S THIS ATMOSPHERIC RIVER,
IT'S THIS NARROW BAND OF
MOISTURE THAT IS GOING TO IMPACT
TRAVEL FOR SURE.
THEY'RE CALLING IT THE CATEGORY
4 OF ATMOSPHERIC RIVERS SO IT'S
GOING TO COME WITH BIG-TIME
WINDS UP TO 60 MILES PER HOUR.
SUNDAY TRAVELING THROUGH L.A.X.
YOU COULD HAVE SIGNIFICANT RAIN
AND THEN AS YOU TRAVEL I-5 IF
YOU'RE ON THE ROADS UP THROUGH
THE SIERRA, A FOOT AND A HALF OF
SNOW AND SEATTLE TWO TO FIVE
INCHES OF RAIN.
>> A LOT COMING.
LET'S TAKE A CLOSER LOOK RIGHT
NOW.
HERE ARE THE PLANES IN THE SKY
AS TODAY IS EXPECTED TO BE AS
CECILIA SAID THE BUSIEST
CHRISTMAS TRAVEL DAY AT AIRPORTS
EVER.
VICTOR OQUENDO ON THE TARMAC THE
HARTSFIELD-JACKSON IN ATLANTA,
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, FROM
THE BUSIEST AIRPORT IN THE WORLD
THIS DELTA FLIGHT IS LOAD UP
HEADING FOR RICHMOND AND IT IS
ON TIME.
AS YOU JUST MENTIONED IT IS
EXPECTED TO BE THE BUSIEST AIR
TRAVEL DAY ON RECORD FOR THE
WINTER HOLIDAYS.
ABOUT 3 MILLION ARE EXPECTED TO
FLY AND AS YOU TAKE A LOOK AT
THE NUMBERS WE DO NOT EXPECT
THOSE TO SLOW DOWN ANY TIME
SOON.
BUT THERE ARE SOME SWEET SPOTS.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO AVOID THE
BIG RUSH, THE LIGHTEST TRAVEL
DAYS WILL BE CHRISTMAS EVE,
CHRISTMAS DAY AND NEW YEAR'S
EVE.
TSA EXPECTS TO SCREEN ABOUT 4%
MORE PASSENGERS THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON COMPARED TO LAST SO
ALREADY ADDITIONAL OFFICERS IN
PLACE.
OVER THANKSGIVING THE AVERAGE
WAIT TIME WAS ABOUT 30 MENS AND
THEY WOULD LIKE TO MAINTAIN THAT
THE ADVICE FROM THE TSA
ADMINISTRATOR, YOU CAN STOP ME
IF YOU HAVE HEARD IT BEFORE, GET
TO THE AIRPORT EARLY, BE
PREPARED AND A BIT PATIENT.
THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM,
250,000 PASSENGERS WILL MAKE
THEIR WAY THROUGH ATLANTA AND
EVERYONE ON THE GROUND TELLS ME
THEY'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> GIVE YOURSELF MORE TIME AND
ALLEVIATE SOME STRESS.
>>> IF YOU'RE MAKING YOUR
HOLIDAY GETAWAY ON THE ROADS
GOOD NEWS FOR YOU THIS MORNING.
GAS PRICES ARE DOWN.
THEY'RE THE LOWEST THEY'VE BEEN
IN SEVERAL MONTHS AND GIO
BENITEZ IS AT ONE OF THE FEW GAS
STATIONS HERE IN MANHATTAN WITH
MORE.
GOOD MORNING, GIO.
>> Reporter: HEY, MICHAEL, GOOD
MORNING.
WE COULD SEE A RECORD FOR
HOLIDAY TRAVEL ON THE ROADS THIS
YEAR, TAKE A LOOK AT THESE
NUMBERS RIGHT NOW BECAUSE WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT NEARLY 105 MILLION
AMERICANS, THE MOST ON RECORD.
THEY'RE GOING TO DRIVE TO THEIR
HOLIDAY DESTINATIONS FROM THIS
SUNDAY TO NEW YEAR'S DAY.
4 MILLION MORE THAN LAST YEAR, A
WHOLE LOT MORE.
THE DEPARTMENT OF ENERGY SAYING
THE NATIONAL AVERAGE FOR GAS IS
$20.53 FOR REGULAR.
EXPERTS EXPECT PRICES TO DROP A
BIT MORE BEFORE THE NEW YEAR AND
IN SOME PARTS OF THE SOUTH,
MICHAEL, YOU COULD ACTUALLY FIND
GAS FOR UNDER $2 A GALLON.
>> THAT SOUNDS LIKE A DREAM BUT
WITH SO MANY ON THE ROAD IS
THERE A TIME THAT YOU SHOULD
STAY OFF THE ROADS WITH SO MANY
PEOPLE TRAVELING?
>> Reporter: YEAH, I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN THAT DAY IS, THURSDAY,
DECEMBER 26th, MICHAEL.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE DRIVING IN
THE AFTERNOON INTO THE EVENING.
IT COULD TAKE YOU TWICE AS LONG
TO GET SOMEWHERE SO IF YOU CAN,
TRY TO STAY OFF THE ROAD ON
DECEMBER 26th.
>> WILL DO MY BEST.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GI
CECILIA.
>>> WE HEAD TO WASHINGTON AND A
STALEMATE OVER IMPEACHMENT.
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI REFUSING TO
SEND THE ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT
OVER TO THE SENATE AND NOW WITH
THE HOUSE ADJOURNED, WHEN WILL
THE TRIAL BEGIN?
WHAT IS THE SPEAKER'S STRATEGY
GOING INTO THIS?
>> Reporter: A BIT OF A RISKY
MOVE BUT DEMOCRATS ARE HOPING
HOLDING UP THE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT WILL GIVE THEM MORE
LEVERAGE AS THEY TROY TO
NEGOTIATE WHAT A TRIAL IN THE
SENATE WILL ACTUALLY LOOK LIKE
AND DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO CALL
THE PRESIDENT'S BLUFF.
HE SAID HE WOULD LIKE HIS TOP
AIDES TO TESTIFY.
DEMOCRATS WANT HIM TO PROVE IT.
THEY ARE AT AN IMPASSE AND
DEMOCRATS ARE DEMANDING
WITNESSES LIKE ACTING WHITE
HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF MICK
MULVANEY AND FORMER SECURITY
ADVISER JOHN BOLTON.
REPUBLICANS AREN'T BUDGING.
MITCH McCONNELL SAYS THE SPEAKER
WANTS TO PREVENT A TRIAL, FINE
WITH ME, BUT THE PRESIDENT WANTS
THIS TRIAL AND ONE OF HIS TOP
ALLIES SAYS TRUMP IS MAD AS
HELL.
>> LOOKING FOR VINDICATION.
>> LET'S GET MORE ON THE WHITE
HOUSE RESPONSE FROM OUR CHIEF
WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT JON
KARL.
WE HEARD THE MARY SAY THE
PRESIDENT IS MAD AS HELL.
THEY WERE A BIT SURPRISED BY
THIS MOVE FROM SPEAKER PELOSI.
>> Reporter: NO DOUBT ABOUT
THAT, GEORGE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN ASKING
HIS AIDES WHAT PELOSI IS UP TO
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT THE
STRATEGY IS, WHAT IS HAPPENING
NEXT.
BUT AS YOU HEARD MARY MENTION,
McCONNELL, MITCH McCONNELL, THE
REPUBLICAN LEADER HAS BEEN
SAYING HE DIDN'T WANT A TRIAL IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
HE'D BE FINE NOT TO HAVE ONE.
THAT IS NOT THE MESSAGE HERE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE AS THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF TWEETED LAST NIGHT, I
WANT AN IMMEDIATE TRIAL.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS A SENATE
TRIAL BECAUSE HE KNOWS THAT
BARRING SOME SEISMIC EVENT HE
WILL PREVAIL.
THE DEMOCRATS WILL FALL FAR
SHORT OF REMOVING HIM FROM
OFFICE AND HE WILL POINT TO THAT
AS VINDICATION.
>> HE WANTS IT BUT DOES HE
REALLY WANT WITNESSES?
>> NO, HE DOES NOT -- HE'S BEEN
ALL OVER THE MAP PUBLICLY BUT
THE WHITE HOUSE POSITION IS THEY
DO NOT WANT ANY WHITE HOUSE
STAFFERS TESTIFYING.
>> MEANTIME, WE SAW OVERNIGHT
THE EVANGELICAL MAGAZINE
"CHRISTIANITY TODAY" COMING OUT
WITH AN EDITORIAL SAYING THE
PRESIDENT SHOULD BE REMOVED FROM
OFFICE.
>> Reporter: YEAH, THIS IS
INTERESTING.
THIS WAS THE PUBLICATION FOUNDED
BY BILLY GRAHAM, THE LATE
EVANGELICAL LEADER AND IN THE
EDITORIAL THEY WRITE, UNSAVORY
DEALINGS AND IMMORAL ACTS BY THE
PRESIDENT AND THOSE CLOSE TO
LIMB HAVE RENDERED THIS
ADMINISTRATION MORALLY UNABLE TO
LEAD.
THEY WANT HIM REMOVED FROM
OFFICE.
NOW, BILLY GRAHAM'S SON FRANKLIN
GRAHAM HAS REACTED TO THIS BY
SAYING THAT HIS FATHER, WHO DIED
LAST YEAR, WOULD BE EMBARRASSED
BY THIS EDITORIAL AND HE SAYS
THAT HIS DAD VOTED FOR DONALD
TRUMP.
>> JON KARL, THANKS VERY MUCH.
MICHAEL.
>>> NOW WE TURN TO THE DEMOCRATS
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT IN THAT
FIERY DEBATE OVERNIGHT.
THE LAST ONE OF THE YEAR AND
GLOVES WERE OFF WITH PETE
BUTTIGIEG FEELING THE HEAT AND
LINSEY DAVIS WAS THERE FOR IT
ALL AND JOINS US FROM LOS
ANGELES.
GOOD MORNING, LINSEY.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD MORNING
TO YOU, MICHAEL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THINGS CERTAINLY GOT HOT AT
TIMES LAST NIGHT DESPITE THE
FACT THAT THE FIRST HOUR WAS
PRETTY MUCH POLITICS AS USUAL
BUT THEN THERE WAS A SHARP TURN
AS THE CONVERSATION CHANGED TO
CAMPAIGN FINANCING WHICH
PROMPTED A MASSIVE PILE ON MAYOR
PETE AND THAT WOULDN'T BE THE
ONLY CLASH OF THE NIGHT.
FAST-RISING CANDIDATE PETE
BUTTIGIEG WALKED ONTO THE DEBATE
STAGE WITH A TARGET ON HIS BACK
AND IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR THE
GLOVES TO COME OFF.
>> THE MAYOR JUST RECENTLY HAD A
FUND-RAISER THAT WAS HELD IN A
WINE CAVE FULL OF CRYSTALS AND
SERVED $900 A BOTTLE WINE.
THINK ABOUT WHO COMES TO THAT.
BILLIONAIRES IN WINE CAVES
SHOULD NOT PICK THE NEXT
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> MR. MAYOR, YOUR RESPONSE.
>> YOU KNOW, ACCORDING TO
"FORBES" MAGAZINE, I AM
LITERALLY THE ONLY PERSON ON
THIS STAGE WHO IS NOT A
MILLIONAIRE OR A BILLIONAIRE.
SO IF --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
THIS IS THE PROBLEM WITH ISSUING
PURITY TESTS YOU CANNOT YOURSELF
PASS.
[ CHEERS ]
>> -- DID NOT COME HERE TO
LISTEN TO THIS ARGUMENT.
I CAME HERE TO MAKE A CASE FOR
PROGRESS AND I HAVE NEVER EVEN
BEEN TO A WINE CAVE.
I'VE BEEN TO THE WIND CAVE IN
SOUTH DAKOTA WHICH I SUGGEST YOU
GO TO.
>> Reporter: BUTTIGIEG, THE
MAYOR OF SOUTH BEND, INDIANA HAS
BEEN PICKING UP STEAM IN IOWA
AND NEW HAMPSHIRE BUT THE
YOUNGEST CANDIDATE HAS ALSO
FACED QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS
EXPERIENCE AND ELECTABLE.
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR CALLING
HIM OUT ON AN EARLIER LOSS IN A
STATEWIDE RACE.
>> AND I WOULD -- MAYOR, IF
YOU -- IF YOU HAD WON IN INDIANA
THAT WOULD BE ONE THING.
YOU TRIED AND YOU LOST BY 20
POINTS.
>> Reporter: BUT THE MAYOR
FIRING BACK.
>> IF YOU JUST GO BY VOTE
TOTALS, MAYBE WHAT GOES ON IN MY
CITY SEEMS SMALL TO YOU.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
CAPACITY TO WIN, TRY PUTTING
TOGETHER A COALITION TO BRING
YOU BACK TO OFFICE WITH 80% OF
THE VOTE AS A GAY DUDE IN MIKE
PENCE'S INDIANA.
>> Reporter: ON IMPEACHMENT
DEMOCRATS WERE UNITED.
>> A CONSTITUTIONAL NECESSITY
FOR THE HOUSE TO ACT AS IT DID.
>> Reporter: THE FINAL DEBATE
WAS THE SMALLEST YET WITH ONLY
SEVEN CANDIDATES ON THE STAGE.
THERE WAS MORE TALKING TIME TO
GO AROUND BENEFITING THE ONLY
MINORITY AT THE DEBATE, ANDREW
YANG.
>> AND THE QUESTION IS WHY AM I
THE LONE CANDIDATE OF COLOR ON
THIS STAGE?
FEWER THAN 5% OF AMERICANS
DONATE TO POLITICAL CAMPAIGNS.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU NEED TO DONATE
TO THOSE?
DISPOSABLE INCOME.
>> Reporter: IT WAS THIS MOMENT.
>> A LITTLE KID WHO SAYS I, I, I
CAN'T TALK.
WHAT TWO I DO?
>> Reporter: IT PROMPTED AN
ATTACK FROM SARAH SANDERS
MOCKING HIS STUTTER.
HE WROTE BACK, I HAVE WORKED MY
WHOLE LIFE TO OVERCOME A
STUTTER.
IT IS MY GREAT HONOR TO MENTOR
KIDS WHO HAVE EDGE EXPERIENCED
THE SAME.
IT'S CALLED EMPATHY.
LOOK IT UP.
SANDERS LATER APOLOGIZED AND
WHILE BIDEN DID HAVE A STRONG
NIGHT, THE GENERAL CONSENSUS AT
LEAST FROM INSIDE THE ROOM IS
THAT SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR
SHINED AS SHE TRIED TO MAKE A
CASE WHILE SOMEBODY FROM THE
MIDWEST OUGHT TO OVAL OFFICE.
>> I THINK ACTUALLY, LINSEY, ONE
OF THESE DEBATES THAT ONE OF THE
BEST DEBATES OF THE CYCLE.
THE MODERATORS DID A GOOD JOB
AND EVERYBODY HAD AND SAW A LOT
IN THAT PIECE, MOMENTS TO SHINE
FROM BIDEN TO KLOBUCHAR TO
BUTTIGIEG, SANDERS AND WARREN SO
IT'S ALMOST A SHAME IT HAPPENED
SO LATE IN THE YEAR RIGHT BEFORE
THE HOLIDAY.
>> FEWER CANDIDATES ALLOWED THE
LESSER ONES TO SHINE.
>>> WE SHIFT AND HEAD TO
BREAKING NEWS.
>>> A POSSIBLE BREAK IN THE CASE
INVOLVING THAT MISSING TEXAS
MOTHER AND HER INFANT.
AUTHORITIES SURROUNDING A HOME
IN HOUSTON OVERNIGHT.
ABC'S MARCUS MOORE HAS THE VERY
LATEST ON THIS STORY, GOOD
MORNING, MARCUS.
>> Reporter: CECILIA, GOOD
MORNING.
THESE FAST-MOVING DEVELOPMENTS
COMING A FULL WEEK AFTER HEIDI
BROUSSARD AND HER 3-WEEK-OLD
BABY WERE REPORTED MISSING AND
THIS MORNING, WE KNOW THAT
OVERNIGHT AUTHORITIES FOUND A
1-MONTH-OLD BABY IN A HOME AND
OUR STATION KTRK IN HOUSTON ALSO
REPORTS A BODY WAS REMOVED FROM
THAT HOUSE AS WELL.
DOZENS OF LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICERS SWOOPING IN ON THIS
HOME NEAR HOUSTON OVERNIGHT.
A PUBLIC SAFETY OFFICIAL SAYING
INVESTIGATORS WERE THERE IN
CONNECTION WITH THE
DISAPPEARANCE OF HEIDI BROUSSARD
AND HER 3-WEEK-OLD DAUGHTER.
A 1-MONTH-OLD BABY WAS FOUND
SAFE AND UNHARMED ACCORDING TO A
FIRE DEPARTMENT OFFICIAL, BUT
THE INFANT'S NAME HAS NOT BEEN
RELEASED.
THIS IS THE LAST KNOWN IMAGE OF
THE 33-YEAR-OLD MOTHER, A
SURVEILLANCE PICTURE OF HER
DROPPING OFF HER 6-YEAR-OLD SON
AT SCHOOL.
SHE NEVER RETURNED TO PICK HIM
UP.
HER FIANCE SAYS HER PURSE AND
WALLET WERE LEFT INSIDE HER
UNLOCKED CAR.
HER BABY'S DIAPER BAG WAS INSIDE
THE APARTMENT BUT HER KEYS AND
CELL PHONE WERE GONE.
>> DROP HER OFF ANYWHERE.
I DOESN'T CARE.
JUST MAKE SURE SHE'S SAFE AND
OKAY.
THE BABY IS OKAY.
>> Reporter: THE FBI JOINED
FORCES WITH THE TEXAS RANGERS
AND AUSTIN POLICE IN A
WIDESPREAD SEARCH ACROSS THE
STATE.
I SPOKE WITH BROUSSARD'S PARENTS
WHO WERE PRAYING FOR A HOPEFUL
ENDING.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE SHE LEFT ON HER
OWN?
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> NO WAY.
SHE WOULD NOT LEAVE HER SON.
HER KIDS ARE HER HEARTBEAT.
>> OH, YES, SHE WOULDN'T HAVE
LEFT ON HER OWN.
>> Reporter: AND IF THE BABY
THAT WAS FOUND IS, INDEED,
MARGOT, IT WOULD BE PRAYERS
ANSWERED FOR THE FAMILY BUT THIS
NORPG THERE'S STILL A LOT WE
DON'T KNOW AND ANTICIPATE THE
POLICE DEPARTMENT WILL RELEASE
MORE INFORMATION ABOUT THIS
DISCOVERY THAT HAPPENED
OVERNIGHT.
GEORGE.
>> OKAY, MARCUS, THANKS.
>>> OVERSEAS FOR THE LATEST ON
THE ATTACK AT THE HEAD OF
RUSSIA'S SPY SERVICE AND
UNLEASHED AS PRESIDENT PUTIN
DELIVERED A SPEECH HONORING THE
SECURITY SERVICES.
IAN PANNELL IS IN MOSCOW WITH
THE DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING, IAN.
>> Reporter: YEAH, GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE HUNT IS ON TO TRY TO
IDENTIFY THE MAN AND MOTIVE
BEHIND THIS SHOOTING AT THE
HEART OF RUSSIA'S SECURITY
ESTABLISHMENT.
NOW, IT TOOK PLACE HERE AT THE
FSB HEADQUARTERS.
THAT IS THE INTERNAL SECURITY
SERVICES, THE SUCCESSOR TO THE
KGB.
ACCORDING TO AUTHORITIES WHAT WE
KNOW THERE WAS A LONE GUNMAN
THAT OPENED FIRE JUST AROUND THE
CORNER AND KILLED ONE FSB
OFFICER, SHOTS RANG OUT,
PASSERS-BY WERE RUNNING FOR
COVER AND FIVE CIVILIANS WERE
ALSO INJURED -- SORRY, FOUR
OFFICERS, ONE CIVILIAN AND
TRYING TO ESTABLISH THE MOTIVE.
WAS IT A LONE GUNMAN SLIGHTLY
UNHINGED OR A TERRORIST ATTACK?
WE BELIEVE THAT THEY HAVE NOW
IDENTIFIED PERHAPS WHERE THE MAN
LIVED.
EITHER WAY THIS IS AN AUDACIOUS
ATTACK IN THE HEART OF RUSSIA'S
STATE SECURITY, MICHAEL.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT,
IAN.
>>> WE ARE JUST FIVE DAYS AWAY
FROM CHRISTMAS.
THIS IS THE FINAL WEEKEND BEFORE
THE HOLIDAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE A BUSY ONE FOR
SHOPPERS.
THE WQUESTION IS, CAN YOU STILL
ORDER ONLINE AND GET THEM IN
TIME?
REBECCA JARVIS HAS A REALITY
CHECK.
GOOD MORNING, REBECCA.
>> Reporter: HEY, MICHAEL.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS THE HEART OF THE ACTION
HERE IN NEW YORK CITY WHERE THEY
HAVE MORE THAN 3,000 EMPLOYEES
WORKING AROUND THE CLOCK,
650,000 EMPLOYEES AROUND THE
COUNTRY TRYING TO GET THOSE
PACKAGES DELIVERED ON TIME
ACROSS THE COUNTRY WITH
DELIVERIES UP THIS YEAR FOR ALL
THE CARRIERS, 21% SINCE
THANKSGIVING, YOU COMBINE THAT
WITH THE WINTER WEATHER WE'VE
SEEN AND A NUMBER OF CARRIER,
FEDEX AND U.P.S. ARE ACTUALLY
RUNNING BEHIND IN TERMS OF THEIR
DELIVERIES.
THE U.S. POSTAL SERVICE ON THE
OTHER HAND ARE UP FROM LAST
YEAR, THEIR ON TIME DELIVERIES
ARE UP BUT DEADLINES ARE COMING
TO A CLOSE.
IF YOU WANT IT THERE BY
CHRISTMAS MORNING AT THE LEAST
EXPENSIVE OPTION YOU HAVE THIS
MORNING TO SHOP TARGET AND BEST
BUY.
THEIR CUTOFF FOR ONLINE DELIVERY
OPTIONS IS THIS MORNING.
MACY'S CUTOFF TOMORROW AND THEN
WALMART AND AMAZON PARTICULARLY
IF YOU'RE A PRIME MEMBER, THAT
CUTOFF IS ON SUNDAY, MICHAEL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE A PROCRASTINATOR, IT'S
TIME TO GET GOING.
>>> THANKS.
WE TURN TO THAT HISTORY-MAKING
ROCKET LAUNCH.
BOEING SENDING THE STARLINER
INTO SPACE MOMENTS AGO AND DAVID
KERLEY IS AT CAPE CANAVERAL WITH
ALL THE DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING, DAVID.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
CECILIA.
IT WAS JUST A COUPLE OF MINUTES
AGO THIS FINAL TEST, A BIG TEST
FOR BOEING TO BE THE FIRST
COMPANY TO SEND AMERICANS BACK
IN SPACE FROM AMERICAN SOIL IN
NEARLY A DECADE CALLED A
STARLINER ON TOP OF AN ATLAS V
ROCKET AND BLASTED OFF AT CAPE
CANAVERAL.
INSIDE IS A TEST DEVICE.
IT'S A DUMMY KNOWN AS ROSIE THE
ROCKETEER WITH MORE THAN A
DOZENS SORES, NOW SET TO DOCK
WITH THE SPACE STATION TOMORROW.
A BIG FINAL TEST, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, DAVID.
WE ARE FOLLOWING OTHER STORIES
THIS MORNING INCLUDING OUR
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH
WHOOEMEST PAT SAJAK AFTER THAT
EMERGENCY SURGERY.
>>> THE REVIEWS ARE IN FOR
"CATS."
CAN TAYLOR SWIFT SAVE THE MOVIE?
LET'S HEAD BACK TO GINGER.
>> IMAGE OF GAINESVILLE WITH
FROST ON THE WINDSHIELD.
THAT'S WHY IT'S A BIG DEAL.
>> Veronica: EXPECT COLD
SUNSHNE TODAY, SO MAKE SURE YOU
BUNDLE UP HEADING OUT, BUT IT IS
GOING TO BE DRY, AT LEAST FOR
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS, AND
HIGHER TEMPERATU COMING YOUR
WAY FOR THE HOLIDAY BREAK.
SO PICK UP TIME FOR THE BUS
STOP, THE KIDS IN THE 20S.
ABOUT 40 DEGREES DROP OFF TIME.
AGAIN, SUNSHINE WITH US TODAY.
WE'LL PICK UP A FEW CLOUDS EARLY
TOMORROW, UP UNTIL ABOUT 2:00.
YOUR HIGH 42, AND THEN FOR
SUNDAY, THE HIGH TEMPERATURE OF
47.
BUT CHECK OUT CHRISTMAS EVE AND
CHRISTMAS DAY.
53 AND 52.
WE'RE DRY ON THAT SEVEN-DAY
>>> WE'RE GOING DOWN THE MOVIE
LIST.
I WANT TO SEE "CATS."
>> "STAR WARS."
>> I HAVE TO SEERST.
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Once a year,
cats come together
to compete for the
chance of a new life.
You should be on
the World Stage.
Yes.
- Yeah!
I'm a magic cat.
Now it is time to
make the choice.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
Thanks, Stef!
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Surprise!
No, I'm not gonna
get a date in this.
We had a lot of great
dates in this car.
Ugh, no. No, ew.
[Sneezing]
We had a lot of great
dates in♪♪his car.
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
The third stair always creaked.
And your mother told me
all her life
that I should fix it.
And now it reminds me of her.
I'm just glad
I never fixed it.
Listen, you don't need
to go anywhere dad.
Meet Christine, she's going to
help you around the house.
The best home to be in
is your own.
From personal care
and memory care,
to help around the house,
Home Instead offers
personalized in-home services
for your loved ones.
Home Instead Senior Care.
To us, it's personal.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
Home Instead Senior Care.
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
Hi Mom. Hi Dad.
Hey.
How's my little princess?
I want to be a movie director.
Oh!
That's great.
♪♪
Delicious high-fiber
Raisin Bran.
You sure you don't want
me to come with you?
I'm very sure.
Because I can.
(laughs)
Make good choices.
You make good choices.
I am.
Good choices never
tasted so good.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
>> ROBERT: I AM ROBERT BURTON.
HOLIDAY TRAVEL RUSH IS ON.
JOHN GONZALEZ MONITORING THE
ROADS, JOHN, HOW IS IT LOOKING
WHERE YOU ARE?
>> JOHN: RIDING SHOTGUN IN
MOBILE TRACK 7.
495, INNER LOOP LITTLE RIVER
TURNPIKE, IT IS THE PARKING LOT.
DAILY COMMUTE MIXING IN, FRIDAY
MORNING BEFORE CHRISTMAS.
RECORD NUMBERS, OVER 150 MILLION
AMERICANS TRAVELING THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
THIS IS THE EIGHTH STRAIGHT YEAR
OF RECORD BREAKING NUMBERS FOR
THE HOLIDAYS, MORE THAN 100
MILLION FOLKS WILL B TRAVELING
BY CAR.
THAT IS THE LATEST FROM 495 IN
MOBILE TRACK 7.
WE'LL BE BACK IN A FEW WITH