>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS MONDAY
MORNING, THE HOLIDAY EXODUS IS
ON.
DOUBLE TROUBLE.
STORMS ON SIDES OF THE
COUNTRY AS FLOODING SHUTS DOWN A
MAJOR AIRPORT IN FLORIDA CAUSING
CHAOS.
MORE THAN 100 MILLION AMERICANS
HEADING OUT FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
ICE AND FOG BLAMED FOR THIS
MASSIVE PILEUP INVOLVING NEARLY
70 VEHICLES, AND CAUSING DOZENS
OF INJURIES.
WITH MORE SNOW, FLOODING RAIN
AND GUSTING WINDS ON THE WAY,
WE'RE TRACKING IT ALL.
>>> NEW TRAVEL DANGER.
A MAJOR MEASLES OUTBREAK IN
THREE INTERNATIONAL AIRPORTS.
FLIGHTS AROUND THE WORLD COULD
SPREAD THE ILLNESS.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW BEFORE
BOARDING.
>>> BREAKING NEWS.
FIVE PEOPLE SENTENCED TO DEATH,
THREE SENT TO PRISON IN THE
MURDER OF "WASHINGTON POST"
COLUMNIST JAMAL KHASHOGGI,
KILLED LAST YEAR.
>>> STUNNING TWIST IN THE CASE
OF THAT MISSING TEXAS MOM FOUND
DEAD.
HER BABY GIRL FOUND ALIVE, AND
THE SHOCKER.
HER CLOSE FRIEND IN JAIL CHARGED
IN THE CRIME.
>>> JUST ONE MORE DAY IN THE
CHRISTMAS CRUNCH.
THE RUSH TO GET THOSE GIFTS
UNDER THE TREE.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW TO GET
THOSE PACKAGES THERE IN TIME.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, EDDIE
MURPHY.
>> TRIUMPHANT RETURN.
BACK ON STAGE, BETTER THAN EVER.
>> IT'S SOMETHING CALLED
GENTRIFICATION.
IF YOU SAY GENTRIFICATION, BOYS
AND GIRLS?
>> THE FAMOUS FACES JOINING HIM,
AND HIS MESSAGE TO BILL COSBY.
>>> AND AMAZING RESCUE.
THE HERO POLICE OFFICER WHO
STOPPED A RUNAWAY SUV WITH HIS
OWN STRENGTH, SAVING A GROUP OF
SCHOOL KIDS.
WHAT HE'S SAYING THIS MORNING.
>>> AND GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US.
HOW INCREDIBLE WAS THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK ONE MORE
TIME.
THAT WAS SOMETHING THERE, THAT
OFFICER ABLE TO HOLD ON, COULD
HAVE HAD A VERY DIFFERENT ENDING
ON THE ICE THERE GRABBING THE
CAR, PULLING IT BACK, SAVING A
GROUP OF KIDS.
INCREDIBLE.
>> THERE WERE TWO PEOPLE IN THE
CAR, TOO, AT THE SAME TIME.
>> WHO HAS THAT KIND OF STRENGTH
TO JUST HOLD -- THE CAR IS
HEAVY.
>> YEP.
>>> WE BEGIN WITH THE HOLIDAY
EXODUS.
FLOODING COAST TO COAST, AND
EVEN STOPPING FLIGHTS.
VICTOR OQUENDO IS AT AN
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, VICTOR.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, EVA.
A TRAVEL NIGHTMARE HERE AT
HOLLYWOOD INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE AIRPORT HAS
REOPENED.
FLIGHT OPERATIONS IN THE PROCESS
OF RESUMING, BUT THE ROADS ARE A
MESS GETTING HERE, AND THEN
THERE IS THE TRAFFIC.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
COMING IN AT TERMINAL 1, AND AS
WE SWING ALL THE WAY AROUND,
BEHIND ME, NOTHING BUT BRAKE
LIGHTS.
THIS MORNING, TORRENTIAL RAIN
AND FLASH FLOODING FORCING FT.
LAUDERDALE HOLLYWOOD
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT TO CLOSE.
A LINE OF CARS WADING SLOWLY
THROUGH RISING WATERS.
THE FLOOR MATS OF THIS CAR,
SOAKED.
>> OH MY GOD.
>> Reporter: IN VIRGINIA, A
69-CAR PILEUP ON THIS HIGHWAY.
AUTHORITIES SAYING FOG AND ICY
ROADS WERE FACTORS IN THE CRASH.
CARS CRASHING INTO ONE ANOTHER.
THIS FORD PICKUP LANDING ON TOP
OF A CAR.
DRIVERS TRAPPED IN THE CHAOS.
>> A CAR BEHIND US GOING 70
MILES PER HOUR SLAMMED INTO US
AND PUSHED US INTO THE OTHER
VEHICLES AND PINNED YOU US.
>> Reporter: DRIVERS AND
OFFICERS STANDING ON TOP OF
VEHICLES.
50 PEOPLE WERE INJURED IN THE
CRASH.
>> TWO ARE LISTED IN CRITICAL
CONDITION, AND 11 ARE SERIOUS,
BUT NON-LIFE THREATENING.
THE REST ARE EITHER MINOR, OR
THEY WENT TO THE HOSPITAL
THEMSELVES.
>> Reporter: IN MISSOURI, DENSE
FOG HINDERING VISIBILITY ON THE
ROADS.
>> WATCH OUT.
WATCH OUT.
>> Reporter: WHILE IN NEW YORK,
RESIDENTS DUCKING WHILE FALLING
ICE.
A SUDDEN FALL SENDING IT OFF
HIGH-RISES.
>> YOU SAW SHATTERED ICE ON THE
FLOOR, AND THE HOOD OF THE CAR
WAS DENTED.
>> Reporter: AND IN CALIFORNIA,
A STORM WITH 100--MILE-PER-HOUR
WIND GUSTS THROUGH ALPINE
MEADOWS.
NEARLY 105 MILLION AMERICANS
WILL BE DRIVING TO THEIR HOLIDAY
DESTINATIONS THIS YEAR.
THAT'S A RECORD, AND FOR THOSE
FLYING, HERE IS A LOOK AT THE
LIGHTEST TRAVEL DAYS.
CHRISTMAS EVE, CHRISTMAS DAY AND
NEW YEAR'S EVE, AND THOSE OF YOU
FLYING OUT OF FOT. LAUDERDALE
HOLLYWOOD INTERNATIONAL, CHECK
WITH YOUR AIRLINE.
WHIT?
>> THANK YOU.
>>> AS YOU POINTED OUT, THOSE
STORMS CAUSING TROUBLE FOR
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE THIS MORNING.
LET'S CHECK WITH ROB ON THE
TIMING OF ALL THIS.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, WHIT, ON THE
GROUND AND IN THE AIR WE'LL HAVE
ISSUES ON BOTH COASTS.
LOS ANGELES, SOME PROBLEMS
TODAY, BUT WE'LL START WITH THE
SOUTHEAST.
ATLANTA AND ORLANDO, THAT'S
WHERE THE HEAVIEST RAIN WILL BE,
AND THOSE ARE WHERE THE HUBS
WILL BE.
THE HEAVIEST RAIN NOW OUT OF
FORT LAUDER DISABLE AND MIAMI.
YOU GO TO JACKSONVILLE, AND
FLASH FLOOD WATCHES POSTED FOR
GEORGIA, ATLANTA.
YOU COULD SEE 30,
40-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS THERE,
AND THIS IS A LOW THAT WILL HANG
AROUND THE COASTLINE.
YOU TALK ABOUT AUGUSTA, I-20
TOWARDS I-95, CHARLESTON, SOUTH
CAROLINA.
2 TO 4 IMPNCHES OF RAIN, AND
YOU'LL SEE GUSTY WIND.
LET'S TALK WEST COAST.
SAN DIEGO TO LOS ANGELES, THIS
IS A HEAVY RAIN EVENT TODAY AND
TONIGHT.
SNOW LEVELS ARE ABOUT
5,000 FEET, AND WE'LL SEE 3 TO
MAYBE 12 INCHES OF SNOW.
1 TO 2 INCHES OF RAINFALL L.A.
TO SAN DIEGO, AND THAT IS A LOT,
AND ANOTHER STORM COMING ON
CHRISTMAS DAY, WHIT.
>>> I'LL PICK IT UP, ROB.
NOW TO THE LATEST ON THE
IMPEACHMENT.
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI
REFUSING FOR NOW TO SEND THE TWO
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT TO THE
SENATE WHERE THEY WILL HOLD THAT
TRIAL.
SENIOR NATIONAL CORRESPONDENT
TERRY MORAN HAS MORE FROM
CAPITOL HILL.
TERRY, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, TOM.
WASHINGTON IS QUIET RIGHT NOW
WITH CONGRESS OUT OF SESSION UP
HERE ON CAPITOL HILL, AND THE
PRESIDENT IN FLORIDA, BUT DON'T
LET THAT FOOL YOU.
THE BATTLE OVER IMPEACHMENT AS
YOU SAY GRINDS ON WITH THIS NEW
EVIDENCE THAT HAS EMERGED THAT
DEMOCRATS ARE ARGUING THAT THIS
IS JUST ANOTHER REASON THE
SENATE MUST CALL WITNESSES IN
THAT UPCOMING TRIAL OF THE
PRESIDENT.
THIS MORNING, A TROVE OF NEWLY
RELEASED EMAILS ARE SHEDDING
LIGHT ON HOW NEARLY $400 MILLION
WORTH OF SECURITY AID TO UKRAINE
WAS WITHHELD AT THE INSTRUCTION
OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE 146 PAGES OF REDACTED
DOCUMENTS REVEAL THAT JUST 90
MINUTES AFTER THE JULY PHONE
CALL WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP ASKED
UKRAINE'S PRESIDENT ZELENSKY TO,
QUOTE, DO US A FAVOR BY
INVESTIGATING HIS POLITICAL
RIVALS, SENIOR BUDGET OFFICIAL
MICHAEL DUFFEY INSTRUCTED THE
DEFENSE DEPARTMENT TO PLEASE
HOLD OFF ON RELEASING THE FUNDS,
ASKING FOR DISCRETION, DUFFEY
WRITES, GIVEN THE SENSITIVE
NATURE OF THE REQUEST, I
APPRECIATE YOUR KEEPING THAT
INFORMATION CLOSELY HELD.
>> IF THERE WAS EVER AN ARGUMENT
THAT WE NEED MR. DUFFEY TO COME
TESTIFY, THIS IS THAT
INFORMATION.
THIS EMAIL IS EXPLOSIVE.
>> Reporter: THE DOCUMENTS
RELEASED AFTER AN ORDER FROM A
FEDERAL JUDGE ARE RENEWING
DEMOCRATS' CAUSE FOR WITNESSES
TO TESTIFY DURING A SENATE
IMPEACHMENT TRIAL.
SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE NANCY
PELOSI CITING THE UNCERTAINTY
OVER THE NATURE OF THE TRIAL AS
ONE OF HER REASONS FOR
WITHHOLDING THE APPROVED
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT FOR THE
SENATE.
>> WE'RE READY WHEN WE SEE WHAT
THEY HAVE.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
ACCUSING PELOSI OF POLITICAL
MANEUVERING TO GIVE DEMOCRATS
THE UPPER HAND TWEETEDING, CRAZY
NANCY WANTS TO DICTATE TERMS ON
THE IMPEACHMENT HOAX.
THEIR CASE IS DEAD.
>> Reporter: IT'S INTERESTING TO
SEE WHAT NANCY PELOSI HAS OVER
THE SENATE TRIAL.
THEY HAD NO LEVERAGE OVER THE
WAY THE HOUSE CONDUCTED THE
IMPEACHMENT, AND SHE'S TRYING TO
SET THE POLITICAL TERMS.
DEMOCRATS BELIEVE THIS TRIAL
WILL BE UNFAIR.
IT WILL BE A SHOW TRIAL, AND
THEY'RE TRYING TO GET THAT
MESSAGE OUT, BUT THE GENERAL
FEELING IS THESE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT WILL BE TRANSFERRED
EARLY IN THE YEAR.
>> WE'LL SEE HOW THAT PLAYS OUT.
>>> FIVE PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
SENTENCED IN THE DEATH, THE
MURDER OF "WASHINGTON POST"
COLUMNIST JAMAL KHASHOGGI.
IAN PANNELL HAS THE LATEST IN
LO
LONDON.
>> Reporter: FIVE PEOPLE WERE
SENTENCED TO DEATH OF "THE
WASHINGTON POST" COLUMNIST.
HE WAS A WRITER OF THE ROYAL
FAMILY, AND HE WAS MURDERED.
A CIA ASSESSMENT REPORTED THE
FINGER OF BLAME AT THE CROWN
PRINCE, SOMETHING THE SAUDIS
HAVE CONSISTENTLY DENIED.
TRYING TO PORTRAY IT AS A WAY TO
PERSUADE THE WRITER TO RETURN
HOME THAT WENT TERRIBLY WRONG.
IT WAS CONCLUDED THE MURDER WAS
NOT PREMEDITATED, AND TWO HAVE
BEEN FOUND NOT GUILTY AND
RELEASED.
>> WILL THIS DECISION EASE THE
WIDESPREAD CONDEMNATION OF SAUDI
ARABIA?
>> Reporter: WELL, THE SAUDIS
AND THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION MAY
HOPE THIS IS THE END OF THE
AFFAIR, BUT I THINK THE VERDICT
RISKED DOING THE ENTIRE
OPPOSITE.
THEY ARE LIKELY TO REGARD THIS
AS A WHITEWASH.
TWO KEY INDIVIDUALS LEFT OFF.
THE OTHER TWO FOUND GUILTY OF
MANSLAUGHTER, EVEN THOUGH THERE
WAS ONE WHO TOOK A BONE SAW TO
THE MEETING, AND NOT ONE OF THEM
HAS BEEN NAMED.
E
EVA?
>> IAN PANNELL IN LONDON.
THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO RISING TENSIONS WITH
NORTH KOREA WHICH HAS PROMISED
THE U.S. WILL GET A, QUOTE,
CHRISTMAS GIFT DEPENDING ON
PROGRESS IN NUCLEAR TALKS.
THAT COULD BE A MISSILE LAUNCH.
THEY'RE CLOSELY MONITORING ANY
INDICATIONS OF A PROVOCATIVE
MOVE.
SINCE PRESIDENT TRUMP OPENED UP
NEGOTIATIONS WITH KIM JONG-UN 18
MONTHS AGO, NORTH KOREA HAS
CONDUCTED SHORT RANGE, BUT NO
LONG RANGE MISSILE TESTS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION POINTED
TO THAT AS A POSITIVE SIGN.
WHIT?
>>> A SAD MILESTONE IN
AFGHANISTAN.
U.S. OFFICIALS ARE REPORTING
THAT AN AMERICAN SERVICE MEMBER
HAS BEEN KILLED IN ACTION THERE
EARLY THIS MORNING.
THE TALIBAN HAS CLAIMED
RESPONSIBILITY.
THE MILITARY IS NOT SHARING ANY
DETAILS OR LOCATION OF THE
INCIDENT.
THIS DEATH IS THE 20th U.S.
COMBAT DEATH IN AFGHANISTAN IN
2019 MAKING IT THE DEADLIEST
YEAR FOR U.S. TROOPS IN THAT
COUNTRY IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
NOW TO A TRAVEL WARNING WITH A
RECORD NUMBER OF AMERICANS
FLYING FOR THE HOLIDAYS THIS
YEAR, THREE MAJOR AIRPORTS WARE
WARNING OF POSSIBLE MEASLES
EXPOSURE.
ALEX PEREZ IS AT CHICAGO'S
O'HARE.
ALEX, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, TOM.
OFFICIALS HERE AT O'HARE SAY
THEY WERE NOTIFIED OF A
PASSENGER WITH A CONFIRMED CASE
OF MEASLES TRAVELING HERE
THROUGH THE AIRPORT JUST LAST
WEEK, AND NOW AUTHORITIES AT THE
BIG AIRPORTS IN AUSTIN AND
RICHMOND, VIRGINIA ARE ALSO
ALERTING PASSENGERS.
THE RISK OF TRANSMISSION IS
HIGH, AND OFFICIALS ARE NOT ONLY
WORRIED BECAUSE OF THE MANY
OUTBREAKS AROUND THE WORLD, BUT
ALSO BECAUSE IT'S SUCH A BUSY
TRAVEL PERIOD RIGHT NOW.
TOM?
>> SO TRUE, ALEX.
THIS IS VERY CONCERNING.
CAN YOU TELL US ABOUT SOME OF
THE SYMPTOMS AND WHAT SHOULD
PEOPLE DO IF THEY'RE WORRIED
THEY HAVE BEEN EXPOSED?
>> Reporter: IF YOU HAVE BEEN
VACCINATED, IF YOU RECEIVED BOTH
DOSES OF THE VACCINE, YOU'RE
PROTECTED AGAINST THE VIRUS, AND
EVEN IF YOU GOT JUST ONE DOSE,
YOUR RISK IS LOWER, BUT THERE
ARE SOME THINGS THAT YOU CAN
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN FOR,
OFFICIALS SAY, LIKE FEVER A
COUGH, A RUNNY NOSE, RED EYES
AND A RASH WITH RED DOTS.
TOM?
>> ALL RIGHT, ALEX.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR THAT.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
EVA?
>>> NOW TO THAT URGENT MANHUNT
AFTER THE BROTHER OF AN NFL
PLAYER AND ANOTHER MAN WERE
FATALLY STABBED OUTSIDE A
NASHVILLE BAR.
THE KILLING ROCKING THE NFL, AND
POLICE IDENTIFIED ONE OF FOUR
PEOPLE WANTED FOR QUESTIONING.
ADRIENNE BANKERT IS JOINING US
WITH THAT.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
EVERYBODY.
A SAD DAY FOR THE WHOLE TEAM.
TWO FAMILIES AND THE 49ers
MOURNING THE LOSS OF THESE TWO
YOUNG MEN.
THE SEARCH CONTINUES FOR THEIR
KILLER.
THIS MORNING, THE SAN FRANCISCO
49ers ARE RALLYING BEHIND THEIR
QUARTERBACK, C.J. BEATHARD AFTER
HIS BROTHER AND ANOTHER MAN WERE
MURDERED.
NASHVILLE POLICE SAY IT STARTED
OVER UNWANTED ADVANCES OF A
WOMAN.
THEY WERE STABBED AND
TRANSPORTED TO VANDERBILT
MEDICAL CENTER WHERE THEY LATER
DIED.
>> WINS IT AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THE 49ers WON A
THRILLING LAST-MINUTE VICTORY
OVER THE L.A. RAMS, BUT IT
WASN'T UNTIL AFTER THE GAME THAT
COACH KYLE SHANAHAN TOLD THE
TEAM THAT C.J. HAD GIVEN HIM A
MESSAGE TO RELAY TO HIS
TEAMMATES.
>> HE BARELY COULD TALK, AND THE
LAST THING HE SAID TO ME, HE
JUST GOES, MAKE SURE THE GUYS GO
WIN THIS GAME.
THIS GAME DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING
COMPARED TO HIS BROTHER.
EWITH ALL KNOW THAT, BUT YOU
ALSO KNOW C.J.
>> Reporter: FOUR PEOPLE ARE
WANTED FOR QUESTIONING A
23-YEAR-OLD WHO DETECTIVES
IDENTIFIED OVERNIGHT AS SOMEONE
PRESENT IN THIS SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO WITH HOPES THAT WITNESSES
WILL COME FORWARD.
THE BEATHARD FAMILY RELEASED A
STATEMENT TO THE TENNESSEE
NEWSPAPER ABOUT THEIR SON
CLAYTON SAYING, NOBODY'S LIGHT
SHINED LIKE HIS WHEN HE SMILED.
AND THE 49ers SAID THAT C.J. HAS
TAKEN LEAVE TO BE HOME WITH HIS
FAMILY AS THEY GRIEVE.
FOR SOME MEMBERS OF THE TEAM, IT
WAS LIKE THEIR OWN LITTLE
BROTHER DIED.
GEORGE KITTEL HAS KNOWN HIM FOR
ABOUT EIGHT YEARS, AND PLAYED
WITH C.J. IN COLLEGE AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF IOWA AND SAYS THAT
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS ONE OF THE
MOST TERRIBLE DAYS OF HIS
CAREER, HE WAS GLAD THEY COULD
WOMEN IT FOR THE BEATHARD
FAMILY.
>> EMOTIONAL GAME FOR THE TEAM
THIS WEEKEND.
ADRIENNE, THANK YOU.
>>> WE WANT TO TURN TO THAT
SHOCKING MURDER CASE THAT HAS
SHAKEN NEW YORK CITY.
FRIENDS AND FAMILY HOLDING A
MEMORIAL SERVICE THIS WEEKEND
FOR MURDERED COLLEGE STUDENT
TESSA MAJORS AS POLICE HUNT FOR
A 14-YEAR-OLD BOY IN CONNECTION
WITH THE CASE.
TREVOR AULT JOINS US WITH THE
VERY LATEST ON THAT STORY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
THIS IS A HORRIFYING CASE THAT'S
ONLY MADE MORE DISTURBING BY THE
FACT THAT POLICE SAY TEENAGERS
ARE LIKELY RESPONSIBLE AND
THEY'RE NOT TAKING A RARE STEP
HERE.
THEY'RE RELEASING A PHOTO OF ONE
OF THOSE UNDERAGED TEENS THEY
BELIEVE IS CONNECTED WITH THE
CASE.
THIS MORNING, THE URGENT SEARCH
FOR THEIR 14-YEAR-OLD, WANTED IN
CONNECTION WITH THE HEINOUS
KILLING OF BARNARD COLLEGE
FRESHMAN TESSA MAJORS.
>> IT'S ALL HANDS ON DECK.
>> Reporter: THE NYPD ASKING FOR
HELP TRACKING HIM DOWN.
HIS NAME NOT RELEASED BECAUSE
HE'S A MINOR.
THIS COMES AFTER MORE THAN A
THOUSAND FRIENDS AND FAMILY
GATHERED FOR AN EMOTIONAL
FAREWELL TO THE 18-YEAR-OLD IN
HER HOMETOWN OF CHARLOTTESVILLE,
VIRGINIA.
IN NEW YORK CITY, INVESTIGATORS
STILL SEARCHING FOR ANSWERS,
COMBING THROUGH SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO MORE THAN A WEEK AFTER THE
FATAL STABBING.
>> WE HAD OUR POLICE OFFICERS
FROM THOSE ADJOINING PRECINCTS
AS WELL TO MAKE SURE THE PEOPLE
IN THAT NEIGHBORHOOD, CERTAINLY
THROUGHOUT THE CITY IN VARIOUS
PARKS CONTINUE TO FEEL SAFE.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER JUVENILE,
13 YEARS OLD, FACING MULTIPLE
FELONY CHARGES APPARENTLY
IMPLICATING HIMSELF AND TWO
OTHER TEENS FROM HIS MIDDLE
SCHOOL IN THE ROBBERY AND BRUTAL
MURDER.
>> IT SHOULD DISTURB ANY NEW
YORKER WHEN WE HAVE A CHILD
INVOLVED IN SOMETHING THIS
SERIOUS.
>> Reporter: THE PERIMETER OF
THE PARK JUST ONE BLOCK FROM
MAJORS' SCHOOL TURNED CRIME
SCENE NOW SWARMED BY ADDITIONAL
OFFICERS AND CAMPUS SECURITY.
POLICE HAVE ALREADY QUESTIONED A
DIFFERENT 14-YEAR-OLD IN THIS
CASE, BUT HE DIDN'T GIVE ANY
STATEMENTS AND HE WAS RELEASED
WITHOUT BEING CHARGED AND
THROUGH ALL OF THIS, THE NYPD
HAS BEEN ADAMANT WHEN
INTERROGATING THESE TEENAGERS,
THEY HAVE A GUARDIAN OR ATTORNEY
OR BOTH OF THEM PRESENT.
>> SUCH AN UPSETTING CASE.
TREVOR, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE SPACE RACE AND
THE PERFECT ENDING TO A FAILED
MISSION.
THE STARLINER STICKING THE
LANDING IN THE NEW MEXICO DESERT
AFTER THE TRIP TO THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION HAD
TO BE CALLED OFF, BUT YOU CAN
SEE RIGHT THERE.
PERFECT LANDING.
NOT TOO BAD.
>>> WELL, NOW TO THE CHRISTMAS
CRUNCH.
JUST TWO SHOPPING DAYS LEFT, AND
LESS THAN THAT IF YOU ARE
SHIPPING THE GIFTS.
GIO BENITEZ JOINS US WITH SOME
DEALS AND SOME ADVICE ON THAT
WHOLE SHIPPING SITUATION.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, GIO.
>> Reporter: HEY, EVA.
GOOD MORNING.
YEAH, ADMITTEDLY, YOU'RE CUTTING
IT A LITTLE TOO CLOSE, BUT IT'S
NOT TOO LATE JUST YET.
YOU HAVE OPTIONS OUT THERE FOR
THAT LAST-MINUTE SHOPPING.
LET'S SHOW YOU WHAT SOME OF THE
OPTIONS ARE RIGHT NOW BECAUSE
SOME STORES LIKE KOHL'S ARE
STAYING OPEN FOR 24:00 HOURS
UNTIL 6:00 P.M. TOMORROW
CHRIS
CHRISTMAS EVE, SO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE CHECKING THE STORE TIMES
AND THERE ARE REALLY GOOD DEALS
OUT THERE.
GOOGLE HOME DEVICES ARE 50% OFF.
ECHO DEVICES ARE UP TO 50% OFF.
KINDLES, 23% OFF.
THIS IS THE LAST CHANCE TO GET
NEXT-DAY DELIVERY BY TOMORROW,
BUT A NUMBER OF LARGE RETAILERS
LIKE TARGET AND AMAZON PRIME ARE
OFFERING SAME-DAY DELIVERY
THROUGH TOMORROW.
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET FREE
TWO-HOUR DELIVERY IN SOME CITIES
THROUGH APPLE AND AMAZON WHO
ALSO HAS PRIME NOW.
YOU NEED A SEPARATE APP NEEDING
TO DOWNLOAD FOR THAT.
GIFT CARDS ARE ALWAYS GREAT.
YOU CAN GET THOSE DIGITALLY ANY
TIME.
BACK TO YOU.
>> HOPEFULLY YOU PICKED UP A
COUPLE FOR US.
>>> WE ARE FOLLOWING A LOT OF
OTHER STORIES THIS MORNING
INCLUDING THE TRAGIC END TO THAT
MISSING MOM MYSTERY IN TEXAS.
THE WOMAN FOUND DEAD.
HER CLOSE FRIEND IS NOW IN
CUSTODY.
SO MANY QUESTIONS IN THIS CASE.
THE VERY LATEST IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
>>> AND THAT HERO POLICE OFFICER
WHO SAVED A GROUP OF SCHOOL KIDS
FROM A RUNAWAY SUV.
HE TELLS US HOW HE DID IT.
THAT'S COMING UP.
>>> FIRST, BACK TO ROB.
THERE'S A CHRISTMAS THAW ON THE
WAY.
>> THERE IS, AT LEAST FOR NOW,
AND THAT THAW CREATED SOME
PROBLEMS.
WE SAW THE ICE AND FOG WHEN YOU
GET THAT WARM AIR COMING OVER
ICY, SNOWY CONDITIONS.
YOU GET FOG, BUT YOU ALSO GET
ICE THAT'S FALLING OVER
WATERFALLS LIKE THIS SPOT IN NEW
YORK JUST OUTSIDE OF ROCHESTER.
CLOSE TO THE FINGER LAKES AND
YOU GET THOSE LANDSCAPES THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
THIS IS KIND OF WEIRD, AND I
HEAR THERE'S A NEW LENS THAT THE
GOPRO THAT'S 360, AND YOU'RE
SEEING A 360 LENS AND THIS FISH
EYE GLOBAL VIEW.
IN VIRGINIA WHERE THEY HAVE SOME
ARTIFICIAL SNOW TO HELP YOU GET
THROUGH THE HOLIDAYS BECAUSE THE
TEMPERATURES WILL BE 40s, 50s
AND 60s.
CHICAGO, HIGH TEMPERATURE ON
CHRISTMAS DAY OF ABOUT 50
DEGREES TO MAKE IT WARMER THAN
THIS PAST THANKSGIVING AND
HALLOWEEN.
SPOOKY.
TIME NOW FOR YOUR SELECT CITIES
BROUGHT TO YOU BY WALMART.
SUNDAY.
>> Veronica: TRAVELING LOCALLY,
OUR WEATHER IS GOING TO BE
QUIET.
TODAY AND ALL WEEK LONG.
THE ONLY STORM SYSTEM FOR THE
EASTERN HALF OF THE COUNTRY,
THIS ONE.
IT'S GOING TO HANG OUT DOWN
ACROSS AREAS AROUND FLORIDA,
AROUND THE CAROLINAS BEFORE
FINALLY PUSHING OFF THE COAST
EARLY TOMORROW.
AROUND HERE, WE'RE PARTLY SUNNY.
THE HIGH 502 YOUR DAY TOMORROW,
CHRISTMAS EVE, UP TO 50 DEGREES.
FEELING MORE LIKE FALL VERSUS
WINTER.
NEXT BIG WEATHER MAKER DOESN'T
MAKE IT'S WAY INTO OUR AREA
UNTIL THE SECOND HALF OF THE
WEEKEND.
HIGH TEMPERATURE O
>>> HAVE YOU GUYS FINISHED YOUR
CHRISTMAS SHOPPING?
>> OH, DONE.
>> A COUPLE OF GIFTS LEFT.
>> STAY WITH US.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
What's going on?
I got you something.
Oh wow!
Did you get these at Pier 1?
I did.
I got you...
I got you a car.
I mean, look ...
Get up to 40% off all
Christmas now at Pier 1.
Mom, did you see the acorn?
(Click)
♪ I promise that you'll
never find another ♪
♪ Like me-ee-ee ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ I'm the only one of me ♪
♪ Baby, that's the fun of me ♪
♪ Eeh-eeh-eeh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
It's Taylor Swift!
With the Capital One
Savor card
you earn 4%
cash back on dining
and 4% on entertainment.
So when you go out,
you cash in.
What's in your wallet?
So when you go out,
you cash in.
♪ ♪
Leave no man behind.
Or child.
Or other child.
Or their new friend.
Or your giant nephews
and their giant dad.
Or a horse.
Or a horse's brother,
for that matter.
The room for eight,
9,000 lb towing Ford Expedition.
Wrap up your holiday shopping
with the Blitz In,Blitz Out Sale
at JCPenney!
For 5 days only
shop Nike and adidas.
Keurig and NutriBullet.
and up to
80% off jewelry.
Or take an extra 20% off with
your JCPenney Credit Card
JCPenney!
NyQuil Severe gives you powerful
relief
for your worst cold and
flu symptoms,
on Sunday Night and every night.
NyQuil Severe.
The Nightime, Sniffling,
Sneezing,
Coughing, Aching, Stuffy Head,
Best Sleep with a Cold,
Medicine.
♪
Slow laptop?
Shhhh.
[whispering] How about
one that boots up fast?
It's switching time.
♪
How's that for fast?
Switch to booting up
as fast as six seconds.
Switch to Chromebook.
We have some big news...
No!
Yes!
Girl, No!
You got this from Pier 1?
And this?
Get up to 40% off all
Christmas now at Pier 1.
Congratulations on these.
I like that.
♪
Everything your trip needs,
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
"GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON" FINAL
DAYS OF HOLIDAY TRAVEL RUSH, I
AM JESSOB REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
7 ON YOUR SIDE KEEPING A CLOSE
EYE ON THE FLIGHTS,
TRANSPORTATION REPORTER SAM
SWEENEY LIVE AT REAGAN NATIONAL
THIS MORNING.
DOWN IN SOUTH FLORIDA, MOST OF
THE FLIGHTS ON TIME.
VERY FEW CANCELLATIONS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
LET'S LOOK AT THE MAP AND SHOW
YOU WHAT IS SHOWING, 100 MILLION
PEOPLE TRAVELING FOR THIS
CHRISTMAS SEASON.
BUSIEST DAY ON THE ROADS,
DECEMBER 26TH D A A A A AFTER
>> EILEEN: AT 7:26, DENSER ALONG
THE BAY BRIDGE, TEMPERATURES
BELOW FREEZING, IF I COULD GET
MY CLICKER TO WORK.
TEMPERATURES CLIMB INTO THE 50S
LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU CAN FIND OUT MORE
INFORMATION ON WJLA.COM.
BOBBIE LORI.
>> FOG NORTHBOUND 395, EILEEN,
ROUTE 110 OVER TO THE 14TH
STREET BRIDGE.
AVERAGE SPEED OF 13 MILES AN
HOUR.
WHAT YOU ARE SEEING IS A
DISABLED VEHICLE OFF THE
ROADWAY.
PRETTY SLOW, 13 MILES AN HOUR.
AS WE -- ADRIANNA, OVER TO YOU.
>> ADRIANNA: GET
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> JESSOB:
AMERICA" BACK IN TWO MINUTES ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS FOR THE LATEST LOCAL NEWS
ON "GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON."
Congrats, Kim!
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Did you trade it in?
My parents handed it down
to my little brother.
- You Ready?
- Yea.
Surprise!
No. Not Beige Betty!
You guys can't do this
to me, seriously!?
That car is like
a rite of passage.
How do you expect me
to drive this?
Just turn the key...and yea,
it's just uh, automatic,
dual cupholders.
Go with the one that's here
to help life go right.
State Farm.
Get to Kohl's...
And take an extra 15 or 20% off!
to help life go right.
Plus - save even more right now
on last minute gifts!...
Save on fine jewelry sets...
The Xbox One S...
And on celebrity fragrance gift
sets.
Plus - get Kohl's Cash!...
Plus - buy online, two hour
store pickup!...
Plus - stores are now open 24
hours!
Kohl's
Once a year,
cats come together
to compete for the
chance of a new life.
You should be on
the World Stage.
Yes.
- Yeah!
I'm a magic cat.
Now it is time to
make the choice.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
♪♪
JCPenney. Remember the little
things.
♪
>> CHEWY!
>> YOU DIDN'T SAY MY NAME, BUT
I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> NOTHING CAN PREPARE YOU FOR
THE END.
>> OH, THE DRAMA.
WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
"STAR WARS: THE RISE OF
SKYWALKER," RISING TO THE TOP OF
THE BOX OFFICE OVER THE WEEKEND.
THE BLOCKBUSTER END TO
SKYWALKER'S SAGA TAKING IN A
WHOPPING $176 MILLION, AND
$400 MILLION GLOBALLY.
I SAW IT WITH MY DAUGHTER, LOVED
IT.
IT'S INTENSE THOUGH, LIKE, HIGH
SPEED, RAPID FIRE, LIKE, THE
PACING, YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
>> DID YOU FEEL THE FORCE?
>> I FELT THE FORCE.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
>>> WE'LL HAVE MUCH MORE AHEAD,
BUT FIRST, THE TOP HEADLINES.
WILD WEATHER FROM COAST TO COAST
COULD MAKE YOUR HOLIDAY TRAVEL A
MESS.
CAUSING A MAJOR AIRPORT TO CLOSE
DOWN, AND LOOK AT THIS PILEUP IN
VIRGINIA.
NEARLY 70 CARS INVOLVED.
WE'RE TRACKING IT ALL THIS
NORTHERN.
>>> THE VOLCANO ERUPTION HAS
TAKEN THE LIFE OF ANOTHER
AMERICAN.
MARY SINGH FROM AMERICA, AND HER
HUSBAND PAUL WERE SIGHTSEEING ON
THE ISLAND.
PAUL IS IN THE HOSPITAL, AND
MARY IS THE 19th PERSON TO DIE
FROM THAT ERUPTION.
>>> AND THE LIGHTING OF THE
NATIONAL MENORAH IN FRONT OF THE
WHITE HOUSE ON SUNDAY MARKING
THE START OF HANUKKAH.
WISHING HAPPY HOLIDAYS TO JEWISH
PEOPLE IN THE U.S., ISRAEL AND
ACROSS THE WORLD.
>>> FIRST, THAT STUNNING TWIST
IN THE CASE OF THE MISSING TEXAS
MOTHER WHO VANISHED WITH HER
NEWBORN.
NOW HEIDI BROUSSARD HAS BEEN
FOUND DEAD AND A BABY GIRL
BELIEVED TO BE HER DAUGHTER IS
SAFE.
A CLOSE FRIEND IS NOW BEHIND
BARS FACING CHARGES RELATING TO
THAT YOUNG MOTHER'S MURDER.
KAYLEE HARTUNG IS IN AUSTIN WITH
MUCH MORE.
KAYLEE, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, TOM.
IN THE DAYS SINCE MEGYN
FIERAMUSCA'S ARREST, WE CONTINUE
TO LEARN JUST HOW SHOCKING THIS
NEWS IS TO HEIDI BROUSSARD'S
FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
THESE TWO WOMEN FORWERE THE CLOT
OF FRIENDS FFR 20 YEARS.
NO MURDER CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED IN THIS CASE.
AT THIS TIME, FIERAMUSCA IS THE
ONLY PERSON IN CUSTODY IN
RELATION TO THE DISAPPEARANCE OF
HEIDI BROUSSARD AND HER NEWBORN
BABY.
POLICE SAY 33-YEAR-OLD HEIDI
BROUSSARD WAS STRANGLED TO
DEATH.
HER 3-WEEK-OLD BABY FOUND INSIDE
THE HOME OF HER FRIEND MAGEN
FIERAMUSCA.
CARESSA NOLTE WHO SAYS SHE'S A
FRIEND OF BOTH WOMEN TALKS ABOUT
IT ON A PODCAST AS POLICES ZEROD
IN.
>> THAT'S MAGEN'S HOUSE.
OH MY GOD.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT'S HER BEST BEST FRIEND.
SHE WOULD NOT BE THERE.
SHE HAS BEEN, LIKE, SICK OVER
THIS.
>> Reporter: SHE SAID SHE HAD
GIVEN BIRTH TO A BABY GIRL, BUT
HAD NEVER SEEN ANY PHOTOS OF THE
CHILD.
>> WHAT?
>> SHE HAD A BABY?
>> YES.
>> HOW LONG AGO?
>> SHE'S 15 DAYS OLD, 16 DAYS
TOED.
HER AND HEIDI ARE BEST, BEST
FRIENDS.
>> DID YOU SEE HER BABY?
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN PICTURES OF
HER.
>> Reporter: POLICE TELL ABC
NEWS THEY'RE INVESTIGATING
WHETHER OR NOT FIERAMUSCA WAS
ACTUALLY PREGNANT OR IF SHE
PLANNED TO SNATCH BABY MARGOT
ALL ALONG.
SHE CREATED THESE BABY
REGISTRIES, ASKING FOR ITEMS
LIKE HATS AND BLANKETS.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW SINCERE
SHE SOUNDED.
>> Reporter: TIM MILLER, ONE OF
THE SEARCHERS ON THE CASE NEVER
SUSPECTED SHE WAS INVOLVED IN
BROUSSARD'S DISAPPEARANCE.
>> I WAS JUST KIND OF SCRATCHING
MY HEAD TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW
IN THE WORLD COULD THIS PERSON
SOUND SO CONVINCING.
>> Reporter: BROUSSARD'S MOTHER
TELLING ABC NEWS, THE FAMILY IS
OVERWHELMED WITH GRIEF.
WITH CHRISTMAS COMING UP, THEIR
FOCUS IS ON SPENDING TIME WITH
HEIDI'S 6-YEAR-OLD SON WHO HAS
NOW LOST HIS MOTHER.
>> I LOVE YOU, HEIDI.
>> MISS YOU FOREVER.
>> Reporter: OVERNIGHT, FRIENDS
AND FAMILY OF HEIDI BROUSSARD
RELEASING BALLOONS INTO THE SKY
AT A VIGIL SAYING GOOD-BYE.
>> SHE WAS SO FRIENDLY.
SHE WAS VERY ADVENTUROUS.
SHE LOVED TRYING NEW THINGS.
I'M REALLY GOING TO MISS HER
VOICE.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER VIGIL IS
PLANNED TONIGHT HERE IN HOUSTON
AS HEIDI'S FAMILY AND FRIENDS
STRUGGLE WITH THIS.
THAT BABY BELIEVED TO BE HEIDI'S
IS IN THE CARE OF CHILD
PROTECTIVE SERVICES.
THEY HOPE TO HAVE THE RESULTS
BACK TODAY TO CONFIRM THAT
BABY'S IDENTIFY.
EVA?
>> THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE AMAZING HERO,
THAT OFFICER RUSHING TO STOP A
RUNAWAY SUV WITH NO DRIVER AS IT
HEADS FOR A GROUP OF SCHOOL
CHILDREN.
THE OFFICER USIING ALL OF HIS
STRENGTH TO PULL THE VEHICLE TO
A STOP.
HE'S TALKING ABOUT IT THIS
MORNING.
LINSEY DAVIS IS HERE WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, LINSEY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
IT'S A BIRD, IT'S A PLANE.
IT'S A BRIDGEPORT, CONNECTICUT
POLICE OFFICER.
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE WORK OF A
SUPERHERO, CHASING DOWN AN SUV
AND BRINGING IT TO A STOP AS IT
SLIPPED OUT OF PARK AND ROLLED
DOWNHILL INTO TRAFFIC WITHOUT A
DRIVER BEHIND THE WHEEL.
THIS MORNING, A POLICE OFFICER
FROM CONNECTICUT IS BEING HAILED
A HERO AFTER SINGLEHANDEDLY
STOPPING A MOVING SUV FROM
COLLIDING WITH A GROUP OF
TEENAGERS WHO WERE WALKING HOME
AFTER THEIR SCHOOL'S DISMISSAL.
CARLOS CARMO JR. NOTICES THE
DRIVERLESS CAR WITH TWO PEOPLE
STILL INSIDE AND SPRINTS TOWARD
THE MOVING VEHICLE.
YOU CAN SEE HIM MOVE TOWARD THE
MOVING TRUCK, AND THAT BRAVE
OFFICER SPOKE EXCLUSIVELY TO ABC
NEWS ABOUT THE HARROWING
INCIDENT.
>> I WAS JUST THINKING IN MY
MIND JUST, I GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO STOP THIS.
>> Reporter: WATCH AGAIN.
YOU CAN SEE DOZENS OF YOUNG
PEOPLE ON THE SIDEWALK UNAWARE
THEY WERE IN HARM'S WAY.
>> THE KIDS ACTUALLY THEY
BASICALLY -- THEY ALL HAD
HEADPHONES ON, AND I WAS
SCREAMING AT THEM.
THEY BASICALLY DIDN'T EVEN HEAR
ME.
I DON'T THINK THEY KNEW WHAT WAS
GOING ON UNTIL IT WAS OVER, BUT
THE PEOPLE IN THE CAR AS I WAS
HOLDING IT TRYING TO STOP IT,
THEY WERE FREAKING OUT A LITTLE
BIT.
>> Reporter: HE SAID IT WAS
ADRENALINE, INSTINCT AND DUTY.
>> WE GO THROUGH A LOT OF
SCENARIOS, BUT THAT'S NOT A
SCENARIO THEY TEACH US IN THE
ACADEMY.
THAT'S WHERE YOUR INSTINCT KICKS
IN, AND YOU DO WHAT YOU GOT TO
DO TO KEEP THESE KIDS SAFE.
>> HE SUSTAINED MINOR INJURIES
AND HE WAS TREATED AT THE
HOSPITAL.
THE MAYOR SAYS HE WILL BE
HONORED FOR HIS BRAVERY AND
QUICK THINKING IN A SITUATION
THAT COULD HAVE ENDED ENTIRELY
DIFFERENTLY HAD HE NOT
INTERVENED.
H
CAN YOU IMAGINE BEING IN THE
BACKSEAT IN THIS RUNAWAY CAR?
>> TOM WAS DOING PUSH-UPS.
>> I WAS DOING SOME CURLS JUST
IN CASE THAT HAPPENS.
>> THE OFFICER LOOKS LIKE HE
WORKS OUT.
>> YES.
>> WE ARE SALUTING THAT OFFICER.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HIS BRAVERY.
THANK YOU, LINSEY.
APPRECIATE IT.
>>> WE WANT TO TURN NOW TO
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" AND THE
RETURN THAT EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ABOUT.
EDDIE MURPHY, BACK WHERE HE
STARTED BRINGING BACK SOME OF
THE CHARACTERS THAT HELPED MAKE
HIM A STAR AND GETTING RAVE
REVIEWS AS WELL.
KENNETH MOTON IS HERE WITH THAT
STORY.
KENNETH, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, WHIT.
PEOPLE PLAN THEIR WHOLE SATURDAY
NIGHT AROUND THIS ONE.
I DID.
EDDIE'S BIG RETURN TO "SNL,"
THERE WAS A LOT OF HYPE, AND THE
EDGY LEGENDARY ACTOR AND
COMEDIAN DID NOT DISAPPOINT
BRINGING THE LAUGHS AND THE
HIGHEST RATINGS THIS SHOW HAS
SEEN IN 2 1/2 YEARS.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, EDDIE
MURPHY.
>> Reporter: AFTER 35 YEARS
EDDIE MURPHY RETURNED TO THE
"SNL" STAGE AS HOST RECEIVING A
STANDING OVATION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND WHILE HE MAY BE OLDER, HIS
JOKES, SHARPER THAN EVER.
>> I HAVE TEN KIDS NOW.
11 IF YOU COUNT KEVIN HART.
>> Reporter: THE "SNL" LEGEND
UPDATING HIS ICONIC CHARACTERS
FOR THE MODERN AUDIENCE.
♪ IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD ♪
>> Reporter: BRINGING BACK
CLASSIC SKETCHES LIKE MR.
ROBINSON'S NEIGHBORHOOD.
TAKING ON ISSUES LIKE RACE AND
GENTRIFICATION HEAD-ON.
>> DON'T WORRY, BOYS AND GIRLS.
MR. ROBINSON KNOWS JUST WHAT TO
SAY IN SITUATIONS LIKE THIS.
OH, YOU THINK I STOLE YOUR TV
BECAUSE I'M BLACK?
>> NO.
>> IT ALWAYS WORKS, BOYS AND
GIRLS.
>> Reporter: ALSO IN THE
SPOTLIGHT, FAN FAVORITES LIKE
HIS WILDLY POPULAR VERSION OF
BUCKWHEAT FROM "THE LITTLE
RASCALS."
♪
AND HIS ANGRY, FOUL-MOUTHED
VERSION OF GUMBY.
>> I AM GUMBY.
I WANT TO SMOKE A CIGAR, I SMOKE
A CIGAR.
>> Reporter: HIS RETURN
DELIVERING RECORD RATINGS AND AN
EDGE TO THE STUDIO.
EVEN TAKING A SHOT AT BILL COSBY
WHO APPARENTLY YEARS AGO SAID
MURPHY WAS A BAD INFLUENCE.
>> IF YOU WOULD HAVE TOLD ME 30
YEARS AGO THAT I WOULD BE THIS
BORING, STAY-AT-HOME, YOU KNOW,
HOUSE DAD AND BILL COSBY WOULD
BE IN JAIL --
[ LAUGHTER ]
-- EVEN I WOULD HAVE TOOK THAT
BET.
SAY.
WHO IS AMERICA'S DAD NOW?
>> Reporter: THROUGHOUT HIS
CAREER, MURPHY HAS HELPED
SHEPARD OTHER UP AND COMING
COMEDIANS WITH THREE OF THE MOST
FAMOUS JOINING HIM ON STAGE FOR
HIS BIG NIGHT.
>> WHAT WAS THE LAST TIME WE WAS
TOGETHER LIKE THIS?
>> LAST THURSDAY AT SINBAD'S.
>> Reporter: NOT EVERYBODY WAS
LAUGHING.
COSBY WHO IS SERVING TIME FOR
SEXUAL ASSAULT SHOT BACK SAYING,
IT'S SAD MURPHY WOULD MAKE
DISPARAGING REMARKS AGAINST A
MAN WHO BROKE COLOR BARRIERS IN
THE ENTERTAINMENT INDUSTRY.
I CAN TELL YOU THE FOCUS IS ON
THE HILARIOUS SKITS, THE GUEST
STARS AND ALSO MURPHY WHO
REPORTEDLY HADN'T BEEN ON THE
SHOW FOR YEARS BECAUSE OF AN OLD
FEUD WITH A FORMER CAST MEMBER.
>> AND THE RATINGS DELIVERED AS
WELL.
>> IT SURE DID.
>> EVERYTHING WAS FUNNY.
HE WAS HYSTERICAL IN EVERY
SINGLE SKETCH.
>> I WAS DO MY FAVORITE
BUCKWHEAT IMITATION FOR YOU, BUT
I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD BE
GOOD.
>> WE GOT TO GO TO BREAK.
>> WE'LL SAVE YOU HERE, KENNETH.
>>> COMING UP, WHY THE DIRECTOR
OF "CATS" IS TRYING TO CHANGE
RUTAL
REVIEWS.
♪
Mornings were made
for better things
than rheumatoid arthritis
or psoriatic arthritis.
When considering
another treatment,
ask about XELJANZ XR,
a once-daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis or
active psoriatic arthritis
for whom methotrexate did
not work well enough.
It can reduce pain,
swelling,
and significantly improve
physical function.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections like TB;
don't start XELJANZ if
you have an infection.
Taking a higher than
recommended dose of
XELJANZ for RA can increase
risk of death.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections,
cancers including lymphoma,
and blood clots have happened.
As have tears in the
stomach or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
and changes in lab results.
Tell your doctor if you've
been somewhere
fungal infections
are common,
or if you've had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone
to infections.
Don't let another
morning go by
without asking your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
♪
Nothing shines brighter
than you.
You are my diamond.
For the diamond
in your life,
get up to 40% off
storewide
or get these one of
a kind deals
at the “You
Are My Diamond” Event.
Exclusively at Zales,
the Diamond Store.
♪ Work so hard ♪he “You
♪ Give it everything you got ♪
♪ Strength of a lioness ♪
♪ Tough as a knot ♪
♪ Rocking the stage ♪
♪ And we never gonna stop ♪
♪ All strength, no sweat. ♪
♪ Just in case you forgot ♪
♪ All strength. ♪
♪ No sweat ♪♪
Secret. All strength. No sweat.
SFX: [sneezing]
I am not for ignoring
the first sign of a cold.
I am for shortening my cold,
with Zicam!
Zicam is
completely different.
Unlike most other
cold medicines,
Zicam is clinically proven to
shorten colds.
I am a ZiFan for Zicam!
Oral or Nasal.
Don't judge Miss Mongols.
♪♪
You ain't seen nothing.
You try baking a pie.
>>> BACK NOW WITH A NEW LIFE
FOR "CATS."
THE DIRECTOR MAKING SOME
LAST-MINUTE CHANGES TO THE MOVIE
AFTER IT LANDED IN THEATERS WITH
A THUD.
WILL REEVE IS HERE WITH MORE ON
THAT.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, WILL.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
CATASTROPHIC.
I'LL STOP THE PUNS, BUT THAT
WON'T CHANGE THE BOTTOM LINE.
CRITICS' CLAWS ARE OUT F
FOR "CATS."
IT FLOPPED AT THE BOX OFFICE.
WHAT HAS CHANGED THOUGH IS THE
MOVIE ITSELF.
DIRECTOR TOM HOOPER SENDING
THEATERS A NEW VERSION WITH
SUPPOSEDLY BETTER VISUAL
EFFECTS.
IT'S AN UNPRECEDENTED MOVE.
♪ SO EASY TO LEAVE ME ♪
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, HOW
MANY LIVES DOES "CATS" HAVE?
THE STUFF OF NIGHTMARES.
>> I FELT LIKE A PARASITE WAS
EATING MY BRAIN WHILE I WAS
WATCHING THIS MOVIE.
>> Reporter: AFTER A BATCH OF
SCATHING REVIEWS OF THE
ADAPTATION BRINGING IT TO THE
LITTER BOX BEFORE IT EVEN
OPENED, UNIVERSAL STUDIOS OPENED
THOUSANDS OF THEATERS NATIONWIDE
IT WOULD BE SENDING NEW VERSIONS
OF THE MOVIE WITH SOME IMPROVED
VISUAL EFFECTS.
IT'S A MOVE INSIDERS SAY IS
UNHEARD OF.
>> MORE OFTEN THAN NOT, A MOVIE
IS COMPLETE WEEKS, IF NOT,
MONTHS BEFORE.
IT'S VERY RARE THAT A MOVIE
WOULD BE REISSUED TO THEATERS
DURING OPENING WEEKEND.
>> Reporter: THEY SPENT CLOSE TO
$100 MILLION ON THE BUDGET.
DIRECTOR TOM HOOPER ADMITTING
THAT HE HAD TO RACE TO FINISH
THE MOVIE BY ITS RELEASE DATE.
THE FINISHED PRODUCT WAS MET
WITH AGGRESSIVELY BAD REVIEWS.
ONE CRITIC CALLING "CATS,"
QUOTE, A SINISTER ALL-TIME
DISASTER FROM WHICH NO ONE
EMERGES UNSCATHED.
ANOTHER ONE WRITING AB
ABOUT "CATS," STATISTICALLY IT'S
A HAIRBALL.
THE DRAW OF STARS LIKE TAYLOR
SWIFT, IDRIS ELBA AND JUDI DENCH
NOT CATNIP FOR AUDIENCES.
THOSE BAD REVIEWS ADDING UP TO
JUST AN 18% RATING ON ROTTEN
TOMATOES.
JASON DERUE DOE TELLS TMZ THIS
MESSAGE, TO ALL THE HATERS.
>> IT DON'T MATTER.
IT DON'T MATTER.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO GO SEE IT.
>> Reporter: THE ANDREW LLOYD
WEBER MUSICAL GROSSED
$400 MILLION WORLDWIDE.
IT'S THE FIRST MUSICAL TO SELL
MERCHANDISE.
I THINK MOVIE THEATERS SHOULD
SELL I SAW "CATS" T-SHIRTS ON
THE WAY OUT AS A COLLECTOR'S
ITEM.
>> WHILE IT DOESN'T MATTER TO
DE
DERULO, THE MONEY DOES MATTER.
>> THEY NEED THAT BUMGT.
>> AND IT'S AFTER THE MOVIE CAME
OUT.
>> NEVER HAPPENS.
>> COMboINs up
as fast as 6 seconds
when you're running late?
Shhhh.
[whispering]
It's switching time.
♪
How about a battery that
lasts up to 12 hours?
[bell rings]
Order up!
♪
Now we're cooking.
Or how about one with
virus protection built in?
Which...
would be helpful...
right...
about...
now...
Yeah, if you want all that,
switch to Chromebook.
♪
[Baby crying]
Pampers is the first and only
diaper with Air Dry Channels
they stay up to 3 times drier,
so babies can sleep
soundly...all night.
Pampers.
[Sneezing]
♪♪
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
♪ 24 KARAT MAGIC IN THE AIR ♪
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW WITH OUR
"PLAY OF THE DAY," AND CHRISTMAS
CAME EARLY FOR ONE YOUNG
BASKETBALL FAN.
ANTETOKOUNMPO, THEY CALL HIM.
ALL IN THE SPIRIT OF GIVING FANS
WEARING HIS NUMBER HIS SIGNATURE
GAME SNEERKS AFTER THE GAME ON
SUNDAY.
LOOK AT THAT, THE REACTION
PRICELESS.
SAYS IT ALL RIGHT THERE.
A GOOD DAY TO BE A BUCKS FAN.
THE TEAM BEAT THE INDIANA PACERS
117-89.
>> I DIDN'T CATCH THE PLAYER'S
NAME.
WHAT WAS THAT AGAIN?
>> ANTETOKOUNMPO.
>> OH, GOOD JOB, WHIT.
>>> COMING UP, HOW TO LOWER YOUR
RISK AS WE GATHER WITH FRIENDS
AND FAMILY FOR THE HOLIDAYS.te
to severe psoriasis
or psoriatic arthritis,
little things
can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
differently.
For psoriasis, 75%
clearer skin is achievable,
with reduced redness,
thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis,
Otezla is proven to reduce
joint swelling,
tenderness, and pain.
And the Otezla
Prescribing Information
has no requirement
for routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic
to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have
a history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor
your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory
tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor
about your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat
differently with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
Get to Kohl's...
And take an extra 15 or 20% off!
Plus - save even more right now
on last minute gifts!...
Save on fine jewelry sets...
The Xbox One S...
And on celebrity fragrance gift
sets.
Plus - get Kohl's Cash!...
Plus - buy online, two hour
store pickup!...
Plus - stores are now open 24
hours!
Kohl's
I'm Christina Stembel
and I chose the Spark cash
card from Capital One
With unlimited 2% cash
back on everything I buy
Why wouldn't I get this card?!
I redeemed $115,000
in cash back,
which doubled our marketing
budget last summer.
What's in your wallet?
LET'S BE HONEST,
QUITTING SMOKING
IS FREAKING HARD.
LIKE QUITTING
EVERY MONDAY HARD.
QUITTING FEELS SO BIG.
SO, TRY MAKING IT SMALLER.
AND YOU'LL BE SURPRISED AT
HOW EASILY STARTING SMALL...
...CAN LEAD TO SOMETHING BIG.
START STOPPING
WITH NICORETTE
Wrap up your holiday shopping
with the Blitz In,Blitz Out Sale
at JCPenney!
For 5 days only
shop Nike and adidas.
Keurig and NutriBullet.
and up to
80% off jewelry.
Or take an extra 20% off with
your JCPenney Credit Card
JCPenney!
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
I'm your Mother in Law.
And I like to question your
every move.
Like this left turn.
It's the next one.
You always drive this slow?
How did you make someone I love?
That must be why you're always
so late.
I do not speed.
And that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
My son, he did say that you were
the safe option.
And that's the nicest thing you
ever said to me.
So get Allstate.
Stop bossing.
Where good drivers save 40% for
avoiding mayhem, like me.
This is my son's favorite color,
you should try it.
[Mayhem] You always drive like
an old lady?
[Tina] You're an old lady.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
TIME FOR YOUR "GMA" MOMENT.
WE GO TO STEAMBOAT SPRINGS,
COLORADO.
THERE'S OLD CHRIS KRINGLE TAKING
A BREAK FROM THE WORKSHOP AND
THEN RIDING HOME ON HIS STEED IN
FRONT OF THE BARN THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SANTA GETS
ALL THIS TIME.
>>> COMING UP, HOW SOME KIDS ARE
ORDERING GIFTS USING ALEXA, AND
WHAT YOU CAN DO TO STOP THESE
CRIMINALS.
>>> PLUS, BEHIND THE SCENES WITH
THE NEW BACHELOR AS PILOT PETE
GETS READY TO TAKE
>> 7 ON YOUR SIDE RIGHT NOW WITH
LIVE LOCAL NEWS FROM "GOOD
MORNING WASHINGTON."
>> ADRIANNA: "GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON" I AM
>> JESSOB: "GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
DRAMA SURROUNDING INJURY TO
REDSKINS QUARTERBACK DWAYNE
HASKINS.
HE TRIED TO GET BACK IN THE GAME
SAID REDSKINS OWNER DAN SNYDER
TOLD HIM NOT TO.
HE ONLY TOLD HIM TO LYNN TO THE
MEDICAL ADVICE.
>> ADRIANNA: HUNDREDS GATHER FOR
THE LIGHTING OF THE NATIONAL
MENORAH.
HONDA CONTINUES TO DECEMBER
30TH.
>> EILEEN: TRACKING PATCHY -- WE
ARE PRECIPITATION FREE TODAY.
LITTLE MORE SUNSHINE.
BY THIS AFTERNOON, YOU'LL BE IN
A LIGHT JACKET.
IT WILL FEEL GREAT FOR LAST
MINUTE SHOPPING, 52, COMFORTABLY
COOL.
50° CHRISTMAS EVE.
WARMEST DAY THIS WEEK ON
THURSDAY, 54.
NEXT CHANCE OF WET WEATHER,
BOBBY COMES SUNDAY.
>> BOBBY: SOUNDS GOOD, EILEEN.
I-95 NORTHBOUND MARYLAND ROUTE
100.
ACCIDENT KEEPING TWO RIGHT LANES
BLOCKED.
BACK AT ROUTE 32.
VOLUME BUILDING UP.
DELAYS STRETCH DOWN TO ROUTE
198.
THEN OVER ON I-95 IN VAN DORN.
ALL THE WAY UP TO THE OCCOQUAN
AVERAGE SPEED MOVING ALONG
WITHOUT PROBLEMS, I-270
SOUTHBOUND LOOKING GOOD,
ADRIANNA?
>> ADRIANNA: GET
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> JESSOB:
AMERICA" BACK IN TWO MINUTES ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS FOR THE LATEST LOCAL NEWS
ON "GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON."
>>> DOUBLE TROUBLE.
STORMS SLAMMING BOTH COASTS AS
THE HOLIDAY EXODUS GETS UNDER
WAY.
MORE THAN 100
HITTING THE ROADS AND THE SKY
FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
THE MASSIVE PILEUP INVOLVING
ALMOST 70 CARS, CAUSING DOZENS
OF INJURIES.
WE'RE TRACKING IT ALL.
>>> NEW THIS MORNING, THE NUMBER
OF FLU CASES SKYROCKETING.
HOW TO STAY HEALTHY AND LOWER
YOUR RISK AS YOU HIT THE ROAD
FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
DR. ASHTON IS HERE.
>>> MOVE OVER, SANTA.
THIS YEAR, SOME KIDS ARE
ORDERING THEIR OWN PRESENTS FROM
AMAZON ALEXA.
WHAT PARENTS SHOULD KNOW SO
THERE AREN'T ANY SURPRISES UNDER
THE TREE.
♪ CAN'T HURRY LOVE ♪
>>> FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELTS.
PILOT PETE IS BACK, AND WE HAVE
AN EXCLUSIVE BEHIND-THE-SCENES
LOOK AT THE NEWEST HIGH-FLYING
BACHELOR AND THE BRAND-NEW
SE
SEASON.
>>> HILARY DUFF GETS HITCHED.
THE "YOUNGER" STAR TYING THE
KNOT, SHARING A SHOT OF HER
BACKYARD WEDDING.
ALL THE DETAILS THIS MORNING.
>>> AND TREVOR JACKSON IS HERE
AS WE SAY, GOOD MORNING,
AMERICA.
♪
>>> AND GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
THANKS FOR STARTING YOUR HOLIDAY
WEEK HERE WITH US.
>> BUSY WEEK HERE, AND IF YOU
HAVEN'T PLANNED OUT THAT
CHRISTMAS EVE DINNER YET, WE
HAVE JUST THE THING FOR YOU.
ANGIE MAR IS HERE, AUTHOR OF THE
COOKBOOK "BUTCHER AND BEAST."
SHE'S COOKING UP MEAT DISHES FOR
US.
GREAT MAIN COURSE FOR THE FAMILY
AND A WHOLE LOT MORE TO GO WITH
IT.
>> GET READY FOR THE MEAT
SWEATS.
>>> WE BEGIN WITH THE HOLIDAY
EXODUS AS MILLIONS OF AMERICANS
TAKE TO THE ROADS AND SKY, AND
LET'S GO BACK TO VICTOR OQUENDO.
GOOD MORNING AGAIN TO YOU,
VICTOR.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, EVA.
IT HAS BEEN A VERY LONG MORNING
FOR ALL THE TRAVELERS HERE
BEHIND ME.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE AIRPORT HAS
REOPENED AND IN THE PROCESS OF
RESUMING FLIGHT OPERATIONS, BUT
THE LINES HERE ARE VERY LONG.
THEY'RE STRETCHING CLEAR ACROSS
THE TERMINAL, AND THERE ARE A
LOT OF DELAYS FLASHING ON THAT
BIG BOARD RIGHT NOW.
IT WAS A BRUTAL MORNING,
TORRENTIAL RAIN AND FLASH
FLOODING FORCING THE AIRPORT TO
CLOSE RIGHT AROUND 4:00 A.M.
LOOK AT THIS LINE OF CARS SLOWLY
GETTING THROUGH RISING WATERS.
THERE WAS A DANGEROUS SITUATION
IN VIRGINIA.
A 69-CAR PILEUP ON THE HIGHWAY
THERE.
AUTHORITIES SAY FOG AND ICY
ROADS WERE FACTORS IN THE CRASH.
PEOPLE STANDING ON THE HOODS OF
THEIR CARS WHILE THE HIGHWAY WAS
AT A STANDSTILL.
50 PEOPLE IN TOTAL INJURED IN
THAT CRASH.
NEARLY 105 MILLION AMERICANS
WILL BE DRIVING TO THEIR HOLIDAY
DESTINATIONS THIS YEAR.
THAT IS A RECORD, AND FOR THE
MILLIONS FLYING, DEFINITELY GIVE
YOURSELF SOME EXTRA TIME, AND IF
YOU ARE FLYING OUT OF THIS
AIRPORT, YOU WANT TO CHECK WITH
THE AIRLINE FIRST.
WHIT?
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
>>> NOW TO THE STORMS ON BOTH
COASTS CAUSING TROUBLE FOR
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE.
LET'S GO BACK TO ROB WHO HAS
BEEN TRACKING IT ALL.
>> LOTS OF TROPICAL RAIN IN THE
SOUTHEAST.
WE HAD A FOOT OF RAIN.
WE'LL START IN THE SOUTHEAST
BECAUSE THIS IS A SLOW MOVER AND
IT'S REALLY GOING TO BE HITTING
THE ATLANTA HARTSFIELD AIRPORT,
AND THE ORLANDO AIRPORT WILL BE
HIT, AND OBVIOUSLY L.A.X., BUT
THE RAIN WITH THIS WILL BE SLOW
MOVING OFF THE EAST COAST, AND
NORTHERN FLORIDA AND EVENTUALLY
IN THROUGH SOUTH CAROLINA DURING
THE DAY TODAY, AND IN THROUGH
TONIGHT, THAT'S WHERE THE
HEAVIEST RAIN AND WIND WILL BE.
COULD SEE 2 TO 4 INCHES OF
RAINFALL THERE.
ALSO FROM LOS ANGELES DOWN TO
SAN DIEGO.
WE'RE TALKING 1 TO 2 INCHES, BUT
THAT'S A LOT FOR SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
WE'LL GET MOUNTAIN SNOW ABOVE
5,000 FEET.
COMING IN ON CHRISTMAS DAY FOR
THE WEST COAST.
TOM, OVER TO YOU.
>> THANKS FOR THAT.
>>> WE ARE DOWN TO THE WIRE NOW.
IT'S YOUR LAST CHANCE TO SHIP
THOSE CHRISTMAS GIFTS AND GET
THEM UNDER THE TREE IN TIME.
WHAT ARE YOUR OPTIONS?
LET'S GO BACK TO GIO BENITEZ AT
MACY'S WITH WHAT YOU NEED TO
KNOW.
AGAIN, GIO, LET US NKNOW.
WHAT DO WE NEED TO KNOW RIGHT
NOW?
>> Reporter: YOU NEED TO KNOW,
TOM, THIS IS THE LAST DAY TO GET
THAT NEXT-DAY DELIVERY.
A LOT OF DIFFERENT SERVICES AND
RETAILERS ARE OFFERING FREE
NEXT-DAY DELIVERY RIGHT NOW.
LET'S LOOK AT WHAT WE FOUND.
LAST DAY TO GET THAT NEXT-DAY
DELIVERY BY TOMORROW, AND MAKE
SURE YOU'RE CHECKING THE
SHIPPING DEADLINES BEFORE YOU
PLACE AN ORDER.
TARGET AND AMAZON PRIME OFFER
SAME-DAY DELIVERY THROUGH
TOMORROW.
I GOT AN EMAIL FROM APPLE SAYING
MANY CITIES YOU CAN GET FREE
TWO-HOUR DELIVERY IF YOU PLACE
THAT ORDER BY 4:00 P.M.
TOMORROW.
OTHER STORES DOING THE SAME.
AMAZON HAS A SEPARATE SERVICE
CALLED PRIME NOW.
JUST REMEMBER THAT IS A SEPARATE
APP THAT YOU NEED TO DOWNLOAD.
THAT IS PRIME NOW, BUT LISTEN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, DIGITAL
GIFT CARDS ARE GREAT.
RESTAURANT GIFT CARDS ARE GREAT,
AND THEY'RE PRETTY EASY TO GET
RIGHT NOW.
HAPPY SHOPPING.
>> AND CASH IS ALWAYS GOOD.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOBODY SAYS NO TO CASH,
RIGHT?
>> AS LONG AS TOM GETS HIS LULU
LE
LEMONS.
>> SIZE MEDIUM.
>>> COMING UP, THE FLU ON THE
RISE.
WHAT TENS OF MILLIONS TRAVELING
FOR THE HOLIDAYS, WHAT YOU CAN
DO TO STAY HEALTHY.
DR. JEN ASHTON IS HERE.