>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
THIS WEDNESDAY WILL LONG BE
REMEMBERED.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SET TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN
HISTORY TO BE IMPEACHED.
THE HISTORIC VOTE JUST HOURS
FROM NOW.
DEMOCRATS RALLY SUPPORT
OVERNIGHT, AS PRESIDENT TRUMP
SLAMS SPEAKER PELOSI IN A
BLISTERING LETTER.
PELOSI FIRES BACK.
NOW HOW THE WHITE HOUSE IS
PREPARING.
WHAT'S NEXT ON CAPITOL HILL.
WE'RE LIVE IN WASHINGTON WITH
ALL THE LATEST ON THIS MOMENTOUS
DAY.
>>> DANGEROUS DEEP FREEZE.
AS THAT DEADLY WINTER STORM
MOVES OUT, THE COLDEST AIR OF
THE SEASON MOVES IN.
TEMPERATURES SET TO PLUNGE ALL
ACROSS THE EAST COAST.
>>> HORROR FROM ABOVE.
A WOMAN KILLED BY FALLING DEBRIS
FROM A HIGH-RISE RIGHT HERE IN
TIMES SQUARE.
THE INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY.
WERE REPAIR ORDERS IGNORED BY
BUILDING MANAGEMENT?
>>> MISSING MOM MYSTERY.
THE FBI NOW JOINS THE SEARCH FOR
THAT MOTHER AND INFANT WHO
DISAPPEARED NEARLY A WEEK AGO.
THE YOUNG MOTHER'S PARENTS ARE
SPEAKING OUT.
THEY SAY THERE'S "NO WAY" SHE
LEFT ON HER OWN.
>>> HOLIDAY SHIPPING SURGE.
WITH JUST ONE WEEK UNTIL
CHRISTMAS, WILD WEATHER AND A
RECORD NUMBER OF DELIVERIES
MAKING FOR A LAST-MINUTE FRENZY.
WHY HEADING OUT TO PICK UP THOSE
PACKAGES MAY BE YOUR BEST BET.
>>> PUPPY LOVE.
THE NEW VIDEO SHOWING THE MOMENT
THIS BEAR ZEROES IN ON A
DRIVER'S DOG, HOPPING UP ON THE
TRUNK TO SAY HELLO.
♪ THAT'S THE JINGLE BELL ROCK ♪
>>> AND JINGLE BELL JACKPOT!
CHRISTMAS COMING EARLY FOR A
VERY LUCKY MEGA MILLIONS WINNER
WHO'S WAKING UP $372 MILLION
RICHER THIS MORNING.
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US ON THIS
HISTORIC DAY.
>> INDEED A HISTORIC DAY.
LIVE LOOK AT THE U.S. CAPITOL
WHERE AT 9:00 A.M. THE FULL
HOUSE WILL MEET TO IMPEACH THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
A POWER ENSHRINED IN THE
CONSTITUTION.
A MOVE RARELY DEPLOYED.
>> ANDREW JOHNSON IT WAS FIRST
USED ON.
BILL CLINTON IN 1998, ALMOST
EXACTLY 21 YEARS AGO, RICHARD
NIXON RESIGNED JUST BEFORE THE
HOUSE VOTE IN 1974 BUT PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S RESPONSE ON THE EVE OF
THIS VOTE COULD NOT BE MORE
DIFFERENT.
HE UNLEASHED A DEFIANT LETTER
PACKED WITH INSULTS AND
INACCURACIES THAT LABELED IT AN
ILLEGAL ATTEMPTS COUP WORSE THAN
THE SALEM WITCH TRIALS.
NANCY PELOSI HAD A LETTER OF HER
OWN ADDING "REALLY SICK" ON
CAMERA.
THE HOUSE BEGINS ITS BITTER
DEBATE.
OUR SENIOR CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MARY BRUCE WILL BE
THERE ON CAPITOL HILL FOR THIS
MOMENT OF HISTORY.
GOOD MORNING, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
THERE IS NO QUESTION THIS IS A
DAY FOR HISTORY BUT IT IS ALSO
ONE THAT THE SPEAKER HOPED TO
AVOID BUT NOW PELOSI SAYS THE
PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS HAVE SIMPLY
LEFT HER NO CHOICE AND LATER
TODAY THE PRESIDENT IS EXPECTED
TO BE IMPEACHED FOR ABUSING HIS
POWER AND OBSTRUCTING CONGRESS.
HE IS WELL AWARE THE STAIN THIS
WILL LEAVE ON HIS LEGACY ADAMANT
HE DID NOTHING WRONG BUT
ADMITTING HE IS POWERLESS TO
STOP THIS OUTCOME.
AFTER TWO MONTHS OF
INVESTIGATING, MORE THAN 0 HOURS
OF HEARINGS AND 16 WITNESSES,
THE HISTORIC VOTE NOW JUST HOURS
AWAY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, DO YOU TAKE
ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE FACT
THAT YOU ARE ABOUT TO BE
IMPEACHED?
>> NO, I DON'T TAKE ANY.
ZERO TO PUT IT MILDLY.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
INCENSED LASHING OUT IN A
SCATHING SIX-PAGE LETTER TO THE
HOUSE SPEAKER FLATLY DENYING THE
CHARGES AGAINST HIM AND FIRING
BACK UNFOUNDED ALLEGATIONS
AGAINST DEMOCRATS.
CALLING THE IMPEACHMENT PROCESS
OUTLINED BY THE CONSTITUTION AN
ILLEGAL PARTISAN ATTEMPTED COUP.
AND ACCUSING SPEAKER PELOSI OF
DECLARING OPEN WAR ON AMERICAN
DEMOCRACY.
TRUMP WARNS PELOSI YOUR LEGACY
WILL BE THAT OF TURNING THE
HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES FROM A
REVERED LEGISLATIVE BODY INTO A
STAR CHAMBER OF PARTISAN
PERSECUTION.
AND HE SAYS AMERICANS WILL HOLD
DEMOCRATS RESPONSIBLE IN 2020
SAYING THEY WILL NOT SOON
FORGIVE YOUR PERVERSION OF
JUSTICE AND ABUSE OF POWER.
AND TRUMP RAILS AGAINST THE
PROCESS INSISTING MORE DUE
PROCESS WAS AFFORDED TO THOSE
ACCUSED IN THE SALEM WITCH
TRIALS WHEN PEOPLE WERE
EXECUTED.
HE EVEN ACCUSES PELOSI OF BEING
DISINGENUOUS WHEN SHE SAYS SHE
PRAYS FOR HIM.
>> I ALWAYS PRAYED FOR THE
PRESIDENT AND I STILL PRAY FOR
THE PRESIDENT.
I PRAY FOR THE PRESIDENT ALL THE
TIME.
>> YOU ARE OFFENDING AMERICANS
OF FAITH BY CONTINUALLY SAYING I
PRAY FOR THE PRESIDENT, TRUMP
WRITE, WHEN YOU KNOW THIS
STATEMENT IS NOT TRUE UNLESS IT
IS MEANT IN A NEGATIVE SENSE.
THE SPEAKER CALLS THE LETTER
RIDICULOUS.
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY FULLY READ
IT.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING.
I'VE SEEN THE ESSENCE OF IT AND
IT IS REALLY SICK.
>> IT ESSENTIALLY AMOUNTS TO ONE
LONG TWITTER RANT.
>> BEFORE THE HOUSE VOTES THE
SENATE IS FIGHTING OVER THE
TRIAL TO COME.
MITCH McCONNELL MAKING IT CLEAR
HE WANTS A QUICK TRIAL WITH NO
WITNESSES.
>> IF HOUSE DEMOCRATS' CASE IS
THIS DEFICIENT, THIS THIN, THE
ANSWER IS NOT FOR THE JUDGE AND
JURY TO CURE IT OVER HERE IN THE
SENATE.
THE ANSWER IS THE HOUSE SHOULD
NOT IMPEACH ON THIS BASIS IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
>> Reporter: BUT DEMOCRATS ARE
DEMANDING TO HEAR TESTIMONY FROM
FOUR WITNESSES INCLUDING ACTING
CHIEF OF STAFF MICK MULVANEY AND
FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER
JOHN BOLTON.
>> IMPEACHMENT TRIALS LIKE MOST
TRIALS HAVE WITNESSES.
WHO IS FOR AN OPEN AND FAIR
TRIAL?
WHO IS FOR HIDING FACTS?
RELEVANT FACTS, IMMEDIATE FACTS.
>> Reporter: NOW THIS PROCESS
WILL UNFOLD OVER SIX HOURS OF
DEBATE HERE SPLIT EVENLY BETWEEN
THE TWO PARTY, THE FINAL CHANCE
FOR BOTH SIDES OF THE AISLE TO
MAKE THEIR CASE TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE AND THEN THERE WILL BE
TWO VOTES ON THE TWO CHARGES AND
THEY ARE EXPECTED TO BE NEAR
PARTY LINE VOTES.
>> THAT IS LIKELY TO HAPPEN BY
THE END OF THE DAY, MARY, AND
THE DEBATE OVER THE SENATE TRIAL
ALREADY INTENSE.
>> Reporter: YEAH, THE TWO SIDES
ARE PUBLICLY JOCKEYING OVER WHAT
EXACTLY THIS TRIAL IS GOING TO
LOOK LEAN AND MITCH McCONNELL IS
BLUNT SAYING HE IS NOT AN
IMPARTIAL JUROR AND GOING TO
WORK IN TOTAL COORDINATION WITH
THE WHITE HOUSE WHILE DEMOCRATS
ARE ADAMANT THEY WANT TO HEAR
FROM THE FOUR WITNESSES AND
INSIST REPUBLICANS ARE TRYING TO
HIDE SOMETHING.
>> LET'S BRING IN JON KARL FOR
MORE.
JON, I KNOW YOU WERE COVERING IT
AS WELL, THE IMPEACHMENT OF BILL
CLINTON IN 1998, A FEW DAYS
BEFORE THE IMPEACHMENT HE WENT
INTO THE ROSE GARDEN AND
APOLOGIZED.
THE RESPONSE FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP SO DIFFERENT, BUT ALSO
SLE
VERY MUCH IN CHARACTER.
>> Reporter: ABSOLUTELY.
THAT SIX-PAGE LETTER IS VINTAGE
TRUMP.
AN INTERESTING THING ABOUT THE
DRAFTING OF IT, THE WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL'S OFFICE, THE WHITE
HOUSE LAWYER, THOSE WHO WILL BE
LEADING THEORETICALLY THE
IMPEACHMENT DEFENSE WERE NOT
PART OF DRAFTING THAT LETTER.
THE PRESIDENT BROUGHT IN HIS
LONGTIME POLICY ADVISER AND
SPEECH WRITER STEPHEN MILLER,
ANOTHER AIDE HERE ERIC UHLAND
AND VENTED TO THEM AND THEY
TRANSFORMED HIS WORDS INTO THAT
LETTER.
>> JON, YOU MENTIONED IT,
VINTAGE TRUMP.
THIS LETTER GIVES US A LOOK INTO
THE PRESIDENT'S MIND-SET.
HE IS HEADING INTO TODAY MORE
DEFIANT THAN EVER.
>> Reporter: HE SURE IS.
WHILE THE LETTER LOOKS ANGRY AND
CERTAINLY IS AS MANY HAVE CALLED
IT A RANT, I AM TOLD THAT THE
PRESIDENT'S MOOD IS ACTUALLY
QUITE POSITIVE HERE.
HE IS IN THIS FIGHT.
HE DID NOT WANT TO BE IMPEACHED.
THAT WAS ABUNDANTLY CLEAR BUT
NOW THAT IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S ALL
BUT CERTAIN TO HAPPEN HE IS
LOOKING FORWARD TO THAT FIGHT IN
THE SENATE AND TRUST ME,
CECILIA, HE WILL DECLARE
COMPLETE AND TOTAL VINDICATION
IF AS EXPECTED THE SENATE DOES
NOT VOTE TO REMOVE HIM.
THIS WILL BE COMPLETE AND TOTAL
VINDICATION IN THE MINDS OF
DONALD TRUMP AND HE WILL GO OUT
AND DECLARE AS SUCH.
>> WE WILL SEE HIM TONIGHT.
ALL OF US HERE FOR THE LIVE
COVERAGE OF THE DEBATE AND VOTES
IN THE HOUSE, HISTORIC VOTES
THAT STARTS AT 9:00 A.M.
EASTERN.
>> MICHAEL.
>> WE MOVE TO THE DEEP FREEZE
MOVING IN ON THE HEELS OF THAT
DEADLY WINTER STORM THAT BROUGHT
TORNADOES, SNOW AND ICE.
GINGER HAS THE VERY LATEST.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, GINGER.
>> GOOD MORNING, MICHAEL.
MANY OF US HAVE BEEN ENCASED IN
ICE FROM MARYLAND TO MY BACKYARD
JUST NORTH OF NEW YORK CITY AND
THIS ISN'T GOING ANYWHERE.
THE COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON IS
ABOUT TO SETTLE IN.
>> WHAT THE HECK.
>> Reporter: THICK ICE TAKING
DOWN POWER LINES IN PITTSTOWN,
NEW JERSEY, PILEUPS AND TRAFFIC
HALTED FROM THIS HIGHWAY IN
WELLESLEY, MASSACHUSETTS, TO
SPINOUTS IN FISHKILL, NEW YORK.
THAT ICE ACCUMULATING AND TWO
TEEN BROTHERS FACING
LIFE-THREATENING INJURIES AFTER
THEIR TRUCK SLID OFF THE ROAD
AND WRAPPED AROUND THIS TREE.
THE SAME SYSTEM PRODUCING 38
REPORTED TORNADOES FROM
LOUISIANA TO GEORGIA.
THIS VIDEO CAPTURING THE DAMAGE
IN OCILLA, GEORGIA AND IN
LOUISIANA, A DIFFICULT SCENE
JUST BEFORE THE HOLIDAYS, HOMES
SHREDDED.
THE COMMUNITY HERE ALSO RAVAGED
BY AN EF-2 TORNADO.
BY TOMORROW MORNING THAT'S WHEN
IT ALL SETTLES IN.
WE WILL FEEL THE TEENS, ACTUAL
TEMPERATURE IN THE TEENS BUT
WILL FEEL LIKE 1 BELOW.
7 FOR PITTSBURGH.
EVEN RALEIGH DROPPING INTO THE
TEENS.
ATLANTA, YOU'RE NOT OUT OF THE
WOODS EITHER.
LET'S HEAD TO THE SOUTHEAST
WHERE NUMBERS WILL BE TUMBLING.
ALREADY FROM YESTERDAY'S HIGHS
IN THE 60s AND 70s, EVEN THE 80s
IN FLORIDA, FLORIDA NOT IMMUNE,
WATCH AS THE BLUE AND GREEN TAKE
OVER THE SOUTHEAST.
WE'RE GOING TO GO AHEAD AND
CLICK AND SHOW YOU WHEN THAT
TEMPERATURE DROPS BY TOMORROW
MORNING.
YOU'LL FEEL LIKE FREEZING IN
TALLAHASSEE.
A FREEZE WATCH ALONG THE
FLORIDA/GEORGIA STATE LINE.
MONTGOMERY, 25 AND ATLANTA WILL
FEEL LIKE 23.
>> THANKS.
>>> WE HEAD TO THE INVESTIGATION
INTO THE TRAGEDY HERE IN NEW
YORK CITY.
A PROMINENT ARCHITECT KILLED BY
FALLING DEBRIS WHILE WALKING ON
A MANHATTAN STREET.
EVA PILGRIM IS THERE ON THE
SCENE WITH THE VERY LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, EVA.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
THE SCAFFOLDING HERE IS NEW THIS
MORNING.
THE CITY ORDERING IT PUT UP
AFTER WITNESSES SAY DEBRIS FELL
OFF THAT BUILDING KILLING A
WOMAN.
THE SIDEWALK THERE REMAINS
CLOSED.
OVERNIGHT CREWS SCRAMBLING TO
INSTALL PROTECTIVE SCAFFOLDING
AFTER DEBRIS FROM A HIGH-RISE
UNDER CONSTRUCTION FELL 17
STORIES TO THE GROUND KILLING A
PROMINENT NEW YORK ARCHITECT,
60-YEAR-OLD ERICA TISHMAN WHO
WAS WALKING IN THE HEART OF
MIDTOWN MANHATTAN WHEN WITNESSES
SAY PIECES OF THE FACADE CAME
CRUMBLING OFF THE BUILDING.
NOW NEW QUESTIONS OVER SAFETY AS
THOUSANDS OF PEDESTRIANS PASS BY
BUILDINGS UNDER RENOVATION EVERY
DAY.
>> I AM LIKE WITHOUT WORDS I
REALLY DON'T KNOW HOW SOMETHING
LIKE THAT COULD HAPPEN IN THE
CITY WHERE SO MANY TOURISTS ARE.
>> Reporter: CITY RECORDS SHOW
THE OWNERS WERE KITED IN APRIL
FOR DAMAGED TERRA-COTTA AT AREAS
ABOVE 15th FLOOR IN SEVERAL
LOCATIONS WHICH POSES A FALLING
HAZARD FOR PEDESTRIANS.
IN JULY 2019, THE BUILDING WAS
PERMITTED TO BEGIN MASONRY
REPAIR ON ITS FATHER SAID ON THE
PENTATONIXHOUSE AND ROOF.
THE OWNER RELEASING A STATEMENT
SAYING WE ARE SADDENED BY THIS
TRAGEDY AND OUR HEARTS GO OUT TO
THE FAMILY.
THE COMPANY WILL FULLY COOPERATE
WITH THE CITY IN THE ONGOING
MATTER.
AND THE CITY IS LOOKING INTO
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED AND THAT
INCLUDES WHETHER OR NOT THIS
SCAFFOLDING SHOULD HAVE ALREADY
BEEN UP.
MICHAEL.
>> ALL RIGHT, HORRIBLE ACCIDENT
THERE, EVA, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'RE SWITCHING GEARS NOW TO
THAT HOLIDAY SHIPPING RUSH WHERE
WE ARE OFFICIALLY A WEEK AWAY
FROM CHRISTMAS AND THE RACE IS
ON TO DELIVER GIFTS IN TIME AND
REBECCA JARVIS IS OUTSIDE MACY'S
JUST DOWN THE STREET FROM US.
GOOD MORNING, REBECCA.
THERE'S SOME NEW CHALLENGES
PUTTING DELIVERIES AT RISK.
>> OH, THERE ARE, MICHAEL.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND BELIEVE IT OR NOT, WE'RE
PART OF THE PROBLEM.
61% OF AMERICANS, MYSELF
INCLUDED, HAVE YET TO FINISH
THEIR HOLIDAY SHOPPING, COMBINE
THAT WITH THE WILD WINTER
WEATHER AND IT'S A MAD DASH TO
CHRISTMAS.
THIS MORNING, A DOUBLE WHAMMY IN
THE RACE TO GET THOSE GOODIES
UNDER THE TREE CHRISTMAS
MORNING.
WILD WINTER WEATHER AND A RECORD
NUMBER OF PACKAGES.
>> THE WEATHER IS A GREAT
CHALLENGE AND ON THESE
LAST-MINUTE DELIVERIES AND ON
THE DELIVERY SIDE, JUST THE
SHEER AMOUNT OF VOLUME AND THE
AMOUNT OF TIME WE HAVE LEFT.
>> Reporter: THE U.S. POSTAL
SERVICE EXPECTING TO PROCESS AND
DELIVER NEARLY 2.5 BILLION
PIECES OF MAIL INCLUDING
PACKAGES THIS WEEK ALONE.
USPS OFFERING SUNDAY DELIVERY IN
MANY LOCATIONS WITH HIGH VOLUME
AND MOST MAJOR CITIES.
AMAZON THIS WEEK TEMPORARILY
BLOCKING THIRD PARTY SELLERS
FROM USING FEDEX GROUND SHIPPING
FOR PRIME CUSTOMERS CITING A
DROP IN THE DELIVERY
PERFORMANCE.
FEDEX SAYS IT'S FACED BAD
WEATHER AND THE HIGHEST VOLUME
OF HOLIDAY PACKAGES EVER BUT
SAYS THEY'RE STILL ABLE TO
ACCOMMODATE THE SURGE.
AMAZON IS OFFERING AMAZON
LOCKERS AT VARIOUS CONVENIENCE
STORES, MALLS AND WHOLE FOODS
LOCATIONS AROUND THE COUNTRY.
U.P.S. MY CHOICE GIVES YOU THE
OPTION TO REDIRECT YOUR PACKAGES
TO A U.P.S. ACCESS POINT
LOCATION WHERE IT'LL BE HELD FOR
PICKUP AND WHAT SOME EXPERTS ARE
CALLING YOUR BEST DELIVERY BET,
NO DELIVERY AT ALL.
BUY ONLINE, PICK UP IN STORE
OFFERED BY NAUMEROUS RETAILERS
INCLUDING NORDSTROM, MACY'S,
GAP, TARGET, WALMART AND BEST
BUY.
>> I THINK BUY ONLINE AND PICK
UP IN STORE HAS GONE UP A LOT.
VERY CONVENIENT.
KNOCK OUT SOME SHOPPING.
DELIVERED TO A COMMERCIAL
LOCATION YOU GET AWAY FROM SOME
PROBLEMS YOU HAVE ON RESIDENTIAL
DELIVERY, RESIDENTIAL DELIVERIES
SEEM TO DISAPPEAR MORE OFTEN
THAN COMMERCIAL DELIVERIES.
>> Reporter: THE BOTTOM LINE
HERE IS PROCRASTINATORS, TIME
FOR SOME ACTION.
GET ON IT.
GET SHOPPING AND KNOW THAT
STORES LIKE MACY'S, GAP,
WALMART, TARGET, BEST BUY, THEY
WILL ALL HAVE EXTENDED HOLIDAY
HOURS LEADING RIGHT UP UNTIL
CHRISTMAS, MICHAEL, SO IF YOU
REALLY NEED THAT LAST-MINUTE
RUSH AND YOU WANT TO BE A PART
OF IT, YOU CAN, MICHAEL.
>> WELL, I'M THE PROCRASTINATOR
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT SO I BETTER
GET TO WORK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, REBECCA.
GEORGE.
>> THANKS.
>>> A FAMILY IS CELEBRATING
THEIR CHRISTMAS MIRACLE AFTER
TWO SIBLINGS MISSING WERE FOUND
SAFE IN THE WOODS NEAR THEIR
HOME AND VICTOR OQUENDO IS IN
JACKSONVILLE WITH THE STORY.
GOOD MORNING, VICTOR.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
A HUGE SIGH OF RELIEF FOR THE
FAMILY AND TOF THIS COMMUNITY.
POLICE BELIEVE THOSE KIDS JUST
WANDERED OFF.
>> WE HAVE BOTH KIDS.
WE'RE HEADING OUT OF THE WOODS.
>> Reporter: THE BEST POSSIBLE
OUTCOME, 6-YEAR-OLD BRAXTON AND
5-YEAR-OLD SISTER BRI'YA FOUND
ALIVE NEARLY THREE DAYS AFTER
VANISHING INTEREST THEIR YARD.
>> IT'S A MIRACLE, CHRISTMAS
MIRACLE AND IT'S A BLESSING.
A LOT OF HARD WORK AND THANK
GOOD FOR IT.
>> Reporter: THEY WERE LAST SEEN
PLAYING IN THEIR FRONT YARD.
RESCUE TEAMS OUT IN FULL FORCE.
IN THE AIR AND ON THE GROUND
CANVASSING 400 HOMES AND 100
ACRES WITH HELP FROM THE
COMMUNITY.
TUESDAY AMP THE BREAK THEY HAD
BEEN WAITING FOR.
>> ONE OF THE RESCUE TEAM
MEMBERS HEARD A VOICE, THOUGHT
IT WAS A CHILD'S VOICE AND SO
THEY FANNED OUT AND FOUND THEM
AND HEARD THEM TALKING.
>> SEARCH TEAM ONE FROM COMMAND,
GIVE ME A LOCATION.
>> WE'RE DEEP IN THE WOOD.
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE AS SOON AS WE
GET OUT.
>> Reporter: FOUND IN A PUMP
HOUSE IN THICK SWAMPY WOODS A
QUARTER MILE FROM HOME.
>> BOTH ARE IN VERY GOOD
CONDITION.
>> Reporter: THE FAMILY'S
AGONIZING WAIT WAS OVER.
THE CHILDREN'S FATHER TELLING
OUR JACKSONVILLE STATION GOD IS
GOOD.
I FEEL LIKE I GOT THE LIFE PUT
BACK INTO ME.
THIS GIVES ME A REASON TO KEEP
ON GOING.
>> LIKE A --
>> A BIG SIGH OF RELIEF.
>> YES, SO IT WAS SO EXCITING
AND I'M JUST READY TO SEE THEM.
>> Reporter: TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL FOR OBSERVATION.
THANKFULLY JUST A LITTLE
DEHYDRATED WITH SOME BUMPS AND
BRUISES.
>> THEY'RE ALIVE AND THEY'RE
WELL AND --
>> RIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS.
RIGHT BEFORE.
SO THIS IS AN AWESOME CHRISTMAS
GIFT FOR EVERYBODY.
>> Reporter: TEMPERATURES DID
DIP HERE OVERNIGHT.
GOOD THING THEY FOUND THEM WHEN
THEY DID.
THE FIRST THING BRAXTON AND
BRI'YA ASKED FOR WHEN RESCUED,
CANDY AND A CHEESE PIZZA, GUY.
>> GOOD REQUEST.
AWESOME CHRISTMAS GIFT.
THANK YOU, VICTOR.
>>> WE ARE GOING TO TURN TO
ANOTHER GREAT STORY, THAT JINGLE
BELL JACKPOT.
THERE IS A VERY LUCKY WINNER IN
OHIO THIS MORNING.
A SINGLE WINNING TICKET SOLD FOR
THE MEGA MILLIONS JACKPOT WORTH
372 MILLION BUCKS.
JESSI SCHULTZ FROM OUR AFFILIATE
WEWS IS AT THE STORE WHERE THAT
TICKET WAS SOLD.
GOOD MORNING, JESSI.
>> Reporter: CECILIA, SOME LUCKY
PERSON WALKED RIGHT INTO THIS
GIANT EAGLE HERE IN OHIO AND
USED THE QUICK PICK FEATURE AND
WALKED OUT A WHOLE LOT RICHER.
THIS MORNING, WE DON'T KNOW WHO
THAT WINNER IS, BUT THEY HAVE
WON 180 DAYS TO CLAIM THE
JACKPOT AND FROM NOW UNTIL THEN,
THEY'LL MOST LIKELY EXPERIENCE
THEIR LAST MOMENTS OF NORMALCY.
THIS JACKPOT OF $372 MILLION
WITH A CASH PAYOUT OF $251
MILLION IS THE 14th LARGEST
PRIZE IN THE HISTORY OF THE
GAME.
AND GET THIS, THE ODDS OF
WINNING THAT JACKPOT WERE 1 IN
302 SO I WOULD BET THAT SEVERE
SOMEONE HERE IS GOING TO HAVE
THEIR BEST HOLIDAY YET.
BACK TO YOU, GUY.
>> WHAT A GREAT STORY.
THANK YOU.
>> GREAT HOLIDAY FOR THEM.
FOLLOWING A LOT OF OTHER STORIES
INCLUDING THE FAMILY OF A
MISSING MOTHER AND HER INFANT
SPEAKING OUT NOW AND THEY SAY
THERE'S NO WAY THAT THAT MOTHER
LEFT ON HER OWN.
>>> ALSO THE NEW VIDEO OF THIS
CRAZY MOMENT.
YOU'LL REMEMBER IT.
A MASSIVE BEAR JUMPING ON A CAR.
WELL, NOW THERE'S NEW FOOTAGE
IN
INSIDE, THAT BEAR HAVING A
MOMENT WITH THE DOG.
WHAT THE DRIVER IS SAYING.
>>> THE NEW WAY RING CAMERAS ARE
BEING USED TO HELP FIND MISSING
CHILDREN.
>>> I HAVE BAD NEWS FOR SANTA'S
SLEIGH, THE RUNNERS ARE GOING --
THEY HAVE A TOUGH TIME.
WARMER THAN AVERAGE TEMPERATURES
COMING IN.
IT DOES NOT LOOK LIKE A LOT OF
FOLK ALSO HAVE A WHITE
CHRISTMAS.
FROM PARTS OF THE GREAT LAKES
THROUGH THE SOUTHEAST INTO THE
NORTHEAST SO PRETTY MUCH
EVERYBODY EAST OF THE ROCKIES
LOOKING LIKE ABOVE AVERAGE GOING
INTO THE HOLIDAY WEEK.
SORRY, SANTA.
>> Eileen: WELL, STORM WATCH 7
TRACKING SUNSHINE, BUT ALSO
TUMBLING TEMPERATURES AS WE HEAD
THROUGH TONIGHT AND INTO
TOMORROW.
NOTICE YOUR NEXT HOURS, 42
TODAY, BUT TONIGHT WE'RE DOWN
INTO THE 20S UNDER CLEAR SKIES.
WINDCHILL VALUES TOMORROW
MORNING THIS TIME WILL BE IN THE
TEENS.
SUNNY BUT COLD TOMORROW, 34
DEGREES.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE LOOKING
DRY AS WE HEAD INTO THE UPCOMING
WEEKEND.
WINTER BEGINS ON SATURDAY.
42.
THE FIRST DAY OF HANUKKAH ON
SUNDAY,
>>> SO SINCE A LOT OF US WON'T
HAVE THE WHITE CHRISTMAS MAYBE
WE TAKE IT FROM MASON AND DO
SOME GRASS ANGELS.
THAT'S IN BRADENTON, FLORIDA.
>> I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> WHY NOT.
>> HE'S PRACTICING.
THANK YOU, GINGER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Drill?
Cordless.
Noted.
That's a good one.
Introducing the Capital One
Walmart Rewards Card.
Earn unlimited 5% back
on everything you buy
at Walmart online...
♪What's in your wallet?♪
Find your rhythm.
Your happy place.
Find your breaking point.
Then break it.
Every Emergen-C gives you a
potent blend of nutrients
so you can emerge your best,
with Emergen-C.
It's time to make
mopping history.
Introducing the new
Braava jet m6 robot mop.
With an adjustable precision jet
spray and advanced pad system
Braava jet breaks up messes
and gets deep in corners.
Braava jet.
Only from iRobot.
Introducing the all-new
2020 Ford Escape.
It's got an available
head-up display.
Adaptive cruise control
with stop-and-go.
And Ford Co-Pilot360 technology.
Looks like someone
got everything on
their list this year.
Now, who's your Santa?
The totally redesigned
2020 Ford Escape.
Ford. Built For The Holidays.
LET'S BE HONEST,
QUITTING SMOKING
IS FREAKING HARD.
LIKE QUITTING
EVERY MONDAY HARD.
QUITTING FEELS SO BIG.
SO, TRY MAKING IT SMALLER.
AND YOU'LL BE SURPRISED AT
HOW EASILY STARTING SMALL...
...CAN LEAD TO SOMETHING BIG.
START STOPPING
WITH NICORETTE
When you've crossed Fruit of
the Loom off your list,
you know your holiday
shopping is complete.
Feel free to
celebrate.
Welcome to our
Lipton tea factory.
Where these sun-soaked
tea leaves
are picked at the peak
of freshness.
For a naturally smooth taste.
And drinking Lipton
every day
can help support a
healthy heart!
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
A FOUR YEAR OLD BADLY INJURED
AFTER BEING HIT BY A CAR IN
ROCKETSHIP SOUTHEAST.
CHILD IS A STUDENT AT THE
SCHOOL.
PARENTS HAVE CALLED FOR A
CROSSWALK AND CROSSING GUARD IN
THAT AREA.
>> MELANIE: MAN ACCUSED OF A
STABBING OUTSIDE OF POPEYES IN
CONNECTION TO THE DEATH OF
28-YEAR-OLD KEVIN DAVIS.
STABBING STEMS FROM AN ARGUMENT
AFTER DAVIS CUT WAITING TO ORDER
FOOD.
>> ADRIANNA: BUSY MORNING,
SEVERAL ACCIDENTS
Well it finally
happened, Zachary.
Somebody burned
down my she shed.
Your she shed was
struck by lightning.
Is my she
shed covered by State Farm?
Your she shed's covered, Cheryl.
That's wonderful news.
Home insurance trusted by
more people than any other.
State Farm.
Home insurance trusted by
more people than any other.
Oh-
Yes!
And it's on Rollback.
So cool!
She's going to love this.
♪♪
Sound bar?
So she can watch her cartoons
in Surround Sound.
And football.
You don't let a cold ruin your
day.
You take DayQuil Severe
LiquiCaps
and crush it.
DayQuil Severe.
The Daytime, Coughing, Aching,
Stuffy-head, Fever, Sore Throat,
Power Through Your Day,
Medicine.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
♪ THE WAY GLENN MILLER PLAY
SONGS THAT MADE THE HIT PARADE ♪
>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
WE LOVED IT THE FIRST TIME AND
NOW JIMMY KIMMEL AND NORMAN LEAR
ARE BACK AT IT BRINGING TWO
CLASSICS BACK TONIGHT, "ALL IN
THE FAMILY" AND "GOOD TIMES."
OF COURSE, IT'S A STAR-STUDDED
CAST OF WOODY HARRELSON, VIOLA
DAVIS, TIFFANY HADDISH AND A LOT
MORE AND THAT'S IN OUR NEXT
HOUR.
WE'RE GOING BEHIND THE SCENES
BEFORE THEIR BIG PERFORMANCE.
THAT IS COMING UP.
>> WHAT A GREAT IDEA THIS WAS.
>> FANTASTIC.
>>> FOLLOWING A LOT OF BIG
STORY, THAT HISTORIC DAY ON
CAPITOL HILL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SET TO BECOME
THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN
HISTORY TO BE IMPEACHED.
VOTES WILL TAKE PLACE HOURS FROM
NOW.
ALSO THIS MORNING NEW REPORTS
SHOWS TEEN VAPING OF "WASHINGTON
POST" ON THE RISE SURGING IN
2019 ACCORDING TO NEW GOVERNMENT
DATA AND RESEARCHERS RAISING
CONCERNS.
>>> A DEEP FREEZE ON THE WAY
MOVING TO THE EAST COAST AND
COULD BE NEAR ZERO HERE IN NEW
YORK CITY TOMORROW.
>>> WE TURN TO THE LATEST ON
THAT MISSING MOTHER AND INFANT
WHO DISAPPEARED IN TEXAS LAST
WEEK.
THE FBI AND TEXAS RANGERS NOW
JOINING IN THE SEARCH AS WE HEAR
FROM THE WOMAN'S PARENTS.
MARCUS MOORE SPOKE WITH THEM AND
JOINS US FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
GOOD MORNING, MARCUS.
>> Reporter: CECILIA, GOOD
MORNING.
HEIDI BROUSSARD HAS BEEN MISSING
NEARLY A WEEK ALONG WITH HER
NEWBORN BABY AND HER PARENTS ARE
PRAYING THEY WILL BE FOUND AND
SAYING NO WAY SHE WOULD LEAVE ON
HER OWN.
>> THE MORE YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
THE WORSE IT GETS.
>> Reporter: THE MISSING MOTHER
CAPTURED IN THIS SURVEILLANCE
IMAGE DROPPING OFF HER SON AT AN
AUSTIN SCHOOL.
POLICE SAY SHE LATER WENT TO HER
APARTMENT AND NEVER RETURNED TO
PICK UP HER SON.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE SHE LEFT ON HER
OWN?
>> NO.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> NO WAY.
SHE WOULD NOT LEAVE HER SON.
HER KIDS ARE HER HEARTBEAT.
>> OH, YES.
>> Reporter: THE SEARCH FOR
CLUES ENTERING A NEW PHASE.
FBI AGENTS GOING DOOR TO DOOR.
POLICE NOT NAMING ANY SUSPECTS,
SAYING THEY'RE OPERATING ON THE
ASSUMPTION BROUSSARD IS STILL
ALIVE.
>> IT'S POSSIBLE THAT HEIDI AND
MARGOT HAVE LEFT ON THEIR OWN
ACCORD.
WE DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER.
>> Reporter: BROUSSARD'S FIANCE
SHANE CAREY REPORTING HER
MISSING HOURS AFTER SHE
DISAPPEARED BELIEVING THEY WERE
TAKEN.
>> THERE'S NOTHING VALUABLE
MISSING.
HUR PURSE AND WALLET WAS HERE.
HER CELL PHONE IS MISSING AND
HAS BEEN TURNED OFF.
>> Reporter: PLEADING FOR THEIR
RETURN.
>> I LOVE YOU, HEIDI.
I LOVE YOU, MARGOT.
CONTACT ANYBODY.
IF YOU SEE HER, JUST DO WHATEVER
YOU CAN.
WE DEFINITELY APPRECIATE IT.
>> Reporter: RELYING ON THEIR
FAITH BROUSSARD'S PARENTS ARE
PRAYING FOR THE MOMENT THEY CAN
EMBRACE THEIR DAUGHTER AND
GRANDDAUGHTER.
>> NO WORDS.
THERE WILL JUST BE HEARTBEATS.
>> Reporter: THE WAIT HAS BEEN
AGONIZING FOR THIS FAMILY.
BROUSSARD SAID THAT IF HIS
DAUGHTER IS BEING HELD BY
SOMEONE, SHE IS ABSOLUTELY A
FIGHTER.
THEY ALSO SAID THAT THERE IS NO
WAY SHE WOULD LEAVE HER SON SO
THEY KNOW SOMETHING IS WRONG.
CECILIA.
>> SUCH A SAD STORY.
MARCUS, THANK YOU.
MICHAEL.
>>> NOW TO A CAR ACCIDENT CAUGHT
ON CAMERA INVOLVING A TRUCK, A
YOUTUBE STAR AND POP SINGER
ELLIE GOULDING WHO CAME TO THE
RESCUE.
MAGGIE RULLI IS IN LONDON WITH
THE STORY.
GOOD MORNING, MAGGIE.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
THIS WAS A WILD SCENE.
IT HAPPENED JUST UP THE ROAD
FROM HERE.
A YOUTUBE STAR GETTING
ESSENTIALLY SNOWPLOWED BY A
TRUCK AND THE FIRST PERSON ON
THE SCENE WAS A POP STAR, ELLIE
GOULDING.
SHE SAID IT WAS ONE OF THE
CRAZIEST THINGS SHE HAS EVER
SEEN.
CAUGHT ON CAMERA, THIS TRUCK
BARRELING DOWN THE HIGHWAY WITH
A CAR PLASTERED ACROSS HIS
GRILL.
ONLOOKERS DESPERATELY TRY TO GET
THE TRUCK'S ATTENTION AS HE
PUSHES AHEAD SEEMINGLY UNAWARE.
>> I HONESTLY DIDN'T SEE.
>> YOU DIDN'T SEE?
>> I DIDN'T SEE.
>> Reporter: CAUGHT UP IN THE
CONFUSION POP STAR ELLIE
GOULDING.
♪ I'LL LET YOU SET THE PACE ♪
>> Reporter: I'M THE ONE IN THE
CAR CHECKING IT THIS GUY WAS
OKAY.
CRAZIEST THING I'VE EVER SEEN ON
THE ROAD.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Reporter: ELLIE LATER TALKING
TO BBC RADIO ONE.
>> WE SAW A CAR AND FIRST WE
THOUGHT THAT'S WEIRD THEN WE SAW
IT WAS BEING DRAGGED ALONG FOR
ABOUT HALF A MILE OR SOMETHING
SO WE JUST KIND OF DROVE UP
RIGHT NEXT TO IT TO BE LIKE,
MATE, YOU'VE GOT A CAR ON YOU.
>> Reporter: BEHIND THE WHEEL OF
THAT T-BONED CARJACK JOY, THE
YOUTUBE STAR BEHIND CAR THROTTLE
DUBBED THE PLACE FOR THE NEXT
GENERATION OF YOUNG CAR FANS.
DES
DESPITE THE DANGEROUS RIDE NO
INJURIES REPORTED.
THEY'RE CALLING IT A PERSONAL
MATTER AND SAY THEY'RE NOT
INVESTIGATING.
NOW, THAT TRUCK INVOLVED WAS
PART OF THE ROYAL MAIL.
THEY SAY THEY ARE INVESTIGATING
AND THEN YOU ARE WONDERING HOW A
YOUTUBE STAR WHO SPECIALIZES IN
CARS COULD HAVE ENDED UP AT THE
CENTER OF A VIRAL CAR CRASH.
GUYS.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU, MAGGIE.
>>> VIDEO NOW OF THAT CLOSE
ENCOUNTER WITH A BROWN BEAR WE
SHOWED YOU.
IT TAKES US INSIDE THE CAR THE
MOMENT THE BEAR JUMPS ON TOP.
IT TURNS OUT THE BEAR SPOTTED A
DOG INSIDE.
>> THE DOG SPOTTED THE BEAR
RIGHT BACK.
IT WAS A BIT OF THIS.
A BIT OF A STARING MATCH BETWEEN
THE TWO ANIMALS.
THE BEAR IN SEQUOIA NATIONAL
PARK IS HIGHLY INQUISITIVE AND
THE WIDE ANGLE VIEW WENT VIRAL.
SOMEHOW THE MAN INSIDE THE CAR
HAD THE WITHWITHAL TO FILM
EVERYTHING.
THIS MORNING, NEW VIDEO FROM
INSIDE THE CAR THAT A BEAR WAS
FILMED JUMPING ON TOP OF AT
SEQUOIA NATIONAL PARK EARLIER
THIS MONTH.
THAT VIDEO WENT VIRAL.
BUT NOW WE HAVE A FIRSTHAND LOOK
FROM THE CALIFORNIA MAN INSIDE
SHOWING JUST HOW CLOSE THE
ENCOUNTER REALLY WAS.
>> I WAS JUST TRYING TO GET A
GOOD VIDEO LIKE CLOSE UP AND
THEN JUST STARTED APPROACHING
THE CAR AND CLIMBED UP.
I WASN'T REALLY SCARED TO BE
HONEST, LIKE BECAUSE I SEE BEARS
AS BIG DOGS LIKE BIG FLUFFY DOGS
BASICALLY.
IT COULD MAUL YOU BUT IT'S A
DOG.
>> Reporter: KARO ORUDZHYAN WAS
VISITING THE PARK WITH HIS DOG
ICE WHO LIVED UP TO HIS NAME,
COOLEY AND QUIETLY STARING BACK
AT THE BEAR AS IT SWIPED AT THE
VEHICLE.
SEPARATED BY JUST A THIN LAYER
OF WINDOW GLASS.
WATCH AS THE BEAR PAWS ITS WAY
TO THE BACK BEFORE MAKING ITS
BIG MOVE.
>> IT JUMPED ON THE TRUNK.
I GOT WORRIED ABOUT THE GLASS
THINKING HIS PAW MIGHT GO
THROUGH IT.
>> Reporter: AN ONLOOKER
CAPTURING THAT AND THE BEAR
HOPPING OFF AS QUICKLY AS IT GOT
ON BEFORE RUNNING AWAY LEAVING
ORUDZHYAN WITH AN INDELIBLE
MEMORY.
>> MY FIRST TIME SEEING A BEAR
ACTUALLY SO I WAS REALLY EXCITED
TO SEE IT.
I'M HAPPY I WAS EVEN ABLE TO
HOLD MY PHONE, YOU KNOW, IN THE
MOMENT.
>> Reporter: NOBODY, NOT KARO OR
ICE OR THE BEAR INJURED.
KARO TELLING OUR AFFILIATE HIS
CAR SUFFERED ONLY A FEW
SCRATCHES AND MENTIONED BEARS
BEING LIKE DOGS.
HE'S NOT WRONG, THEY ARE
DISTANTLY RELATED.
THEY ARE IN THE SAME SUBORDER.
>> CAME AS A FAMILY REUNION.
>> FAMILY REUNION CAUGHT ON
CAMERA FOR THE MEMORY.
>> SOME FAMILY YOU DON'T WANT TO
REUNITE WITH.
>> A GREAT STORY, THANKS.
>>> COMING UP THAT ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE.
HOW THE MAKER OF THE POPULAR
RING CAMERA IS TRYING TO H MISS.
My body is truly powerful.
I have the power to lower
my blood sugar and A1C.
Because I can still
make my own insulin.
And Trulicity activates
my body to release it
like it's supposed to.
Trulicity is for people
with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
Trulicity isn't for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity
if you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if you have an
allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects
may include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea or insulin
increases low blood sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting, belly pain,
and decreased appetite,
which lead to dehydration and
may worsen kidney problems.
I have it within me
to lower my A1C.
Ask your doctor about Trulicity.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
V8 has 30 calories.
For that many calories you
could have 9 Veggie Chips.
These are more chip than
veggie.
While V8 is a snack you can
veg out on.
V8 the original plant powered
drink.
Veg up.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you have fast-acting
power over pain,
So the whole world
looks different.
The unbeatable strength
and speed of Advil Liqui-Gels.
What Pain?
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THAT ABC
NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
THOSE POPULAR RING CAMERAS, YOU
KNOW THEY'VE BEEN IN THE NEWS A
LOT LATELY BUT NOW THERE'S A NEW
WAY THEY MIGHT BE USEFUL TO HELP
FIND KIDNAPPED OR MISSING
CHILDREN.
THE MAKER OF RING IS TEAMING UP
WITH THE NATIONAL CENTER FOR
MISSING & EXPLOITED CHILDREN AND
GIO BENITEZ IS HERE WITH ALL THE
DETAILS ON THIS.
>> HEY, CECILIA, GOOD MORNING.
WE TOLD YOU JUST HERE JUST WEEKS
AGO HOW POLICE DEPARTMENTS ARE
TEAMING UP WITH RING TO CATCH
PORCH PIRATES AND OTHER
CRIMINALS.
NOW THAT TINY LITTLE CAMERA MAY
BE A CRITICAL NEW TOOL IN
FINDING MISSING CHILDREN.
IT'S CAUGHT THIEVES IN THE ACT.
>> HELP ME!
>> Reporter: AND FRIGHTENING
ABDUCTIONS.
>> MY DAUGHTER JUST GOT
KIDNAPPED.
>> Reporter: WHICH EVENTUALLY
LED TO AN ARREST.
NOW THE MAKERS OF THE RING
CAMERA ARE PARTNERING WITH THE
NATIONAL CENTER FOR MISSING &
EXPLOITED CHILDREN TO TRY TO
HELP FIND THE SOME 400,000
CHILDREN AND TEENS WHO GO
MISSING EVERY YEAR.
>> WE WANT TO SAFEGUARD THOSE
COMMUNITIES AND ALSO HELP
RECOVER MISSING CHILDREN BY
POSTING OUR MISSING CHILDREN'S
POSTERS THROUGH THE NEIGHBORS'
APP ALLOWING MORE EYEBALLS TO
SEE THESE MISSING CHILDREN'S
POSTERS IN HOPES THEY CAN
RECOVER THE CHILDREN AND
HOPEFULLY REUNITE THEM.
>> Reporter: THE NEIGHBORS APP
IS FREE AND DESIGNED TO CONNECT
COMMUNITIES WHETHER YOU OWN ONE
OR NOT AND NOW THE NATIONAL
CENTER'S MISSING CHILD POSTERS
WILL APPEAR DIRECTLY IN THE APP
TARGETED TO A THREE TO FIVE-MILE
RADIUS WHERE THE CHILD WAS LAST
SEEN.
>> WE'RE EXCITED OUR INNOVATION
WILL BRING ANOTHER CHANNEL TO
TAKE THEIR INFORMATION AND
FASTER TO A TARGETED AND ENEDGE
GAED COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: "GMA" GIVEN A FIRST
LOOK THIS MORNING AT WHAT THE
ALERTS WILL LOOK LIKE ON THE
APP.
USING THE CASE OF 15-YEAR-OLD
ALICIA THAT REGARD VERY MISSING
SINCE SEPTEMBER FROM GLENDALE,
ARIZONA, USERS CAN CLICK ON THE
PHOTO TO GET MORE INFORMATION,
EVEN COMMENT ON POSSIBLE
SIGHTINGS.
>> BELIEVE IT IS A GAME CHANGER.
THIS HE CAN DO IT IN REALTIME
AND THE FASTER YOU GET TO AN
ENGAGED COMMUNITY THE HIGHER
LIKELIHOOD FOR A POSITIVE
OUTCOME.
>> Reporter: ALREADY IT SOLVED A
CASE.
IN 2018 A 14-YEAR-OLD WENT
MISSING AND HIS PARENTS POSTED
THIS WITH A PLEA FOR HELP AND
THE APP SOMEONE REACHED OUT
KNOWING WHERE HE WAS HELPING TO
GET HIM HOME SAFELY.
>> WHEN A CHILD GOES MISSING
TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
GETTING THIS INFORMATION OUT AS
QUICK AS POSSIBLE IS A GREAT
EXAMPLE OF HARNESSING THE POWER
OF TECHNOLOGY AND LEVERAGING
COMMUNITIES TO HELP BRING
CHILDREN HOME FASTER THAN EVER
BEFORE.
>> Reporter: RING OFFICIALLY
LAUNCHES THIS PROGRAM THIS
MORNING ON THEIR NEIGHBORHOODS'
APP.
IT COULD MAKE SUCH A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
>> HOW DOES THIS DIFFER FROM
AMBER ALERT THAT'S ALREADY OUT
THERE.
>> AMBER ALERT, INCREDIBLY
IMPORTANT.
VERY, VERY HELPFUL.
YOU GET THOSE MESSAGES ON YOUR
PHONE BUT YOU DON'T SEE THE
PHOTO OF THE CHILD AND THAT'S
REALLY WHAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
YOU NEED TO SEE THAT FACE TO GO
AHEAD AND MATCH IT WITH MAYBE
SOMEONE RECOGNIZING THE CHILD IN
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
SO IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
>> THAT IS TRUE.
ALL RIGHT.
GREAT JOB, GIO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> COMING UP, "THE REAL
HOUSEWIVES OF NEW JERSEY" STARS
ARE CALLING IT QUIT, JOE AND
TERESA GIUDICE SEPARATING AFTER
0 YEARS.
ALL THE DETAILS AHEAD.
>>> THE WILD RIDE, ANOTHER
ANIMAL STORY.
THE GIRAFFE THAT JUST WANTED A
SNACK.
IT'S OUR "PLAY OF THE DAY."
(Beep)
The ups and downs
of frequent mood swings
can plummet you
to extreme lows.
(Crying)
Lift you to intense highs.
(Muffled arguing)
Or, make you feel
both at once.
Overwhelmed by
bipolar I symptoms?
Ask about VRAYLAR.
Some medications only treat
the lows or the highs.
VRAYLAR effectively
treats depression,
acute manic and mixed
episodes of bipolar I.
Full-spectrum relief
of all symptoms.
With just one pill,
once a day.
Elderly patients with
dementia-related psychosis
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor
about unusual changes
in behavior or
suicidal thoughts.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in children and young adults.
Report fever, stiff
muscles, or confusion,
which may mean
a life-threatening reaction,
or uncontrollable
muscle movements,
may be permanent.
Side effects may not appear
for several weeks.
Metabolic changes may occur.
Movement dysfunction,
restlessness, sleepiness,
stomach issues are
common side effects.
When bipolar I overwhelms,
VRAYLAR helps smooth
the ups and downs.
Welcome back to our
Holiday PJ party.
It's time to gift wrap.
Did someone say gift rap?
♪ Sittin' with my crew all
cozy by the fire ♪
♪ please don't be so jealous
of my holiday attire ♪
Shop UP TO SEVENTY-FIVE PERCENT
OFF everything,
with gifts for ONE, TWO,
THREE and FOUR BUCKS!
- Are we actually not
wrapping any gifts?
- Only at Old Navy!
We ordered 10,000 units.
That sounds good.
Pretty cool, huh?
They're speaking to Mom in
Japanese, and Mom hears them in
English.
♪
Can you understand me?
Yes, I can understand you.
Okay.
I have a lot of questions.
How do you guys fly? What does
Santa do in the summer?
Is Mrs. Claus a good cook?
Do you guys get presents?
Can you roller skate or ice
skate?
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
♪ BORN TO BE WILD ♪
>> WE ALWAYS GET THE APPROPRIATE
MUSIC.
WE'RE BACK NOW WITH OUR "PLAY OF
THE DAY" AND A QUESTION, WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN YOU DON'T FEED A
HUNGRY GIRAFFE?
WELL, MEET THE MAYNARD FAMILY.
TAKE A LOOK WHAT HAPPENED WHEN
THEY VISITED THE WILD ANIMAL
SAFARI IN GEORGIA.
THE THREE BOYS --
>> WHOA.
>> STOP.
OOH.
>> GETS EVEN BETTER.
>> AAAGH!
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THREE BOYS
WERE IN THE BACKSEAT.
AND THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED.
I LOVE IT.
THAT IS 9-YEAR-OLD WAYNE YELLING
ZEBRA SO IT BE A LITTLE FUN
AFTER CHURCH AND WENT TO CHECK
OUT THE PARK WHERE YOU CAN BUY
FOOD SAFE FOR THE ANIMALS BUT
YOU'RE ADVISED NOT TO FEED THEM
BY THE HAND AND YOU SEE WHY.
>> ARMS AND HANDS INSIDE THE
VEHICLES AT ALL TIMES.
>>> COMING UP WE ARE TAKING YOU
BEHIND THE SCENES BEFORE THAT
HUGE TV EVENT TONIGHT.
"ALL IN THE FAMILY" AND "GOOD
TIMES" L
>> DY-NO-MITE!
riatic arthritis,
little things
can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
differently.
For psoriasis, 75%
clearer skin is achievable,
with reduced redness,
thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis,
Otezla is proven to reduce
joint swelling,
tenderness, and pain.
And the Otezla
Prescribing Information
has no requirement
for routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic
to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have
a history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor
your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory
tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor
about your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat
differently with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
♪ You've got something
up your sleeve ♪
♪ What you didn't know
was you were surprising ♪
♪ your father-in-law Steve ♪
♪ The Best Part of
Wakin' Up is Folgers
in your Cup ♪
♪♪
Capital One knows
life doesn't update you
about your credit card.
So, meet Eno,
the Capital One assistant
that catches things
that might look wrong,
and helps you fix them.
Another way Capital One is
watching out for your money,
when you're not.
What's in your wallet?
♪
What's going on?
Oh, darn!
Let me help.
Here we go. Lift and push and
push!
There... it's up there. Oh, boy.
Hey Joshie...
Wrinkles Send the Wrong Message.
Help prevent them before they
start
with new Downy WrinkleGuard.
Hey! Bud.
Hey, Pop Pop!
So you won't get caught with
wrinkles again.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GOOD
MORNING AMERICA."
YOU KNOW WE GET TO GIVE YOU A
"GMA" MOMENT HERE.
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF DOGS TRAINED
TO USE THE DOORBELL BUT HOW
ABOUT A GOAT?
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THAT'S MAYBELLE IN OKLAHOMA.
WATCH HER.
YEP.
SHE DOES THAT WHEN SHE NEEDS
SOMETHING.
WE THOUGHT THAT WAS SO FUNNY.
THAT ONE WORKED WELL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SENDING
THAT IN.
HOW ABOUT THE SANTA ANA WINDS,
UP TO 91-MILE-PER-HOUR GUSTS.
NOT ONLY WAS IT FLIPPED, DID YOU
SEE IT ACTING LIKE A SAIL.
IT WAS MOVING WITH THE WIND.
CHECK THAT OUT.
UNBELIEVABLE.
STILL HAVE BREEZINESS BUT THE
ATMOSPHERIC RIVERS ARE LINING UP
AND YOU'LL END UP HAVING
MOISTURE AND BELOW AVERAGE
TEMPERATURES RIGHT INTO THE
PACIFIC NORTHWEST.
THIS IS GOING TO MEAN MOUNTAIN
SNOW ESPECIALLY FOR THE CASCADES
AND NORTHERN SIERRA.
>>> COMING UP HERE ON "GMA" A
HEALTH ALERT.
THE NEW STUDY ABOUT HOW BAD
SLEEP CAN AFFECT YOUR RISK OF
MIGRAINES.
DR. ASHTON IS HERE TO TALK ABOUT
THE TIMING.
>>> BEHIND THE SCENES BEFORE THE
LIVE SHOWS OF "GOOD TIMES" AND
"ALL IN THE FAMILY."
THEY'RE BACK.
>>> "JUST MERCY" STAR MICHAEL B.
JORDAN IS HERE IN TIMES SQUARE
LIVE.
THIS WHOLE SEGMENT SPONSORED BY
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY DOWNY WRINKLEGUARD.
WRINKLES SEND THE WRONG MESSAGE.
HELP PREVENT THEM WITH DOWNY
WRINKLEGUARD.
HOPKINS.
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
TODAY CLOSING ARGUMENTS EXPECTED
TO START IN THE TRIAL OF SEAN
URBANSKI.
ACCUSED OF KILLING ARMY
LIEUTENANT RICHARD COLLINS,
2017, UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND.
JUDGE DISMISSED HATE CRIME
CHARGES, EVEN THOUGH HE HAD
RACIST MATERIAL ON HIS HOME, NOT
ENOUGH EVIDENCE THAT THE
STABBING OF COLLINS WAS RACIALLY
MOTIVATED.
>> ADRIANNA: A SETTLEMENT HAS
BEEN -- WASHINGTON GAS WILL PAY
AN UNDISCLOSED AMOUNT.
SEVEN KILLED AUGUST 16TH.
NTSB DETERMINED THE CAUSE WAS
LINKED TO A FAILED GAS
REGULATOR.
>> MELANIE: NOW THE TEMPERATURES
TAKING A DIVE, EILEEN.
>> EILEEN: THAT IS RIGHT.
EVERYONE BELOW FREEZING,
TEMPERATURES, 24-32.
BUNDLE UP OUT THE DOOR WHEN THE
KIDS ARE GETTING OFF THE BUS,
42.
BREEZY TO WINDY.
COLD, 34.
TEMPERATURES MODERATE
APPROACHING CHRISTMAS, JULIE.
>> JULIE: STILL MONITORING
PROBLEMS INTO D.C. NOT EASY OFF
OF 66 CRASH CLEAN UP CONTINUES
AT THIS POINT.
46 MINUTE RIDE INBOUND FROM THE
BELTWAY, TRYING TO GET PAST
FALLS CHURCH.
ONLY ONE LANE OPEN.
EASTBOUND FREEWAY, CRASH AT
THIRD STREET TUNNEL.
ALMOST AN HOUR AND A HALF
COMMUTE, THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC
WATCH.
BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> MELANIE: THANK YOU, JULIE,
GET TRAFFIC, WEATHER, AND NEWS
ANY TIME WITH THE ABC 7 APP.
>> ADRIANNA:
AMERICA" BACK IN TWO MINUTES ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS FOR THE LATEST LOCAL NEWS
ON "GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON."
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
IT'S 8:00 A.M.
IMPEACHMENT DAY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ON THE VERGE OF
BECOMING THE THIRD PRESIDENT
IMPEACHED IN AMERICAN HISTORY.
JUST HOURS FROM NOW THE HISTORIC
VOTE SET.
HOW THE WHITE HOUSE IS PREPARING
AND WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN ON
CAPITOL HILL.
WE'RE LIVE IN WASHINGTON WITH
THE LATEST.
>>> DANGEROUS DEEP FREEZE.
THE COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON
MOVING IN.
TEMPERATURES SET TO PLUNGE ALL
ACROSS THE EAST COAST.
JUST DAYS BEFORE CHRISTMAS.
>>> "GMA" HEALTH ALERT.
THE DOWNSIDE OF NOT GETTING
ENOUGH SLEEP.
HOW IT COULD UP YOUR CHANCES OF
GETTING A MIGRAINE EVEN DAYS
LATER.
DR. ASHTON BREAKS IT DOWN.
>>> CALLING IT QUITS.
THESE AND JOE GUIDICE SPLITTING
AFTER 20 YEARS OF MARRIAGE, TWO
PRISON SENTENCES AND POSSIBLE
DEPORTATION.
>>> GET READY FOR A PRIMETIME
BLAST FROM THE PAST.
"ALL IN THE FAMILY" AND "GOOD
TIMES."
BACK FOR A LIVE SPECIAL EVENT
THIS WEDNESDAY.
OUR BEHIND-THE-SCENES PREVIEW AS
WE COUNT DOWN TO TONIGHT.
♪ 24 KARAT MAGIC ♪
>>> MICHAEL B. JORDAN IS HERE
LIVE BRINGING THE MOVES.
>> NO MATTER WHAT IT IS.
>> DISHING ON HIS BRAND-NEW
MOVIE.
HE'S HERE TO SAY --
>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US ON
THIS WEDNESDAY MORNING AND WE
ARE EXCITED TO HAVE MICHAEL B.
JORDAN HERE WITH US.
>> WE ARE AND FROM MICHAEL B.
JORDAN TO BABY YODA, TAKING OVER
THE GALAXY AND NOW OUR CHRISTMAS
BAKING, WENDY KOU IS HERE TO
SHOW US HOW TO MAKE THESE
COOKIES AT HOME COMING UP.
>>> WE ARE COVERING THIS
HISTORIC VOTE IN THE HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SET TO BECOME
THE THIRD AMERICAN PRESIDENT IN
HISTORY TO BE IMPEACHED.
ANDREW JOHNSON, BILL CLINTON,
THE OTHER TWO.
TWO ARTICLES ABUSE OF POWER,
OBSTRUCTION OF CONGRESS.
BACK TO MARY BRUCE ON CAPITOL
HILL.
GOOD MORNING, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP THIS MORNING IS
ON THE CUSP OF IMPEACHMENT.
IN A SHORT TIME MEMBERS WILL
WALK THROUGH THE HALL AND INTO
THE HOUSE CHAMBER TO BEGIN THE
FINAL DEBATE.
NO QUESTION THIS IS A DAY FOR
HISTORY BUT IT IS ALSO A DAY
THAT THE SPEAKER HAD HOPED TO
AVOID BUT NOW SHE SAYS THE
PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS HAVE SIMPLY
LEFT HER NO CHOICE AND BY THE
END OF THE DAY THE PRESIDENT IS
EXPECTED TO BE IMPEACHED FOR
ABUSING HIS POWER AND
OBSTRUCTING CONGRESS.
THE PRESIDENT THOUGH IS WELL
AWARE OF THE STAIN THIS WILL
LEAVE ON HIS LEGACY AND HE IS
FIGHTING BACK IN HIS TYPICAL
FIERY FASHION, ADAMANT THAT HE
DID NOTHING WRONG.
IN A SCATHING SIX-PAGE LETTER TO
THE SPEAKER, THE PRESIDENT
INSISTS THAT -- EXCUSE ME, THE
PRESIDENT CALLS THE IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS WHICH IS OUTLINED BY THE
CONSTITUTION, QUOTE, AN ILLEGAL
PARTISAN ATTEMPTED COUP.
NOW, THE SPEAKER RESPONDED WITH
TWO WORDS CALLING IT "REALLY
SICK," CECILIA.
>> MARY BRUCE, THANK YOU.
GEORGE WILL ANCHOR LIVE COVERAGE
OF THE IMPEACHMENT OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP WITH OUR ENTIRE POLITICAL
TEAM STARTING AT 9:00 A.M.
EASTERN.
WE ARE NOW GOING TO TURN TO THAT
BRUTAL DEEP FREEZE HERE IN THE
NORTHEAST WITH WINDCHILLS BELOW
ZERO EXPECTED FROM WASHINGTON TO
BOSTON.
GINGER, OF COURSE, IS TRACKING
THAT BITTER COLD AND THE ICY
MESS ON THE ROADS.
IT IS MESSY OUT THERE, BEGINER.
>> THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
WE HAD FREEZING DRIZZLE OR RAIN
FOR ALMOST THE ENTIRE DAY
YESTERDAY.
THIS IS MY BACKYARD.
WE'RE ENCASED IN ICE, A QUARTER
TO A HALF INCH EASILY.
IN MARYLAND, IT WAS HIGHER THAN
THAT AND THE POWER LINES DID NOT
DO WELL.
THOUSANDS WITHOUT POWER BECAUSE
OF THAT.
THE FIRE WAS CAUSED BY A POWER
LINE CAUSING AND, PILEUP,
SPINOUTS ANDS THAT PEA WHAT THEY
DID THIS MASSACHUSETTS DOWN TO
CONNECTICUT.
LOTS OF PICTURES.
I WISH I COULD TELL YOU IT'S
GOING SOMEWHERE AND IT WILL
BOTTOM OUT.
IT WILL TOMORROW MORNING AND
THAT'S WHY WE'RE NOT GOING TO
SEE ANY OF THAT ICE GO ANYWHERE.
IT WILL FEEL LIKE 8 BELOW IN
BOSTON.
THE COLDEST AIR SETTLING IN.
NEW YORK CITY WITH ACTUAL
TEMPERATURES IN THE TEENS WILL
FEEL SUBZERO, 7, PITTSBURGH, 10,
CINCINNATI AND DOESN'T STOP
THERE.
FLORIDA, YOU'RE NOT IMMUNE,
JACKSONVILLE OVER TO
TALLAHASSEE, A FREEZE WATCH
ALONG THE STATE LINE OF FLORIDA
AND GEORGIA SO IT GOES DEEP THIS
TIME.
>> JUST HOLD ON TO THE THOUGHT
THAT SPRING IS COMING
EVENTUALLY.
WE'LL GET THERE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GINGER.
>>> COMING UP, WHAT TERESA AND
JOE GUIDICE ARE SAYING ABOUT
SEPARATING AFTER 20 YEARS OF
MARRIAGE.
>>> THE NEW STUDY ABOUT
MIGRAINES AND POOR SLEEP.
DR. ASHTON IS HERE TO BREAK IT
DOWN FOR US AND LARA IS
UPSTAIRS.
>> WE HAVE A BIG SURPRISE FOR
MILITARY FAMILIES IN VIRGINIA.
♪ CHRISTMAS IS HERE AGAIN ♪
>> IS THAT THEM?
>> "GMA'S" SECRET SANTA IS ON
THE WAY.
I WAS WHISPERING FOR THAT BUT
I'M NOT FOR THIS.
THE BEST AUDIENCE IN THE BIZ
RIGHT HERE ON "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA."
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT B
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
Everything your trip needs
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
Hi Mom. Hi Dad.
Hey.
How's my little princess?
I want to be a movie director.
Oh!
That's great.
♪♪
Delicious high-fiber
Raisin Bran.
You sure you don't want
me to come with you?
I'm very sure.
Because I can.
(laughs)
Make good choices.
You make good choices.
I am.
Fiber is good for
DIGESTIVE HEALTH.
Good choices never
tasted so good.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
NyQuil Severe gives you powerful
relief
for your worst cold and
flu symptoms,
on Sunday Night and every night.
NyQuil Severe.
The Nightime, Sniffling,
Sneezing,
Coughing, Aching, Stuffy Head,
Best Sleep with a Cold,
Medicine.
♪
So Josh, you going for our
Drive Safe and Save discount?
Yup, using the app.
Driving safe.
You wanna go bro?
Do not mess with my discount.
Woooo!
(sighs)
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe and Save™.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Welcome to our
Lipton tea factory.
Where these sun-soaked
tea leaves
are picked at the peak
of freshness.
For a naturally smooth taste.
And drinking Lipton
every day
can help support a
healthy heart!
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA" AND I
GOT TO SAY WE HAVE A GREAT
WEDNESDAY AUDIENCE HERE IN OUR
STUDIO WITH US.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND WE'RE COUNTING DOWN TO "STAR
WARS," YOU GUYS, SO TOMORROW,
STAR OSCAR ISAAC IS GOING TO
JOIN US HERE LIVE.
CANNOT WAIT FOR THAT.
GOT TO GET SECRETS OUT OF HIM.
>> BUT FIRST IT'S TIME FOR "POP
NEWS" WITH LARA.
>> YES, INDEED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU, GUYS.
GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY.
WE'RE GOING TO BEGIN WITH ONE OF
OUR FAVORITE PERFORMERS, LIZZO
WHOSE SONG "GOOD AS HELL" DOES
NOT TRY HOW SHE'S FEELING.
OVERNIGHT SHE CANCELED TWO SHOWS
DUE TO THE FLU.
YEAH.
WE'RE WISHING HER THE BEST.
"TIME" MAGAZINE'S ENTERTAINER OF
THE YEAR WRITING IN A STATEMENT
I'M SO SORRY.
I HATE LETTING MY FANS DOWN MORE
THAN ANYTHING.
I HOPE THAT YOU ALL CAN FORGIVE
ME WHILE I RECOVER AND I PROMISE
WE ARE DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
LIZZO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
THAT.
JUST GET BETTER.
WE UNDERSTAND.
>> YEAH, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> YOU HAD A BIG YEAR.
SHARING THIS PHOTO ON INSTAGRAM
OF THE MOMENT HER FEVER DROPPED
BELOW 100 DEGREES ASKING FANS
FOR SUPPORT.
WRITING, Y'ALL, I'VE NEVER BEEN
THIS SICK.
PLEASE PRAY FOR ME.
LIZZO'S NEXT GIG IS ON NEW WE'RE
EVE IN LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE HOPING SHE'S ALL BETTER BY
THEN.
>> YES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NO FUN.
>>> ALSO POPPING THIS MORNING
MARIAH CAREY IS ADDING NEW
MEANING TO THE TERM MERRY AND
BRIGHT THIS HOLIDAY SEASON
FLIPPING THE SWITCH ON THE
EMPIRE STATE BUILDING'S LIGHT
SHOW IN HONOR OF THE 25th
ANNIVERSARY OF HER HIT "ALL I
WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS YOU."
WHAT A BIG HONOR THEY BESTOWED
ON HER.
THERE'S THE VIDEO OF THE
ORIGINAL.
THE SONG MAY BE A QUARTER
CENTURY OLD BUT IT'S NEVER BEEN
MORE POPULAR FINALLY HITTING
NUMBER ONE ON THE BILLBOARD
CHARTS FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER
AND NOW MARIAH GIVING US ANOTHER
GIFT, A BRAND-NEW VIDEO TO GO
ALONG WITH THE SONG.
MARIAH SHARING THIS CLIP WITH
FANS ON TWITTER, TAKE A LOOK.
♪ YEAH I DON'T WANT A LOT FOR
CHRISTMAS ♪
♪ THERE IS JUST ONE THING I
NEED ♪
>> YES.
>> AMAZING.
>> EXACTLY THE SAME.
>> WHAT A FAN LIKE THAT.
>> LOOKS SO MUCH THE SAME.
I THOUGHT -- THAT'S NOT NEW.
>> IT DOESN'T HAVE THE QUALITY
OF THE VIDEO AND THERE ARE MANY
WHO THINK THE ORIGINAL WAS JUST
PERFECT AS IT WAS BUT THAT
LOOKED GOOD.
THE ORIGINAL HAS OVER 600
MILLION VIEWS ON YOUTUBE.
JUST SUCH A SONG THAT IS --
>> MAKES YOU HAPPY.
>> WE LOVE IT.
YOU CAN SEE THE NEW VERSION OF
THE VIDEO DECEMBER 20th AT
MIDNIGHT.
THAT'S WHEN IT DROPS.
IF YOU'RE IN NEW YORK CITY THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON PLEASE DO STOP BY
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING.
ITS LIGHT SHOW SET TO "ALL I
WANT FOR CHRISTMAS" PLAYS EVERY
NIGHT AT 8:00 P.M. THROUGH
CHRISTMAS.
I RECOMMEND IT AND IT'S FREE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>>> ALSO IN THE NEWS, WE WANT TO
YOU MEET A MOM WHO KNEW THE
LIMBS OF HER MULTITASKING AND
FIGURED OUT HOW TO BE IN TWO
PLACES AT ONCE.
THE MOM MADE A LIFE-SIZE CUTOUT,
MADE TWO.
THOSE ARE CUTOUTS OF HERSELF TO
HELP HER TODDLER SON COPE WHEN
SHE LEAVES THE ROOM.
HE WOULD GET VERY UPSET IF SHE
WENT TO THE NEXT ROOM AND SHE
HAD TO DO THINGS LIKE GO TO THE
BATHROOM SO SHE HAD TO DO IT.
SHE SHARED THESE PHOTOS ON
TWITTER OF THE CUTOUTS, ONE
SITTING, ONE STANDING AND PUT
THEM TO THE TEST TO SEE IF HER
SON WOULD NOTICE.
MOM AND DAD WROTE THAT THE
CUTOUTS ARE NOT USED AS
REPLACEMENTS OF MOM.
JUST A WAY FOR THE TODDLER TO
FEEL LIKE HE'S CONNECTED AND
NEVER TOO FAR WHEN SHE'S IN THE
NEXT ROOM SO I JUST WANT TO SAY
BEFORE YOU SEND NOTES THIS IS IN
NO WAY A SUBSTITUTE FOR THE REAL
THING.
SHE JUST NEEDS SOMETIMES TO DO,
YOU KNOW, WHAT WE NEED TO DO.
>> AND I WONDER WHAT THE KID --
DID SHE SET THEM UP IN FRONT OF
THE KID?
DOES SHE --
>> I THINK SHE DOES IT WHEN HE'S
BUSY PLAYING WITH BLOCKS SO IF
HE LOOKS UP, HE DOESN'T FREAK
OUT.
>> GO TO COLLEGE WITH THEM?
>> THE FIRST TIME HE GOES TO
GIVE A HUG AND SHE FALLS OVER,
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
>>> FINALLY, EVERYBODY, THE
HUMANE SOCIETY IN MISSOURI JUST
HELD THEIR ANNUAL DECK THE HOWLS
EVENT WHERE KIDS COME TO THE
SHELTER AND READ TO THE ANIMALS.
I THINK THIS IS SO GREAT.
THESE ANIMALS ARE WAITING FOR
THEIR FOREVER HOMES.
THE KIDS WEAR THEIR FAVORITE
PJs, SOMETIMES SANTA SUIT AND
READ HOLIDAY STORIES TO THE
ANIMAL BY CANDLELIGHT.
THE HUMANE SOCIETY HAS BEEN
DOING IT FOR FIVE YEARS.
ORIGINALLY STARTING THE PROGRAM
TO HELP SHELTER DOGS BECOME MORE
COMFORTABLE AROUND KIDS.
HELPING THEM BECOME MORE
ADOPTABLE EVEN.
THEY SAY OVER THE YEARS IT'S
ALSO HELPED KIDS GROW MORE
CONFIDENT READING IN FRONT OF
AUDIENCES.
THE SHELTER SAYS SINCE THE
PROGRAM STARTED THEY'VE REDUCED
THE AVERAGE TIME DOGS ARE IN
SHELTERS BY AN AVERAGE OF SIX
DAYS BECAUSE THEY GET MORE
COMFORTABLE AROUND HUMANS.
>> WIN/WIN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THAT'S "POP NEWS," EVERYBODY.
>> THAT IS A GREAT "POP NEWS."
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT,
LARA.
>>> NOW WE'RE GOING TO GO TO OUR
"GMA" COVER STORY.
"THE REAL HOUSEWIVES OF NEW
JERSEY" STARS JOE AND TERESA
GIUDICE REVEALING THEY'RE
CALLING IT QUITS SEPARATING
AFTER 20 YEARS OF MARRIAGE.
PAULA FARIS HAS MORE.
>> THEY WERE CHILDHOOD
SWEETHEARTS BUT HAVE BEEN LIVING
APART FOR FOUR YEARS AND THIS
MORNING THE NEWS WE'VE EXPECTED
FOR SOME TIME, THEY'RE SPLITTING
UP.
THIS MORNING, TERESA AND JOE ARE
CALLING IT QUITS AFTER 20 YEARS
OF MARRIAGE, TWO PRISON
SENTENCES AND POSSIBLE
DEPORTATION, THE REAL HOUSEWIFE
OF NEW JERSEY, TERESA GIUDICE IS
SAYING THAT SHE IS ENDING HER
RELATIONSHIP WITH HUSBAND JOE.
A SOURCE SAYING DIVORCE IS
CURRENTLY NOT ON THE TABLE FOR
THEM.
WE SPOKE WITH TERESA WHEN SHE
RETURNED FROM SEEING JOE AFTER
HE WAS SENT BACK TO ITALY IN
OCTOBER.
>> ARE YOU PLANNING ON FILING
FOR DIVORCE?
>> NO.
>> DO YOU SEE A FUTURE WITH HIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU COULD FIND
HAPPINESS AND LOVE AGAIN WITH
JOE?
>> TO BE DETERMINED.
>> SO YOU HAVEN'T RULED IT OUT.
>> WE'RE TAKING IT DAY BY DAY.
>> Reporter: OVER A DECADE AGO
TERESA DAY PEWED ON "THE REAL
HOUSEWIVES OF NEW JERSEY"
VIBRANT AND OUTSPOKEN AND MAKING
HER MARK WITH THIS UNFORGETTABLE
MOMENT.
FANS HAD BEEN WATCHING
THROUGHOUT THE YEARS AS TERESA
AND JOE'S MARRIAGE HAS SUSTAINED
MAJOR UPS AND DOWNS, TERESA
SPENT ALMOST A YEAR IN FEDERAL
PRISON FOR MULTIPLE COUNTS OF
FRAUD WHILE JOE SERVED MORE THAN
THREE YEARS FOR MAIL, WIRE AND
BANKRUPTCY FRAUD.
AFTER HIS RELEASE JOE WHO IS NOT
A U.S. CITIZEN WAS IMMEDIATELY
SENT TO AN I.C.E. DETENTION
FACILITY FIGHTING DEPORTATION.
NOW LIVING IN ITALY, JOE AWAITS
THE RULING ON HIS THIRD
DEPORTATION APPEAL.
>> HOW DO YOU MAKE A MARRIAGE
LIKE THAT WORK?
I MEAN IT'S KIND OF HARD LIKE I
WANT TO WAKE UP WITH SOMEONE, GO
TO SLEEP WITH SOMEONE -- I WANT
TO WAKE UP -- I WANT TO SPEND
EVERY DAY WITH THAT PERSON.
>> Reporter: JOE IS REPORTEDLY
ALREADY SEEING OTHER PEOPLE BUT
TERESA IS STAYING FOCUSED ON HER
DAUGHTERS, BUSINESS VENTURES AND
TAKING CARE OF HER FATHER.
>> YOU'D BE OKAY SEEING HIM
HAPPY WITH ANOTHER WOMAN.
>> OF COURSE, IF THAT'S THE PATH
WE CHOOSE, YES.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'D BE HAPPY
SEEING YOU WITH ANOTHER MAN?
>> WE ONLY REALLY WANT THE BEST
FOR EACH OTHER.
>> AND THEIR FOUR DAUGHTERS ARE
HEADED TO ITALY FOR CHRISTMAS TO
SPEND TIME WITH THEIR FATHER,
JOE.
TERESA, MEANTIME, IS STAYING IN
NEW JERSEY TO BE WITH HER
FATHER.
THIS IS ALL VERY AMICABLE BUT WE
HAD A STRONG SENSE THIS WAS OVER
WHEN WE SPOKE WITH HER LAST
MONTH AND SAID SHE HAD NO PLANS
ON GOING BACK TO ITALY TO SEE
HIM.
>> WE ARE WISHING THEM WELL.
>>> A "GMA" HEALTH ALERT ABOUT
THE DANGERS OF NOT GETTING
ENOUGH SLEEP.
A STUDY SAYS LESS SLEEP COULD
INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF GETTING
A MIGRAINE.
DR. ASHTON IS HERE TO BREAK ALL
OF THIS DOWN FOR US.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> HERE WE GO, ANOTHER ONE.
>> TALKING ABOUT SLEEP.
WE DON'T KNOW A LOT ABOUT THE
CONNECTION BETWEEN SLEEP AND
MIGRAINES SO THIS IS AN
IMPORTANT STUDY.
>> LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT IT.
IT WAS DONE IN BOSTON.
APPEARED IN THE JOURNAL
"NEUROLOGY."
98 PATIENTS WITH A HISTORY OF
MIGRAINE AND FOLLOWED THEM FOR
SIX WEEKS AND GAVE THEM
QUESTIONNAIRES AND TRACKED SLEEP
WITH A WRIST DEVICE AND WHAT
THEY WERE LOOKING AT WAS HOW
LONG THEY SLEPT, HOW WELL THEY
SLEPT AND HOW EFFICIENTLY THEY
SLEPT AND DEFINED EFFICIENCY AS
HOW MANY HOURS OF ACTUALLY SLEEP
THEY GOT WHILE THEY WERE AT REST
AND THE FINDINGS WHICH WERE THE
FIRST OF ITS KIND SHOWED THAT
PEOPLE WITH LOW SLEEP EFFICIENCY
HAD AN INCREASED RISK BY 39% OF
GETTING A MIGRAINE, NOT THE NEXT
MORNING THAT THEY WOKE UP, BUT A
DAY LATER.
SO THIS WAS THE FIRST STUDY TO
SHOW THIS PARTICULAR ASSOCIATION
WITH TIMING OF MIGRAINES AND THE
LARGEST OF ITS KIND.
>> A DAY LATER IS REALLY
IMPORTANT.
DO WE KNOW WHAT CAUSES
MIGRAINES?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, WE DON'T.
THERE ARE A LOT OF THEORIES AND
THERE ARE A LOT OF KNOWN
TRIGGERS.
THE KEY IF YOU SUFFER FROM
CLASSIC MIGRAINES IS KNOWING
WHAT YOUR TRIGGER IS.
BUT THAT LIST IS PRETTY
EXTENSIVE AND A LOT OF IT
REVOLVES AROUND CHANGES IN
THINGS THAT WE DO ALL THE TIME
SO CHANGES IN EATING CERTAIN
FOODS OR EXPOSURE TO ALCOHOL OR
CHANGES IN WEATHER, IN SLEEP,
HORMONAL CHANGE, EVEN STRESS,
ONCE YOU CAN IDENTIFY YOUR
TRIGGER, THEN YOU CANNOT ONLY
HELP TO TARGET IT AND AVOID IT
BUT IF POSSIBLE EVEN
PROPHYLACTICALLY TREAT IT WITH
CERTAIN MEDICATION.
>> HERE WE ARE ONCE AGAIN
TALKING ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF
SLEEP.
>> YES.
>> CONNECTED TO SO MANY THINGS
IN OUR LIFE.
>> RIGHT, ON THE SHOW WHERE WE
ALL DON'T GET A LOT.
THIS FIELD OF SLEEP MEDICINE
INVOLVES PULL MOW KNOLL GIST,
EAR, NOSE AND THROAT SPECIALIST,
PSYCHIATRISTS AND AN AREA OF
INTENSE SLEEPING BUT NOT HOW
MUCH BUT THE QUALITY SO WHAT I'M
TELLING PEOPLE, THINK OF SLEEP
AS THE CORNERSTONE OF NOT ONLY
OUR HEALTH, BUT OUR ILLNESS AND
DISEASE AS WELL IF YOU'RE
FEELING GOOD, LOOK AT YOUR SLEEP
BECAUSE THAT'S LIKELY GOING
WELL.
IF YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL, LOOK
AT YOUR SLEEP FIRST.
>> DOCTOR'S ORDER, GO TO SLEEP.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> LARA, OVER TO YOU.
> I'M LISTENING.
>>> RIGHT NOW WE'RE GOING BEHIND
THE SCENES OF TONIGHT'S HUGE
LIVE TV EVENT.
TWO ALL-STAR CASTS BRINGING THE
CLASSICS "ALL IN THE FAMILY" AND
"GOOD TIMES" TO LIFE FOR A
SPECIAL "LIVE IN FRONT OF A
STUDIO AUDIENCE" EVENT.
CHRIS CONNELLY IS IN L.A. WITH
DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING, CHRIS.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, LAHR
R WE ARE AT SONY STUDIOS IN
CULVER CITY WHERE WE ARE IN
FRONT OF THE TALENT TRAILERS
WHERE TONIGHT'S ELITE PERFORMERS
WILL BE CHILLAXING UNTIL
8:00 P.M. EASTERN WHEN ALL THESE
WONDERFUL PERFORMERS WILL BE A
WHOLE LOT OF LIVE.
>> I WAS SO EXCITED WHEN THEY
ANNOUNCED THAT THEY WERE DOING
ANOTHER ONE BECAUSE IT'S JUST A
THRILL.
♪ BOY THE WAY GLENN MILLER
PLAYED SONGS THAT MADE THE HIT
PARADE ♪
>> Reporter: IT'S BACK.
THIS TIME ALL-STAR CASTS PERFORM
HOLIDA
HOLIDAY-THEMED EPISODES.
THE GROUNDBREAKING "GOOD TIMES"
AND ICONIC "ALL IN THE FAMILY."
>> WE GAINED A MEATHEAD.
>> Reporter: "LIVE IN FRONT OF A
STUDIO AUDIENCE," LIVE TO THE
WORLD.
>> DON'T TRY TO BUTTER ME UP,
UH, EDITH.
>> NO RUSH THAT'S PROBABLY EQUAL
TO THAT IN WHAT I DO.
>> IT IS VERY MUCH LIKE IF YOU
TOOK LIKE AN AMERICANA AND
POURED IN A RED BULL THEN A JOLT
COLA AND THEN GAVE A QUICK
DEFIBRILLATOR.
>> WHAT IS THE ADRENALINE GOING
TO BE LIKE RIGHT BEFORE YOU GO
OUT.
>> YOU SAY ADRENALINE.
I SAY NERVES.
I SAY SHEER FEAR BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT, IT IS EXCITING TO ME
BECAUSE I HAVE A 31-YEAR CAREER.
I COME FROM THE THEATER.
I LIVE FOR THAT ADRENALINE.
♪ DECK THE HALLS WITH BOUGHS OF
HOLLY ♪
>> Reporter: CENTERED ON THE
FAMILY OF FLORIDA, A MAID OF
EDITH'S COUSIN MAUDE.
>> YOU'RE IN MY CHAIR, MAUDE.
>> Reporter: "GOOD TIMES" WAS
MUCH WHO ARE THAN A SPIN-OFF OF
A SPIN-OFF.
>> THE EVANS ARE A BLACK FAMILY
LIVING IN THE PROJECTS IN
CHICAGO.
THERE'S A KIND OF EARTHINESS, A
REALITY THAT NORMAN LEAR IS
TRYING TO SET UP IN A CERTAIN
WAY THAT I THINK IS APPEALING TO
PEOPLE.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> Reporter: ITS CAST AND TWO
AFRICAN-AMERICAN CREATOR MADE IT
A MAJOR TV MILESTONE AND A
SOURCE OF LAUGHTER AND
INSPIRATION TO VIOLA DAVIS.
>> TO SEE A FAMILY LIVING IN A
SORT OF FINANCIALLY CHALLENGING
SITUATION IN THE GHETTO BUT
STILL TRYING TO FIND SOME, YOU
KNOW, PATCHES OF JOY AND
HAPPINESS AND FORWARD MOVEMENT
AND STILL THRIVING JUST REALLY
SPOKE TO ME.
>> Reporter: "GOOD TIMES" ALSO
FEATURED A BREAKOUT CHARACTER IN
OLDER SON J.J. AND "SNL" VET JAY
PHAROAH READY TO DEPLOY HIS
CATCHPHRASE THAT SWEPT THE
NATION.
>> DY-NO-MITE!
>> YOU GO LIKE THIS AND SAY
DY-NO-MITE.
IT JUST MAKES YOU FEEL GOOD.
>> Reporter: CORRINE FOX,
DAUGHTER OF JAMIE FOXX WHO
STARRED AS GEORGE JEFFERSON LAST
SPRING.
>> YOU HEAR THAT.
SHE CALLED ME MR. JEFFERSON.
>> Reporter: IS ON BOARD AS THE
EVANS DAUGHTER THELMA.
>> HE KEEPS OFFERING TO HELP ME.
I'LL HELP YOU RUNG YOUR LINES.
I'M LIKE, I HAVE VIOLA DAVIS TO
RUN MY LINES.
>> Reporter: 50 YEARS AFTER ITS
INCEPTION "ALL IN THE FAMILY"
AND ARCHIE BUNKER STILL STIR
AUDIENCES TO LAUGHTER AND
OUTRAGE AND BACK AGAIN.
>> YOU AIN'T GOT A BLACK
PRESIDENT, JEFFERSON, BECAUSE
GOD AIN'T READY FOR THAT YET.
>> WAIT A SECOND.
WAIT A SECOND.
WHAT?
>> IT FEELS LIKE AS MUCH AS
THINGS HAVE CHANGED THEY ALSO
HAVE NOT CHANGED AS MUCH SO SOME
OF THE LINES THAT COME OUT OF
ARCHIE'S MOUTH YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE IS SAYING THIS.
>> WHAT IS IT LIKE TO GET THE
LAUGHS FROM THE LIVE STUDIO
AUDIENCE WHEN PLAYING THIS
CHARACTER?
>> THAT IS EUPHORIA.
>> IT COULDN'T BE MORE EXCITING.
WHAT I GET OUT OF IT ALL, THE
LAUGHTER I GET OUT, I AM
POSITIVE HAS ADDED TIME TO MY
LIFE
♪ THOSE WERE THE DAYS ♪
>> SO LET THERE BE LAUGHTER AND
LOTS OF IT TONIGHT, LARA.
>> I CANNOT WAIT.
CHRIS, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU GUYS CAN CHECK IT OUT
TONIGHT ON ABC.
MEANTIME, WE NEED TO HEAD OVER
TO GINGER.
>> LARA, I'VE GOT A "GMA" MOMENT
FROM DAVENPORT, IOWA.
SOMEBODY IS NOT IN THE HOLIDAY
SPIRIT.
♪
♪ SILENT NIGHT ♪
>> YEAH.
THAT'S 4-YEAR-OLD LIAM.
HE DOES THE WHOLE SONG LIKE
THAT, BY THE WAY.
THANK YOU FOR SENDING THAT TO
US.
WE GOT A GOOD LAUGH.
HOPE YOU DID TOO.
SHARE YOUR "GMA"
>> Eileen: WELL, STORM WATCH 7
TRACKING SUNSHINE, BUT ALSO
TUMBLING TEMPERATURES AS WE HEAD
THROUGH TONIGHT AND INTO
TOMORROW.
NOTICE YOUR NEXT HOURS, 42
TODAY, BUT TONIGHT WE'RE DOWN
INTO THE 20S UNDER CLEAR SKIES.
WINDCHILL VALUES TOMORROW
MORNING THIS TIME WILL BE IN THE
TEENS.
SUNNY BUT COLD TOMORROW, 34
DEGREES.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE LOOKING
DRY AS WE HEAD INTO THE UPCOMING
WEEKEND.
WINTER BEGINS ON SATURDAY.
42.
THE FIRST DAY OF HANUKKAH ON
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WE TURN TO AN EMMY AWARD WINNING
REALITY SHOW CALLED "BORN THIS
WAY" CHANGING THE WAY WE
PERCEIVE PEOPLE WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
ABBIE BOUDREAU SAT DOWN WITH THE
CAST.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
>> Reporter: THE CAST BACK
TOGETHER FOR ONE LAST TIME WITH
AN EMOTIONAL HOLIDAY SERIES
FINALE.
>> YOU ARE MY INSPIRATION.
th THE EMMY AWARD WINNING
REALITY SHOW FOLLOWING THE LIVES
OF YOUNG ADULTS WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT THEM TO SEE.
>> THAT I'M A PUBLIC SPEAKER.
I WANT THEM TO SEE HOW MUCH I'VE
GROWN LIKE INDEPENDENT.
>> IS THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU AS
HER FATHER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THEY ARE CAPABLE OF MANY, MANY
THING, MUCH MORE THAN MOST
PEOPLE KNOW.
>> WHAT ARE SOME COMMON
MISCONCEPTIONS ABOUT PEOPLE WITH
DOWN SYNDROME.
>> I THINK SOME OF THE BIGGEST
MISCONCEPTIONS IS THAT THEY
CAN'T BE INCLUDED IN CLASSROOMS.
THAT THEY CAN'T GRADUATE FROM
HIGH SCHOOL.
THEY CAN'T HAVE JOBS OR
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> OR GET MARRIED.
>> OR GET MARRIED OR LIVE
INDEPENDENTLY.
>> Reporter: BUT THE SHOW
SHATTERING THOSE STEREOTYPES.
AND MAKING A REAL DIFFERENCE.
>> I SEE ALL THE MOMS COMING TO
ME AND SAYING, YOU REALLY HAVE
TOUCHED ME AND MY CHILD AND I
WANT TO KEEP MY CHILD BECAUSE OF
YOU GUYS.
>> Reporter: RACHEL AND MEGAN
WITH BIG DREAMS BEYOND THE SHOW.
>> MY NEXT STEP IS MOVIES.
>> WHAT IS NEXT FOR YOU?
>> I THINK TRYING TO START TO
HAVE MY OWN TALK SHOW.
AND BE A TV HOST.
LIKE "GOOD MORNING AMERICA"
OR --
>> SHE'S TRYING TO TAKE MY JOB.
TRYING TO TOTALLY TAKE MY JOB.
>> DON'T LIMIT HER.
>> Reporter: FOR "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA," I'M ABBIE BOUDREAU,
LOS ANGELES.
>> THANKS TO ABBIE FOR THAT
SPECIAL STORY.
THE "BORN THIS WAY" SERIES AIRS
TONIGHT ON A&E.
>>> COMING UP, GUYS, MICHAEL B.
JORDAN.
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
VERY BUSY MORNING ON THE ROADS.
GLEEB ROAD TO ROUTE 50 WEST SHUT
DOWN.
ONE OF MANY ACCIDENTS ON THE
MORNING COMMUTE.
LET'S HEAD TO JULIE WRIGHT FOR
AN UPDATE.
>> JULIE: THAT IS ONE OF THEM.
WE STILL HAVE RESIDUAL DELAYS.
BACKED UP FROM WASHINGTON
BOULEVARD FINALLY IMPROVEMENT
HERE ON 66.
LONG STANDING CRASH CLEARED.
30 MINUTE RIDE BELTEDWAY TO THE
ROOSEVELT BRIDGE.
>> EILEEN: ALL RIGHT.
DRY PAVEMENT, SUNNY AND COLD.
HIGH, 42.
35 BY 5:00 MORE CLOUDS AND MAYBE
A FEW FLURRIES.
TOMORROW MORNING, WIND CHILL
TEENS, TOMORROW HIGH 34.
DRY THROUGH THE WEEKEND AND INTO
NEXT WEEK HIGHS INTO THE 50S,
GUYS.
>> ADRIANNA: GET TRAFFIC,
WEATHER, AND NEWS ANY TIME WITH
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> JESSOB:
NEWS ON "GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON."
AMERICA" BACK IN ONE MINUTE ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS FOR THE LATEST LOCAL NEWS
ON "GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON."
♪
♪ THAT'S JUST THE WAY YOU MAKE
ME FEEL ♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA" AND WE
HAVE A GREAT GUEST TO BRING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW HIM FROM THE "CREED"
MOVIES AND "BLACK PANTHER" NOW
STARRING IN AND PRODUCING THE
NEW MOVIE, "JUST MERCY," PLEASE
WELCOME MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING, LARA.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> HELLO.
HELLO.
>> PLEASURE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> REALLY GOOD, MAN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YOU KNOW, I'M JUST GOING TO
SAY, I HAVE NOT -- I HAVE NOT
SEEN A -- WE HAVEN'T SEEN A
STANDING OVATION IN A LONG TIME,
MAN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> MY FAN CLUB TRAVELS IN PACKS
RIGHT HERE SO I APPRECIATE THEM
SHOWING UP TO REPRESENT.
>> WE CALLED IN EXTRA SECURITY
SO WE GOT YOU, MAN.
YOU GREW UP IN THE NEW YORK
AREA.
>> I DID.
>> CHECKING YOU OUT ON INSTAGRAM
THE OTHER DAY, YOU GOT TO BE
EXCITED TO BE HOME BECAUSE I'M
WATCHING INSTAGRAM AND YOU LOOK
EXCITED.
YOU WERE GROOVING, MAN.
>> I BEEN IN BERLIN FOR THE PAST
THREE MONTHS SO I GOT A CHANCE
TO COME HOME AND JUST BEING
AROUND FAMILIAR AREAS, I JUST
GOT INSPIRED.
>> HAPPY FEET.
>> I DID.
>> I WAS MOVING.
I HAD A GOOD TIME.
>> SO WILL YOU SPEND THE
HOLIDAYS HERE?
>> GETTING READY TO GO BACK TO
LOS ANGELES SO UNFORTUNATELY
I'VE LEFT THE EAST COAST BUT,
YEAH, IT IS BETTER FOR MY
FAMILY.
THE WEATHER IS A LITTLE BITTER.
MOM AND DAD, EASIER LIVING FOR
THEM OUT THERE AND I JUST HAD A
NEPHEW SO I'M UNCLE MIKE NOW.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO FINALLY MEET
HIM.
I'M GETTING READY TO GO BACK
WEST AND MEET MY NEPHEW
>> THAT'S FANTASTIC.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT IT.
>> WE WANT TO TALK ABOUT "JUST
MERCY."
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT IS SO WONDERFUL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> IT IS SUCH AN IMPORTANT MOVIE
AND YOU PLAY BRYAN STEVENSON THE
ATTORNEY IN THIS MOVIE.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE TALK ABOUT
BRYAN STEVENSON AS A REAL-LIFE
SUPERHERO, AN ANGEL.
WAS THERE PRESSURE TO GET THIS
ROLE JUST RIGHT?
>> I WAS DEFINITELY INTIMIDATED
WHEN I FIRST MET HIM.
ONLY BECAUSE I KNOW HOW GREAT OF
A MAN HE IS AND I KNOW HOW
IMPORTANT HIS WORK IS, I JUST
DIDN'T WANT TO MESS THAT UP.
YOU KNOW, AFTER YOU MEET HIM,
HE'S SO HUMBLE.
HE'S SO PASSIONATE AND HE'S
DEDICATED HIS ENTIRE LIFE TO
THIS AMAZING CAUSE.
AND I WANTED TO JUST MAKE HIM
PROUD.
HE IS A MUCH BETTER PERSON THAN
A MANY.
AFTER TALKING TO HIM I SAID,
LISTEN, I GOT TO DO ET ABOUTER.
HE ALSO MOTIVATED ME TO PUT THIS
MOVIE TOGETHER AND ALSO CONTINUE
HIS WORK AND CONTINUE HIS
MESSAGE OUTSIDE OF THE MOVIE
BECAUSE I THINK IT'S EXTREMELY
IMPORTANT TODAY.
I THINK IT'S EXTREMELY IMPORTANT
>> THAT'S THE WHOLE TAKEAWAY.
IT MOTIVATES US ALL TO DO BETTER
AND CARRY MORE.
>> I KNOW CECILIA HAS SEEN IT.
YOU'VE DONE HIM JUSTICE.
TRUST ME.
YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE A LITTLE
BIT HERE?
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
THIS IS "JUST MERCY."
LET'S CHECK IT OUT, MICHAEL B.
JORDAN.
>> YOU CAN'T KEEP AN INNOCENT
MAN IN PRISON WHILE YOU SALVAGE
YOUR REPUTATION.
>> THE PEOPLE IN THIS COUNTY
HIRED ME TO KEEP THEM SAFE.
>> WHAT PEOPLE ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT RIGHT NOW?
THE ONES FROM THIS NEIGHBORHOOD
OR THE ONES FROM THE BLACK
COMMUNITY YOU TOOK HIM FROM?
DO YOU THINK THEY FEEL SAFE?
>> YOUR JOB ISN'T TO DEFEND A
CONVICTION, TOMMY.
IT'S TO ACHIEVE JUSTICE.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP FIGHTING
THIS, SOMEONE FROM YOUR COUNTY
HAS LITERALLY GOTTEN AWAY WITH
MURDER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> IT'S SO DEEP.
IT'S HEAVY.
>> IT'S A LOT OF HEAVY MATERIAL.
YOU KNOW, ESPECIALLY SHOOTING IN
THE SOUTH, JUST BEING IN THAT
ENVIRONMENT AND REALLY YOU -- IT
JUST PUTS YOU IN THE MOOD OF --
YOU KNOW, THE CIVIL RIGHTS ERA.
IT PUTS YOU IN THE MOOD OF THOSE
FREEDOM FIGHTERS AND TRYING TO
CHANNEL THAT ESSENCE AND, YOU
KNOW, JAMIE DID AN AMAZING JOB
ON SET OF PLAYING MUSIC THAT
REALLY GOT US INTO MOOD AND OUT
OF THE MOOD, YOU KNOW, SO HE
KIND OF BROKE THE TENSION WITH
SOME SONGS BUT HE ALSO HELPED
US, YOU KNOW, SET THE TABLE FOR
WHERE WE WERE GETTING READY TO
PERFORM THESE SCENES AND IT WAS
HEAVY BUT WE FOUND MOPES OF
LEVITY TO KIND OF BREAK THE
TENSION BUT IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE
MOVIE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE SHOOTING THAT
ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> JAMIE WAS HERE AND TALKED
ABOUT HOW PROUD HE WAS OF YOU,
NOT JUST FOR YOUR ROLE AND
ACTING BUT FOR WHAT YOU DID
BEHIND THE SCENES WITH INSISTING
THAT THE PRODUCTION CAST AND SET
BE ALL INCLUSIVE.
>> YES.
>> WHAT IS IT GOING TO TAKE FOR
THE INDUSTRY TO CATCH UP WITH
THAT.
>> I THINK IT'S TIME, HONESTLY.
I THINK -- IF WE DEMAND
SOMETHING, I MEAN, THE VOICE OF
THE PEOPLE IS EXTREMELY
POWERFUL, YOU KNOW, THE PEOPLE
THAT HAVE SPOKEN IS SOMETHING
THAT GOES BACK SINCE FOREVER AND
I THINK IF WE COLLECTIVELY
CONTINUE TO DEMAND ANSWERS FROM
THESE SOMEWHAT BIASED SYSTEMS
THAT WE'LL START TO SEE A CHANGE
AND, YOU KNOW, THANKFULLY WARNER
BROTHERS RAN TOWARDS THE IDEA OF
THE INCLUSION WRITER, YOU KNOW,
THEY ADOPTED IT WITH THIS MOVIE
BUT ALSO WARNER MEDIA AND ALL OF
THEIR COMPANIES UNDER THEIR
UMBRELLA ALSO ADOPTED THAT, YOU
KNOW, INCLUSION AGO AS WELL SO
WE HAD A CHANCE TO HELP WRITE
THE LANGUAGE SO THOUSAND THEY
HOLD THEIR COMPANIES, YOU KNOW,
TO A CERTAIN STANDARD WITH THAT
INCLUSION AND I THINK THAT'S
EXTREMELY IMPORTANT.
>> JAMIE IS SAYING THE SAME
THING.
>> IT'S A STEP.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE A LOT OF STEPS
TO GO.
>> FORWARD MOMENTUM IS A GOOD
THING.
HE ALSO ON A LIGHTER NOTE, WELL,
HE CALLED YOU A HEARTTHROB.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> IT WAS HIM.
>> HE'S ALWAYS THROWING
COMPLIMENTS UP.
>> WHAT DO I SAY TO THAT?
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> WHY, THANK YOU.
>> HE'S VERY FOND OF YOU.
>> HE'S A MENTOR AND A BIG
BROTHER AND ALWAYS BEEN LOOKING
OUT FOR ME.
ALWAYS GIVING ME ADVICE AND HE
JUST -- HE'S BEEN THROUGH IT.
YOU KNOW, SO HE KIND OF SEES ME
GOING THROUGH SIMILAR THINGS
SOMETIMES AND JUST WANTS TO MAKE
SURE THAT I'M NOT MAKING TOO
MANY MISTAKES.
>> HE'S LOOKING OUT FOR YOU
BECAUSE YOU GUYS HAVE KNOWN EACH
OTHER WHEN YOU WERE TEENAGERS
WHEN YOU FIRST MOVED TO L.A.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME YOU TWO
HAVE HAD A CHANCE TO WORK
TOGETHER.
I WAS WITH YOU THE OTHER DAY AND
YOU WERE TELLING ME YOU WERE
GIANTS FANS.
YOU HAD MY JERSEY ON AND
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO IT.
>> YEAH, PRO BOWL JERSEY.
I WAS BACK IN -- I WAS IN HIGH
SCHOOL.
PROBABLY IN 11th GRADE OR SO
AND, YOU KNOW, MY BEST FRIEND,
GOD REST HIS SOUL, HE PASSED
AWAY A FEW YEARS AGO BUT AT A
BARBECUE, YOU KNOW, AND HE THREW
ME IN THE POOL.
DURING THE TIME WE WERE JUST
THROWING PEOPLE IN POOLS.
DIDN'T HAVE CELL PHONES SO THERE
WAS NO WORRY.
HE TOSSED ME INTO THE POOL AND
THE FAMILY OF THE HOUSE THAT WE
WERE AT ENDED UP DRYING THE
JERSEY AND FOR WHATEVER REASON I
NEVER GOT THE JERSEY BACK AND IT
WAS SOMETHING I ALWAYS KIND OF A
LITTLE UPSET ABOUT.
>> IT'S OKAY, BUDDY.
WE GOT YOU.
>> ALL-STAR JERSEY, MAN, THAT'S
HARD.
>> PRO BOWLS IS TOUGH.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE AS
UPSET SO I GOT YOU A REGULAR
JERSEY.
WE'LL WALK IT OUT HERE, MAN.
>> OH, MAN.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
>> COME HERE, MAN.
>> YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, BROTHER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> APPRECIATE YOU.
>> NO DOUBT.
I APPRECIATE YOU.
>> OKAY.
THIS MAKES ME FEEL BETTER.
YES.
>> BUT I TELL YOU WHAT, MICHAEL,
YOU DESERVE A STANDING OVATION.
EVERYTHING YOU DO HAS MADE
PEOPLE FEEL BETTER AND INSPIRES
PEOPLE AND THIS MOVIE DOES MORE
OF THE SAME.
THIS IS AN AMAZING PIECE OF
WORK.
WE'RE SO HAPPY YOU DID THIS AND
EVERYBODY, PLEASE GO SEE "JUST
MERCY."
IT IS IN SELECT THEATERS
CHRISTMAS DAY.
IT OPENS NATIONWIDE ON JANUARY
10th.
GIVE IT UP FOR MICHAEL B.
JORDAN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE OUR
SECRET SANTA SURPRISE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> WE ARE BACK NOW WITH OUR
"GMA" SECRET SANTA SERIES.
WE'RE SPREADING HOLIDAY CHEER
ALL ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THIS MORNING, SANTA'S GOT AN
EPIC SURPRISE FOR NAVY
SERVICEMEN AND WOMEN BASED IN
NORFOLK, VIRGINIA.
BUT FIRST LET'S MEET SOME OF
THESE INSPIRING MILITARY
FAMILIES.
THEY ARE THE FAMILIES OF THE
NORFOLK NAVAL STATION.
>> I WAS OUT TO SEA AND I JUST
GOT BACK YESTERDAY AND I'M
EXCITED TO BE HOME TO SEE MY
DAUGHTER AND MY HUSBAND AND TO
SPEND TIME WITH THEM THIS
HOLIDAY SINCE I WASN'T ABLE TO
SPEND TIME WITH THEM LAST
CHRISTMAS.
>> BEING AWAY FROM FAMILY IS
ALWAYS ROUGH.
>> Reporter: ALL THESE FAMILIES
CHERISHING THE TIME THEY'RE ABLE
TO SPEND WITH LOVED ONE THIS
YEAR LIKE PATINA ALEXANDER WHOSE
HUSBAND JOSEPH WAS ALMOST
DEPLOYED FOR CHRISTMAS.
>> WE WERE NOT EXPECTING HIM TO
BE HERE FOR CHRISTMAS.
IT'S FORTUNATE HE'S HERE.
I'M CHERISHING EVERY MOMENT HE'S
HERE.
>> Reporter: AND TRYING TO MAKE
THE SEASON MAGICAL FOR THE
CHILDREN IN THEIR LIVE.
>> NICE TO PUT UP A TREE AND SEE
CHRISTMAS THROUGH THE EYES OF A
CHILD BECAUSE IT'S SO DIFFERENT,
IT'S LIKE NOTHING THAT YOU SEE
ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> Reporter: FOR THE HOLMAN
FAMILY THE MONTHS THEY SPEND
SEPARATED HELPED THEM START A
SPECIAL TRADITION THEY STILL
CARRY ON EACH CHRISTMAS EVE.
>> WHEN MY HUSBAND WOULD PULL
INTO PORTS HE WOULD GO TO THE
LIBRARY THEY HAD LOCATED ON THE
BASES AND HE WOULD PICK OUT
CHILDREN'S BOOKS TO AGE
APPROPRIATE FOR OUR CHILDREN AND