>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS CHRISTMAS
EVE MORNING, WE'RE TRACKING THE
LATEST ON THE STORMS CAUSING
HOLIDAY TRAVEL HAVOC.
DOUBLE WHAMMY.
WICKED WEATHER HITTING BOTH
COASTS THIS HOLIDAY.
MASSIVE FLOODING.
UPROOTED TREES PLUS WE'RE
TRACKING THE NEW STORM HEADING
FOR THE WEST THAT COULD BRING
SNOW TO CALIFORNIA ON YOUR DRIVE
HOME FROM CHRISTMAS.
>>> ALSO OVERNIGHT, FALLOUT
AFTER THE FIRING OF THAT BOEING
CEO AS THE 737 MAX
RECERTIFICATIONS ARE DELAYED.
WHAT'S NEXT FOR THE AIRCRAFT
GIANT.
>>> SHOPPING STAMPEDE.
THE SCARY MOMENT A CROWD
SCRAMBLES FOR PRIZES HIDDEN IN
BALLOONS AT THE MALL PUTTING
SEVERAL IN THE HOSPITAL WITH
JUST HOURS TO GO UNTIL CHRISTMAS
AND THE BEST WAY TO GET THOSE
LAST-MINUTE GIFTS.
>>> BACK HOME, THE BABY OF THAT
MURDERED TEXAS MOTHER REUNITED
WITH HER FAMILY OVERNIGHT.
FRIENDS STILL IN SHOCK AS PEOPLE
GATHERED TO REMEMBER THE MOTHER
OF TWO.
>>> ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
LUCKY TO BE ALIVE.
THE SURFER ATTACKED BY A GREAT
WHITE SHARK SPEAKING OUT, THE
HARROWING TALE AND THE QUICK
THINKING THAT SAVED HIS LIFE
ONLY ON "GMA."
>>> A VERY ROYAL CHRISTMAS.
HARRY, MEGHAN AND BABY ARCHIE,
THEIR ADORABLE HOLIDAY CARD
REVEALED.
♪
>>> A CHRISTMAS MIRACLE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ONE CHURCH HELPING THOUSANDS OF
FAMILIES PAY OFF MILLIONS.
THE STUNNING HOLIDAY SURPRISE.
♪
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS EVE AND WE START
TODAY WITH THE BIG EXCLUSIVE.
WE HAVE A SNEAK PEEK AT SANTA'S
NAUGHTY AND NICE LISTS.
>> ARE YOU ON THE NAUGHTY LIST?
>> I'VE SEEN IT AND HEARD WHAT
YOU DID THIS YEAR.
>> IT IS A DANGEROUS REVEAL.
THAT STILL AHEAD.
ONE GUY WHO IS DEFINITELY READY
FOR CHRISTMAS, SANTA CLAUS.
WE ARE TRACKING ST. NICK RIGHT
NOW.
WE'LL BE WATCHING HIM ALL
MORNING FLYING OVER NEW ZEALAND
AS SUI SPEAK.
HE'S ALREADY DELIVERED MORE THAN
300 MILLION PRESENTS TO MANY
HAPPY CHILDREN OUT THERE AND
MANY MORE TO COME.
>> AND ADULTS.
>> DON'T FORGET THE ADULTS.
>>> WE BEGIN WITH THAT SEVERE
WEATHER.
STORMS ALONG BOTH U.S. COASTS
CAUSING TROUBLE FOR LAST-MINUTE
TRAVELERS.
ROB IS TRACKING THE LATEST WITH
JUST HOURS TO GET TO CHRISTMAS
EVE DINNER.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING.
SANTA WOULD NEED WATER SKIS
YESTERDAY AND THIS MORNING
ACROSS PARTS OF THE SOUTHEAST.
CHARLESTON, SOUTH CAROLINA, IT
FLOODS ON A GOOD DAY AND HAD
ANYWHERE BETWEEN 3 AND 5 INCHES
IN A SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME IN THE
LOW COUNTRY.
HOLLYWOOD, FLORIDA, BROWARD
COUNTY, WE TALKED ABOUT IT
YESTERDAY.
THEY SAW OVER A FOOT OF RAINFALL
AND THAT IS VERY LOW COUNTRY TOO
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY THE LEAST TO
GET AROUND TOWN.
HERE'S OUR LOW.
IT'S KIND OF SLOW TO GET OUT OF
HERE.
WILL DO SO EVENTUALLY.
AROUND HILTON HEAD UP THROUGH
WILMINGTON YOU'LL SEE COASTAL
FLOODING AND RAIN.
A COUPLE STORMS OUT WEST.
THE FIRST ONE THAT BROUGHT ONE
TO TWO INCHES OF RAINFALL.
FRAZIER PARK, 5,000 FEET, A
PRETTY WARM STORM BUT WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORIES.
NORTH OF PHOENIX I-17 WILL BE AN
ISSUE AND COULD SEE 6 TO 12
INCHES OF SNOW AND ANOTHER 5 TO
6.
STATES ARE UNDER WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORIES.
ANOTHER ONE TO TWO INCHES 6 OF
RAIN FOR SAN DIEGO AND REDONDO
BEACH AND THAT INCLUDES I-5, THE
GRAPEVINE.
YOU'LL SEE A LITTLE IN THE WAY
OF SNOW THERE.
DIFFICULT GO ACROSS PARTS OF THE
WEST.
>> THANKS.
>>> NOW TO WASHINGTON AND A NEW
FRONT IN THE IMPEACHMENT
SHOWDOWN.
LAWYERS FOR HOUSE DEMOCRATS
RAISING THE POSSIBILITY OF
IMPEACHING PRESIDENT TRUMP A
SECOND TIME AS THE PRESIDENT
LASHES OUT AT NANCY PELOSI OVER
HER REFUSAL TO SEND ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT TO THE SENATE.
RACHEL SCOTT IS IN WEST PALM
BEACH TRAVELING WITH THE
PRESIDENT AS HE SPENDS THE
HOLIDAY IN FLORIDA.
RACHEL, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: TOM, GOOD MORNING.
YES, PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL SPEND
THIS CHRISTMAS EVE WISHING
MEMBERS OF THE MILITARY A HAPPY
HOLIDAYS OVER A VIDEO
TELECONFERENCE BUT IMPEACHMENT
IS TOP OF MIND AND LASHING OUT
AND RAILING AGAINST HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI ACCUSING
HER OF TRYING TO TAKE OVER THE
SENATE AND DICTATE THE TERMS OF
A TRIAL.
PELOSI THOUGH IS STANDING FIRM.
SHE SAYS SHE WILL NOT TURN OVER
THE ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT TO
THE SENATE UNTIL REPUBLICANS
REVEAL HOW THE TRIAL WOULD BE
STRUCTURED AND SHE CHALLENGED
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO TURN OVER
DOCUMENTS AND ALLOW TOP AIDES TO
TESTIFY.
TOM.
>> RACHEL, SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER MITCH McCONNELL RAISED
EYEBROWS SAYING HE IS OPEN TO
THE IDEA OF HAVING WITNESSES AT
THE TRIAL?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SAYS HE HAS NOT RULED OUT THE
IDEA BUT THERE IS ONE CATCH.
HE SAYS IT WOULD HAVE TO FIRST
BE APPROVED BY THE MAJORITY OF
THE SENATE.
WELL, REPUBLICANS OUTNUMBER
DEMOCRATS AND MANY KEY
REPUBLICANS HAVE ALREADY SAID
THEY ARE AGAINST THAT IDEA.
DEMOCRATS, THOUGH, ARE NOW
SEIZING ON THOSE NEWLY RELEASED
EMAILS THAT SHOW ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS DISCUSS THE HOLDUP OF
MILITARY AID 90 MINUTES AFTER
THE PRESIDENT'S NOW INFAMOUS
PHONE CALL WITH THE LEADER.
ONE ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL SAYS
THAT TIME SOMETHING A
COINCIDENCE BUT SENATOR SCHUMER
SAYS IT'S ALL THE MORE REASON
WHY THEY NEED DOCUMENTS AND
WITNESSES.
>> RACHEL, THANK YOU.
>>> TOM, TO GROWING FEARS OVER
NORTH KOREA AFTER A NEW IMAGE
APPEARS TO SHOW A NEWLY BUILT
STRUCTURE AT A MILITARY FACTORY
THERE.
THE U.S. HAS BEEN ON HIGH ALERT
SINCE NORTH KOREA THREATENED A,
QUOTE, CHRISTMAS GIFT THAT COULD
BE A MISSILE TEST AND MATT
GUTMAN IS IN SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA
WHERE TENSIONS ARE RUNNING HIGH.
>> Reporter: ALL THAT TALK OF A
CHRISTMAS GIFT HAS OFFICIALS NOT
ONLY IN THE U.S. BUT ALSO IN
JAPAN AND HERE IN SOUTH KOREA ON
HIGH ALERT THIS MORNING.
NOW, THAT SATELLITE DID SPOT
POSSIBLE CONSTRUCTION AT A NORTH
KOREAN MILITARY BASE THAT HAS
PRODUCED MISSILES IN THE PAST.
THE BIG QUESTION IS, WHAT DOES
KIM JONG-UN PLAN TO STUFF THAT
CHRISTMAS STOCKING WITH?
IT COULD BE SHORT-RANGE MISSILE
LAUNCHES OR EVEN THE TESTING OF
MISSILE ENGINES BUT IT COULD
ALSO BE THE LAUNCH OF LONG-RANGE
MISSILES CAPABLE OF HITTING THE
UNITED STATES.
THAT WOULD VIOLATE U.N. SECURITY
COUNCIL RESOLUTIONS AND ALSO
BREAK THE PROMISE THAT KIM MADE
TO TRUMP, TO PRESIDENT TRUMP TO
STOP TESTING THOSE KINDS OF
WEAPONS.
NOW, THE LAST TIME THAT WE SAW A
LONG-RANGE MISSILE LAUNCH WAS
BACK IN 2017.
THAT'S WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
THREATENED TO RAIN FIRE AND FURY
ON NORTH KOREA.
BUT THERE IS A REASON FOR THIS
NORTH KOREAN SABER RATTLING.
THE NORTH KOREANS APPEAR TO WANT
THE U.S. TO DROP ITS DEMAND FOR
TOTAL DISARMAMENT.
THEY ALSO WANT THE U.S. TO LET
GO OF THAT STRANGLEHOLD THAT'S
BEEN CHOKING OFF THE NORTH
KOREAN ECONOMY WITH THOSE
ECONOMIC SANCTIONS.
WHIT.
>> AND, MATT, YOU MENTIONED
PRESIDENT TRUMP THERE.
WHAT COULD THIS MEAN FOR TRUMP'S
DIPLOMATIC EFFORTS WITH NORTH
KOREA?
>> Reporter: NOW, IF IT'S
SHORT-RANGE MISSILE, PROBABLY
NOT MUCH.
THERE'S WIGGLE ROOM FOR
DIPLOMACY.
IF WE SEE THE LAUNCH OF
LONG-RANGE MISSILES IT MIGHT
REQUIRE THE PRESIDENT TO BACK
AWAY FROM DIPLOMACY, MAYBE ISSUE
SOME KIND OF U.S. RESPONSE.
WHIT.
>> MATT GUTMAN FOR US IN SEOUL,
SOUTH KOREA, THANK YOU.
>>> BOEING IN CRISIS.
THE COMPANY FIRING ITS CEO
FOLLOWING THE 737 MAX CRASHES
AND THE BOTCHED SPACELINER TEST
OVER THE WEEKEND.
DAVID KERLEY HAS THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENTS.
HIS REPLACEMENT ALREADY TAKING
CHARGE.
>> Reporter: ALREADY, EVA, GOOD
MORNING.
THE CEO WHO WAS CHAIRMAN OF THE
BOARD UNTIL YESTERDAY DOESN'T
REALLY OFFICIALLY START FOR
THREE WEEKS BUT HE'S ALREADY
BEEN ON THE PHONE WITH THE FAA
AND AIRLINE CUSTOMERS TRYING TO
RESET RELATIONSHIPS.
AND THOSE RELATIONSHIPS HAVE
FRAYED SINCE THOSE TWO CRASHES.
A 737 MAX KILLING 350 AND THE
INABILITY TO GET THAT JET BACK
INTO THE AIR MAY HAVE BEEN THE
LAST STRAW FOR DENNIS MUILENBURG
LEADING TO HIS OUSTER.
BOEING JUST ORDERED THE SHUTDOWN
OF THE PRODUCTION LINE.
THAT WAS A SERIOUS CONCERN FOR
THE BOARD.
THERE ARE ALREADY 400 BRAND-NEW
JETS SITTING AROUND THE COUNTRY
THAT CANNOT BE DELIVERED TO
AIRLINE CUSTOMERS AND MUILENBURG
ACTUALLY ANGERED THE FAA WHEN HE
ANNOUNCED THEY WOULD START
DELIVERIES THIS MONTH BEFORE IT
ACTUALLY HAS BEEN APPROVED FOR
CERTIFICATION.
NOW, WE ARE TOLD THAT THE CHANGE
IN LEADERSHIP MAY NOT CHANGE THE
ACTUAL RECERTIFICATION AND
RETURN TO FLIGHT OF THE 737 MAX,
BUT IT COULD ACTUALLY CHANGE
THOSE RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN
BOEING AND THE FAA AND ITS
AIRLINE CUSTOMERS, EVA.
>> ALL RIGHT, DAVID KERLEY.
THE CEO IS FIRED.
DOES HE LEAVE EMPTY HANDED?
>> Reporter: WE DON'T KNOW BUT
HAS THE POTENTIAL FOR A NEARLY
$40 MILLION PAYOFF IN SEVERANCE.
BOEING DOESN'T WANT TO TALK
ABOUT COMPENSATION NOW, JUST THE
TRANSITION.
WE JUST RECEIVED WORD THERE IS
MORE ADDITIONAL POSSIBLY
EMBARRASSING COMMUNICATIONS
BETWEEN BOEING EMPLOYEES ABOUT
THE SYSTEM THAT MAY HAVE BEEN
INVOLVED IN THESE TWO CRASHES
WHICH THE FAA HAS NOW BEEN GIVEN
AND THEY ARE REVIEWING, EVA.
>> DAVID KERLEY FOR US, THANK
YOU.
>>> NOW TO NEW DETAILS IN THE
MURDER OF THAT TEXAS MOTHER AND
THE CLOSE FRIEND NOW FACING
KIDNAPPING CHARGES.
OFFICIALS NOW SAY THAT LITTLE
GIRL IS BEING REUNITED WITH HER
FAMILY AND KAYLEE HARTUNG HAS
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: A BITTERSWEET
REUNION.
>> SHE'S COMING HOME TONIGHT
AND, YOU KNOW, THAT'S THE BEST
THING THAT, YOU KNOW, COULD EVER
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: BABY MARGO FINALLY
RETURNING HOME AFTER SHE AND HER
MOTHER VANISHED DECEMBER 12.
A WEEK-LONG SEARCH ENDING IN
HORROR, HER BODY FOUND STRANGLED
TO DEATH IN THE TRUNK OF HER
BEST FRIEND'S CAR BUT AN INFANT
BELIEVED TO BE MARGOT WAS FOUND
SAFELY INSIDE THIS HOME AND THEY
NEEDED TO CONFIRM HER IDENTITY
BEFORE RETURNING HER HOME.
HER GRANDFATHER DELIVERING THE
LONG AWAITED NEWS.
>> IT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE BUT
IT'S OVER NOW.
>> Reporter: MAGEN FIERAMUSCA,
BROUSSARD'S CLOSE FRIEND OF MORE
THAN 20 YEAR, CHARGED WITH THEIR
KIDNAPPING.
BROUSSARD'S LOVED ONES IN
DISBELIEF.
>> THAT WAS THE BIGGEST SURPRISE
OF MY LIFE.
THAT WAS INSANE.
>> Reporter: POLICE
INVESTIGATING IF FIERAMUSCA
PLOTTED TO STEAL BABY MARGOT AND
PASS HER OFF AS HER OWN.
BROUSSARD'S MOM SAYING SHE HAD
BEEN UNEASY WITH MAGEN SAYING
EVERYBODY LOVED HER.
WE THOUGHT MAGEN LOVED HER TOO.
BUT EVIDENTLY THAT WASN'T THE
CASE.
FRIENDS AND STRANGERS COMING
TOGETHER TO HONOR HEIDI.
AND CELEBRATE BABY MARGOT'S SAFE
RETURN.
>> IT'S REALLY GOOD SHE'S COMING
HOME AND I HOPE SHE LOOKS LIKE
HEIDI WHEN SHE GROWS UP.
>> Reporter: HEIDI'S BEST FRIEND
MAGEN FIERAMUSCA BEING HELD AT
THIS JAIL IN AUSTIN FACING TWO
CHARGES OF KIDNAPPING BUT STILL
NO MURDER CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED HERE.
LOCAL POLICE IN AUSTIN TELL US
THIS IS AN ONGOING INVESTIGATION
AND EXPECT MORE CHARGES TO BE
FILED IN THE COMING DAYS.
WHIT.
>> AN AWFUL CASE AND A LOT OF
QUESTIONS.
KAYLEE HARTUNG FOR US, THANK
YOU.
>>> NOW TO SOME HAPPY NEWS FOR
THE ROYAL FAMILY.
JUST IN TIME FOR CHRISTMAS,
PRINCE PHILIP WAS JUST RELEASED
AFTER SPENDING FOUR NIGHTS IN
THE HOSPITAL.
LAMA HASAN JOINS US WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU, WHIT.
YES, THIS MORNING BUCKINGHAM
PALACE RELEASING A SHORT BUT
SWEET STATEMENT SAYING PRINCE
PHILIP HAS BEEN DISCHARGED BY
HIS DOCTOR AND AFTER THANKING
THE HOSPITAL'S MEDICAL STAFF,
98-YEAR-OLD WALKED OUT ON FOOT
FIRST TRAVELING BY CAR AND IN A
HELICOPTER HEADING HOME JUST IN
TIME FOR ALL THE ROYAL CHRISTMAS
CELEBRATION AT THE QUEEN'S
SPRAWLING ESTATE IN SANDRINGHAM.
THE PALACE IS STAYING MUM ABOUT
HIS CONDITION ONLY REVEALING
THAT PRINCE PHILIP WAS ADMITTED
TO THE HOSPITAL FOR OBSERVATION
AND TREATMENTED OF A
PRE-EXISTING CONDITION.
NEVERTHELESS THIS WILL BE
WELCOME NEWS FOR THE ROYAL
FAMILY WHERE IN KEEPING WITH
GERMAN TRADITION THEY OPEN THEIR
GIFTS ON CHRISTMAS EVE.
WHIT.
>> NOTABLY ABSENT FROM THAT
HOLIDAY GATHERING, THE DUKE AND
DUCHESS OF SUSSEX.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HARRY AND MEGHAN ARE SPENDING
THE HOLIDAYS IN CANADA TAKING A
SIX-WEEK BREAK FROM THE
SPOTLIGHT BUT THEY DID JUST
REVEAL THEIR HOLIDAY CARD
SHOWING AN ADORABLE 7-MONTH-OLD
ARCHIE FRONT AND CENTER.
HIS GRINNING DOTING PARENTS IN
THE BACKGROUND DOING IT THE
ENVIR
ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY WAY BY
EMAILING IT TO THEIR FRIENDS AND
COLLEAGUES.
WHIT.
>> ARCHIE, NOT LOOKING AFRAID OF
THE CAMERA ONE BIT.
THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO A DEVELOPING STORY.
THIS INTENSELY BUSY HOLIDAY
TRAVEL PERIOD, FIVE AIRPORTS
REPORTING PASSENGERS WITH
CONFIRMED CASES OF MEASLES THIS
MONTH.
LOS ANGELES, CHICAGO, DENVER,
AUSTIN AND RICHMOND, DR.
JENNIFER ASHTON IS HERE.
HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE TO SEE
THESE SYMPTOMS AND WHAT ARE
THEY?
>> THIS IS CONCERNING, EVA.
LET'S GO THROUGH THE TIME LINE
IF YOU WILL FOR MEASLES.
FIRST OF ALL, THIS CAN BE A
PERIOD OF SEVERAL WEEKS.
THERE IS AN INCUBATION PERIOD OF
ABOUT 10 TO 12 DAYS THEN WE GET
INTO A PERIOD OF TIME WHERE YOU
HAVE THE EARLY SYMPTOMS, COUGH,
PINK EYE, RUNNY NOSE AND THE
CLASSIC RASH THAT OCCURS TWO
WEEKS AFTER EXPOSURE ON THE FACE
AND HEAD AND WORKS ITS WAY DOWN
AND PEOPLE CAN BE CONTAGIOUS
FOUR DAYS BEFORE THE RASH AND
FOUR DAYS AFTER.
THIS COULD BE A LONG PERIOD OF
TIME.
>> THERE IS A REASON WHY PEOPLE
WHO ARE TRAVELING SHOULD KNOW
ABOUT THIS BECAUSE IT'S SO
POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS.
>> THIS IS NOT JUST AN
INCONVENIENCE.
WE HAVE TO REMEMBER THE
COMPLICATIONS RANGE FROM EAR
INFECTIONS, ONE IN TEN CASE, 1
IN 20 CHANCE OF DEVELOPING
PNEUMONIA AND BRAIN SWELLING, 1
IN 1,000 AND A DEATH RATE OF 1
TO 2 PER THOUSAND CASES.
CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN, THE
ELDERLY MORE SUSCEPTIBILITY.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANKS÷d■uOR THAT
HEALTH ALERT.
WHIT.
>>> NOW TO THE HOLIDAY CONTEST
TAKING A SCARY TURN.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS VIDEO HERE.
PRIZES AND VOUCHERS DROPPED FROM
ABOVE.
THAT LARGE CROWD OF SHOPPERS AT
A MALL IN AUSTRALIA.
PEOPLE STARTED SCRAMBLING AND
THEN FALLING INTO THE BARRICADES
THERE.
MORE THAN A DOZEN PEOPLE WERE
INJURED.
>>> THAT COUNTDOWN TO CHRISTMAS
DOWN TO JUST ONE DAY AND IF YOU
STILL HAVEN'T DONE YOUR SHOPPING
WE HAVE SOME HOPE FOR YOU.
TREVOR AULT JOINS US WITH MORE
ON THAT.
TREVOR, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: WHIT, GOOD MORNING.
I'M INSIDE THE KOHL'S IN
SEACAUCUS, NEW JERSEY, AND IT
ISN'T NECESSARILY PACKED BUT
IT'S NOT EMPTY SEEING A STEADY
STREAM OF PEOPLE MAKING
LAST-MINUTE HOLIDAY PURCHASES.
THIS KOHL'S OWN EVERY OTHER
KOHL'S LOCATION HAVE BEEN OPEN
24 HOURS A DAY SINCE FRIDAY.
AT 6:00 THEY'LL CLOSE THEIR
DOORS SO THEIR HARD WORKING
EMPLOYEES CAN GET A CHRISTMAS
DINNER AND MOST NATIONAL CHAINS
WILL CLOSE TONIGHT AT 6:00.
IF YOU NEED A FEW EXTRA HOURS
THERE ARE SOME OTHER OPTIONS
AVAILABLE.
WE KNOW THAT TARGET AND KMART
WILL CLOSE AT 10:00 TONIGHT AS
WILL THE DEEP DISCOUNTERS LIKE
BIG LOTS, DOLLAR GENERAL AND
ROSS STORES.
WE'RE NOT NECESSARILY
ENCOURAGING WAITING UNTIL THE
LAST MINUTE BUT THE CHOICES ARE
THERE.
>> THAT LAST-MINUTE SHOPPING CAN
BE RISKY BUSINESS BUT THE
MILLIONS DOING IT TODAY ARE
PERHAPS THE MOST DESPERATE.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THAT'S WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT
YOU KNOW THAT YOU HAVE YOUR
OPTIONS AND IT'S KIND OF
SURPRISING HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
DECIDING TO WAIT OR OTHER
PEOPLE, THE HOLIDAYS JUST GET
AWAY FROM THEM.
FROM THE NATIONAL RETAIL FED
INDICATION, 39% OF SHOPPERS SAY
THEY PLAN TO WRAP UP BY DECEMBER
18th, A WEEK BEFORE CHRISTMAS
BUT 6% OF THEM, A SMALL CHUNK
BUT A CHUNK THERE SAID THEY
WOULD BE WAITING UNTIL THAT LAST
MINUTE.
TODAY WE'RE SEEING SOME OF THEM
SHOPPING.
I'M ONE OF THEM AS WELL SO IF
YOU HAVE IDEAS I'LL TAKE THEM.
>> TOM, TRYING TO GET THE BEST
DEAL ON THAT NORDICTRACK.
>> AND PANTS, A NICE PAIR OF
PANTS FOR CHRISTMAS.
>>> IF YOU CAN'T GET TO THE
STORE WE HAVE DIY CHRISTMAS
HACKS COMING UP IN OUR SECOND
HOUR.
>> I STILL HAVE MY SHOPPING TO
DO TOO SO I FEEL YOU.
>> CLOCK IS TICKING.
>>> NOW TO INCREDIBLE HOLIDAY
SURPRISE FOR THOUSANDS OF
FAMILIES IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
A CRUNCH TIME AND A CHURCH
PAYING MORE THAN $5 MILLION IN
MEDICAL DEBT THANKS TO DAY
NATIONS FROM ITS MEMBERS AND
MARCUS MOORE HAS THE STORY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: HEY, TOM, GOOD
MORNING.
THE CONGREGATION SAYS THERE ARE
NO STRINGS ATTACHED HERE.
AN EXTRAORDINARY MOVE, ONE A
CO-PASTOR SAID WILL HELP
RECIPIENTS FIND HAPPINESS AND
ALSO IT WILL GET THEM BACK ON
THEIR FEET AND AVOID
HOMELESSNESS.
THIS MORNING, ONE CHURCH IS
CREATING THEIR OWN CHRISTMAS
MIRACLE HELPING NEARLY 6,000
PEOPLE PAY OFF MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS WORTH OF MEDICAL DEBT.
>> WE ARE CANCELING ALL OF THE
UNPAID MEDICAL DEBT,
$5.3 MILLION AS A CHRISTMAS GIFT
TO ALL OF THE POOR IN ALL 28
NEIGHBORHOODS.
>> Reporter: CHRISTIAN ASSEMBLY
CHURCH IN EAGLE ROCK,
CALIFORNIA, IS WORKING TO
ELIMINATE MEDICAL DEBT FOR MORE
THAN 5,500 FAMILIES IN
NEIGHBORHOODS ACROSS LOS
ANGELES.
WHEN CHURCH LEADERSHIP SHARED
THE PLAN WITH THE CONGREGATION,
THE ROOM ERUPTING IN APPLAUSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THE CHURCH TEAMING UP WITH
NONPROFIT ORGANIZATION RIP
MEDICAL DEBT, THE COMPANY THAT
BUYS DEBT FOR ONE PENNY PER
DOLLAR MEANING THANKS TO THIS
PARTNERSHIP THOUSANDS OF LETTERS
WILL BE SENT THIS WEEK READING
IN PART, YOU NO LONGER HAVE ANY
OBLIGATION TO PAY THIS DEBT TO
ANYONE.
LIFTING THE HEAVY BURDEN OF DEBT
FOR SCORES OF FAMILY IN AN
UNIMAGINABLE CHRISTMAS GIFT.
>> THEY OPEN AND SAY I'M GLAD I
OPENED IT BECAUSE I HAD TO READ
IT THREE TIMES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEBODY WOULD
BE ABOLISHING MY DEBT.
>> Reporter: THE RECIPIENTS
DON'T KNOW WHO THEY ARE YET
BECAUSE THE LETTERS DON'T GO OUT
UNTIL NEXT WEEK AND BECAUSE OF
PRIVACY LAWS, THE NAMES, THEY
WON'T BE RELEASED BUT WHAT A
SURPRISE CHRISTMAS GIFT FOR SO
MANY FAMILIES.
GUYS.
>> YEAH, THAT CHURCH DOING SO
MUCH GOOD.
MARCUS, WE THANK YOU FOR THAT.
WE'RE FOLLOWING STORIES THIS
MORNING.
THE URGENT SEARCH FOR TWO IDAHO
SIBLINGS WHO HAVEN'T BEEN SEEN
IN MORE THAN THREE MONTHS AND
NOW BELIEVED TO BE IN SERIOUS
DANGER.
THE NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT THEIR
PARENTS AS THE FBI JOINS THAT
INVESTIGATION.
>>> AN ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
THE SURFER WHO SURVIVED AN
ATTACK BY A 15-FOOT GREAT WHITE
SHARK.
NOW HE IS TELLING HIS HARROWING
STORY ONLY ON "GMA" BUT FIRST
LET'S GO BACK TO ROB AND THAT
CHRISTMAS FORECAST.
>> LOOK, WE HAVE FOG IN CHICAGO.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
30 DEGREES SO FREEZING FOG,
DANGEROUS SITUATION AND ACROSS
PARTS OF I-90 INTO NORTHERN
INDIANA GETTING INTO OHIO AS
WELL.
TAKE IT EASY OUT THERE IF YOU'RE
DRIVING.
>> Eileen: WELL, SUNNY SKIES
EXPECTED OVER THE NEXT 12 HOURS.
TEMPERATURES THIS MORNING
STARTING OFF COLD IN THE 30S,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO CLIMB THIS
AFTERNOON INTO THE LOWER 50S
WITH BREEZY SUNSHINE.
WE STAY DRY WITH TEMPERATURES
FALLING BACK DOWN INTO THE 30S
AFTER 8:00 TONIGHT.
NOW, WHEN SANTA COMES TO TOWN
TONIGHT, SKIES WILL BE CLEAR.
WE COULD HAVE A BIT OF PATCHY
FOG POSSIBLE, SO BE MINDFUL OF
THAT WAKING UP TOMORROW MORNING.
YOUR CHRISTMAS DAY, PARTLY SUNNY
>>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
STAY WITH US.
as fast as 6 seconds
when you're running late?
Shhhh.
[whispering]
It's switching time.
♪
How about a battery that
lasts up to 12 hours?
[bell rings]
Order up!
♪
Now we're cooking.
Or how about one with
virus protection built in?
Which...
would be helpful...
right...
about...
now...
Yeah, if you want all that,
switch to Chromebook.
♪
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you have fast-acting
power over pain,
So the whole world
looks different.
The unbeatable strength
and speed of Advil Liqui-Gels.
What Pain?
♪
Introducing a razor that works
differently.
The Gillette Skinguard
has a guard between the blades
that helps protect skin.
The Gillette Skinguard.
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
Wrap up your holiday shopping
with the Blitz In,Blitz Out Sale
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
at JCPenney!
For 5 days only
shop Nike and adidas.
Keurig and NutriBullet.
and up to
80% off jewelry.
Or take an extra 20% off with
your JCPenney Credit Card
JCPenney!
With the savings rates offered
at some banks,
your money almost
seems like it's frozen.
But not here.
With Capital One, you can open
a new savings account
in about 5 minutes
and earn five times
the national average.
Open one from here.
Or here - in a Capital One Café.
Plus, there are no fees
or minimums
on savings or checking accounts
because that's how it should be.
This is banking reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
Ow!
So, you think Santa will like
these red and green M&M'S?
I don't know! I never met the
guy!
Whaaaaa!
He does exist!
They do exist!
Uhm... Santa?
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
>> NANCY: I AM NANCY CHEN.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
WE ARE DEALING WITH A WATER MAIN
BREAK ON IOWA AVENUE CREWS
WORKING ON REPAIRS TO FILL A
HOLE WHERE THE BREAK IS.
NO TIMETABLE WHEN REPAIRS WILL
BE DONE OR WHEN RESIDENTS WILL
HAVE SERVICE RESTORED.
>> NANCY: VOTE COMES AFTER
DEMOCRATS TOOK CONTROL OF BOTH
HOUSES IN VIRGINIA GENERAL
ASSEMBLY.
MORE MONEY FOR FIREARMS
EDUCATION AND STRONG PENALTIES
FOR ADULTS THAT ALLOW■C
>> EILEEN: CLEAR AND COLD THIS
CHRISTMAS EVE MORNING.
COLDEST TEMPERATURES, 22
MANASSAS.
COLD, GRAB A NICE WARM COAT OUT
THE DOOR, DRY CONDITIONS,
TEMPERATURES, OUT OF THE 30S
INTO THE 40S.
EVENTUALLY TO AROUND 52 DEGREES
LATER THIS AFTERNOON, DRY AND 49
CHRISTMAS DAY.
BOBBY, NEXT CHANCE OF CHRISTMAS
WEATHER SUNDAY INTO MONDAY.
>> BOBBY: TRAVELING NORTHBOUND
ON THE BW PARKWAY IN BETWEEN
ROUTE 197-198 WE HAD A CRASH.
STILL WORKING THROUGH THOSE
DELAYS, AVERAGE SPEED 7 MILES AN
HOUR.
ALSO LOOKING AT AN ACCIDENT
INNER LOOP AFTER BRADDOCK
EVERYTHING MOVED OVER INTO THE
ONRAMP FROM BRADDOCK ADRIANNA?
>> ADRIANNA: GET
WEATHER, AND NEWS ANY TIME WITH