♪
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
AS YOU CELEBRATE WITH YOUR LOVED
ONES, WE REFLECT ON THE MEANING
BEHIND THE SEASON WITH ONE OF
CHRISTIANITY'S TOP LEADERS.
HERE WITH THEIR MESSAGE THIS
CHRISTMAS MORNING.
>>> ALSO AHEAD, HOLIDAY HEROES.
>> MAKE SURE Y'ALL GET SOME GOOD
STUFF.
>> HOW THIS NBA WITH A HUGE
HEART IS PULLING OFF NOT ONE,
NOT TWO, BUT SIX DAYS OF GIVING.
♪
>>> HIGH FLYING HOLIDAY.
INSIDE THE INCREDIBLE CIRQUE du
SOLEIL SHOW.
>> THIS IS WHERE I TURN INTO A
CIRQUE PLAYER.
>> GINGER BEHIND THE SCENES.
>>> HOW TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE
SEASON'S HOTTEST TOYS.
FROM SMART SPEAKERS, AND HOW TO
ACTIVATE THOSE SMARTPHONES
BEFORE YOUR KIDS TAKE CONTROL.
>>> AND MOVIE MAGIC FROM ELSA,
AND THE CREW FROM "FROZEN 2."
THE FORCES WITH US THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
WE HAVE THE HOTTEST FILMS FOR
YOU AND YOUR FAMILY HITTING
THEATERS RIGHT NOW.
♪
>> Announcer: FROM TIMES SQUARE,
THIS IS A SPECIAL CHRISTMAS DAY
EDITION OF "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA."
♪
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
HAPPY HANUKKAH.
EVERYTHING.
TO ALL HERE IN OUR STUDIO AS
WELL.
WE WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW THAT
WE'RE ON TAPE THIS MORNING SO
ALL OF US COULD CELEBRATE WITH
OUR LOVED ONES AT HOME.
WE HOPE THAT YOU ARE HAVING THE
BEST TIME EVER.
>> ONE OF OUR HOLIDAY
TRADITIONS.
WE HAVE THE NEW YORK
UNIVERSITY'S VOCAL PERFORMANCE
CORRAL HERE.
ANOTHER GREAT TRADITION.
>> YES.
THEY SOUND GREAT, AND WE CAN'T
WAIT TO SHARE REALLY INSPIRING
STORIES WITH YOU.
CELEBRATE PEOPLE WHO GIVE BACK
IN BIG WAYS.
WE HAVE A SPECIAL SURPRISE FOR A
WOMAN WHO MAKES IT HER MISSION
TO FEED HER COMMUNITY.
THAT'S COMING UP JUST AHEAD.
>> I JUST LOVE THE SOUND.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL, THIS CHOIR.
>>> ALL COMING UP, BUT FIRST, WE
WANT TO GET TO THE MORNING'S TOP
HEADLINES.
GOOD MORNING, EVA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU.
>> ROBIN, MERRY CHRISTMAS, AND
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO EVERYONE AT
HOME.
HOPEFULLY YOU ARE WHERE YOU WANT
TO BE FOR CHRISTMAS THIS
MORNING.
FOR SOME TRAVELING ON CHRISTMAS
EVE, IT WASN'T EASY GETTING TO
THEIR DESTINATION.
MORE THAN 2,700 FLIGHTS WERE
DELAYED, MANY BY DENSE FOG.
CHICAGO'S TWO AIRPORTS WERE THE
MOST AFFECTED.
THOUSANDS OF PASSENGERS WERE
STRANDED AT O'HARE AND MIDWAY,
AND HAD TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO
REBOOK MISSED CONNECTIONS.
YOU DON'T TYPICALLY THINK OF NEW
MEXICO WHEN YOU DREAM OF A WHITE
CHRISTMAS.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THE WEATHER
STRAIGHT AHEAD.
>>> OF COURSE, TODAY IS
CHRISTMAS, AND CHRISTIANS AROUND
THE WORLD ARE CELEBRATING ONE OF
THE HOLIEST DAYS OF THE YEAR.
IN VATICAN CITY, POPE FRANCIS
TOLD THE FAITHFUL THAT THE BIRTH
OF CHRIST WAS A REMINDER OF
GOD'S UNCONDITIONAL LOVE, AND HE
WAS TRANSFORMED BY JESUS' CRAZY
LOVE.
>>> AND PEOPLE GATHERED IN THE
WEST BANK OF BETHLEHEM, THE
TRADITIONAL BIRTHPLACE OF JESUS.
IT'S NEAR THE SPOT WHERE
CHRISTIANS BELIEVE JESUS WAS
BORN.
>>> AND FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
MORE THAN 200 YEARS, THE NOTRE
DAME CATHEDRAL WAS CLOSED FOR
CHRISTMAS SERVICES.
THE PARIS LANDMARK IS TOO
RAVAGED BY THE FIRE EARLIER THIS
YEAR TO ALLOW VISITORS INSIDE.
MASS WAS HELD AT A NEARBY
CHURCH.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS SPENDING
CHRISTMAS IN FLORIDA.
HE ATTENDED A RELIGIOUS SERVICE
LAST NIGHT AFTER SPEAKING WITH
U.S. SERVICE MEMBERS IN A
TELECONFERENCE, AND DESPITE
BEING AWAY FROM WASHINGTON, HE'S
MAINTAINING HIS FIGHT AGAINST
IMPEACHMENT.
ABC'S RACHEL SCOTT REPORTS.
>> I WANT TO WISH EVERYBODY A
REALLY INCREDIBLE NEW YEAR, A
MERRY CHRISTMAS, A HAPPY
HANUKKAH.
>> Reporter: AFTER WISHING THE
TROOPS A HAPPY HOLIDAYS,
PRESIDENT TRUMP FIELDING
QUESTIONS FROM REPORTERS,
UNLEASHED A STRING OF INSULTS ON
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI.
>> SHE HATES THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
SHE HATES ALL THE PEOPLE THAT
VOTED FOR ME AND THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
SHE'S DOING A TREMENDOUS
DISSERVICE TO THE COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: LAWMAKERS SPENDING
THE HOLIDAY RECESS ENTRENCHED IN
A PARTISAN STALEMATE.
THE PRESIDENT FIRING OFF TWEETS
GOING AFTER PELOSI FOR REFUSING
TO SEND THE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT TO THE SENATE UNTIL
REPUBLICANS REVEAL HOW A TRIAL
WOULD BE STRUCTURED, BUT THE
HOUSE SPEAKER NOT BUDGING.
IN A LETTER TO HOUSE DEMOCRATS,
PELOSI CALLING ON SENATE
MAJORITY LEADER MITCH McCONNELL
TO MAKE THE NEXT MOVE WRITING,
IT MNOW REMAINS FOR THE SENATE O
SHOW HOW WE WILL PROCEED.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE'S IN A
GOOD POSITION.
>> NOW THEY COME TO THE SENATE.
THEY WANT EVERYTHING.
SO NOW THEY GET TO THE SENATE,
AND NOW WE HAVE THE MAJORITY AND
IT'S UP TO MITCH McCONNELL.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
SPENDING THE HOLIDAY IN FLORIDA,
ATTENDING A CHURCH SERVICE WITH
THE FIRST LADY ON CHRISTMAS EVE,
BUT ADMITTING HER GIFT WASN'T
UNDER THE TREE JUST YET.
>> WHAT DID YOU GET MRS. TRUMP
FOR CHRISTMAS THIS YEAR?
>> THAT'S A TOUGH QUESTION.
I REALLY SHOULD SAY A VERY
BEAUTIFUL CARD AND I'M WORKING
ON IT A LOT.
I GOT HER A BEAUTIFUL CARD THAT
ACTUALLY I HAD A NUMBER OF THEM
PICKED AND I PICKED THE NICEST
ONE, AND I'M STILL WORKING ON A
CHRISTMAS PRESENT.
IS THAT OKAY?
>> Reporter: RACHEL SCOTT, ABC
NEWS, WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA.
>>> THERE'S MORE RESEARCH
SHOWING CAFFEINE IS A GOOD WAY
TO SHED THOSE EXTRA HOLIDAY
POUNDS.
RESEARCHERS IN ILLINOIS SAY A
STUDY OF RATS FOUND THOSE GIVEN
COFFEE OR CAFFEINATED TEA GAINED
LESS WEIGHT.
ONE STUDY SAYS CAFFEINE IS AN
ANTI-OBESITY AGENT, AND DOCTORS
SAY IT MAY AFFECT METABOLISM
ISSUES THAT MAY LEAD TO WEIGHT
PROBLEMS.
>>> AND AFTER THE CONGREGATION,
FATHER PETER O'CONNOR TOLD KIDS
HE WAS GIVEN A SCOOTER FROM
SANTA, AND HE WANTED TO TRY IT
>> GOOD MORNING, I MAY BE 7
STEVE RUDIN.
HOPE YOU'RE HAVING A NICE
CHRISTMAS.
TEMPERATURES MOVED TO THE
AFTERNOON HOURS AROUND THE DMV
WILL MAKE IT IN THE MIDDLE TO
UPPER 40S.
WE WILL SEE ADDED CLOUDS BY 3
AND 4 O'CLOCK.
WE STAY DRY.
FOR THIS EVENING CLOUDS WILL
CLEAR OUT.
TEMPERATURES DROPPED THROUGH
THE 30S.
OVERNIGHT TEMPERATURES WILL
DROP AROUND THE FREEZING MARK.
TOMORROW L
>>> THAT'S IT FROM HERE.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, EVA.
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU, AND OF
COURSE, THIS DAY, SUCH A GREAT
DAY TO REFLECT.
PAULA FARIS IS HERE, AND PAULA,
YOU GOT A CHANCE TO SIT DOWN
WITH PROMINENT CHRISTIAN LEADERS
AND GET THEIR PERSPECTIVE.
>> WE DO A GOOD JOB OF
COMMERCIALIZING THIS HOLIDAY,
DON'T WE?
THIS HOLIDAY ISN'T ALL ABOUT
PRESENTS AND UGLY CHRISTMAS
SWEATERS.
IT'S A TIME TO GET TOGETHER, AND
HEAL AND UNITE.
FAITH LEADERS SAY THAT MESSAGE
IS AS POIGNANT AS IT'S EVER
BEEN.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, "GMA"
IS REFLECTING ON THE TRUE
MEANING OF CHRISTMAS.
TO DO THAT, WE SPOKE TO CARDINAL
TIMOTHY DOLAN.
HE'S THE ARCHBISHOP OF NEW YORK,
PASTOR HEIDI NEWBARK, AND
MICHAEL CURRY OF THE EPISCOPAL
CHURCH WHO GAVE THAT FAMOUS
SERMON AT THE WEDDING OF PRINCE
HARRY AND MEGHAN.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO BE
PREACHING ABOUT THIS CHRISTMAS?
>> WELL, JOHN 3:16 WHICH IS A
PASSAGE THAT'S USUALLY
ASSOCIATED WITH THE CRUCIFIXION
OF JESUS.
HE SAID, GOD SO LOVED THE WORLD
HE GAVE UP HIS ONLY SON.
THAT THE POINT OF CHRISTMAS IS
THE RADICAL, INCREDIBLE,
DEMONSTRABLE, UNYIELDING LOVE OF
GOD FOR THIS CREATION, AND FOR
ALL OF US AS GOD'S CHILDREN.
ALL OF US.
>> IT'S NOT RARE THAT AFTER
LISTENING TO THE NEWS OR LOOKING
AT THE PAPER OR TURNING ON THE
RADIO, YOU KIND OF EXHALE AND
SAY, BOY, DO WE EVER NEED HELP.
THE WORLD NEEDS HELP, I NEED
HELP, MY FRIENDS NEED HELP, MY
FAMILY NEEDS HELP, THE CHURCH
NEEDS HELP, AND YOU'RE THINKING,
WHERE IS THAT ULTIMATE HELP
GOING TO COME FROM?
THERE AGAIN, WE TURN TO THE
LORD.
>> IN OTHER WORDS, WE LIVE IN A
BROKEN WORLD.
>> WAY TO GO.
>> THAT'S THE HOPE OF CHRISTMAS,
CORRECT?
>> WAY TO GO.
WAY TO GO.
MY DAD SAID, CHRISTMAS IS SO
GOOD BECAUSE ALL THE TOOIDES AR
WORKING.
THE NEXT DAY, EVERYTHING'S
BROKEN.
>> I HAD AN EXPERIENCE THAT I
THINK PREPARED ME FOR MY
CHRISTMAS MESSAGE.
WE WERE PUTTING OUT NEWSPAPERS
FOR CHILDREN TO MAKE CHRISTMAS
CRAFTS AND I WAS LOOKING AT THE
NEWSPAPERS AND I THOUGHT, THIS
IS TERRIBLE NEWS.
THIS NEWS IS NOT GOOD FOR
CHILDREN, BUT THE CHILDREN CAME,
AND WE HAVE -- THERE WERE
CHILDREN WHO WERE HOMELESS AND
SOME CHILDREN WHO WERE
UNDOCUMENTED, AND THEY ALL CAME
AND THEY STARTED COVERING THE
NEWSPAPERS WITH GOLD GLITTER AND
PASTE AND THEY WERE MAKING
ANGELS AND STARS AND DECORATING
COOKIES, AND I THOUGHT, THIS IS
THE HOPE OF CHRISTMAS.
THAT -- THAT THIS BAD NEWS
SPREAD OUT ON THESE NEWSPAPERS
AND ALL AROUND US DOES NOT HAVE
THE FINAL WORD.
THE FINAL WORD BELONGS TO THE
ONE WHO COMES IN LOVE.
>> CARDINAL, THERE ARE SO MANY
PEOPLE THAT ARE HURTING IN THIS
WO
WORLD.
>> YES.
>> AND THAT HURT SEEMS TO BE
PRONOUNCED THIS TIME OF YEAR.
HOW DO YOU COMFORT THEM AT THIS
MOMENT IN TIME?
>> THAT'S ONE OF THE DOWNSIDES
WHEN EVERYBODY ELSE IS HAVING A
GOOD TIME.
THAT'S ONE OF THE DOWNSIDES OF
WHEN SOME SAY -- SOME OF THEM
OUR HOME BOUND AND SICK LOOK OUT
THE WINDOW, AND SEE CARS PULL UP
THE STREET WITH BUNDLES OF
GIFTS.
WHAT DO I SAY TO THEM?
I SAY, I KNOW YOU'RE TEMPTED TO
THINK YOU'RE ALONE, BUT YOU'RE
NOT.
>> IF YOU ARE COMFORTABLE, FIND
A WAY TO BE WITH SOMEONE.
THE TRUTH IS, AND FOR THOSE OF
US WHO HAVE FAMILIES AND HAVEN'T
LOST, THINK OF SOMEBODY YOU
WOULD LIKE TO INVITE SO THEY CAN
BE PART OF THE COMMUNITY THAT
YOU CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS WITH.
>> FAITH DOES NOT PROVIDE US
WITH ALL THE ANSWERS, BUT FAITH
CAN GIVE US COURAGE AND HOPE TO
KEEP GOING.
>> WHAT IS THE IMPORTANCE OF
FAITH IN 2020?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I WOULD SAY --
WHAT I WOULD SAY, PAULA, IS
THIS.
FAITH ALLOWS US TO
RE-ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS IN LIFE ARE NOT
SEEN.
WE LIKE TO DWELL ON WHAT WE CAN
SEE AND TOUCH AND HEAR, AND PUT
ON A COMPUTER OR LOOK AT UNDER A
LAB IN A MICROSCOPE.
FAITH SAYS, HEY.
ALL THOSE THINGS ARE GOOD, BUT
THE MOST ESSENTIAL THINGS OF
LIFE CANNOT BE SEEN.
LOVE, FIDELITY, LOYALTY,
FRIENDSHIP, GOD, HOPE, BUT WE
CAN'T SEE THEM, RIGHT?
CHRISTMAS INVITES US TO SAY, AND
FAITH INVITES US TO SAY, I WANT
TO STAKE MY LIFE ON THINGS THAT
CANNOT BE ACTUALLY PROVED.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT I KNOW THEY'RE REAL.
>> AND IN THE SEASON OF
REFLECTION, I'M GRATEFUL FOR
FAMILY AND MY DEEP FAITH AND I
HOPE THE CONVERSATIONS THAT YOU
JUST HEARD ABOUT THE TRUE
MEANING OF THE SEASON BRING JOY,
COMFORT AND PEACE.
>> GREAT TO HEAR THAT.
>> AND YOUR PODCAST YOU TALK
ABOUT THIS YEAR.
>> IT'S SO IMPORTANT TO YOU, AND
SO MANY OF YOU OUT THERE.
WE WANT TO REMEMBER THE REASON
FOR THE SEASON.
>> TODAY AND EVERY DAY.
>> THANKS, PAULA.
>> NICE SWEATER.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> AND NOW TO THE HIT HOLIDAY
PERFORMANCE THAT ONLY CIRQUE du
SOLEIL CAN PULL OFF.
IT'S CALLED " 'TWAS THE NIGHT
BEFORE," AND IT'S THEIR FIRST
EVER CHRISTMAS SHOW.
GINGER GOT A CHANCE TO GO BEHIND
THE SCENES.
♪
>> Reporter: IT'S THE OKAY
ACROBATIC HOLIDAY EXTRAVAGANZA.
IT'S A REIMAGINED CHRISTMAS
CLASSIC FULL OF TRICKS AND FLIPS
AND THOSE COSTUMES.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT TYPE OF
SHOW.
THIS IS A FAMILY SHOW.
>> IT IS.
IT'S A FAMILY SHOW.
>> THAT'S A BIG THING TO START
AT MADISON SQUARE GARDEN AND
JUST COME IN.
>> PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
>> Reporter: THIS IS AERIALIST
KATH
KATHERINE ARNOLD GIVING US A
BEHIND-THE-SCENES GLIMPSE OF THE
ENSEMBLES WORN BY THE CAST.
>> THIS CALLS TO ME.
WHAT IS THE ONE THING WARDROBE
PEOPLE MISS?
>> THIS THAT I HAVE ON, HAS, I'M
NOT KIDDING, ABOUT A HUNDRED
SNAPS IN THE BACK.
I HA
I CANNOT GET INTO IT MYSELF.
>> Reporter: ONE THING SHE DOES
HERSELF -- YOU DID THAT
YOURSELF?
>> YES.
>> HER MAKEUP.
THE OTHERS DO TOO.
YOUR LASHES TOO?
>> NO!
>> SHOULD I TRANSFORM?
THIS IS WHERE I TURN INTO A
PLAYER.
>> Reporter: MARYSE HAS BEEN
DESIGNING THE MAKEUP.
THIS WAS WEIRD WALKING AROUND.
I FEEL LIKE AN OOMPA LOOMPA OR
SOMETHING.
IT'S VERY FLEXIBLE.
I'M READY.
I'M A DIABLO.
THESE GUYS ARE CALLED DIABLOS.
AN INSANELY TALENTED GROUP FROM
TAIWAN THAT'S BEEN TOGETHER FOR
16 YEARS.
HI, GUYS.
I'M PART OF YOUR GROUP NOW.
THEY TAUGHT ME THEIR MAGICAL
WAYS.
WELL, TRIED.
WHOA!
DO NOT BE IN THE SHOW WHEN I'M
IN IT.
YOU WILL GET INJURED.
OH MY GOODNESS.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT,
GINGER, AND LARA, YOU GOT
SOMETHING FOR US.
>>> I SURE DO, MICHAEL.
SO WE ALL LOVE SEEING HOW PEOPLE
GIVE BACK DURING THE HOLIDAYS
AND THIS NBA ATHLETE YOU'RE
ABOUT TO MEET IS GOING ABOVE AND
BEYOND.
THE BROOKLYN NETS' DeANDRE
JORDAN IS AN ALL-STAR ON AND OFF
THE COURTS.
HE'S CELEBRATING THE HOLIDAYS
WITH WHAT HE CALLS SIX DAYS OF
GIVING, AND T.J. HOLMES GOT TO
SEE IT FIRST HAND, DIDN'T YOU?
>> YEAH.
YOU THINK OF SANTA CLAUS, AND
YOU THINK OF A BIG DUDE, RED
SUIT, WHITE BEARD.
THIS GUY COMES IN WITH A 17 SIZE
SHOE AND RIPPED.
THAT'S ANOTHER SANTA CLAUS, BUT
UNLIKE THE OTHER SANTA, THIS ST.
NICK, HE DOES MORE THAN JUST ONE
DAY OF GIVING IN DECEMBER.
♪
>> JORDAN STANDING RIGHT UNDER
THE BASKET.
>> Reporter: BROOKLYN NETS' STAR
DeANDRE JORDAN GIVES HIS ALL ON
THE COURT.
>> THE REBOUND, AND A STOP.
>> Reporter: OFF THE COURT, HE
GIVES QUITE A BIT AS WELL.
RECENTLY INVITING DOZENS OF KIDS
TO A FUN-FILLED DAY AT
NICKELODEON UNIVERSE INSIDE THE
BRAND-NEW AMERICAN DREAM MALL IN
NEW JERSEY.
>> I'M FEELING REALLY EXCITED.
HE'S REALLY MY ROLE MODEL.
>> Reporter: DEANDRE, A
SELF-ADMITTED BIG KID JOINS THEM
ON THE RIDES.
>> I'M A LITTLE DIZZY RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: EVEN A ROLLER
COASTER.
>> WHOO!
OH.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST THE ONES
HE CAN FIT IN.
>> I HAVE BEEN BANNED FROM THIS
RIDE BECAUSE I'M TOO TALL.
>> Reporter: IT'S ALL PART OF
WHAT HE CALLS D.J.'S SIX DAYS OF
GIVING.
HE CREATES SIX MEANINGFUL
EXPERIENCES FOR DESERVING
FAMILIES IN THE DAYS LEADING UP
TO CHRISTMAS.
>> ONE KID ASKED ME, WAS THAT
REAL?
THAT HIT ME.
HE WAS, LIKE, YOU'RE REAL?
I'M, LIKE, YEAH.
I'M REAL.
CAN I SHAKE YOUR HAND?
ABSOLUTELY.
I SHOOK HIS HAND, GAVE HIM A
HUG, AND JUST TO, YOU KNOW, PUT
A SMILE ON THEIR FACES IS A
GREAT FEELING FOR ME.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE SIX DAYS
THIS YEAR, WE'RE AT THE FLAGSHIP
NBA STORE IN NEW YORK WHERE WITH
THE HELP OF THE MOBILE RETAILER
FANATICS, HE GIFTED MORE THAN 40
KIDS $100 GIFT CARDS.
>> DO YOU KNOW MY NAME?
>> YES.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> DEANDRE.
>> YOU FOR SURE GET ONE.
>> Reporter: THESE ARE KIDS OF
THE BROOKLYN COMBINE, SUPPORTING
THE LOW INCOME AND UNDERSERVED
COMMUNITIES.
>> IT MEANS A LOT TO ME BECAUSE
KIDS DON'T HAVE TO PAY.
THEY GET THEIR OWN GIFT CARD.
>> Reporter: AT 6'11", AND A
SIZE 17 SHOE, HE'S A DIFFERENT
KIND OF ST. NICK.
7 FOOT BLACK SANTA CLAUS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
>> I CAN BE THAT GUY.
>> Reporter: WITH HIS BROOKLYN
NETS THEMED SANTA HAT IN
PLACE --
>> GET SOME GOOD STUFF.
>> Reporter: HE CAN BEGIN.
>> GET A HOODIE.
IT'S THE SEASON FOR HOODIES.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING FOR TODAY?
>> SHOES.
SHOES?
YOU CAN GET SHOES OUT OF IT
TODAY?
>> WAS THIS AN ACCIDENT?
ARE THEY SUPPOSED TO BE IN
THERE?
HOW WE GET FROM BROOKLYN TO
CHICAGO?
>> Reporter: THE NBA STAR
TREATED THE KIDS TO PHOTO OPS,
SIGNATURES --
>> HE SIGN IT FOR YOU ALREADY?
THAT THING JUST WENT UP IN
VALUE.
>> Reporter: AND LIFE LESSONS.
>> JUST EAT A LOT OF CEREAL.
>> Reporter: TO THESE KIDS WHO
LITERALLY LOOK UP TO HIM --
>> SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG.
REMEMBER, THIS IS MY FIRST DAY
WORKING HERE.
>> Reporter: JUST MEETING AN NBA
STAR WAS A PRETTY BIG DEAL.
>> MY HEART IS PUMPING.
I'M GOING TO REMEMBER THIS FOR
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
THIS IS A BIG BONUS FOR MY
CHRISTMAS.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO SIX DAYS OF
GIVING.
WHY?
>> I DIDN'T HAVE THAT AS A
CHILD, AND FOR ME TO BE ABLE TO
USE MY PLATFORM AS A WAY TO HELP
KIDS AND MAKE OTHER KIDS SMILE,
I THINK THAT'S -- THAT'S GREAT
FOR ME.
I LOVE THAT.
>> Reporter: AND HIS GIFTING
DIDN'T STOP WITH THE KIDS.
>> OH, YEAH.
THAT'S THE ONE.
>> I'LL TELL YOU.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD, MAN.
WELL DONE, MAN.
WELL DONE.
>> I'M TRYING, I'M TRYING.
I'M TRYING.
>> AND THAT WAS REAL, GUYS.
I GOT MY OWN BROOKLYN JERSEY.
YOU LIKE THAT?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> SANTA STRIKES AGAIN.
>> GOING TO SIGN ME TO A
CONTRACT.
REALIZED I WAS 42 AND HADN'T
PLAYED IN 20 YEARS.
>> HE'S A REAL DEAL.
>> HE'S A GOOD DUDE, COMES FROM
A GOOD FAMILY, HAS SOME
BROTHERS, BUT A BIG KID.
>> BIG HEART.
THAT WAS GREAT.
ESPN HAS YOU COVERED WITH A DAY
OF CHRISTMAS BASKETBALL.
YOU CAN SEE FIVE BIG NBA GAMES
STARTING AT NOON.
I KNOW I'LL BE WATCHING.
>> YES, INDEED.
>>> COMING UP, AS YOU UNWRAP
THOSE PRESENTS, WE HAVE YOUR
GUIDE TO GET THOSE TECH GIFTS UP
AND RUNNING.
>>> AND WE'LL BRING YOU SOME
MAGIC.
>>> AND THE VOCAL PERFORMANCE
CORRAL IS HERE GETTING YOU IN
THE SPIRIT ALL MORNING LONG.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ JINGLE BELLS, JINGLE BELLS,
JINGLE BELLS, JINGLE ALL THE
WAY ♪
>> I'M WANTING TO WISH MY
DAUGHTER AND GRANDDAUGHTER IN
TEMPLE, TEXAS, A VERY MERRY
CHRISTMAS.
>> THIS IS CORPORAL JEFF SHARP
IN KUWAIT WITH THE MARINES.
THIS IS A SHOUTOUT TO MY FAMILY
BACK HOME IN PORTLAND, OREGON.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, HAPPY NEW YEAR.
I LOVE YOU GUYS AND I'LL SEE YOU
REAL SOON.
♪ THE HORSE WAS LEAN AND LANK ♪
♪
♪ JINGLE BELLS, JINGLE BELLS,
JINGLE ALL THE WAY ♪
♪ OH, WHAT FUN IT IS TO RIDE IN
A ONE-HORSE OPEN SLEIGH ♪
♪
So Josh, you going for our
Drive Safe and Save discount?
Yup, using the app.
Driving safe. Heh.
You wanna go? Wanna go bro?
Hey, uh, do not mess
with my discount.
Woooo!
You could save up to 30%.
Let's go!
Nice to meet you,
go get 'em tiger!
Woooo!
Sounds like you've got this?
Yeah. Definitely.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe and Save™
from State Farm.
♪
Hey, need a laptop that boots up
as fast as 6 seconds
when you're running late?
Shhhh.
[whispering]
It's switching time.
♪
How about a battery that
lasts up to 12 hours?
[bell rings]
Order up!
♪
Now we're cooking.
Or how about one with
virus protection built in?
Which...
would be helpful...
right...
about...
now...
Yeah, if you want all that,
switch to Chromebook.
♪
[Sneezing]
♪♪
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
♪♪
JCPenney. Remember the little
things.
RUDIN.MAS.
I HOPE YOUR DAYS OFF TO A
FANTASTIC START.
AS MOVE THROUGH THE MIDDAY
TEMPERATURES REBOUND TO MIDDLE
UPPER 40S.
THAT WILL BE OUR DAYTIME HIGHS.
AS BEEN TO THE EVENING SKIES
WILL CLEAR OUT.
TEMPERATURES DROPPED TO THE 40s
AND 30S.
LATER ON TONIGHT LOOKING AT
NIGHTTIME LOWS THAT WILL RANGE
AROUND THE FREEZING MARK IN
SIGHT AND OUT OF THE CAPITAL
BELTWAY.
COLDER ALONG THE I 80 CORE
DOOR.
DAYTIME HIGHS WILL MAKE IT TO
AROUND 40 DEGREES.
FRIDAY, STILL DRY.
TEMPERATURES LOWER 50s AS A
MOVE INTO THE UPCOMING WEEKEND.
HER WATCHING FOR NEXT WET
WEATHER MAKER.
SATURDAY DAYTIME HIGHS WILL BE
IN THE MIDDLE TO UPPER 50S.
THAT WILL BE IN THE UPPER 50s
TO CLOSE TO 60 DEGR  H@CLOSED C
k
RUDIN.MAS.
I HOPE YOUR DAYS OFF TO A
FANTASTIC START.
AS MOVE THROUGH THE MIDDAY
TEMPERATURES REBOUND TO MIDDLE
UPPER 40S.
THAT WILL BE OUR DAYTIME HIGHS.
AS BEEN TO THE EVENING SKIES
WILL CLEAR OUT.
TEMPERATURES DROPPED TO THE 40s
AND 30S.
LATER ON TONIGHT LOOKING AT
NIGHTTIME LOWS THAT WILL RANGE
AROUND THE FREEZING MARK IN
SIGHT AND OUT OF THE CAPITAL
BELTWAY.
COLDER ALONG THE I 80 CORE
DOOR.
DAYTIME HIGHS WILL MAKE IT TO
AROUND 40 DEGREES.
FRIDAY, STILL DRY.
TEMPERATURES LOWER 50s AS A
MOVE INTO THE UPCOMING WEEKEND.
HER WATCHING FOR NEXT WET
WEATHER MAKER.
SATURDAY DAYTIME HIGHS WILL BE
IN THE MIDDLE TO UPPER 50S.
THAT WILL BE IN THE UPPER 50s
TO CLOSE TO 60 DEGR
I'm Christina Stembel
and I chose the Spark cash
card from Capital One
With unlimited 2% cash
back on everything I buy
Why wouldn't I get this card?!
I redeemed $115,000
in cash back,
which doubled our marketing
budget last summer.
What's in your wallet?
Cake in the conference room!
Showing 'em you're ready...
to be your own boss.
That's the beauty of your smile.
Crest's three dimensional
whitening...
...removes stains,...
...whitens in-between teeth...
...and protects from future
stains.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles for
life.
♪ ♪
Hurry in for UP TO
SEVENTY-FIVE PERCENT OFF
storewide...
...and ALL JEANS on sale,
with adults from FIFTEEN DOLLARS
and kids from TEN DOLLARS.
Only at Old Navy!
[Coughs] Kim is now
demonstrating her congestion.
Save it, slimeball.
I've upgraded to Mucinex.
We still have 12 hours
to Australia.
Mucinex lasts 12 hours,
so I'm good.
Now move-
that lasts 3x longer,
Kim nooooo!!ablet
for 12 hours.
♪ LET IT SNOW, LET IT SNOW ♪
♪ OH, THE WEATHER OUTSIDE IS
FRIGHTFUL, BUT THE FIRE IS SO
SLIGHTFUL ♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
YOU'RE LISTENING TO NYU'S VOCAL
PERFORMANCE CORRAL SINGING SOME
OF OUR FAVORITE HOLIDAY TUNES
GETTING US IN THE SPIRIT, AND WE
WANT TO LET YOU KNOW THAT WE
ARE, OH, GOSH.
WE'RE ON TAPE THIS MORNING.
WE WANTED TO BE WITH OUR FAMILY
AND FRIENDS.
WE WANTED OUR CREW TO BE WITH
FAMILY AND FRIENDS SO WE CAN
CELEBRATE JUST LIKE YOU ARE.
WE HOPE TO ON THIS VERY SPECIAL
DAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME
GREAT CHORAL MUSIC AND HAVE SOME
FUN.
WE HAVE THE GUYS FROM "THE DECK
THE HALLMARK" PODCAST.
SOME CHRISTMAS TRADITIONS,
INCLUDING FRUITCAKE.
>> YES.
>> A NEW TWIST ON FRUITCAKE.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT.
>>> WE HAVE A BIG SURPRISE FROM
ONE OF THE PEOPLE WE MET EARLIER
THIS YEAR DURING OUR MAKE YOUR
MONDAY SEGMENT.
SHE DEVOTED HER LIFE TO FEEDING
THOSE IN NEED IN MY HOMETOWN,
HOUSTON, TEXAS.
WAIT UNTIL WE SEE WHAT WE GOT IN
STORE.
>> IT WAS AMAZING WHEN SHE WAS
HERE BEFORE.
NOW AGAIN.
>>> NOW WE HAVE OUR GIFT GURU.
BECKY WORLEY IS HERE TO SHOW US
THE HIGH TECH PRESENTS YOU'RE
UNWRAPPING UNDER THE TREE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY ASSISTANCE THIS
MORNING?
>> Reporter: I DO.
MY TWINS ARE ALMOST 12 YEARS
OLD.
THIS YEAR THEY'LL TAKE ON THE
ROLE OF SANTA'S HELPERS FOR THE
GADGETS YOU JUST RECEIVED AS
GIFTS.
♪
>> WHOA.
>> Reporter: THE MAGIC OF
CHRISTMAS MAKES US ALL FEEL LIKE
LITTLE CHILDREN AGAIN.
THIS YEAR, I'M GIVING MYSELF THE
GIFT OF REST AND RELAXATION.
YOU GUYS ARE ON DUTY TO HELP
PEOPLE GET THEIR CHRISTMAS
PRESENTS UP AND RUNNING.
>> REALLY?
>> OKAY.
>> Reporter: EMMY STARTS US OUT
WITH WEARABLES.
>> IF YOU HAVE GOT AN APPLE
WATCH OR ANY OTHER FITNESS
TRACKER THIS HOLIDAY SEASON, YOU
SET IT UP WITH YOUR PHONE.
I DON'T HAVE A PHONE.
MOMMY?
>> Reporter: DOWNLOAD THE APP,
PAIR THE DEVICE, AND THEN YOU
CUSTOMIZE IT THROUGH THAT APP.
>>, IN FACT, THAT'S HOW YOU SET
UP ALMOST ANY SMART DEVICE THESE
DAYS.
>> OH, YOU'RE DOING SUCH A GOOD
JOB.
>> STAGE MOTHER.
>> Reporter: THERMOSTAT, APP
FIRST.
ROBOTIC VACUUM CLEANER, APP
>> SMART SPEAKER, APP FIRST.
MOMMY, THIS IS GETTING
REDUNDANT.
>> OKAY.
IT'S FINN'S TURN ANYWAY.
FINN?
>> IF YOU GOT A GAMING CONSOLE,
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU THE
PARENTS NEED TO DO FIRST.
>> Reporter: YOU HAVE TO CREATE
THE PARENT ACCOUNT FOR THE
DEVICE.
YOU DO THIS ONLINE AT SONY FOR A
PS4 OR AT MICROSOFT FOR AN XBOX.
ONLY THEN DO YOU CREATE SUB
ACCOUNTS FOR THE KIDS.
IF YOU TRY TO SET UP A PARENTAL
ACCOUNT LATER FOR TIME LIMITS OR
MANAGING AGE-APPROPRIATE
CONTENT, THAT MEANS THE KID
LOSES ALL OF THEIR IN-GAME
PROGRESS.
>> YEAH, AND THAT DEFEATS THE
WHOLE PURPOSE OF GIVING THEM A
GIFT IN THE FIRST PLACE.
PLUS, IT WOULD MAKE ME SUPER
FRUSTRATED.
>> Reporter: AND ABOUT PARENTAL
LIMITS.
IF YOU GAVE YOUR KID A PHONE AS
A GIFT, NOW'S THE TIME TO START
THINKING ABOUT PARENTAL
CONTROLS.
>> THESE THINGS CAN BE REALLY
ADDICTIVE TO US.
EVEN WORSE FOR THEM.
>> SEE?
>> Reporter: EVEN THE BUILT-IN
SCREEN TIME CONTROLS FOR APPLE
AND ANDROID DEVICES, PARENTS CAN
LIMIT TOTAL TIME, CREATE
BEDTIMES WHERE THE PHONE GOES
OFF
OFFLINE, AND PUT AGE-APPROPRIATE
CONTENT FILTERS ON.
THAT'S THE ADVICE THAT WILL SET
YOU --
>> HOW COME FINN GOT TO TALK
ABOUT TWO THINGS AND I ONLY GOT
TO TALK ABOUT ONE?
>> TWINS.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
TALK ABOUT GIFT CARDS.
>> OKAY.
IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THESE, TREAT
IT LIKE CASH.
>> Reporter: MEANING USE IT
RIGHT AWAY SO FRAUDSTERES ONLINE
CAN'T DRAIN THE BALANCE.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO SHOP NOW,
YOU CAN GO TO YOUR ONLINE
ACCOUNT FOR THAT STORE.
IN THIS CASE, IT'S A TARGET GIFT
CARD, AND THERE YOU REDEEM IT.
THE VALUE IS TRANSFERRED INTO
YOUR ACCOUNT FOR FUTURE USE AND
A CRIMINAL CAN'T GET AT IT.
OKAY.
YOU HAD TWO TIPS.
YOU GOT TWO TIPS.
EVERYBODY'S HAPPY.
THAT WASN'T ACTUALLY AS RELAXING
AS I THOUGHT, BUT MAYBE WE CAN
SEASONED YOU OUT WITH SOME
CHEER.
>> All: MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> WE TEAMED UP WITH THE FOLKS
AT COMMON SENSE MEDIA, AND THEY
HAVE INSTRUCTIONS FOR SETTING UP
THE PARENTAL CONTROLS ON OUR
WEBSITE.
IT'S THE LAST YEAR I CAN FORCE
MY KIDS TO HELP ME WITH WORK.
>> THEY DID A GREAT JOB.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> SAME TO YOU GUYS.
>>> WE'RE HERE WITH REBECCA
JARVIS TO TALK ABOUT IF YOU
DIDN'T GET THE GIFTS ON YOUR
LIST.
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU.
THERE ARE KEY THINGS TO KNOW
ABOUT WHEN YOU CAN MAKE THOSE
RETURNS.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
MICHAEL.
WE ALL GOT THE GIFTS WE WANT, OF
COURSE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, BUT ALMOST 80%
OF PEOPLE PLAN TO RETURN AT
LEAST ONE GIFT THIS YEAR.
WE ALL KNOW IT'S THE THOUGHT
THAT COUNTS, BUT SOMETIMES YOU
HAVE TO WONDER IF THERE WAS ANY
THOUGHT TO BEGIN WITH.
WELL, GOOD NEWS.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF WAYS YOU CAN
TURN THINGS AROUND.
IT'S THE MOST WONDERFUL TIME OF
THE YEAR TO TURN THAT LUMP OF
COAL INTO A DIAMOND.
AMERICANS RETURN $100 BILLION
WORTH OF GIFTS OVER THE
HOLIDAYS, AND IN YOUR FUTURE,
KEEP IN MIND THE WINDOW TO MAKE
THE SWAP CAN BE SHORT.
LOOK AT THOSE GIFT RECEIPTS AND
CHECK THEM TWICE.
SOME STORES GIVE YOU JUST 15
DAYS.
OTHERS AS MANY AS 30, 45, EVEN
90.
A NUMBER OF THE LARGEST
RETAILERS INCLUDING WALMART,
TARGET, BEST BUY AND AMAZON
EXTEND RETURN POLICIES OVER THE
HOLIDAYS, BUT BEWARE, NOT ALL
PRODUCTS ARE INCLUDED UNDER THAT
UMBRELLA.
ONE STANDOUT BEING ELECTRONICS.
IF YOU ARE DREADING THAT
FRENZIED TRIP TO THE MALL, DON'T
STRESS JUST YET.
MANY STORES NOW OFFER FREE
SHIPPING ON GIFT RETURNS MAKING
YOUR POST-HOLIDAYS LESS OF A
HASSLE.
IF YOU DO DECIDE TO BRAVE THE
CROWDS, THE BUSIEST DAYS FOR
RETURNS ARE HISTORICALLY
DECEMBER 26th AND 27th.
FINALLY TURN THOSE UNWANTED GIFT
CARDS INTO CASH LIKE GIFT CARD
GRANNY AND CARDPOOL.
YOU CAN INSTANTLY TURN YOUR GIFT
CARD INTO CASH.
AND REMEMBER THE DAYS AND WEEKS
AHEAD ARE THE MOST WONDERFUL
TIME OF THE YEAR TO STOCK UP ON
HAPPILY DISCOUNTED HOLIDAY
DECOR, BEDDING, WINTER WEAR AND
EXERCISE KPIMT, GUYS.
IF YOU DIDN'T SHOP ENOUGH BEFORE
THE HOLIDAY, THERE'S STILL MORE
DEALS TO BE HAD.
>> ALWAYS A STEAL.
>> ALWAYS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE THE
LITTLE WOMEN ABOUT TO DOMINATE
THE BIG SCREEN.
ALL THE MOVIES THAT ARE GETTING
OSCAR BUZZ THAT YOU CAN SEE WITH
YOUR FAMILY THIS GLORIOUS
CHRISTMAS.
>> I'M STATIONED AT AN AIR BASE.
I WANT TO SAY MERRY CHRISTMAS
AND HAPPY NEW YEAR TO MY
FAMILIES AND FRIENDS IN NEW
CASTLE, DELAWARE.
>> I'M CURRENTLY DEPLOYED IN
KUWAIT, AND I JUST WANT TO GIVE
A SHOUTOUT AND ALL MY LOVE THE
MY FAMILY BACK HOME.
I HOPE YOU'RE STAYING WARM.
MERRY CHRISTMAS AND HAPPY
HOLIDAYS.
>> I WANT TO GIVE A SHOUTOUT TO
MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS IN FRESNO,
CALIFORNIA.
SAY HAPPY HOLIDAYS AND MERRY
CHRISTMAS.
GO DOGS.
Honey, can you get the snacks?
Guess who's early?
Good thing Walgreens is right
around the corner
with last minute holiday
supplies.
Get in. Get out. Get jolly.
with last minute holiday
supplies.
My name is Jay,
and a little thing I like about
the grilled nuggets is
they taste fresh, juicy and
delicious.
Quiet frankly, eating them plain
in their own seasoning
really hits the spot,
and it tastes like grilling
chicken in your backyard.
They definitely got it right.
Hey I'm Colin.
I like Chick-fil-A's mac &
cheese because
it reminds me of my nana's mac &
cheese.
But this is a little bit better
because
it has the perfect amount of
smoothness and creaminess.
But I still love you, Nana.
Well it finally
happened, Zachary.
Somebody burned
down my she shed.
Nobody burned down
your she shed, Cheryl.
Well my she shed's on fire.
Your she shed was
struck by lightning.
Zachary, is my she shed
covered by State Farm?
Your she shed's covered, Cheryl.
You hear that Victor?
I'm getting a new
she shi-er she shed.
She shi-er?
Mhhm.
That's wonderful news.
Home insurance trusted by
more people than any other.
State Farm.
Home insurance trusted by
more people than any other.
Good morning
More treatment?
We're going to try something
different today.
Hi! Awwww, so pretty.
Dogs bring out the good in us.
PEDIGREE® brings out the
good in them.
♪
Everything your trip needs,
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
(Man and Woman)
[Burst of talking to animals]
for everyone you love.
♪
(VO)
It feels good to give back.
(Attendant)
Thank you so much.
(Woman)
Oh, you are so welcome.
(VO)
You can choose the ASPCA to get
two hundred and fifty dollars
from Subaru when
you get a new Subaru,
like the all new Outback.
(VO 2)
Get 0.9% on a new Outback
during the Subaru share the love
event.
You can't fake the goodness
of real strawberries
The crunch of real almonds
The taste of real raspberries
We use real ingredients
Because you can't fake...
delicious
Special K
>>> HEY.
I'M REBA McENTIRE WISHING
EVERYBODY A VERY MERRY
CHRISTMAS.
>> I'M BRAD PAISLEY.
HAPPY HOLD IDAYS.
>> I'M JOHN CENA HERE WISHING
YOU AND YOURS A HAPPY HOLIDAY
SEASON.
>>> LET'S LOOK AT THE MOVIES AT
THE BOX OFFICE SEASON
FROM "LITTLE WOMEN" TO "CATS."
CHRIS CONNELLY HAS THAT.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
WE USUALLY SEE HIGHER PROFILE
AWARD HOPEFUL FILMS AND THIS
YEAR IS NO EXCEPTION.
WHATEVER YOUR TASTE IN SINEMA,
CHANCES ARE YOU'LL FIND WHAT YOU
ARE LOOKING FOR TODAY AT THE
MOVIES.
TWO OF 2019'S SHINIEST MOVIE
PRESENTS GET UNWRAPPED TODAY.
>> MY GIRLS HAVE A WAY OF
GETTING INTO MISCHIEF.
>> Reporter: GRETA
GERWIG'S "LITTLE WOMEN," AND THE
HOLIDAY'S HIGHEST CAST OPENS AT
LAST.
>> I HAVE A BROTHER IN THE 2nd
BATT
BATTALION.
>> Reporter: AS DOES "1917."
IN THE TRENCHES WORLD WAR I
DRAMA, FILMED AND EDITED FOR
MAXIMUM BREATHLESSNESS.
>> I REMEMBER THAT MOTORCYCLE.
>> Reporter: EWWHILE REMAINING
ELITE MOVIE HOUSES ARE THOSE OF
TERRANCE MALIK.
>> PREYING ON THE WEAK.
>> Reporter: FOR "HIDDEN LIGHT."
IF YOU ARE DODGING SOCIAL MEDIA
SPOILERS FOR "STAR WARS: THE
RISE OF SKYWALKER" -- ♪
>> THE FORCE BROUGHT US
TOGETHER.
>> Reporter: -- YOU HAVE GOT
MORE JUST SERVED OPTIONS TOO.
"JUST MERCY" FOR ONE, WITH JAMIE
FOXX AND BRIE LARSON.
"CATS," WITH ITS MUCH MEOWED
OVER VISUALS.
♪ CHASING THE SUN ♪
>> Reporter: PLUS A NEW TRACK
FROM TAYLOR SWIFT, AND THE JUST
AROUND THE CORNER "CLEMENCY,"
WITH AN OSCAR CONTENDER.
>> IT MEANS NOTHING.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING OF
WHICH --
>> I DISAGREE.
I DISAGREE, GARY.
>> Reporter: FIND OUT WHY ADAM
SANDLER'S ENJOYING AWARD SEASON
BUZZ IN "UNCUT GEMS," RIPPED
FROM THE HEADLINES
OFFERINGS, "THEN AND NOW."
CLINT EASTWOOD'S "RICHARD
JEWEL," AND JAY
ROACH'S "BOMBSHELL," WITH NICOLE
KIDMAN AND CHARLIZE THERON.
>> I'M GOING TO BE THE STORY.
>> NO.
>> Reporter: THAT'S WILL SMITH
AND TOM HOLLAND IN "SPIES IN
DISGUISE."
OTHERS OFFERING A "SHAUN THE
SHEEP" MOVIE, AND "ARMAGEDDON."
AND NOW THAT YOU MENTION
IT, "FROZEN II" IS STILL IN
THEATERS.
>> WHAT WOULD I DO WITHOUT YOU?
>> YOU'LL ALWAYS HAVE ME.
>> Reporter: WITH ITS ICE SCAPES
READY TO BECKEN YOU INTO THE
UNKNOWN TODAY.
♪ INTO THE UNKNOWN ♪
>> Reporter: OKAY.
PLENTY OF CHOICES TO HELP YOU
STAY OUT OF THE WEATHER AND TO
GET READY FOR POSSIBLE OSCAR
NOMINATIONS.
GUYS?
>> THANKS TO CHRIS FOR THAT.
SO MANY GREAT MOVIES.
>> I WANT TO SEE THAT.
HAVEN'T SEEN THAT YET.
>> I WANT TO SEE "UNCUT GEMS."
>> I HAVE SEEN IT.
IT'S GOOD.
>> "LITTLE WOMEN."
"CATS" SOUNDS AMAZING.
>> A LOT OF CHOICES.
>> EBB PROWATCHING IT RIGHT NOW.
>>> HOW TO HAVE A STRESSLESS
CHRISTMAS COMING UP, AND A
SPECIAL PERFORMANCE FROM NYU'S
CORRAL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
d woke up first ♪
♪ Now you've got something
up your sleeve ♪
♪ What you didn't know
was you were surprising ♪
♪ your father-in-law Steve ♪
♪ Take a minute
to clear your head ♪
♪ Because that was really bad ♪
♪ Oh, no, yeah ♪
♪ And the worst part is, you
just started calling him "Dad" ♪
♪ The Best Part of Wakin' Up
is Folgers in your Cup ♪
I'm your 70lb St. Bernard puppy,
and my lack of impulse control,
is about to become your problem.
Ahh no, come on.
I saw you eating poop earlier.
Hey!
My focus is on the road,
and that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
Who's the dummy now?
Whoof!
So get Allstate where good
drivers save 40%
for avoiding mayhem, like me.
Sorry!
He's a baby!
SFX: [sneezing]
I am not for ignoring
the first sign of a cold.
I am for shortening my cold,
with Zicam!
Zicam is
completely different.
Unlike most other
cold medicines,
Zicam is clinically proven to
shorten colds.
I am a ZiFan for Zicam!
Oral or Nasal.
[♪♪]
Even when
your car is clean,
does it still
smell stuffy or stale?
Try Febreze CAR.
It eliminates
stuffy car odors
and leaves behind a fresh
scent for up to 30 days.
Try Febreze CAR
in a variety of scents
including extra light.
LET'S BE HONEST,
QUITTING SMOKING
IS FREAKING HARD.
LIKE QUITTING
EVERY MONDAY HARD.
QUITTING FEELS SO BIG.
SO, TRY MAKING IT SMALLER.
AND YOU'LL BE SURPRISED AT
HOW EASILY STARTING SMALL...
...CAN LEAD TO SOMETHING BIG.
START STOPPING
WITH NICORETTE
♪♪
JCPenney. Remember the little
things.