>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS THURSDAY
MORNING, PRESIDENT TRUMP
OFFICIALLY IMPEACHED.
OVERNIGHT, HE'S FIGHTING BACK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP THE THIRD
AMERICAN PRESIDENT IMPEACHED.
THE VOTE SPLIT DOWN PARTY LINES.
DEMOCRATS SAY TRUMP'S ABUSE OF
POWER LEFT THEM NO CHOICE.
REPUBLICANS CALL IT REVENGE FOR
LOSING THE ELECTION.
TRUMP FIRED UP AT A RALLY
OVERNIGHT, SAYING DEMOCRATS WILL
PAY A POLITICAL PRICE.
>> CRAZY NANCY PELOSI'S HOUSE
DEMOCRATS HAVE BRANDED
THEMSELVES WITH AN ETERNAL MARK
OF SHAME.
>> AND THE NEW QUESTION THIS
MORNING, WILL SPEAKER PELOSI TRY
TO DELAY THE SENATE TRIAL?
THE WHITE HOUSE PRESS SECRETARY
STEPHANIE GRISHAM JOINS US LIVE.
>>> BONE-CHILLING COLD AS THE
HOLIDAY TRAVEL RUSH GETS
UNDERWAY.
THE LOWEST TEMPERATURES OF THE
SEASON NOW MOVING IN WITH
DANGEROUS SNOW SQUALLS CAUSING
MASSIVE PILEUPS IN THE EAST.
GINGER HAS THE LATEST AS THE
BUSIEST CHRISTMAS TRAVEL SEASON
ON RECORD BEGINS.
>>> STATE OF EMERGENCY.
THE U.S. NOW SENDING
FIREFIGHTERS OVERSEAS TO HELP AS
RECORD HEAT BLANKETS AUSTRALIA,
CAUSING A MASSIVE OUTBREAK OF
MORE THAN 100 WILDFIRES.
>>> "HORRIBLE AND HURTFUL."
SINGER CAMILA CABELLO AND HER
EMOTIONAL APOLOGY TO FANS AFTER
PAST SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS ARE
DISCOVERED THAT SHE NOW CALLS
"UNEDUCATED AND IGNORANT.”
>>> ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE, THE
QUICK THINKING 4-YEAR-OLD WHO
MAKES A LIFE-SAVING 911 CALL.
>> MY MOMMY FALLED DOWN.
>> NOW BEING HAILED AS A HERO
HOW SHE KNEW WHAT TO DO.
HER FAMILY IS SPEAKING OUT ONLY
ON “GMA.”
♪ GOOD TIMES ANY TIME YOU MAKE A
PAYMENT ♪
>>> AND LET THE GOOD TIMES ROLL.
OVERNIGHT, TWO-STAR STUDDED
CASTS BRINGING "GOOD TIMES" AND
"ALL IN THE FAMILY" BACK TO LIFE
ON LIVE TV.
♪ AND A PARTRIDGE IN A PEAR
TREE ♪
>> THE BIG SURPRISES AND WHAT
THEY'RE SAYING ABOUT IT ONLY ON
"GMA."
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
WE HOPE YOU HAD A CHANCE TO
CHECK OUT THOSE SHOWS LAST
NIGHT.
TWO CLASSICS BACK ON TV FOR A
LIVE EVENT.
WE'LL HEAR FROM SOME OF THE
STARS AHEAD IN THE SHOW.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO THAT.
>>> A BIG NIGHT LAST NIGHT AND
BUSY THURSDAY MORNING HERE.
TAKE A LIVE LOOK AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS WAKING UP
THERE THIS MORNING AS THE THIRD
AMERICAN PRESIDENT IN HISTORY
EVER TO BE IMPEACHED FACING
THESE HEADLINES IN MAJOR
NEWSPAPERS.
YOU CAN SEE IT RIGHT THERE,
FRONT PAGES ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
>> HEADLINES THE PRESIDENT NEVER
HOPED TO SEE BUT AT A RALLY
OVERNIGHT TRUMP BLASTED THE
EFFORT CALLING IT A POLITICAL
SUICIDE FOR DEMOCRATS.
NEXT UP A SENATE TRIAL BUT HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI IS RAISING
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE TIMING AND
FAIRNESS OF THAT TRIAL.
MARY BRUCE WAS THERE ON CAPITOL
HILL FOR THIS HISTORIC MOMENT
TRACKING THE FALLOUT NOW.
GOOD MORNING, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
MONTHS OF INTENSE DEBATE CAME TO
A PARTISAN PINNACLE HERE LAST
NIGHT BUT THIS FIGHT IS FAR FROM
OVER.
ALL EYES ON THE SENATE AND THE
POWER PLAYS THERE THAT WILL
DETERMINE THE PRESIDENT'S FATE
JUST MONTHS BEFORE THE ELECTION.
OVERNIGHT HISTORY IN THE HOUSE.
>> ARTICLE 1 IS ADOPTED.
>> Reporter: WITH THAT SWING OF
THE GAVEL HIS LEGACY MARKED WITH
IMPEACHMENT.
ONLY THE THIRD PRESIDENT IN U.S.
HISTORY.
THE CHARGES ABUSE OF POWER AND Z
OBSTRUCTION OF CONGRESS.
THE VOTES ALONG NEAR PARTY
LINES.
NOT A SINGLE REPUBLICAN BREAKING
RANKS.
DEMOCRATS LARGELY UNITED TOO,
JUST A FEW OPPOSING IMPEACHMENT.
AS THE HOUSE WAS VOTING -- TRUMP
RALLYING HIS TROOPS.
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE WE'RE
BEING IMPEACHED.
WE DID NOTHING WRONG AND WE HAVE
TREMENDOUS SUPPORT IN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY LIKE WE'VE
NEVER HAD BEFORE.
>> Reporter: HE INSISTS
DEMOCRATS ARE THE ONES WHO WILL
PAY THE POLITICAL PRICE.
>> THROUGH THEIR DEPRAVED
ACTIONS TODAY, CRAZY NANCY
PELOSI'S HOUSE DEMOCRATS HAVE
BRANDED THEMSELVES WITH AN
ETERNAL MARK OF SHAME.
>> Reporter: HE ATTACKED
DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSWOMAN DEBBIE
DINGELL WHO VOTED TO IMPEACH HIM
GOING AFTER HER HUSBAND,
CONGRESSMAN JOHN DINGELL WHO
DIED EARLIER THIS YEAR.
>> MAYBE HE'S LOOKING UP.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
BUT LET'S ASSUME HE'S LOOKING
DOWN.
>> Reporter: THE CONGRESSWOMAN
RESPONDING YOUR HURTFUL WORDS
JUST MADE MY HEALING MUCH
HARDER.
ON CAPITOL HILL, REPUBLICANS
LOCKSTEP WITH THE PRESIDENT
ADAMANT HE DID NOTHING
IMPEACHABLE.
>> THIS VOTE THIS DAY IS ABOUT
RUN
ONE THING AND ONE THING ONLY,
THEY HATE THIS PRESIDENT.
THEY HATE THOSE OF US WHO VOTED
FOR HIM.
THEY THINK WE'RE STUPID.
THEY THINK WE MADE A MISTAKE.
THEY WANT TO TAKE AWAY MY VOTE
AND THROW IT INTO THE TRASH.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY
TRUMP'S AKZS LEFT THEM NO CHOICE
AND INVITED FOREIGN INTERFERENCE
INTO THE U.S. ELECTION BY ASKING
UKRAINE TO INVESTIGATE ONE OF
HIS CHIEF RIVAL, JOE BIDEN.
>> HE COMPROMISED OUR NATIONAL
SECURITY SO THAT HE COULD KEEP
POWER, NOT POWER FOR THE PEOPLE,
POWER FOR HIMSELF.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY THEY
HAD TO ACT NOW BECAUSE THE
PRESIDENT PRESENTS A CLEAR AND
PRESENT DANGER.
CHAIRMAN ADAM SCHIFF WITH A
WARNING ACROSS THE AISLE.
>> IF YOU IGNORE IT, IF YOU SAY
THE PRESIDENT MAY REFUSE TO
COMPLY, MAY REFUSE LAWFUL
PROCESS, MAY COERCE AN ALLY, MAY
CHEAT AN ELECTION BECAUSE HE'S
THE PRESIDENT OF OUR PARTY, YOU
DO NOT UPHOLD OUR CONSTITUTION.
YOU DO NOT UPHOLD YOUR OATH OF
OFFICE.
WELL, I WILL TELL YOU THIS, I
WILL UPHOLD MINE.
I WILL VOTE TO IMPEACH DONALD
TRUMP.
>> Reporter: IT MOVES TO THE
REPUBLICAN CONTROLLED SENATE AND
EXPECT McCONNELL AND SCHUMER
WILL SIT DOWN AND HAMMER OUT A
PLAN FOR THE TRIAL EARLY NEXT
YEAR BUT THE REPUBLICAN LEADER
MADE VERY CLEAR HE PLANS TO BE
IN, QUOTE, TOTAL CORD NATION
WITH THE WHITE HOUSE AND DOES
NOT EXPECT THE PRESIDENT TO BE
REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
>> ONE THING THAT COULD DELAY
THE TRIAL, MARY, THIS IDEA THAT
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI IS
NOW CONSIDERING HOLDING --
WITHHOLDING SENDING HOUSE
IMPEACHMENT MANAGERS OVER TO THE
SENATE AS LEVERAGE IN
NEGOTIATIONS OVER SENATE
WITNESSES.
>> Reporter: THIS CAME AS A BIT
OF A SURPRISE.
THE SPEAKER AFTER THE VOTE WOULD
NOT COMMIT TO SENDING THE
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT OVER TO
THE SENATE CITING CONCERNS ABOUT
AN UNFAIR TRIAL.
NOW, SOME DEMOCRATS HAVE BEEN
SUGGESTING THEY DO THIS TO GET
SOME LEVERAGE IN A FIGHT OVER
THEIR TERMS INCLUDING, OF
COURSE, DEMOCRATS' DEMANDS THAT
THEY CALL CERTAIN WITNESSES.
>> MARY BRUCE, THANKS VERY MUCH.
LET'S BRING IN WHITE HOUSE PRESS
SECRETARY STEPHANIE GRISHAM.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
WE HEARD PRESIDENT TRUMP
OVERNIGHT CALLING THIS AN
ETERNAL MARK OF SHAME FOR
DEMOCRATS BUT HOW CONCERNED IS
HE BEHIND CLOSED DOORS THAT
IMPEACHMENT WILL BE AN INDELIBLE
MARK ON HIS RECORD?
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID MANY
TIMES THAT THIS ISN'T SOMETHING
HE NECESSARILY WANTS ON HIS
RESUME BUT IT'S BEEN VERY CLEAR
FROM THE START THAT THIS HAS
BEEN A VERY PARTISAN IMPEACHMENT
AND HISTORY ISN'T GOING TO LOOK
KINDLY ON THE DEMOCRATS LED BY
NANCY PELOSI AND SCHUMER AND
NADLER AND THAT'S I THINK WHAT
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN SAYING
AND IF YOU LOOK AT THE POLLING
NUMBERS AND IT'S SHOWING THAT
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ALSO ARE
SEEING WHAT'S GOING ON.
HIS POLLING NUMBERS CONTINUE TO
GO UP IN TERMS OF AMERICANS
DON'T WANT TO SEE IMPEACHMENT
AND THEY DON'T SUPPORT
IMPEACHMENT.
>> WELL, SPLIT DOWN THE MIDDLE
ACTUALLY ON IMPEACHMENT BUT
MOVING ON TO THE SENATE TRIAL
RIGHT NOW.
WE NOW KNOW SPEAKER PELOSI AND
THE DEMOCRATS WANT WITNESSES IN
THE SPLAT TRIAL, AN IDEA THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS ENDORSED.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHEN IT'S FAIR, IT WILL FAIR
IN THE SENATE, I WOULD LOVE TO
HAVE MIKE POMPEO.
I
I'D LOVE TO HAVE MICK.
I'D LOVE TO HAVE RICK PERRY AND
MANY OTHER PEOPLE TESTIFY, BUT I
DON'T WANT THEM TO TESTIFY WHEN
THIS IS A TOTAL FIX.
I WANT THEM TO TESTIFY BUT I
WANT THEM TO TESTIFY IN THE
SENATE WHERE THEY'LL GET A FAIR
TRIAL.
>> SO WILL PRESIDENT TRUMP NOW
ASK THOSE WITNESSES TO APPEAR AT
THE SENATE TRIAL?
>> I WON'T GET AHEAD OF THE
LEGAL STRATEGY BEING LOOKED AT
RIGHT NOW AND THEN NOW AS YOU
GUYS TALKED ABOUT EARLIER, NANCY
PELOSI, IT LOOKS LIKE SHE MAY
NOT EVEN SEND THE ARTICLES OVER
TO THE SENATE AND ANOTHER
GIMMICK AND MORE CHANGING OF THE
RULES.
THE PRESIDENT WILL BE
REPRESENTED BY A VERY STRONG
TEAM AND AS HE HAS SAID, AS I
HAVE SAID, WE DO HOPE FOR AND
KNOW AND ARE CONFIDENT WE WILL
GET A FAIR SHAKE IN THE TRIAL
OVER THERE AND WILL BE ABLE TO
TELL OUR STORY AND THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE WILL BE ABLE TO SEE WHAT
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID ALL ALONG
THAT HE'S DONE ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING WRONG.
THE ONLY EVIDENCE -- IF I CAN
SAY ONE MORE THING, THE ONLY
EVIDENCE TRULY OUT THERE ARE THE
TRANSCRIPTS THE PRESIDENT HE
HIMSELF RELEASED AND, AGAIN, HE
DID NOTHING WRONG.
>> 70% ACCORDING TO POLLING OF
AMERICANS THINK HE DID SOMETHING
WRONG AND THERE IS A BODY OF
TESTIMONY SHOWING THE MILITARY
AID WAS WITHHELD AN A WHITE
HOUSE MEETING WAS WITHHELD AS
THE PRESIDENT WAS ASKING FOR
THESE POLITICAL INVESTIGATIONS.
>> NOT POLITICAL INVESTIGATION,
WE WANTED TO LOOK INTO
CORRUPTION.
THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT AND I
THINK IF THE MEDIA WOULD COVER
THIS FAIRLY, THEN PERHAPS PEOPLE
WOULDN'T THINK HE DID ANYTHING
WRONG.
HE WAS LOOKING INTO CORRUPTION.
HE WANTED TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
NEW PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE WAS
HOLDING UP HIS END OF THE DEAL
WHICH IS WHAT HE RAN ON WHICH
WAS NO CORRUPTION.
HE WANTED TO MAKE SURE THAT
BEFORE TAXPAYER DOLLARS WENT TO
ANOTHER COUNTRY THE CORRUPTION
WOULD BE DONE.
>> YOU USED THE WORD CORRUPTION
SEVERAL TIMES.
I A -- A WORD THE PRESIDENT
NEVER USED IN THAT PHONE CALL.
>> HE SAID DO US A FAVOR,
MEANING THE COUNTRY AND HE ASKED
THAT WE LOOK INTO -- THEY LOOK
INTO CORRUPTION WHICH VICE
PRESIDENT BIDEN IS ON THE
VIDEOTAPE TALKS ABOUT AND A
PROSECUTOR IN THE UKRAINE GOT
FIRED AND THEY WOULD WITHHOLD
MONEY.
THAT IS CORRUPTION SO THAT WAS
AN EXAMPLE BEING USED.
>> THAT WAS NOT CORRUPTION.
THAT WAS U.S. FOREIGN POLICY,
THE POLICY OF THE WORLD BANK AT
THE TIME AND POLICY OF THE
EUROPEAN UNION AND, AGAIN, THE
PRESIDENT DIDN'T USE THE WORD
CORRUPTION IN THAT PHONE CALL
BUT I DO WANT TO MOVE ON TO THE
PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS ABOUT
CONGRESSMAN DINGELL LAST NIGHT.
WE SHOWED THEM IN MARY BRUCE'S
PIECE DRAWING REBUKES FROM MANY
DEMOCRATS BUT ALSO FROM
REPUBLICANS.
CINDY McCAIN TWEETED AND FRED
UPTON FROM MICHIGAN HAS PUT UP A
TWEET.
HE SAYS, I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED UP
TO JOHN DINGELL MY GOOD FRIEND
AND A GREAT MICHIGAN LEGEND.
THERE WAS NO NEED TO DIS HIM IN
A CRASS, POLITICAL WAY.
MOST UNFORTUNATE AND AN APOLOGY
IS DUE.
WILL THE PRESIDENT APOLOGIZE TO
THE DINGELL FAMILY.
>> I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO THE
PRESIDENT ABOUT THAT.
I WOULD SAY THAT I AM VERY, VERY
SORRY FOR HER LOSS AND I WOULD
THANK HER AND HER LATE HUSBAND
FOR ALL OF THE SERVICE TO OUR
COUNTRY.
THE PRESIDENT DID LOWER THE
FLAGS AT THE WHITE HOUSE TO
HALF-STAFF TO DO EVERYTHING HE
COULD TO HONOR HIM AT HER
REQUEST.
SO WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS FROM
THERE.
WE DO THANK THEM FOR THEIR
SERVICE AND AGAIN VERY SORRY FOR
HER LOSS.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK THE
PRESIDENT SAID THAT OVERNIGHT.
>> YOU'D HAVE TO TALK TO THE
PRESIDENT ABOUT THAT.
HE WAS AT A POLITICAL RALLY.
HE HAS BEEN UNDER ATTACK AND
UNDER IMPEACHMENT ATTACK FOR THE
LAST FEW MONTHS THEN JUST UNDER
ATTACK POLITICALLY FOR THE LAST
2 1/2 YEARS.
I THINK AS WE ALL KNOW THE
PRESIDENT IS A COUNTERPUNCHER.
IT WAS A VERY, VERY SUPPORT I
HAVE -- SUPPORTIVE AND WILD
CROWD AND HE WAS JUST RIFFING
ON --
>> FINAL QUESTION AND THANK YOU
FOR COMING TODAY.
YOUR FIRST TIME ON "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA."
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> YOU'VE BROKEN WITH TRADITION
BY DOING AWAY WITH THE DAILY
WHITE HOUSE PRESS BRIEFINGS.
IN FACT, AS FAR AS I CAN TELL
YOU'VE NEVER HELD ONE.
WHY IS THAT?
>> OH, SO BEFORE I TOOK OVER
SARAH HADN'T DONE ANY EITHER.
ULTIMATELY THAT WILL BE UP TO
THE PRESIDENT IF I DO A PRESS
BRIEFING.
I'M HAPPY TO DO THEM.
MY TEAM ARE AGO VESTABLE IN
OTHER WAYS DOING INTERVIEWS AND
HAVE REPORTERS IN MY OFFICE AWE
THE TIME.
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU, THE PRESS
BRIEFINGS HAD TURNED INTO LESS
ABOUT EXPLAINING THE PRESIDENT'S
POLICIES AND MORE ABOUT
ARGUMENTS AND THEATER AND I
DON'T THINK THAT IT'S SERVING
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
I THINK WHEN IT'S A LOT OF
REPORTERS USING IT TO BE ABLE TO
PROMOTE THEMSELVES AND SELL
BOOKS AND BE VERY EVER BOAST AND
THROW TANTRUMS THAT'S NOT
SERVING THE PEOPLE AND NOT THE
WAY THE PRESS BRIEFING ROOM
SHOULD BE USED.
HOPEFULLY IF THE TEMPERATURE CAN
BE TAKEN DOWN AND THE PRESIDENT
DECIDES THE BRIEF SOMETHING A
GOOD IDEA I WILL HE ABE BEHIND
THE PODIUM.
>> STEPHANIE GRISHAM, THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
>>> THE IMPEACHMENT OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP SURE TO BE A MAIN TOPIC IN
THE FINAL DEBATE OF THE YEAR AND
LINSEY DAVIS IS THERE IN LOS
ANGELES WHERE THE CANDIDATES
WILL FACE OFF IN JUST A MATTER
OF HOURS FROM NOW.
LINSEY, THE REAL HEADLINE GOING
INTO THIS DEBATE IS NOT -- IS
WHO IS NOT GOING TO BE ON THAT
STAGE TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY RIGHT AND
GOOD MORNING TO YOU, CECILIA.
ONE BIG DIFFERENCE FOR THE SIXTH
DEBATE YOU'LL HAVE FEWER
CANDIDATES.
ONLY SEVEN CANDIDATES HAVE MADE
THE CUT.
YOU HAVE THE USUAL SUSPECTS
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN,
SENATORS ELIZABETH WARREN,
BERNIE SANDERS, MAYOR PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
ONE BIG HEADLINE MONTHS AGO THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY HAD ONE OF THE
MOST DIVERSE FEELS BUT NOW
ANDREW YANG IS THE ONLY MINORITY
CANDIDATE TO HIT THE DNC'S
THRESHOLD TO QUALIFY.
WHAT TO WANT FOR, IS BUTTIGIEG
ABLE TO CONNECT WITH NONWHITE
VOTERS?
SOMETHING HE HAS STRUGGLED TO DO
IN THE PAST.
IMPEACHMENT WILL LIKELY
OVERSHADOW THE NIGHT.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING THE
CANDIDATES DISAGREE ON BUT WOULD
RATHER FOCUS ON OTHER ISSUES AND
WITH FEWER PEOPLE ON STAGE
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR, ANDREW
YANG AND TOM STEYER MAY HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO STAND OUT.
OF COURSE, NOW THERE IS MORE AT
STAKE WITH THE FIRST PRIMARY
VOTING LESS THAN TWO WEEKS AWAY
AND WHILE -- TWO MONTHS AWAY,
SORRY ABOUT THAT AND, OF COURSE,
WHILE YOU HAVE ONLY SEVEN
CANDIDATES ON THE STAGE, 15
DEMOCRATS ARE STILL RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT.
AMONG THEM FORMER MAYOR MICHAEL
WHO LOOMS LARGE, CECILIA.
>> IOWA CAUCUSES IS RIGHT AROUND
THE CORNER.
THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE DEEP FREEZE
SETTLING IN ALL ACROSS THE
NORTHEAST.
THE STORM BROUGHT DANGEROUS SNOW
SQUALLS AND TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
TIME LAPSE SHOWING IT MOVE
ACROSS NEW YORK CITY.
WHOO.
LOOK AT THAT.
IT CAUSED A DEADLY PILEUP AS
WELL AND GIO BENITEZ IS IN
AL
ALBANY, NEW YORK, WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, GIO.
>> Reporter: HEY, MICHAEL.
GOOD MORNING.
IT IS VERY COLD RIGHT NOW.
7 DEGREES, NEGATIVE 11 WITH THE
WINDCHILL.
TAKE A LOOK.
WE LEFT THESE EGGS OUTSIDE
OVERNIGHT AND LOOK AND LISTEN,
MORE LIKE CUE BALLS AND YOU SEE
THIS, IT ACTUALLY STARTED
CRACKING AS IT FROZE.
YOU CAN SEE THAT YOLK FROZEN
SOLID.
INCREDIBLY COLD ACROSS THE
NORTHEAST.
OVERNIGHT WHIPPING BONE-CHILLING
WINDS TAKING AIM AT THE
NORTHEAST.
AN INTENSE SNOW SQUALL WITH
WINDS UP TO 37 MILES AN HOUR
BLANKETING THE TRITATE AREA.
THIS VIDEO SHOWS IT SWEEPING
OVER WESTCHESTER, NEW YORK AND
CARS NAVIGATING THE ICY ROADS.
IN CONNECTICUT YOU CAN BARELY
MAKE OUT THE ROAD FROM THIS
WEATHER TOWER CAMERA.
OUTSIDE BOSTON SNOW FALLING HARD
AND FAST LEAVING HOLIDAY
SHOPPERS SCRAMBLING TO GET TO
THEIR CARS.
IN PENNSYLVANIA A MASSIVE
TRACTOR TRAILER PILEUP KILLING
ONE AND SENDING MORE THAN THREE
DOZEN TO LOCAL HOSPITALS.
DRIVERS SAY WHEN SNOW SQUALLS
MOVED IN VISIBILITY WAS NEXT TO
NOTHING.
SEMI AFTER SEMI SALAMIING INTO
ONE ANOTHER.
IN SYRACUSE AS DRIVERS WERE
MAKING IT HOME FROM THEIR
EVENING COMMUTE, IT WAS A
VIRTUAL WHITEOUT AFTER A SNOW
SQUALL TOOK AIM THERE.
FROSTBITE CAN SET IN IN THESE
CONDITIONS, SO YOU WANT TO MAKE
SURE YOU'RE COVERING UP BECAUSE
IT'S SO DANGEROUS.
>> GET INSIDE BEFORE YOU END UP
LIKE THOSE EGGS.
WE'LL GO OUTSIDE TO GINGER
FEELING THE DEEP FREEZE RIGHT
HERE IN TIMES SQUARE.
HEY, GINGER.
>> WE HAVE NOW DROPPED TO 16.
THAT IS THE COLDEST NEW YORK
CITY HAS SEEN THIS SEASON.
THE WINDCHILL, 2 AND IT ALL CAME
BEHIND THIS COLD FRONT THAT
BROUGHT THAT SNOW SQUALL.
SO MANY PEOPLE TEXTING ME,
DM'ing ME SAYING WHAT IS A SNOW
SQUALLY VISIBILITY REDUCED, 30
TO 60 MINUTES.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
BEHIND IT COLD AIR.
TALKING ABOUT 15 BELOW UP IN
BERLIN, NEW HAMPSHIRE.
SARANAC LAKE AND SOUTHEAST THERE
IS A FREEZE WARNING ALONG THE
GEORGIA/FLORIDA LINE,
JACKSONVILLE, 29 THIS MORNING,
THE WINDCHILL.
>> BRUTAL.
THANK YOU.
THAT BITTER COLD IS MOVING IN AS
THE HOLIDAY TRAVEL RUSH GETS
UNDER WAY STARTING THIS MORNING.
THE TSA PREDICTING THE BUSIEST
WINTER TRAVEL SEASON EVER SO
TAKE A LOOK.
LIVE LOOK AT THE PLANES IN THE
AIR RIGHT NOW.
DAVID KERLEY IS AT DULLES
AIRPORT IN VIRGINIA.
DAVID, THIS IS YOUR SUPER BOWL,
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: YEAH, IT KIND OF
IS.
THE CRUNCH IS ON.
THIS IS THE BEGINNING OF THE
WINTER TRAVEL SEASON AND RIGHT
HERE AT THE TSA CHECKPOINTS IS
WHERE WE'LL FEEL THAT CRUNCH.
TSA EXPECTING 4% MORE PASSENGERS
TO BE SCREENED THIS YEAR
COMPARED TO LAST YEAR SO LIKE
THANKSGIVING THEY'RE BRINGING ON
ADDITIONAL OFFICERS AND USING
OVERTIME TO TRY TO HANDLE THE
LINES.
VERY PROUD ABOUT THANKSGIVING
WHICH WAS THE BUSIEST TRAVEL
SEASON OF THE YEAR.
THEY SAID WAIT TIMES WERE 30
MINUTES OR LESS.
THE BUSY TIMES TOMORROW AND
SATURDAY.
IN FACT, FRIDAY COULD BE AN
ALL-TIME HIGH FOR THIS WINTER
TRAVEL SEASON TEN A LULL THEN
NEXT THURSDAY AND FRIDAY FOLKS
EITHER HEAD HOME TORE GO OUT FOR
NEW WE'RE EVE OR SOMETHING.
THE GOOD NEWS AS YOU HEARD THERE
ARE NO CATASTROPHIC STORMS SO
THE 47.5 MILLION OF US MAY GET
HOME FOR THE HOLIDAYS.
>> WE HOPE THEY DO.
THANK YOU.
SUPER BOWL.
GETTING THIS STUFF DOWN.
WATCH OUT.
MY JOB IS IN JEOPARDY.
>>> ALSO THIS MORNING WE ARE
CELEBRATING THE LIFE OF HERMAN
BOONE.
THE LEGENDARY REAL-LIFE FOOTBALL
COACH PLAYED BY DENZEL
WASHINGTONLE IN "REMEMBER THE
TITANS" AND LED THEM TO A STATE
CHAMPIONSHIP SHORTLY AFTER IT
WAS SEE SEGREGATED AND THE STORY
INSPIRED SO MANY.
BOONE WAS 84 YEARS OLD.
INCREDIBLE COACH AND INCREDIBLE
MAN.
>> INSPIRATIONAL INDEED.
>>> FOLLOWING A LOT OF OTHER
STORIES INCLUDING THAT APOLOGY
FROM CAMILA CABELLO.
THE PAST SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS
RESURFACING AND CALLING THEM
UNEDUCATED AND IGNORANT.
>>> THAT QUICK THINKING
4-YEAR-OLD WHO CALLED 911 AND
SAVED HER MOTHER'S LIFE.
FIRST BACK TO GINGER.
>> THAT WINDCHILL FORECAST
BROUGHT TO YOU BY STATE FARM.
>> Eileen: VERY COLD TODAY, SO
MAKE SURE THAT YOU ARE DRESSED
WARM.
A HEAVY COAT, SCARF, GLOVES, A
HAT.
WE'LL HIT A HIGH OF ONLY 34, BUT
FEELING LIKE THE TEENS OUT THE
DOOR THIS MORNING AND FEELING
LIKE THE 20S LATER THIS
AFTERNOON.
CLEAR AND COLD TONIGHT.
WE'RE BACK DOWN INTO THE TEENS
AND 20S.
TOMORROW, SUNSHINE, STILL COLD,
ONLY 40 DEGREES, BUT AS WE HEAD
INTO THE WEEKEND, TEMPERATURES
START TO MODERATE.
SATURDAY WE'LL BE DRY.
PARTLY CLOUDY, 42.
THE FIRST DAY OF WINTER AND
MOSTLY CLOUDY FOR
>> WE'RE JUST
etty cool, huh?
They're speaking to Mom in
Japanese, and Mom hears them in
English.
♪
Can you understand me?
Yes, I can understand you.
Okay.
I have a lot of questions.
How do you guys fly? What does
Santa do in the summer?
Is Mrs. Claus a good cook?
Do you guys get presents?
Can you roller skate or ice
skate?
With the savings rates offered
at some banks,
your money almost
feels like it's frozen.
With Capital One, you can open
a new savings account
in about 5 minutes
and earn five times
the national average.
This is banking reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
SFX: [sneezing]
I am not for ignoring
the first sign of a cold.
I am for shortening my cold,
with Zicam!
Zicam is
completely different.
Unlike most other
cold medicines,
Zicam is clinically proven to
shorten colds.
I am a ZiFan for Zicam!
Oral or Nasal.
We're proving the new
Keurig K-Duo Brewer
makes any occasion the
perfect coffee occasion.
Breakfast in Bed!
Just add ground
coffee for a carafe,
or pop in a pod for
a freshly brewed cup.
Exactly how I like my coffee.
You've got your carafe.
I've got my light roast.
We're brewing the love.
3 out of 4 women recommend
Dove Cool Essentials
after trying it for a week,
like Crystal.
Underarms are so smooth
to the touch
And I love that fresh smell
I feel amazingly protected
I'm definitely feeling
more confident
Would you switch?
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
As a struggling actor,
I need all the breaks
that I can get.
At Liberty Butchumal-
Cut.
Liberty Biberty-
Cut. We'll dub it.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
HOPKINS.
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
THERE IS A NEW PUSH TO
STRENGTHEN MARYLAND'S HATE CRIME
LAWS, SEAN URBANSKI CONVICTED
YESTERDAY.
JUDGE DISMISSED THE HATE CRIME
CHARGE.
COLLIN'S FAMILY WANTS THE LAW
EXPANDED.
>> MELANIE: IT HAS BEEN 25 YEARS
IN THE MAKING TO BEGIN
CONSTRUCTION LOCATED BETWEEN
BRADDOCK AND REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT BLOOUP AND YELLOW LINES.
SCHEDULED SCHEDULED TO OPEN
2022.
>> ADRIANNA: JUST AHEAD, WEATHER
AND TRAFFIC STAY WITH US, WE'LL
BE BACK IN A FEW SECONDS.
>> EILEEN: MAKE SURE YOU BUNDLE
UP HEADING OUT THE FRONT DOOR,
FREEZING COLD.
TEMPERATURES WILL BE FREEZING
THROUGH EARLY THIS AFTERNOON,
D.C., 34 AT 3:00.
TUMBLE ONCE AGAIN TONIGHT.
WE ARE LOOKING AT A MILDER TREND
APPROACHING CHRISTMAS.
TEMPERATURES, LOWER 50S.
ANOTHER DRY AND COLD DAY
TOMORROW, JEWELS.
>> JULIE: MAJOR TIE UPS IN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY, VIRGINIA AS
WELL.
SECOND ACCIDENT INNER LOOP
BEFORE BRADDOCK, TWO LANES
BLOCKED.
NOW A 36 MINUTE RIDE HEADED
NORTH FROM ANNANDALE TO
MERRIFIELD.
CRASH BEFORE 355 PULLED TO THE
SHOULDER, STILL A TWO-HOUR
DRIVE.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
MEL?
>> MELANIE: JULIE, GET
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> ADRIANNA: "GOOD
(Man and Woman)
[Burst of talking to animals]
♪
(VO)
It feels good to give back.
(Attendant)
Thank you so much.
(Woman)
Oh, you are so welcome.
(VO)
You can choose the ASPCA to get
two hundred and fifty dollars
from Subaru when
you get a new Subaru,
like the all new Outback.
(VO 2)
Get 0.9% on a new Outback
during the Subaru share the love
event.
Oh-
Yes!
And it's on Rollback.
So cool!
She's going to love this.
♪♪
Sound bar?
So she can watch her cartoons
in Surround Sound.
And football.
(Danny)
Pet care ain't easy.
12 hours? 20 dogs?
Where's your belly rubs?
After a day of chasing dogs
you shouldn't have to
chase down payments.
(VO)
Send invoices
and accept payments
to get paid twice as fast.
(Danny)
It's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
>>> THEY CAN FLY NOW?
>> THEY FLY NOW.
>> CONFRONTING FEAR.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
CAN YOU FEEL THE FORCE?
IT IS ALMOST HERE.
"STAR WARS: THE RISE OF
SKYWALKER" JUST HOURS AWAY FROM
HITTING THEATERS GETTING
INCREDIBLE REVIEWS AND WE ARE
GETTING EXCITED HERE BECAUSE
OSCAR ISAAC IS JOINING US LIVE
FRESH OFF LONDON'S PREMIERE AND
A LOT OF QUESTIONS TO ASK HIM
COMING UP IN OUR NEXT HOUR.
>> A LOT OF NEWS TO GET TO.
HERE ARE THE TOP HEADLINES.
OF COURSE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
WAKING UP THIS MORNING AS THE
THIRD AMERICAN PRESIDENT EVER
IMPEACHED.
HE WAS PRETTY FIRED UP AT A
RALLY OVERNIGHT AND SAID
DEMOCRATS WILL PAY A POLITICAL
PRICE BUT STILL FACES A TRIAL IN
THE SENATE AND RE-ELECTION NEXT
YEAR.
NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI WILL TRY TO
DELAY THE TRY.
>>> DEVASTATING WILDFIRES RAGING
IN AUSTRALIA AS THEY FACE RECORD
HEAT.
A SEVEN-DAY STATE OF EMERGENCY
DECLARED AND U.S. FIREFIGHTERS
ARE HEADING THERE TO HELP FIGHT
THE FLAMES.
>>> BACK HERE AT HOME SOME OF
THE COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON,
MILLIONS FROM NEW YORK TO MAINE
FACING WINDCHILL ADVISORIES ON
THE HEELS OF THAT SNOW SQUALL
BECAUSE OF MAJOR PILEUPS ACROSS
THE NORTHEAST.
>>> WE TURN TO THAT APOLOGY FROM
CAMILA CABELLO SPEAKING OUT THIS
MORNING AFTER PAST SOCIAL MEDIA
POSTS WERE DISCOVERED, POSTS
SHE'S CALLING HORRIBLE AND
HURTFUL.
ERIELLE RESHEF IS HERE WITH THE
STORY.
GOOD MORNING, ERIELLE.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU.
A DAY AFTER THOSE DEROGATORY
COMMENTS SURFACED THE SUPERSTAR
TAKING TO SOCIAL MEDIA TO
APOLOGIZE SAYING SHE KNOWS HER
PAST LANGUAGE WAS WRONG AND
ASKING FOR FORGIVENESS.
♪ HAVANA 00H-NA-NA ♪
>> Reporter: MUSIC SUPERSTAR
CAMILA CABELLO FEELING THE HEAT
THIS MORNING.
♪ MY HEART IS IN HAVANA ♪
>> Reporter: APOLOGIZING FOR
PAST RACIST LANGUAGE AND IMAGES
SHE ALLEGEDLY USED ON A NEW
DELETED SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT.
CABELLO WRITING WHEN I WAS
YOUNGER I USED LANGUAGE THAT I'M
DEEPLY ASHAMED OF AND WILL
REGRET FOREVER.
I WAS UNEDUCATED AND IGNORANT
AND ONCE I BECAME AWARE OF THE
HISTORY AND THE WEIGHT AND THE
TRUE MEANING BEHIND THIS
HORRIBLE AND HURTFUL LANGUAGE, I
WAS DEEPLY EMBARRASSED I EVER
USED IT.
♪
♪ WORK, W0RKW0RK."
>> Reporter: THE ACCOUNT SEVERAL
YEARS OLD CONTAINS A SERIES OF
RACIST JOKES AND MEMES WHILE
CABELLO WHO DATES SHAWN MENDES
DID NOT SAY THE ACCOUNT IN
QUESTION WAS HERS --
♪ WHEN YOU CALL ME SENORITA ♪
♪ I WISH IT WASN'T SO HARD --
>> Reporter: SHE SAID I CAN'T
SAY ENOUGH HOW DEEPLY SORRY AND
ASHAMED I FEEL AND I APOLOGIZE
AGAIN FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY
HEART BUT NOT ENOUGH FOR MANY
THIS MORNING WHO ARE TAKING TO
TWITTER TO VENT THEIR
FRUSTRATION.
ONE WOMAN WRITING THAT EVEN
THOUGH THE 22-YEAR-OLD STAR MAY
HAVE MADE THE POST WHEN SHE WAS
A TEENAGER, AT 15 SHE HAD TO
KNOW RACISM IS WRONG.
OTHERS COMING TO HER DEFENSE
TWEETING, AT THIS MOMENT WE MUST
TAKE HER APOLOGY AND HOPE SHE
TRULY MEANS IT.
CABELLO ALSO WRITING IN HER
APOLOGY AS MUCH AS I WISH I
COULD, I CAN'T GO BACK IN TIME
AND CHANGE THE THINGS I SAID IN
THE PAST BUT ONCE YOU KNOW
BETTER, YOU DO BETTER AND THAT'S
ALL I CAN DO SO A LITTLE BIT OF
INTROSPECTION THIS MORNING.
>> LESSON THERE.
>> REMINDER WHEN YOU DO STUFF
WHEN YOU'RE A KID, IT CATCHES UP
TO YOU.
LASTS FOREVER.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN TO THAT 17-YEAR-OLD
GIRL UNDER ARREST FOR STEALING
AND CRASHING A PRIVATE PLANE IN
CALIFORNIA.
NEW SURVEILLANCE VIDEO CAPTURED
IT ALL ON CAMERA AND DIANE
MACEDO HAS THE STORY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, THERE
ARE A LOT OF QUESTIONS THIS
MORNING AS POLICE SAY THAT TEEN
SOMEHOW HOPPED AN AIRPORT FENCE
THEN STOLE AND CRASHED THAT
PLANE ALL WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING
HOW TO DRIVE A CAR.
WATCH AS THIS MILLION DOLLAR
PLANE PULLS A U-TURN AT FRESNO
YOSEMITE AIRPORT AND POLICE
SAYING THE PERSON AT THE
CONTROLS A 17-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
>> WE HAD AN AIRCRAFT HIT THE
BUILDING.
>> Reporter: THE TEEN MANAGED TO
START ONE ENGINE AND GET THE
PLANE MOVING DESPITE NOT EVEN
KNOWING HOW TO DRIVE A CAR, THIS
AFTER THEY SAY SHE GAINED ACCESS
TO THE AIRCRAFT BY CLIMBING OVER
A BARBED WIRE FENCE.
>> THE AIRCRAFT BEGAN TO MOVE
AND PIVOT AND CRASHED INTO A
BUILDING AND A FENCE ON AIRPORT
PROPERTY.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THEY
FOUND THE TEEN SITTING IN THE
PILOT SEAT WEARING THE PILOT'S
HEADSET ADDING THAT SHE SEEMED
DISORIENTED AND HAD RESISTED
ARREST.
MOTIVE IS STILL UNCLEAR BUT
TERRORISM IS NOT SUSPECTED.
>> THE PRESS ANY INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT IS CURRENTLY WORKING
WITH THE FAA, THE FBI AND OTHER
AUTHORITIES TO INVESTIGATE THIS
INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: THE TEEN'S MOTHER
SAID HER DAUGHTER HAD RUN AWAY
EARLIER THIS WEEK AND THAT THIS
WAS THE FIRST TIME SHE HAD SEEN
HER IN DAYS.
AND THE GIRL WAS BOOKED AS A
JUVENILE ON SUSPICION OF THEFT
OF AN AIRCRAFT.
THE PLANE REPORTEDLY WAS
SEVERELY DAMAGED BUT THE BRIGHT
SPOT HERE LUCKILY NO ONE WAS
HURT.
>> THANK GOODNESS FOR THAT.
THANK YOU, DIANE.
>>> NOW TO THAT EXCLUSIVE WITH
THE 4-YEAR-OLD WHO KEPT HER COOL
AND CALLED 911 TO SAVE HER MOM'S
LIFE.
FIRST RESPONDERS HAILING HER AS
A HERO AND THIS MORNING, WE'RE
HEARING FROM HER FAMILY.
WILL REEVE IS HERE WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, WILL.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING.
THE SITUATION WAS URGENT.
HAIL LAY GLASSER FALLING ON THE
GROUND UNCONSCIOUS.
ONLY AT HOME HER OLDEST
4-YEAR-OLD ISLA SAVED HER LIFE
BY CALLING 911 AND ACCORDING TO
POLICE HANDLING THE WHOLE THING
BETTER THAN SOME ADULTS.
>> 9-1-1.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, THIS
4-YEAR-OLD GIRL CALLING 911
SAVING HER MOTHER'S LIFE EARLIER
THIS MONTH.
NOW BEING HAILED AS A HERO.
>> 911, WHAT IS YOUR EMERGENCY?
>> UM, MY MOMMY FALL DOWN AND
SHE CAN'T TALK.
>> Reporter: ISLA SPRINGING INTO
ACTION AFTER HER MOTHER FELL
UNCONSCIOUS AT HER HOME IN NEW
JERSEY CALMLY EXPLAINING THE
SITUATION AND GIVING HER ADDRESS
TO THE DISPATCHER.
>> ARE HER EYES HOPE?
>> NO.
>> WHERE IN THE HOUSE ARE YOU?
>> UM, I'M ON -- UM, I'M IN -- I
DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU IN THE KITCHEN, IN
THE BEDROOM, IN THE TV ROOM?
>> I'M IN THE KITCHEN.
>> Reporter: WITH HER BABY
SIBLINGS INSIDE AND HER MOTHER
STILL ON THE FLOOR, ISLA WAITS
ON THE LINE AS HELP ARRIVES.
>> ONE MINUTE I WAS THINKING I
HAD TO CALL MY DOCTOR AND THE
NEXT I'M LAYING ON MY KITCHEN
FLOOR.
>> Reporter: THE OFFICERS
GETTING TO HALEY.
>> SHE EASILY COULD HAVE BEEN
SCARED AND SHE WAS FACED WITH A
REALLY POTENTIALLY DANGEROUS AND
SCARY SITUATION BUT HANDLED
HERSELF WITH COMPLETE AND UTTER
CONTROL AND COMPOSURE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Reporter: POLICE IN THEIR
HOMETOWN PRAISING ISLA FOR
SAVING HER MOM'S LIFE.
>> I KNOW ADULTS THAT CANNOT
HANDLE THIS TYPE OF AN INCIDENT
WITH THAT MUCH BRAVERY, POISE
AND DISTINCTION.
>> Reporter: AND BESTOWING HER
WITH HONORS.
>> BY ORDER OF THE CHIEF OF
POLICE, YOU ARE HEREBY AWARDED
THIS CERTIFICATE OF COMMENDATION
FOR YOUR BRAVE AND HEROIC
EFFORTS FOR CALLING 911.
>> BECAUSE HALEY HAS A CHRONIC
MEDICAL CONDITION SHE AND HER
HUSBAND SPEND A LOT OF TIME
PREPARING THEIR YOUNG KIDS FOR
THESE TYPES OF EMERGENCIES BY
TEACHING THEM THEIR ADDRESS,
EXPLAINING WHAT 911 IS AND HOW
TO USE IT AND ALSO EXPLAIN WHAT
IS AN EMERGENCY AND WHAT ISN'T.
THEY POINT OUT AUTHORITIES LIKE
POLICE OFFICERS AND FIRST
RESPONDERS IDENTIFYING THEM,
EVEN THOUGH THEY ARE STRANGERS,
THEY ARE GOOD AND THEY CAN HELP.
ALL VERY USEFUL FOLEY EVERYONE.
>> WHAT AN IMPRESSIVE
4-YEAR-OLD.
HAD HER WONDER WOMAN OUTFIT ON.
SHE IS A LITTLE WONDER WOMAN.
BUT IS THAT THE RIGHT AGE TO
TEACH KIDS ABOUT 911 AND WHAT'S
THE IMPORTANT THING TO TELL THEM
WITHOUT SCARING THEM?
>> RIGHT, WELL, THE SOONER THE
BETTER.
IF THEY'RE OLD ENOUGH TO USE A
PLAY PHONE THEY CAN PROBABLY BE
TAUGHT TO USE 911 AND EXPERTS
RECOMMENDING TEACHING YOUR KIDS
HOW TO DO IT ON A CELL PHONE AS
WELL AS A LANDLINE AND NEED TO
EXPLAIN TO THEM WHEN TO CALL,
WHAT'S AN EMERGENCY, WHAT ISN'T,
YOU KNOW, YOUR SISTER STEALING
YOUR TOY, NOT AN EMERGENCY.
BUT IF AN ADULT IS HURT, THEN
YOU SHOULD CALL AND TO KEEP THEM
FROM BEING SCARED YOU NEED TO
TELL THEM WHAT TO EXPECT.
WHAT THE DISPATCHER IS PROBABLY
GOING TO SAY.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN AFTER
THAT AND CLEARLY THE GLASER
FAMILY DID THAT WITH THEIR
DAUGHTER ISLA AND SHE DID THAT.
>> WHEN YOU'RE 4, EMERGENCY IS
RELATIVE.
>> VERY TRUE.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
GLAD EVERYONE IS OKAY IN THIS
REAL EMERGENCY.
>>> COMING UP AN ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE.
OUR REPORTER GOES ON A STING TO
CATCH PORCH PIRATES.
HOW THEY'RE CRACKING DOWN THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
Thousands of women with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of the body,
are living in the moment
and taking IBRANCE.
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor
is for postmenopausal women
or for men with HR+/HER2-
metastatic breast cancer,
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole
significantly delayed
disease progression
versus letrozole,
and shrank tumors in
over half of patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop low
white blood cell counts
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
IBRANCE may cause severe
inflammation of the lungs
that can lead to death.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have new
or worsening symptoms,
including trouble breathing,
shortness of breath,
cough, or chest pain.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if
you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness, nausea,
sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Be in your moment.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
♪ ♪
Only Roomba i7+ uses two
multi-surface rubber brushes.
And picks up more pet hair
than other robot vacuums.
And the filter captures 99%
of dog and cat allergens.
If it's not from iRobot,
it's not a Roomba™.
[ “I Feel Love”
by Sam Smith ]
Save time this season
with Drive Up at Target.
♪ I feel love ♪
Just pull up, tap the app,
and get everything
on your list.
So quick, the kids
won't even notice.
Make your holiday
shopping easy,
and try Drive Up at Target.
We took lifelong pasta experts
and gave one Prego Traditional
and one Ragu Traditional.
This is what happened.
( ♪♪ )
That's because even Ragu users
prefer the taste
of Prego Traditional.
( ♪♪ )
Drivers just wont put their
phones down.
We need a solution.taste
of Prego Traditional.
Introducing... Smartdogs.
The first dogs trained to train
humans.
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
>>> BACK NOW WITH A LOOK AT HOW
POLICE ARE CRACKING DOWN ON
PORCH PIRATES.
MATT GUTMAN IS IN ANAHEIM,
CALIFORNIA, WITH A LOOK BEHIND
THE SCENES OF A STING OPERATION
TARGETING PACKAGE THIEVES.
GOOD MORNING, MATT.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
IT IS THE SEASON WHEN PACKAGES
START PILING UP OUTSIDE OUR DOOR
AND THE SEASON WHEN THEY START
DISAPPEARING.
NOW, SO OFTEN THIS IS A CRIME OF
OPPORTUNITY.
SOMETIMES CAUGHT ON DOORBELL
CAMERAS LIKE THIS ONE BUT NOW
LAW ENFORCEMENT IS TURNING TO
ANOTHER HIGH-TECH DEVICE
INSERTING TRACKERS INSIDE
PACKAGES LIKE THESE TO CATCH
PORCH PIRATES REDHANDED.
THEY ARE THE BRAZEN THIEVES THAT
STRIKE IN BROAD DAYLIGHT AND IN
THE DEAD OF NIGHT.
AND THE HOLIDAYS AREN'T JUST
PEAK SEASONS FOR STORES BUT FOR
GRINCHES GRABBING HOLIDAY CHEER
RIGHT OFF YOUR DOORSTEP.
SO ACROSS THE COUNTRY POLICE
DEPARTMENTS ARE CRACKING DOWN ON
PORCH PIRATES.
"GMA" HAS EXCLUSIVELY TEAMED UP
WITH THE ANAHEIM POLICE
DEPARTMENT THAT LAUNCHED A
PROGRAM OF STING OPERATIONS TO
LURE THIEVES BY PLANTING GPS
TRACKERS IN PACKAGES.
>> WHAT DO YOU INTEND ON PUTTING
INSIDE?
>> WE ARE PUTTING IN TWO
BRAND-NEW iPHONES.
>> Reporter: WORTH NEARLY A
THOUSAND DOLLARS.
THE PHONES AND THE TRACKER GO
INTO THAT BACKPACK AND THAT
LITHIUM ION STICKER MAYBES IT
MORE ENTICING BUT PORCH PIRATES
AREN'T THAT PICKY.
>> THEY'RE JUST TAKING THEM.
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE TAKING.
>> Reporter: THE NEXT STEP, THE
STING.
THE TRAP IS SET.
THERE IS THE BAIT.
AS SOON AS THIS PACKAGE MOVES
EVEN A COUPLE OF FEET IT WILL
TRIGGER AN ALARM THAT WILL GO
OFF AT DISPATCH AND THE
DISPATCHERS ARE GOING TO LET
OFFICERS KNOW THAT THIS THING IS
ON THE MOVE.
>> IF IT'S A GUY THAT'S GOING
TWO MILES AN HOUR WE CAN INFER
HE'S WALKING.
40 MILES AN HOUR WE KNOW TO LOOK
FOR A CAR.
>> Reporter: THEIR OPERATION
SEEMS TO BE WORKING.
THIS POLICE BODY CAMERA FOOTAGE
SHOWS ANAHEIM OFFICERS BOOKING
SUSPECTS WHO HAD NO IDEA THE
PACKAGE THEY WERE SUSPECTED OF
SWIPING LED POLICE TO THEIR
EXACT LOCATION.
BUT PROGRAMS LIKE THESE ACROSS
THE COUNTRY RELY ON ANOTHER TOO
MANY, DOORBELL SURVEILLANCE
CAMERAS.
NOW RING SYSTEMS LIKE THE ONES
OWNED BY ADRIENNE JENKINS ARE
LEADING TO ARRESTS.
>> WE SHARE THE RING VIDEO ON
THE NEIGHBORHOOD APP AND THE
POLICE ACTUALLY CAUGHT THE GUYS.
>> Reporter: NOW THERE ARE A
NUMBER OF THINGS YOU CAN DO TO
AVOID THIS.
SIGN UP FOR DELIVERY ALERTS FROM
YOUR SHIPPER OR YOU CAN HAVE
YOUR PACKAGES DELIVERED TO YOUR
VENDOR'S LOCAL STORE OR DO
SOMETHING A LOT OF THE COPS ARE
DOING AND THAT'S GETTING P.O.
BOXES AND PICKING UP THE
PACKAGES AT YOUR CONVENIENCE
THERE.
NOW, IT MAY SOUND OLD SCHOOL,
LITTLE OLD FASHIONED AND LOW
TECH, BUT IT WORKS.
GUYS.
>> WE'LL TAKE IT.
>> 'TIS THE SEASON OF PORCH
PIRATES.
>> THANK YOU, MATT.
>>> COMING UP A HOLIDAY HEALTH
ALERT.
THE NEW STUDY, WHAT HAS A BIGGER
EFFECT ON WEIGHT LOSS, FOOD OR
YOUR FITNESS ROUTINE?
>>> UP NEXT ON "GMA," THE
GRAVITY-DEFYING GOAL YOU WILL
HAVE TO SEE TO BELIEVE.AY OF TH"
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Problems.
Nobody likes problems.
But why is that?
At IBM, problems
actually inspire us,
to fix things,
to change things,
to push the world forward.
Which is why so many people
who dare to take on
problems work with IBM.
Which is why so many people
Woman 1 OC:
This is my body of proof.
Man 1 VO:
Proof of less joint pain
and clearer skin.
Man 2 VO:
Proof that I can fight
psoriatic arthritis...
Woman 2 VO:
...with HUMIRA.
Woman 3 VO:
HUMIRA targets
and blocks
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes
to both joint
and skin symptoms.
It's proven
to help relieve pain,
stop further
irreversible joint damage,
and clear skin in many adults.
HUMIRA is the number one
prescribed biologic
for psoriatic arthritis.
AVO:
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Man 3 VO:
Ask your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
Woman 4 VO:
Go to HUMIRA.com
to see proof in action.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
- I'm just really stressed.
- Why?
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
I haven't gotten any of my
Holiday shopping done.
Ah...
Go to oldnavy.com
Buy online and pickup
in-store in just
two hours.
- How did you do that?
- Magic!
That's amazing!
Oh... can I get the
weekend off?
- Magically?
- I don't know
that trick.
♪♪
You try baking a pie.
THE DAY" AND MOVE OVER, LeBRON
JAMES, INTERNATIONAL SOCCER STAR
CRISTIANO RONALDO IS CHANNELING
THE ENTIRE NBA WITH THIS
GRAVITY-DEFYING GOAL.
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, SOME SAY -- LOOK AT
THIS.
JUST GLIDING UPWARDLY INTO THE
AIR.
WOW.
SOME SAY HE'S THE MOST FAMOUS
MAN IN THE WORLD.
SOARING TO NEW HEIGHTS JUST WHEN
YOU THOUGHT HE COULDN'T GET UP,
HIS GAME GOT EVEN HIGHER.
HE'S ALWAYS ELEVATING THE
PLAYING FIELD.
>> WOW.
>> ACCORDING TO SKY SPORTS HE
LEAPT MORE THAN TWO FEET OFF THE
GROUND WHEN HE MADE CONTACT WITH
THE SOCCER BALL HE APPEARED TO
BE FLOATING AND SAID HE WAS OVER
EIGHT FEET IN THE AIR AND THAT'S
MAKING ITS ROUNDS ON TWITTER AND
HE EVEN TWEETED HIMSELF SAYING
HE CREDITS HIS AIR JORDANS.
AND THEN CHECK OUT THIS TWEET
FROM GRAPHIC ARTIST BOSSLOGIC,
THE LATEST SPACEX LAUNCH WAS
SPECTACULAR.
THE AMAZING THING IS HE DID IT
ALL WITHOUT MESSING UP HIS HAIR.
>> YEAH.
>> IMPRESSIVE.
>> FAMOUS FOR THAT HAIR.
>>> COMING UP THAT HEALTH ALERT.
WHAT AFFECTS WEIGHT LOSS MORE,
THE BIG QUESTION, FOOD OR YOUR