>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
THE HOLIDAY RUSH IS ON FROM THE
ROADS TO THE SKIES TO THE
STORES.
FRENZY AT THE AIRPORT.
PASSENGERS DITCHING CARS TO
WALK.
WEATHER CAUSING MAJOR PROBLEMS.
HAZARDOUS TRAVEL ON BOTH COASTS
AND SHOPPERS ON A MISSION ON
WHAT TO EXPECT DURING THE
BUSIEST SHOPPING DAY OF THE
YEAR.
WHERE TO SNAP UP LAST-MINUTE
BARGAINS BEFORE YOU HIT THE ROAD
ALONG WITH A RECORD NUMBER OF
TRAVELERS.
>>> CRUISE SHIP COLLISION.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS SHOCKING MOMENT CAUGHT ON
CAMERA.
PASSENGERS INJURED WHEN THEY
WERE ROCKED BY THE IMPACT.
>> OH, MY GOOD.
>> WHEN THE WATER CAME ON BOARD,
THAT'S WHEN PEOPLE REALLY
THOUGHT THAT WE WERE IN REAL
TROUBLE.
>> THE CRUISE COMPANY PLACING
BLAME THIS MORNING.
>>> IMPEACHMENT QUESTIONS.
LAWMAKERS LEAVING WASHINGTON IN
LIMBO OVER THE TIMING OF A
POSSIBLE SENATE TRIAL.
PLUS, THE PRESIDENT TAKES AIM AT
THAT CHRISTIAN MAGAZINE CALLING
FOR HIM TO BE REMOVED FROM
OFFICE.
>>> MISSING MOM ARREST.
A WOMAN FACING CHARGES AFTER A
BODY IS FOUND IN HER CAR.
IS IT A BIZARRE CASE OF BABY
SNATCHING?
>> WE DID RECOVER AN INFANT
FEMALE CHILD.
>> THE LATEST FROM POLICE ON THE
CASE.
>>> AND HIGHWAY DRAMA.
POLICE FIGHTING FLAMES AND THE
CLOCK TO TRY TO SAVE A MAN
TRAPPED IN HIS CAR.
>> WE MIGHT HAVE TO BREAK YOUR
LEG, BRO, I'M SORRY.
>> WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
>>> HEY, GOOD MORNING, HAPPY
ALMOST CHRISTMAS.
WE BEGIN WITH THE MAD DASH THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND ON THE ROADS, IN
THE AIR AND AT THE MALL.
THIS IS PANIC SATURDAY.
NOT SUCH A NICE NAME WITH HUGE
CROWDS EXPECTED AT BRICK AND
MORTAR STORES.
>> DEPENDS ON HOW YOU VIEW
PROCRASTINATING.
A RECORD NUMBER OF DRIVERS HIT
THE ROADS AS A MILLION MORE
AMERICANS TAKE TO THE SKIES ON
TWO OF THE BUSIEST DAYS FOR
FLYERS THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
BACK-TO-BACK YESTERDAY AND AGAIN
TODAY.
>> IN THE MIDDLE OF IT ALL WE
ARE TRACKING TWO STORM SYSTEMS
THIS HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
RECORD RAIN IN SEATTLE LEADING
TO REPORTED LANDSLIDES AND ROAD
CLOSURES SO LET'S GO RIGHT TO
ROB TRACKING IT ALL.
HOW MUCH OF A THREAT DOES THIS
POSE FOR HOLIDAY TRAVELERS?
>> WITH THE RAIN STILL ONGOING
ACROSS PARTS OF THE NORTHWEST, 3
1/4 INCHES IN SEATTLE.
FIFTH WETTEST DAY ON RECORD.
THAT BROKE A RECORD OVER 100
YEARS YESTERDAY.
LOOK AT THAT GUY TRYING TO GET
AROUND.
IN BELLEVUE, WASHINGTON, JUST
OUTSIDE OF SEATTLE, LOOK AT THIS
LANDSLIDE IN RENTON, WASHINGTON.
THE AMTRAK LINES BETWEEN
PORTLAND AND SEATTLE WERE SHUT
DOWN BECAUSE OF A LANDSLIDE
THERE.
ATMOSPHERIC RIVER, A TROPICAL
COMPONENT, THAT'S WHY IT'S SO
HEAVY IT SLIDES FARTHER TO THE
SOUTH GETTING INTO SAN FRANCISCO
BY TOMORROW MORNING.
SOME SNOWS IN THE MOUNTAINS AS
WELL AND ALL -- GETTING INTO LOS
ANGELES BY THE TIME WE GET TO
MONDAY.
ALL ON I-5, AN ISSUE.
I-10 IN THE SOUTHEAST, A PRETTY
SIGNIFICANT SYSTEM DEVELOPING IN
THE GULF.
HEAVY RAIN WITH WIND.
PANAMA CITY UP THROUGH
PENSACOLA, I-75, I-85 THROUGH
TOMORROW AFTERNOON INTO MONDAY
MORNING AS WELL.
SO TWO SIGNIFICANT STORMS AS
FOLKS GET AROUND FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
OVER TO YOU.
>> WE'LL WATCH AND CHECK BACK
WITH YOU SOON.
>>> MORE THAN 3 MILLION
PASSENGERS TOOK TO THE SKIES
FRIDAY TO START THEIR GETAWAYS
IN WHAT WAS THE BUSIEST AIR
TRAVEL DAY THIS HOLIDAY.
AIRPORTS ACROSS THE COUNTRY
BRACING FOR NEARLY AS MANY THIS
MORNING.
ABC'S STEPHANIE RAMOS IS AT NEW
YORK'S LaGUARDIA AIRPORT WITH
THE MAD DASH TO THOSE HOLIDAY
DESTINATIONS.
STEPHANIE, GOOD MORNING.
>> Reporter: HEY, WHIT, GOOD
MORNING.
IT'S PRETTY BUSY HERE.
NO CRAZY LINES JUST YET BUT
PLENTY OF PEOPLE TRYING TO MAKE
THEIR FLIGHT AND ALREADY WE'VE
SEEN A NUMBER OF CANCELLATIONS
AND DELAYS ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND THE BUSY HOLIDAY TRAVEL
SEASON IS JUST GETTING STARTED
BUT IT IS ONLY GOING TO GET
BUSIER.
MORE THAN 40 MILLION PEOPLE ARE
EXPECTED TO TRAVEL BETWEEN NOW
AND NEW YEAR'S DAY.
PACK PATIENCE, HOLIDAY SPIRIT
AND PLAN AHEAD FOR A
RECORD-BREAKING TRAVEL WEEKEND.
CHECK OUT THIS GRIDLOCK AT
L.A.X.
TRAVELERS JUMPING OUT OF THEIR
RIDE SHARES EARLY OPTING TO WALK
TO THEIR TERMINALS.
>> I DITCHED MY UBER AND BECAUSE
THEY WEREN'T MOVING I WAS ABLE
TO GET MY BAG OUT OF THE TRUNK
AND WALKED FROM THE ENTRANCE
RAMP ALL THE WAY HERE.
>> LONG LINES BUILDING UP AT
SOME OF THE NATION'S BUSIEST
AIRPORTS.
MILLIONS ARE EXPECTED TO TAKE TO