>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS THURSDAY
MORNING THE WHITE HOUSE NOW
FORMING AN EMERGENCY TASK FORCE
AS CORONAVIRUS CASES NEAR 8,000.
WORLDWIDE ALERT.
MORE COUNTRIES NOW RACING TO
EVACUATE THEIR PEOPLE FROM
WUHAN, CHINA, AS CASES OF THE
CORONAVIRUS SOAR.
195 AMERICANS NOW BEING
QUARANTINED TAT THIS AIR FORCE
BASE IN CALIFORNIA AS THE WORLD
HEALTH ORGANIZATION MEETS THIS
MORNING ABOUT DECLARING A GLOBAL
HEALTH EMERGENCY AND THE NEW
WARNING ABOUT THOSE MASKS.
SO MANY PEOPLE BUYING THEM.
STORES NOW SELLING OUT.
HOSPITALS AT RISK OF A SHORTAGE.
>>> WAR OVER WITNESSES.
THE BATTLE RIGHT NOW OVER
WHETHER JOHN BOLTON WILL TESTIFY
AT THE PRESIDENT'S TRIAL AS THE
WHITE HOUSE SEEKS TO BLOCK HIS
BOOK FROM BEING PUBLISHED AND
OVERNIGHT, TRUMP'S LEGAL TEAM
CLAIMS THE PRESIDENT COULD
LEGALLY SOLICIT INFORMATION
ABOUT HIS POLITICAL RIVALS FROM
FOREIGN GOVERNMENTS.
>>> BREAKING HER SILENCE.
KOBE BRYANT'S WIFE VANESSA
SAYING SHE'S, QUOTE, COMPLETELY
DEVASTATED ABOUT LOSING HER
HUSBAND AND DAUGHTER IN THAT
HELICOPTER CRASH.
HER MESSAGE FOR THE OTHER
FAMILIES OF THE VICTIMS.
>>> THE MOTHER OF THOSE TWO
IDAHO CHILDREN MISSING SINCE
SEPTEMBER NOW ORDERED TO BRING
THOSE SIBLINGS FORWARD BY THE
END OF THE DAY AS THEIR
GRANDFATHER OFFERS A $20,000
REWARD FOR HELP FINDING THEM.
HE JOINS US ON "GMA" THIS
MORNING.
>>> BOOK CLUB BACKLASH.
OPRAH'S NEW PICK, "AMERICAN
DIRT," UNDER FIRE.
OUTRAGE AND THREATS ON THE
AUTHOR.
THE PUBLISHER NOW CANCELING THE
BOOK TOUR FOR THE NUMBER ONE
BEST-SELLER.
♪
>>> AND SUPER BOWL SECRETS.
WHO MAY JOIN J. LO AND SHAKIRA
ON THE HALFTIME STAGE AS WE
CONTINUE TO COUNT DOWN TO THE
BIG GAME JUST THREE DAYS AWAY.
>>> AND GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
WE HOPE YOU ALL ARE WELL THIS
THURSDAY MORNING AND WANT TO GET
RIGHT TO THE LATEST ON THAT
CORONAVIRUS.
THE WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION IS
MEETING THIS MORNING TO DECIDE
WHETHER TO DECLARE A GLOBAL
HEALTH EMERGENCY AS CASES OF THE
CORONAVIRUS NOW SURPASS SARS.
>> THERE ARE MORE THAN 7700
CONFIRMED CASES WORLDWIDE.
THE DEATH TOLL CLIMBING TO 170
IN CHINA WHERE CASES ARE NOW
CONFIRMED IN EVERY PROVINCE IN
CHINA AND IN 20 COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD.
>> TAKE A LOOK.
THOUSANDS OF PASSENGERS BEING
HELD RIGHT NOW ON THIS CRUISE
SHIP IN ITALY BECAUSE A WOMAN
FROM HONG KONG FELL ILL ON BOARD
THAT CRUISE SHIP.
THAT WOMAN IS NOW BEING
QUARANTINED AS THEY NOW TEST FOR
THE CORONAVIRUS.
>>> BACK HERE AT HOME, THOSE
NEARLY 200 AMERICANS WHO WERE
EVACUATED FROM WUHAN ARE NOW
UNDER QUARANTINE AT THAT AIR
BASE IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
WILL CARR IS THERE AGAIN FOR US
WITH THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, WILL.
>> Reporter: AND, ROBIN, ALL OF
THOSE AMERICANS SPENT THE NIGHT
ON THE BASE BEHIND ME.
THEY'LL BE CUT OFF FROM THE
PUBLIC FOR AT LEAST TWO MORE
DAYS.
IT COMES AS THERE'S STILL AROUND
800 AMERICANS IN THE HOT ZONE IN
CHINA HOPING TO GET BACK TO THE
STATES AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
THIS MORNING, THE NOVEL
CORONAVIRUS SPREADING TO EVERY
PROVINCE IN CHINA AND 20
COUNTRIES AROUND THE WORLD.
RESIDENTS IN HONG KONG STANDING
IN LONG LINES SCRAMBLING TO GET
THE LAST REMAINING PROTECTIVE
MASKS.
IN ITALY, 6,000 PASSENGERS
STRANDED ON THIS ITALIAN CRUISE
SHIP AFTER A COUPLE CAME DOWN
WITH A FEVER RAISING FEARS THEY
CONTRACTED THE VIRUS.
THE COUPLE FROM HONG KONG RUSHED
TO A HOSPITAL IN ROME.
FOR THE FIRST TIME WE'RE SEEING
INSIDE THE FACILITY WHERE 195
AMERICANS ARE UNDER VOLUNTARY
QUARANTINE AFTER BEING EVACUATED
FROM THE EPICENTER OF THE
CORONAVIRUS OUTBREAK.
>> YOU DID A GREAT JOB OF MAKING
US FEEL WELCOME HERE.
>> Reporter: PAT AFRICA STOCKLEY
AND HIS FAMILY SAY THEY PAID
$4400 TO FLY ON THIS CHARTER,
THE HOT ZONE, TO RIVERSIDE
COUNTY, CALIFORNIA.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN A PLANE SET
UP LIKE THAT BEFORE.
IT WAS A WIDE OPEN CARGO PLANE
BUT HAD PASSENGER SEATS IN IT.
IT FELT LIKE SOMETHING OUT OF A
MOVIE.
>> Reporter: THE FAMILY
EXHAUSTED.
>> WE'RE HOPING TO GET BACK HOME
THIS WEEKEND.
>> Reporter: EVERYONE ON THE
PLANE IS NOW PROVIDING BLOOD
SAMPLES AND THE CDC IS RUSHING
TO TEST THE RESULTS.
>> WE'RE HERE TO ENSURE THEIR
SAFETY AND ALSO TO ENSURE THE
SAFETY OF THOSE ON THE BASE,
THOSE IN THIS COMMUNITY AND
ELSEWHERE IN AMERICA.
>> Reporter: SO FAR FIVE PEOPLE
HAVE CONTRACTED THE NEW
CORONAVIRUS IN THE UNITED
STATES.
IN CHINA AT LEAST 170 PEOPLE
HAVE DIED LEAVING AIRLINES LIKE
DELTA, AMERICAN AND UNITED TO
CANCEL SOME ROUTES.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS ALSO
CONSIDERING SUSPENDING ALL
FLIGHTS TO CHINA AND JUST FORMED
A TASK FORCE TO HELP RESPOND.
WE'VE ALSO JUST LEARNED THERE
WILL BE AT LEAST ONE MORE
CHARTER FLIGHT FROM WU-BOWER TO
BRING AMERICANS BACK TO THE
STATES.
AMY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WILL CARR IN
CALIFORNIA.
THANK YOU.
>>> LET'S BRING IN DR. JENNIFER
ASHTON AND, JEN, AS THESE
NUMBERS GO UP, THE BIG QUESTION
IS, HOW DO WE PUT THIS ALL INTO
CONTEXT WITHOUT PANICKING?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, BASED ON
FACT AND NOT FEAR BUT WHEN YOU
TAKE A LOOK AT THE NUMBER, AMY,
WE EXPECT THEM TO GO UP FOR
SEVERAL REASONS.
WE'RE SCREENING.
WE'RE ABLE TO DIAGNOSE.
OUR AWARENESS IS UP AND WHEN YOU
LOOK FOR SOMETHING, YOU WILL
FIND IT IN MEDICINE AND SCIENCE
BUT IT'S ALSO IMPORTANT TO
REALIZE SOMETHING THAT WE CALL A
SURVEILLANCE PYRAMID.
TAKE A LOOK.
IT'S FROM A NEW ENGLAND JOURNAL
OF MEDICINE JUST OUT IN THE LAST
FEW DAYS.
IN GENERAL, THE MORE MILD A
VIRUS IS, THE HARDER IT IS TO
CONTROL BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE LESS
LIKELY TO SEEK MEDICAL
ATTENTION.
AT THE TOP OF THAT PYRAMID WHERE
YOU SEE HIGHER FAY RAT RATES
THEN IT'S GENERALLY EASIER TO
CONTROL A VIRUS AND ACCORDING TO
THIS PAPER, WHAT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT, IT IS POSSIBLE FOR
SOMETHING TO BE A LOW THREAD TO
AN INDIVIDUAL BUT A HIGH THREAT
TO THE POPULATION.
>> WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF THOSE
IMAGES FROM PEOPLE WEARING THOSE
MASKS IN CHINA.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> I WANT TO BE CRYSTAL CLEAR.
THEY'RE FOR HEALTH CARE
PROFESSIONALS ONLY.
THE SURGICAL MASKS ARE NOT FOR
WELL PEOPLE.
THEY'RE FOR SICK PEOPLE TO
PROTECT OTHERS AROUND THEM.
AND IF YOU GO OUT AND MAKE A
RASH PURCHASE FOR BIG QUANTITIES
OF THESE STOCKS, YOU ARE NOT
ONLY ENDANGERING YOURSELF
BECAUSE WHEN YOU TOUCH THE MASK
YOU'RE TOUCHING YOUR FACE AND
INCREASING YOUR RISK.
YOU ARE ENDANGERING HEALTH CARE
WORKERS.
>> THAT'S A VERY IMPORTANT
WARNING TO THINK ABOUT.
IT'S NOT FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE
WELL.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> CAN'T EMPHASIZE THAT ENOUGH.
>>> WE MOVE TO WASHINGTON AND
THE IMPEACHMENT TRIAL OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
TODAY MARKS THE FINAL DAY
SENATORS CAN QUESTION THE LEGAL
TEAM AS HEAD OF THE KEY VOTE
TOMORROW ON GETTING TESTIMONY
FROM WITNESSES LIKE JOHN BOLTON.
THE WHITE HOUSE FIGHTING TO
BLOCK THAT TESTIMONY AND THE
PUBLICATION OF HIS NEW BOOK IN
WHICH HE MAKES CLAIMS THAT
STRIKE AT THE HEART OF TRUMP'S
DEFENSE.
OUR SENIOR CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MARY BRUCE
TRACKING ALL THE LATEST ON
CAPITOL HILL.
GOOD MORNING, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
WELL, SENATORS HERE HAVE ASKED
OVER 90 QUESTIONS IN A POINTED
DEBATE THAT STRETCHED PAST 11:00
LAST NIGHT.
AND THE PRESIDENT'S TEAM IS NOW
ZEROING IN ON AN EYE-RAISING NEW
DEFENSE.
EVEN IF THE ALLEGATIONS ARE
TRUE, THEY SAY USING MILITARY
AID TO GET POLITICAL FAVORS IS
NOT IMPEACHABLE.
AS SENATORS GRILLED BOTH SIDES
LATE INTO THE NIGHT PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S LEGAL TEAM EMPLOYING A
NEW DEFENSE CLAIMING THE
PRESIDENT CAN SOLICIT
INFORMATION FROM FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS ABOUT HIS POLITICAL
RIVALS.
>> IT'S NOT CAMPAIGN
INTERFERENCE FOR CREDIBLE
INFORMATION ABOUT WRONGDOING TO
BE BROUGHT TO LIGHT IF IT'S
CREDIBLE INFORMATION.
>> Reporter: BUT BOTH THE FBI
DIRECTOR AND THE HEAD OF THE
FEDERAL ELECTION COMMISSION HAVE
SAID CAMPAIGNS SHOULD NOT ACCEPT
FOREIGN HELP.
DEMOCRATS FIRED BACK.
>> NOW APPARENTLY IT'S OKAY FOR
THE PRESIDENT TO GET INFORMATION
FROM FOREIGN GOVERNMENTS IN AN
ELECTION.
THAT'S NEWS TO ME.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICANS ARE
PUSHING FOR A SPEEDY TRIAL AND
SAY IF DEMOCRATS CALL WITNESSES
LIKE FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER JOHN BOLTON, THEY'LL
HAVE THEIR OWN WISH LIST TOO.
>> I WANT ADAM SCHIFF.
I WANT HUNTER BIDEN.
I WANT JOE BIDEN.
I WANT THE WHISTLE-BLOWER.
IF WE GET ANYBODY WE WANT WE
WILL BE HERE FOR A VERY LONG
TIME.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY THOSE
WITNESSES AREN'T RELEVANT TO THE
CASE BUT JOHN BOLTON IS.
A FIRSTHAND WITNESS, BOLTON
REPORTEDLY WRITES IN HIS
UPCOMING BOOK THAT TRUMP
DIRECTLY LINKED MILITARY AID TO
UKRAINE TO INVESTIGATIONS INTO
HIS RIVALS.
ON TWITTER THE PRESIDENT
ATTACKING HIS OWN FORMER ADVISER
SAYING BOLTON BEGGED FOR HIS JOB
AND CALLING HIS BOOK NASTY AND
UNTRUE.
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS SENT
BOLTON'S TEAM A LETTER WARNING
THAT HIS BOOK CANNOT BE
PUBLISHED IN ITS CURRENT FORM
CLAIMING IT CONTAINS TOP SECRET
INFORMATION.
ALL EYES REMAIN ON THOSE KEY
UNDECIDED REPUBLICAN SENATORS
WHO COULD VOTE TO CALL
WITNESSES.
>> I SEND A QUESTION TO THE
DESK, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF,
SENATOR MURKOWSKI AND SENATOR
ROMNEY.
>> Reporter: THAT QUESTION, WHAT
IF TRUMP HAD MULTIPLE MOTIVES
FOR PRESSURING UKRAINE?
SOME SERVING HIS PERSONAL
INTERESTS, OTHERS SERVING THE
NATION?
TRUMP'S LAWYER ALAN DERSHOWITZ
WITH A NEW EXPLANATION SAYING
THE TWO ARE ONE IN THE SAME.
>> IF A PRESIDENT DOES SOMETHING
WHICH HE BELIEVES WILL HELP HIM
GET ELECTED IN THE PUBLIC
INTEREST, THAT CANNOT BE THE
KIND OF QUID PRO QUO THAT
RESULTS IN IMPEACHMENT.
>> Reporter: NOW TODAY SENATORS
HAVE ANOTHER EIGHT HOURS OF
QUESTIONING BEFORE THEY FINALLY
GET TO THAT VOTE ON WITNESSES
TOMORROW.
BUT THIS MORNING REPUBLICAN
LEADER MITCH McCONNELL BELIEVES
HE HAS ENOUGH VOTES TO BLOCK
ADDITIONAL WITNESSES AND TOP
REPUBLICANS WE'VE TALKED TO ARE
HOPEFUL THAT THEY COULD MOVE TO
ACQUIT THE PRESIDENT IN THE NEXT
TWO DAYS, GEORGE.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
MORE ON THIS FROM OUR SENIOR
NATIONAL CORRESPONDENT TERRY
MORAN.
LET'S BEGIN WITH PRETTY
BREATHTAKING ARGUMENTS FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S LEGAL TEAM THAT IT'S
PERFECTLY LEGAL TO GET FOREIGN
HELP IN AN ELECTION AND ALAN
DERSHOWITZ GOING FARTHER SAYING
ALMOST ANYTHING A PRESIDENT DOES
TO GET RELE ELECTED IS ALMOST BY
DEFINITION NOT IMPEACHABLE
BECAUSE HE THINKS IT'S IN THE
NATIONAL INTEREST.
>> Reporter: RADICAL.
THAT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S LEGAL TEAM IS BEING
ACCUSED OF.
FOR THE POWER AND PRIVILEGE OF
PRESIDENT -- OF THE PRESIDENCY
IN OUR HISTORY.
RICHARD NIXON ONCE SAID WHEN THE
PRESIDENT DOES IT, THAT MEANS
IT'S NOT ILLEGAL.
IT WAS ROUNDLY CRITICIZED AT THE
TIME BUT THAT IS ESSENTIALLY THE
DEFENSE THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
MAKING AND THE IMPACT OF IT WILL
BE TO STRENGTHEN THE PRESIDENT,
ANY PRESIDENT FROM NOW ON OVER
THE CONGRESS, OVER THE CRIMINAL
LAW, OVER A LOT OF AMERICAN
LIFE.
>> IF INDEED HE IS ACQUITTED.
IT DOES APPEAR THOUGH THAT IT'S
QUITE A PRACTICAL ARGUMENT
THAT'S CARRYING THE DAY WITH THE
SENATORS ON THE FENCE ABOUT
WITNESS, THIS ARGUMENT THAT
BASICALLY THE SENATE WOULD JUST
BE PARALYZED IF YOU KEPT CALLING
IN WITNESSES.
>> Reporter: YEAH, SO
INTERESTING.
LISTENING TO THE QUESTIONS FROM
SENATORS YESTERDAY, YOU'D THINK
THEY WOULD FOCUS ON GUILT OR
INNOCENCE OR THE STANDARDS OF
JUDGMENT.
SO MUCH OF IT FOCUSED ON
PROCESS.
HOW IT WOULD TIE UP THE SENATE.
HOW DIFFICULT IT WOULD BE TO GET
WITNESSES INTO A SENATE AND HOLD
UP THE BUSINESS OF THE SENATE
AND THE COUNTRY FOR A LONG TIME.
ALL PROCESS AND RAISES THE
QUESTION DID THE HOUSE
FAST-TRACK IT TOO FAST?
>> TERRY MORAN, THANKS VERY
MUCH.
YOU'LL JOIN US FOR THE LIVE
COVERAGE.
I'LL ANCHOR WITH OUR POLITICAL
AND LEGAL TEAM STARTING AT 1:00
EASTERN ON ABC.
ROBIN.
>>> AS WE CONTINUE TO THINK OF
THE NINE PEOPLE WHO LOST THEIR
LIVES IN THAT TRAGIC HELICOPTER
CRASH, WE'RE STARTING TO HEAR
FROM THEIR FAMILIES.
HEARTBROKEN, OF COURSE, OVER
THEIR LOSS INCLUDING KOBE
BRYANT'S WIFE VANESSA WHO SAYS
HER FAMILY IS COMPLETELY
DEVASTATED.
SHE SAYS SHE UNDERSTANDS WHAT
THE OTHER FAMILIES ARE GOING
THROUGH.
SHARING IN THEIR GRIEF
INTERMALTLY, THAT'S WHAT SHE
SAID.
TOM LLAMAS CAN AT THE STAPLES
CENTER IN LOS ANGELES WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, TOM.
>> Reporter: ROBIN, GOOD MORNING
TO YOU.
THIS IS A MAJOR STEP FORWARD FOR
THE BRYANT FAMILY.
VANESSA BRYANT'S MESSAGE
STRAIGHT FROM THE HEART, A
TRIBUTE TO HER HUSBAND AND LATE
DAUGHTER AND NOW ALLOWING THE
PUBLIC TO SHARE IN SOME OF THEIR
HAPPIER MEMORIES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Reporter: OVERNIGHT, VANESSA
BRYANT RE-OPENING HER INSTAGRAM
ACCOUNT TO THE PUBLIC.
GIVING FANS ACCESS TO SEVERAL
FAMILY MOMENTS.
SHE HAD MADE HER ACCOUNT PRIVATE
FOLLOWING THE CRASH.
ON THAT INSTAGRAM PAGE, VANESSA
BRYANT ALSO MAKING HER FIRST
PUBLIC STATEMENT SINCE THAT
DEADLY HELICOPTER CRASH THAT
TOOK THE LIVES OF HER HUSBAND,
KOBE BRYANT, THEIR 13-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER GIANNA AND SEVEN
OTHERS.
THANKING FANS FOR THEIR SUPPORT
DURING WHAT SHE CALLS A, QUOTE,
HORRIFIC TIME AND WRITING, WE
ARE COMPLETELY DEVASTATED BY THE
SUDDEN LOSS OF MY ADORING
HUSBAND, KOBE.
THE AMAZING FATHER OF OUR
CHILDREN, AND MY BEAUTIFUL,
SWEET GIANNA.
A LOVING, THOUGHTFUL AND
WONDERFUL DAUGHTER AND AMAZING
SISTER.
ADDING, WE'RE ALSO DEVASTATED
FOR THE FAMILIES WHO LOST THEIR
LOVED ONES ON SUNDAY, AND WE
SHARE IN THEIR GRIEF INTIMATELY.
THERE AREN'T ENOUGH WORDS TO
DESCRIBE HOUR PAIN RIGHT NOW.
I TAKE COMFORT IN KNOWING THAT
KOBE AND GIGI BOTH KNEW THEY
WERE SO DEEPLY LOVED.
BRYANT AND HIS WIFE WERE MARRIED
FOR NEARLY 20 YEARS, TOGETHER
RAISING FOUR DAUGHTERS.
VANESSA OFTEN SPOTTED WATCHING
HIS GAMES COURTSIDE AND RIGHT BY
HIS SIDE AT SPORTS FUNCTIONS.
>> WHAT'S IT LIKE HAVING HIM
HANGING AROUND ALL THE TIME.
>> WE LOVE IT.
YEAH, WE ACTUALLY DO.
WE GOT USED TO HIM BEING AROUND
THE LAST THREE SEASONS BECAUSE
OF HIS INJURIES.
YEAH.
SO --
>> GREAT HAVING HIM HOME.
>> Reporter: VANESSA ALSO
WRITING ON INSTAGRAM, I'M NOT
SURE WHAT OUR LIVES HOLD BEYOND
TODAY.
AND IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO IMAGINE
LIFE WITHOUT THEM.
BUT WE WAKE UP EACH DAY TRYING
TO KEEP PUSHING BECAUSE KOBE AND
OUR BABY GIRL GIGI ARE SHINING
ON US TO LIGHT THE WAY.
ENDING THE POST WITH THREE
HASHTAGS, GIRLSDAD, DADDYSGIRLS
AND FAMILY.
THE CORONER OFFICIALLY
IDENTIFYING ALL NINE INDIVIDUALS
OVERNIGHT RULING THEIR CAUSE OF
DEATH WAS BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA.
THERE STILL ISN'T A DEFINITIVE
ANSWER AS TO WHAT CAUSED
BRYANT'S HELICOPTER TO CRASH.
FOGGY WEATHER JUST ONE PART OF
THE INVESTIGATION.
THE NTSB REPORTING THE CHOPPER
LOST COMMUNICATION WITH ATC AT
2300 FEET CAUSING A HIGH ENERGY
IMPACT CRASH ALL HAPPENING IN
ABOUT A MINUTE.
>> THE WEATHER COULD HAVE CAUSED
SPATIAL DISORIENTATION WHERE THE
PILOT DIDN'T KNOW WHETHER HE WAS
UP OR DOWN AND COULD HAVE
INADVERTENTLY FLOWN IT INTO THE
GROUND.
PERHAPS THERE WAS A MECHANICAL
FAILURE WHERE THE PILOT LOST
CONTROL.
EVERY POSSIBILITY IS ON THE
TABLE.
>> Reporter: ON WEDNESDAY
BRYANT'S FORMER TEAM, THE LOS
ANGELES LAKERS, RETURN TO THE
COURT TO PRACTICE.
PLAYERS STILL TOO DISTRAUGHT TO
TALK TO THE MEDIA.
AND ACROSS TOWN THE LOS ANGELES
CLIPPERS OPENING UP ABOUT
BRYANT.
PLAYERS LIKE PAUL GEORGE, WHO
GREW UP IN THE L.A. AREA
IDOLIZED HIM.
>> I GREW UP HERE.
WE SAW HIM EVERY DAY ON TV.
HE'S THE REASON ALL OF US PLAYED
THE GAME.
SO IT'S DIFFERENT -- IT HITS
DIFFERENT FOR US.
>> Reporter: AND FOR THE FIRST
TIME OVERNIGHT THE LOS ANGELES
LAKERS ALSO PUTTING OUT A
STATEMENT, WE WANT TO PUT IT ON
THE SCREEN NOW FOR YOU.
IT READS IN PART, WORDS CANNOT
EXPRESS WHAT KOBE MEANS TO THE
LOS ANGELES LAKERS, OUR FANS AND
OUR CITY.
MORE THAN A BASKETBALL PLAYER,
HE WAS A BELOVED FATHER, HUSBAND
AND TEAMMATE.
THEIR LOVE AND LIGHT WILL REMAIN
IN OUR HEARTS FOREVER AND,
GEORGE, WE CAN'T SAY IT ENOUGH.
EVERY TIME WE COME BACK HERE TO
THE STAPLES CENTER THESE
MEMORIALS GROW AND GROW AND NOW
ALL OVER THE CITY OF L.A. THERE
ARE MURALS GOING UP IN HONOR OF
KOBE BRYANT.
>> TOUCHED SO MANY LIVES.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN TO THE
BACKLASH OVER A PICK FROM
OPRAH'S BOOK CLUB.
SOME CRITICS ARE CALLING OUT THE
NOVEL, "AMERICAN DIRT," FOR HOW
IT PORTRAYS IMMIGRANTS EVEN
QUESTIONING THE AUTHOR'S RIGHT
TO ADDRESS THE SUBJECT AND NOW
THE PUBLISHER IS CANCELING THE
BOOK TOUR CITING SAFETY
CONCERNS.
GIO BENITEZ HAS THE STORY.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE HIGHLY
ANTICIPATED NOVEL THAT GOT
PUBLISHING'S MOST SOUGHT AFTER
SEAL OF APPROVAL, OPRAH'S BOOK
CLUB.
>> THIS BOOK, "AMERICAN DIRT,"
JUST GUTTED ME.
AND I DIDN'T JUST READ THIS
BOOK, I INHABITED THIS BOOK.
>> Reporter: THE NOVEL,
"AMERICAN DIRT," IS ABOUT A
MOTHER WHO FLEES MEXICO WITH HER
SON PURSUED BY THE HEAD OF A
DRUG CARTEL.
BUT IT WAS QUICKLY CRITICIZED BY
MANY MEXICAN-AMERICAN WRITERS
WHO ACCUSED AUTHOR JEANINE
CUMMINS OF WRITING AN
EXPLOITATIVE OVERSIMPLIFIED AND
ILL-INFORMED NOVEL TOO
OFTENERING ON THE SIDE OF TRAUMA
F
FETISHIZATION.
THEY SAY WE BELIEVE EXISTS REAL
PERIL TO THEIR SAFETY.
SHE'S ASKED WHETHER SHE'S THE
RIGHT PERSON TO TELL THE STORY.
>> I RESISTED FOR A VERY LONG
TIME TELLING THE STORY BECAUSE I
WAS WORRIED THAT I DIDN'T KNOW
ENOUGH.
THAT MY PRIVILEGE WOULD MAKE ME
BLIND TO CERTAIN TRUTHS.
>> Reporter: CUMMINS SAID HER
FATHER IS PUERTO RICAN.
THAT THEE IDENTIFIES AS LATINA
AND THAT SHE SPENT FIVE YEARS
WORKING ON THE BOOK AT TIMES ON
THE U.S./MEXICO BORDER.
BUT MANY SAY THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
ONE PERSON TWEETING, I'M
EXHAUSTED ABOUT OUR STORIES
BEING TOLD BY WHITE AND
NON-IMMIGRANT WRITERS OR
REPORTERS.
MOST OF THEM GET IT WRONG AND
FURTHER DEHUMANIZE US AND OUR
EXPERIENCE.
BUT NOT EVERYONE IS UPSET.
CELEBRATED MEXICAN-AMERICAN
AUTHOR SANDRA CISNEROS DEFENDED
IT ON NPR.
>> IT JUST TOOK ME ON THE
JOURNEY.
IT WAS VERY BELIEVABLE AND I
KNOW FROM TALKING TO PEOPLE WHO
HAVE CROSSED THE BORDER OR WHO
HAVE BEEN DETAINED OR WHO ARE IN
THE SHELTERS, I KNEW THIS STORY.
I WANTED TO SUPPORT IT.
I DO SUPPORT IT AND I DO STAND
BY IT.
>> Reporter: OPPONENT NOW SAYING
SHE WANTS TO HAVE A DEEPER
DISCUSSION.
>> I SPENT THE PAST FEW DAYS
LISTENING TO MEMBERS OF THE
LATINX COMMUNITY TO GET A
GREATER UNDERSTANDING OF THEIR
CONCERNS AND I HEAR THEM.
I DO.
>> Reporter: THE PUBLISHER ALSO
PLANS TO HOLD TOWN HALL MEETINGS
WITH THE AUTHOR AND HER CRITICS.
I HAVE SPOKEN TO SO MANY ON ALL
SIDES AND ONE THING IS CLEAR,
THIS IS COMPLICATED.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE THERE'S NOT
JUST ONE LATINO EXPERIENCE.
THERE'S NOT JUST ONE IMMIGRANT
EXPERIENCE AND SO THE PUBLISHING
INDUSTRY RIGHT NOW IS ASKING WHO
SHOULD BE WRITING THESE NOVELS.
>> WELL, I GET THE IDEA OF
CRITICIZING WHAT'S IN THE BOOK.
THAT'S FAIR GAME WHENEVER A
WRITER -- I DON'T QUITE
UNDERSTAND QUESTIONING A
WRITER'S RIGHT TO WRITE.
>> THAT'S THE DEBATE RIGHT NOW.
>> THANK YOU, GIO.
>>> WE ARE FOLLOWING A LOT OF
OTHER STORIES INCLUDING THE
LATEST ON TWO HIDE SHOW SIBLINGS
MISSING SINCE SEPTEMBER.
TODAY IS THE DEADLINE FOR THEIR
MOTHER TO BRING THEM FORWARD AND
NOW THEIR GRANDFATHER IS JOINING
US.
>> WHO COULD JOIN JENNIFER LOPEZ
AND SHAKIRA ON STAGE FOR THE
HALFTIME SHOW?
FIRST LET'S GO TO GINGER.
>> LET 'GET TO THE COLD CITIES
BROUGHT TO YOU BY COSEQUIN.
>> ANOTHER TRY AND CHILLY DAY
TODAY.
MORE CLOUDS INCREASING.
OUT THE DOOR THIS MORNING
TEMPERATURES BELOW FREEZING.
BY LUNCHTIME CLOUDY, 35.
3:00, 42.
CLOUDY AND GRAY THIS AFTERNOON.
WE HAVE BEEN AT CONVENTION
CENTER FOR WASHINGTON AUTO SHOW
TO THE WEEKEND.
TOMORROW CLOUDY, 46.
CLOUDY SAT
>>> A LOT MORE COMING UP THIS
THURSDAY.
WE
(whistling)
It's important to have
a reliable network.
We all use it
in different ways.
(VO)
Everyone in your family
is different.
Someone's
streaming sports,
someone's video chatting
her friend.
(VO)
So Verizon has plans
to mix and match
starting at $35.
And up to $700
toward our best phones.
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Challenge what soft can be.
NIVEA Essentially Enriched
Body Lotion
with nourishing serum
deeply nourishes skin
for a softness
like never before.
Because soft...
can be powerful.
Just like you.
NIVEA.
Saturdays Happen.
Pain Happens.
Aleve It.
Aleve is proven stronger
and longer on pain
than Tylenol.
When pain happens, Aleve It.
All Day Strong.
Need a reason to switch
your tax provider?
With Jackson Hewitt
upload your tax docs—
— and connect with a tax pro
from home
Taxes done and ready for review
within 24 hours, guaranteed,
—or your tax prep is free.
Taxes fast and easy
with Jackson Hewitt.
—or your tax prep is free.
Cake in the conference room!
Showing 'em you're ready...
to be your own boss.
That's the beauty of your smile.
Crest's three dimensional
whitening...
...removes stains,...
...whitens in-between teeth...
...and protects from future
stains.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles for
life.
Can your hair survive
damage?
ve Conditioner
proves it can.
We treat one brush
with Dove conditioner
and expose both
to damaging conditions.
The difference is clear.
Dove Intensive
Repair conditioner.
For smooth, touchably
beautiful hair.
♪♪
>> LINDSEY: I AM LINDSEY MASTIS.
>> ROBERT: I AM ROBERT BURTON.
COUPLE OF YOUR TOP STORIES U.S.
POSTAL SERVICE WILL UNVEIL 43
STAMP IN THE BLACK HERITAGE
SERIES.
BEFORE SHE DIED IN 2016, CO
ANCHORED PBS NEW FIRST EVER ALL
FEMALE NATIONAL NIGHTLY NEWS
TEAM.
>> LINDSEY: NASA WILL HOLD
NATIONAL DAY OF REMEMBRANCE WILL
LEAD IN OBSERVANCE IN THE
NATIONAL MUSEUM TRIBUTES PLANNED
ELSEWHERE INCLUDING KENNEDY
SPACE CENTER IN FLn4
>> 7:26 BUNDLE UP, WIND CHILL
20S.
SKIES THIS AFTERNOON MOSTLY
CLOUDY, DRY, HIGH, 43.
DRY AND CHILLY TOMORROW.
LOWERED RAIN CHANCES, SATURDAY,
JULIE.
OVERALL, WEEKEND LOOKING GOOD,
MONDAY LOOKS GREAT.
60 DEGREES MONDAY.
>> JULIE: IT IS OKAY TO GET
TONGUE TIED TALKING ABOUT 60S IN
JANUARY.
16 MINUTE RIDE SOUTH 50 TO
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
ROUTE ONE, BETWEEN BUCKMAN ROAD
AND SHERWOOD HALL LANE.
DELAYS STARTING TO BUILD.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
BACK TO YOU.
>> LINDSEY: I AM LINDSEY MASTIS.
You wanna go? Wanna go bro?
Hey, uh, do not mess
with my discount.
Woooo!
You could save up to 30%.
Let's go!
Nice to meet you,
go get 'em tiger!
Woooo!
Sounds like you've got this?
Yeah. Definitely.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe and Save™
from State Farm.
Patients want something that
works faster for them.
Why would somebody want to
suffer if there is options
that they don't need to.
I think dentists will want
to recommend
Sensodyne Rapid Relief
because it's clinically proven
to work in 3 days.
Which means for patients that
they get relief very fast.
ew
Keurig K-Duo Brewer makes
any occasion the
perfect coffee occasion.
Family Brunch!
Just add ground coffee
for a carafe,
or pop in a pod for
a freshly brewed cup.
Good strong coffee.
Our French Roast.
It was a decaf for you, yes?
In your favorite mug.
There we go.
It's no big deal, really.
That little vent that
won't stay open.
Except it IS.
That's why the vent is one
more thing we check
before a car can be a
Certified CarMax car.
The way it should be. CarMax.
>>> OKAY, LADIES GET IN
FORMATION.
>> FELLA, LET'S GET THIS
STARTED.
>> OH, YEAH, NOW BACK HERE ON
"GMA," BEYONCE AN BRUNO OWNING
THE STAGE, SPECIAL GUESTS AT THE
SUPER BOWL LI HALFTIME SHOW BACK
IN 2016.
>> WOKE ME UP.
>> IT DID, RIGHT?
JAMMING OVER HERE AND GUESS
WHAT, WE HAVE SHAKIRA AND J. LO
AND THEY HAVE SURPRISES IN
STORE.
ONE THING WE DO KNOW HOW J. LO
IS GETTING READY.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS PHOTO SHE
POSTED.
SHE CALLS THIS HER SUPER BOWL
KIT.
SHE INCLUDED THE HASHTAG BLING
CUP.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON WHAT THAT
BLING CUP IS.
WE'LL WAIT FOR IT.
>> WE'LL BEGIN WITH THE LATEST
ON IDAHO SIBLINGS.
TODAY IS THE DEADLINE FOR THEIR
MOTHER TO BRING THEM FORWARD AND
PROVE TO AUTHORITIES THEY'RE
OKAY AFTER THEY FINALLY TRACKED
HER DOWN IN HAWAII.
IN JUST A MOMENT WE'LL HEAR FROM
THE GRANDFATHER BUT FIRST WILL
REEVE IS HERE WITH MORE.
WILL.
>> HEY, GOOD MORNING, GEORGE.
YEAH, TODAY IS THE DEADLINE TO
HEAR FROM LORI VALLOW TO SEE THE
KIDS.
SHE'S ONE-TRAVEL OF THAT
DOOMSDAY COUPLE.
SHE WON'T ANSWER THE SIMPLE
QUESTION OF WHERE ARE YOUR KIDS?
NOW TODAY SHE MUST SHOW THEM TO
AUTHORITIES IN IDAHO BUT LAST WE
SAW LORI VALLOW, SHE WAS HALF A
WORLD AWAY.
TODAY IS THE DAY.
LORI VALLOW FACING A DEADLINE
THIS MORNING TO PHYSICALLY
PRODUCE HER MISSING KIDS AND
BRING THEM TO AUTHORITIES.
WHERE ARE YOUR CHILDREN?
VALLOW AND HER HUSBAND CHAD
DAYBELL WERE LAST SEEN WEDNESDAY
IN HAWAII, THOUSANDS OF MILES
AWAY FROM THEIR HOME IN IDAHO.
POLICE TRACKING THEM DOWN THIS
WEEKEND SERVING THEM WITH A
COURT ORDER BELIEVING THE KIDS
ARE IN GRAVE DANGER AND THAT
VALLOW EITHER KNOWS WHERE THEY
ARE CHILDREN, 17-YEAR-OLD TYLEE
RYAN AND 7-YEAR-OLD J.J. ARE OR
WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM.
POLICE SEARCHING THEIR CAR WHILE
CAMERAS FROM EAST IDAHO NEWS
ROLLED.
>> CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE YOUR
KIDS ARE?
WHERE ARE YOUR KIDS?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> NO COMMENT?
THEY'VE BEEN MISSING FOR FOUR
MONTHS.
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO SAY.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE CHILDREN
HAVEN'T BEEN SEEN SINCE
SEPTEMBER.
SHE AND HER HUSBAND LEFT IDAHO
UNDER SUSPICIOUS CIRCUMSTANCES
BOLDING ONE DAY AFTER
AUTHORITIES CONDUCTED A WELFARE
CHECK LOOKING FOR THE KIDS AFTER
OTHER FAMILY MEMBERS CONTACTED
AUTHORITIES, CONCERNED THAT THEY
HADN'T HEARD FROM THEM.
DEATH HAS SURROUNDED VALLOW AND
DAYBELL WHO WERE MARRIED LAST
YEAR SHORTLY AFTER VALLOW'S
EX-HUSBAND, CHARLES, WAS
MURDERED BY HER BROTHER IN WHAT
POLICE AT THE TIME DETERMINED
WAS SELF-DEFENSE.
THAT BROTHER THEN FOUND DEAD OF
UNKNOWN CAUSES MONTHS LATER.
CHAD'S FORMER WIFE TAMMY APPEARS
TO HAVE DIED CURIOUSLY TOO.
AT FIRST OFFICIALS RULING IT
NATURAL CAUSES.
HER REMAINS HAVE SINCE BEEN E
EXHUMED FOR A CLOSER
EXAMINATION.
>> WE'RE SUSPICIOUS THAT THAT
DEATH WAS NOT NATURAL BUT WE'RE
WAITING FOR RESULTS TO COME BACK
FROM THE AUTOPSY.
AND THE LAB WORK THAT WILL
ACCOMPANY THAT.
>> Reporter: IF VALLOW FAILS TO
MEET TODAY'S DEADLINE TO PRODUCE
HER CHILDREN SHE COULD TASTE
CONTEMPT OF COURT OR A MORE
SEVERE PENALTY OR CHARGES, AMY.
>> WILL, THANK YOU.
THE CHILDREN'S GRANDFATHER LARRY
WOODCOCK JOINS US FROM IDAHO.
I KNOW THROUGH THE WHOLE
EXPERIENCE YOU HAVEN'T LOST
HOPE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY?
DO YOU BELIEVE YOU WILL SEE YOUR
GRANDCHILDREN LATER TODAY?
>> DO I BELIEVE?
YES, I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT.
DO I THINK THAT SHE'S GOING TO
BRING THEM?
HONESTLY, NO.
I KNOW LORI WELL ENOUGH NOW FROM
THE LAST YEAR.
OBVIOUSLY I'VE KNOWN HER FOR 13
YEARS AND THE LORI THAT IS
SUPPOSED TO BE HERE TODAY WITH
THE CHILDREN, I PRAY EVERY DAY.
I PRAYED SINCE THIS STARTED
SINCE THEY FOUND HER THAT THE --
BOTH OF THE CHILDREN ARE HERE
AND THEY SHOW UP AND THEY'RE
HEALTHY AND ARE JUST BEING THEIR
NORMAL SELVES.
DO I HONESTLY BELIEVE SHE'LL
BRING THEM AND DO AS THE WARRANT
SAID, YOU KNOW, ABOUT PRODUCING
THE CHILDREN ON THIS DAY, I'D BE
VERY SURPRISED IF SHE DID.
NOTHING WITH LORI RIGHT NOW
MAKES SENSE.
>> THERE ARE SO MANY WHYS AND
THE BIG ONE IS WHY WOULD LORI
NOT TELL AUTHORITIES?
WHY WOULD LORI NOT PRODUCE HER
CHILDREN?
DO YOU HAVE ANY ANSWERS?
>> AT THIS POINT, NO, I DON'T
HAVE AN ANSWER.
I'VE GOT SPECULATION, BUT I
DON'T HAVE A TRUTHFUL ANSWER.
>> LARRY, I KNOW THAT LORI AND
HER HUSBAND ARE REPORTEDLY WHAT
SOME CALL DOOMSDAYERS.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT THEIR BELIEF
SYSTEM IS PART OF THE REASON WHY
YOUR GRANDCHILDREN ARE MISSING?
>> I HAVE TO AT THIS POINT.
BECAUSE IF LORI LOVED J.J. AND
TYLEE THE WAY THAT SHE DID A FEW
MONTHS AGO, LET'S JUST SAY 10,
12 MONTHS AGO, THEN THOSE
CHILDREN WOULD BE WITH HER AND
EVER SINCE SHE'S BEEN INVOLVED
IN THIS DOOMSDAY CULT, THAT IS
NOT THE SAME LORI THAT WE KNEW
FOR 13 YEARS.
AND THE LAST YEAR HAS JUST BEEN
NOT UNDERSTANDABLE.
WE JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW ANY
MOTHER CAN WALK AWAY FROM HER
CHILDREN FOR MONTHS NOW AND THEN
2 1/2 MONTHS PRIOR TO THIS, SO I
DON'T KNOW WHO THAT PERSON IS
ANYMORE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW YOU LOSE
THE LOVE FOR ONE OF THE MOST
K
KINDEST YOUNG MEN -- HE'S 7
YEARS OLD BUT HE'S MY LITTLE MAN
AND JUST WALK AWAY.
>> WE WILL BE THINKING OF YOU
AND YOUR FAMILY LATER TODAY.
LARRY, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US THIS MORNING.
WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
>> AND THANK YOU SO MUCH AND WE
LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING Y'ALL
AGAIN.
>> IT'S SO HEARTBREAKING
LISTENING TO HIM BECAUSE HE'S
BEEN TIRELESSLY TRYING TO FIND
THOSE CHILDREN FOR MONTHS NOW.
>> THIS ALL HAPPENED TO SO FAST,
IT SEEMS.
>> JUST A MATTER OF MONTHS.
>> WELL, HOPEFULLY WE WILL LEARN
TODAY.
>> HOPEFULLY.
>>> COMING UP ANTICIPATION
GROWING FOR THE SUPER BOWL
HALFTIME SHOW.
WHO COULD SHARE THE STAGE WITH
JENNIFER LOPEZ AND SHAKIRA?
COME ON BA
So I stopped in at Chick-fil-A
for lunch
and saw Officer Wilson
come in.
I decided to place a dine in
mobile order
and have a cookie delivered to
him
just to show appreciation for
his service for our community.
A few minutes later I noticed
that Officer Wilson had gotten
up and left,
and I knew he hadn't gotten his
cookie yet.
And I'm headed to my car.
I turn around and see Allie and
she's running after me.
Mr. Policer Officer! Mr. Policer
Officer!
Usually when someone yells,
"Officer, officer!"
they want to ask me about a
ticket they got.
I absolutely wanted the cookie.
This cookie is delicious.
(MOM VO)
We fit a lot of life
into our Subaru Forester.
(DAD)
It's good to be back.
(MOM)
It sure is.
(MOM VO)
Over the years, we trusted
it to carry and protect
the things that were most
important to us.
We always knew we had a lot of
life ahead of us.
(MOM)
Remember this?
(MOM VO)
That's why we chose a car that
we knew would be there for us
through it all.
(MALE VO)
Welcome to the all-new 2019
Subaru Forester.
The longest-lasting, most
trusted Forester ever.
ra Kai,
the lack of control
over my business
made me a little intense.
But now QuickBooks
helps me get paid,
manage cash flow,
and run payroll.
And now I'm back on top...
with Koala Kai.
(VO)
Save over 40 hours a month
with Intuit QuickBooks.
Mornings were made for better
things
than rheumatoid arthritis
or psoriatic arthritis.
When considering
another treatment,
ask about XELJANZ XR,
a once-daily pill for adults
with moderate
to severe rheumatoid arthritis
or active psoriatic arthritis
for whom methotrexate
did not work well enough.
It can reduce pain, swelling,
and significantly improve
physical function.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections like TB;
don't start XELJANZ
if you have an infection.
Taking a higher
than recommended dose
of XELJANZ for RA
can increase risk of death.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections,
cancers including lymphoma,
and blood clots have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
and changes in lab results.
Tell your doctor if
you've been somewhere
fungal infections
are common,
or if you've had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Don't let another morning
go by
without asking your doctor
about
XELJANZ XR.
It's amazing what you
can uncover
with your DNA results
from Ancestry®.
I was able to discover
one cousin,
reached out to him,
visited Ireland,
met another 20 cousins.
They took me to
the Cliffs of Moher,
the ancestral home,
the family bar.
It really gives you a sense
of connection to...
something that's
bigger than yourself.
Greater details.