>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
IT'S CHRISTMAS CRUNCH TIME, AND
THE SCRAMBLE IS ON.
>>> BUSES CATCHING FIRE,
CREATING MORE HEADACHES AT
L.A.X. AS PASSENGERS RUSH TO
MAKE THEIR FLIGHTS.
LINES ACROSS THE COUNTRY GLOWING
-- GROWING ON THIS HUGE TRAVEL
DAY.
BAD WEATHER IMPACTING MAJOR
HUBS.
>>> THIS MORNING, SHOPPERS DOING
THEIR DIZZYING DASH AT THE
STORES AND HOW TO MAKE YOUR
GIFTS GET THERE IN TIME.
>>> BABY SNATCHING PLOT?
THE STUNNING NEW INFORMATION
ABOUT THE WOMAN CHARGED WITH
KIDNAPPING HER CLOSE FRIEND,
FOUND DEAD AND NEWBORN BABY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW SINCERE
SHE SOUNDED.
>> ONE OF THE LEAD SEARCHERS
SPEAKING OUT THIS MORNING.
>>> UKRAINE TIMELINE.
NEWLY RELEASED EMAILS BETWEEN
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, DETAILING
WHEN THE PRESIDENT ASKED ABOUT
MILITARY AID TO UKRAINE.
WHERE IT FITS WITH HIS INFAMOUS
PHONE CALL TO THE PRESIDENT OF
UKRAINE.
>>> DRAMATIC RESCUE.
THIS PLANE CRASHING INTO AN ICY
POND.
>> WE HAVE AN AIRCRAFT IN THE
WATER.
>> WITNESSES MOUNTING THEIR OWN
RESCUE BY CANOE.
>> WE WAS PANICKING.
HE WAS WORRIED HE COULDN'T SWIM.
>> THE NEIGHBORS BANDING
TOGETHER.
>>> AND ROYAL MIXER.
THE ADORABLE NEW PHOTOS WITH
PRINCE GEORGE FRONT AND CENTER
STIRRING UP SOME CHRISTMAS
PUDDING.
SO CUTE.
>>> GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY, ON
THIS SUNDAY.
WE BEGIN WITH THE TOP AND
NONNEGOTIABLE FACT FOR
PROCRASTINATORS.
ONLY THREE SHOPPING DAYS LEFT
UNTIL CHRISTMAS.
>> HERE'S ANOTHER UNCOMFORTABLE
TRUTH.
WE ARE AT THE HEIGHT OF THE
HOLIDAY TRAVEL
SEASON WITH MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
AT THE AIRPORTS AND ON THE
ROADS, AND RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF IT ALL WE HAVE A PAIR OF
STORMS, ONE ON EACH COAST MAKING
THINGS TREACHEROUS.
>> GOT TO KEEP IT INTERESTING,
RIGHT?
>>> WE HAVE ONE DEATH TO REPORT,
A POLICE OFFICER WHO GOT INTO AN
ACCIDENT WHILE DRIVING TO A
CALL.
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE THIS
MORNING, AND WE BEGIN WITH
ZACHARY KIESCH WHO IS ON THE
HIGHWAY HERE IN NEW YORK.
ZACHARY, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: EVA, GOOD MORNING
TO YOU AS WELL.
THE COUNTRY REALLY GETTING HIT
AROUND THE EDGES.
TWO SEPARATE STORMS ON TWO
SEPARATE COASTS EXPECTED TO
BRING HEAVY WIND AND RAIN TO
SOME TRAVEL HUBS.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT PLACES LIKE
SAN FRANCISCO AND L.A. WILL FEEL
PARTS OF THAT, AND LOOKING INTO
MONDAY, YOU GO DOWN TO MIAMI.
DOWN TO MIAMI, THEY'RE EXPECTING
THE SAME WITH HOLIDAY TRAVELERS
FEELING THAT AS FAR NORTH AS
ATLANTA.
A WILD SCENE OUTSIDE OF A PACKED
L.A.X. SATURDAY.
FIRE SHOOTING INTO THE SKY AS
THREE BUSES WENT UP IN FLAMES.
THE AIRPORT JAMMED WITH
TRAVELERS.
FIREFIGHTERS RACING TO THE
SCENE, QUICKLY PUT OUT THE
FLAMES.
MORE THAN 115 MILLION AMERICANS
ARE EXPECTED TO HIT THE RAILS,
ROADS AND SKY THROUGHOUT THE
HOLIDAYS.
TRAVELERS HAVE BEEN WARNED TO
PACK THEIR PATIENCE.
IN SACRAMENTO, AN INTERNET
OUTAGE AT THE AIRPORT THERE
IMPACTING 11 OUTBOUND PLANES.
THE WEATHER CREATING TRAVEL
CHAOS IN SEVERAL PARTS OF THE
COUNTRY.
IN THE WEST, THE CALIFORNIA
COAST BRACING FOR TORRENTIAL
RAIN AND HIGH WINDS, A SYSTEM
THAT ALREADY BROUGHT TO SEATTLE,
ONE OF THE WETTEST DAYS ON
RECORD.
THAT STORM TURNING DEADLY.
A WASHINGTON STATE POLICE
OFFICER WAS KILLED RACING TO THE
SCENE OF A CRIME, HYDROPLANING
ON THE WET ROAD BEFORE CRASHING.
IN THE SOUTHEAST, DRIVERS WILL
BE DEALING WITH
TREACHEROUS TRAVEL AS THE STORM
MOVING IN AND PACKING HEAVY RAIN
WILL DRENCH SEVERAL STATES.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO WILL BE
DRIVING, YOU'RE BEING ENCOURAGED
TO TAKE IT SLOW, AND OF COURSE,
AVOID THOSE FLOODWATERS.
THOSE OF YOU AT THE AIRPORT
TODAY ALREADY PLENTY OF ALERTS
TO GIVE YOURSELF PLENTY OF TIME,
AND OF COURSE, PACK YOUR
PATIENCE.
WHIT?
>> ALL RIGHT, ZACHARY.
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT INFORMATION.
>>> NOW TO THE PROCRASTINATORS
AMONG US.
YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE, BUT WE ARE
NOT JUDGING.
THERE IS INFORMATION THOUGH THAT
YOU NEED TO KNOW FOR THAT
LAST-MINUTE HOLIDAY SHOPPING
BLITZ.
ABC'S MARCI GONZALEZ JOINS US
FROM ALHAMBRA, CALIFORNIA WITH
MORE ON THAT.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: HEY, WHIT.
GOOD MORNING.
YES, THIS IS A JUDGMENT-FREE
ZONE.
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING TO SHOPPERS
AND SOME SAY THEY ACTUALLY WAIT
ON PURPOSE BECAUSE THEY LOVE THE
THRILL OF RUSHING THROUGH STORES
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
FOR EVERYONE ELSE THOUGH, IT IS
A SLIGHTLY LESS PLEASANT
EXPERIENCE.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS.
>> Reporter: IN THE COUNTDOWN TO
CHRISTMAS IT IS CRUNCH TIME.
>> IT'S NUTS.
YEAH, IT'S NUTS.
IT'S, LIKE, THE WORST.
IT'S FUN.
IT'S FUN, BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M
OVERWHELMED.
>> Reporter: SHOPPERS SCRAMBLING
TO GET THEIR LAST-MINUTE GIFTS.
SOME LIKE ERIC FINKLESTEIN
REALLY DOWN TO THE WIRE BEFORE
THE START OF HANUKKAH TONIGHT
GOING STORE TO STORE IN LOS
ANGELES ARMED WITH SEEMINGLY
ENDLESS LISTS.
>> I GOT ONE, AND HERE'S MY
OTHER LIST.
>> Reporter: MANY RETAILERS
OFFERING DEALS TO HELP YOU CROSS
OF THOSE ITEMS.
REEBOK AND EXPRESS ADVERTISING
50% OFF EVERYTHING ONLINE, AND
WALMART DISCOUNTING TOYS AND
GAMES UP TO 60%.
>> YOU GET THE GOOD DEALS
SOMETIMES AT THE LAST MINUTE.
>> PAYS OFF TO PROCRASTINATE I
GUESS.
>> Reporter: AND PROCRASTINATORS
ARE IN LUCK IF THEY'RE SHIPPING
THEIR HOLIDAY PURCHASES.
BEST BUY ADVERTISING FREE
NEXT-DAY DELIVERY ON THOUSANDS
OF ITEMS ORDERED BY TOMORROW.
TARGET AND AMAZON BOTH OFFERING
SAME-DAY DELIVERY IN MANY
LOCATIONS THROUGH CHRISTMAS EVE.
OR IF YOU ARE MAILING GIFTS
YOURSELF, YOU HAVE A FEW OPTIONS
LEFT TO GET THEM UNDER THE TREE
ON TIME.
USING THE U.S. POSTAL SERVICE'S
PRIORITY EXPRESS OR NEXT DAY
AIR.
HOW CAN YOU GET IT ALL DONE?
>> I THINK I CAN DO IT.
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
>> Reporter: FOR FINKLESTEIN
THOUGH, IT'S HOLIDAY MISSION
ACCOMPLISHED.
>> I'M DONE.
I'M DONE.
I'M VERY HAPPY.
>> Reporter: GOOD FOR HIM, AND
TO HELP THE REST OF US FOLLOW IN
HIS FOOTSTEPS, MANY STORES ARE
STAYING OPEN LATE.
OTHERS ARE JUST NEVER CLOSING
LIKE KOHL'S WHICH IS OPEN
NONSTOP UNTIL 6:00 ON CHRISTMAS
EVE, AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
GETTING HERE EARLY IS THE WAY TO
GO.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THERE ARE NO CROWDS AND NO
LINES.
DAN?
>> MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
THAT MAY BE THE STRATEGY.
MARCI, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> ON A MUCH MORE SOMBER NOTE
THIS MORNING, MORE THAN 1,000
PEOPLE ATTENDED A CELEBRATION OF
THE LIFE OF 18-YEAR-OLD BARNARD
COLLEGE STUDENT
TESSA MAJORS WHO WAS FATALLY
STABBED ALMOST TWO WEEKS AGO
HERE IN MANHATTAN.
OUR LOCAL AFFILIATE
WCAV SHOWS MAJORS' CLOSEST
FRIENDS RECITING POETRY, AND
SINGING SOME OF THE BUDDING
MUSICIAN'S FAVORITE SONGS AT HER
FORMER SCHOOL IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
A 13-YEAR-OLD BOY HAS BEEN
ARRESTED AND CHARGED IN
CONNECTION WITH HER MURDER WHILE
THE NYPD IS STILL SEARCHING FOR
MORE SUSPECTS.
>>> THIS MORNING, POSSIBLE NEW
INSIGHTS INTO PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
DEALINGS WITH UKRAINE.
EMAILS SHOWING A TIMELINE ON THE
REQUEST TO FREEZE U.S. MILITARY
AID TO THE COUNTRY.
ABC'S RACHEL SCOTT JOINS US FROM
WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA, WITH
MORE.
GOOD MORNING, RACHEL.
>> Reporter: EVA, GOOD MORNING.
YES, THOSE NEW DOCUMENTS SHOW
OFFICIALS WERE CONCERNED ABOUT
THE HOLDUP OF MILITARY AID, AND
ULTIMATELY RELIEVED WHEN IT WAS
RELEASED, READY TO PUT THIS ALL
BEHIND THEM.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION WAS
FORCED TO TURN OVER EMAILS
BETWEEN GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS WHO
DISCUSSED THE FREEZING OF
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS OF MILITARY
AID TO UKRAINE,
AN ATTEMPT DEMOCRATS SAY WAS TO
GET UKRAINE TO INVESTIGATE THE
PRESIDENT'S POLITICAL RIVALS.
NOW THOSE REDACTED DOCUMENTS
OBTAINED BY THE CENTER FOR
PUBLIC INTEGRITY SHOW THE
PRESIDENT ASKED ABOUT THE AID AS
EARLY AS JUNE.
NOW THAT IS WEEKS BEFORE THE
PRESIDENT'S INFAMOUS PHONE CALL
WITH THE LEADER OF UKRAINE THAT
TRIGGERED THE IMPEACHMENT
INVESTIGATION, AND IT ALSO SHOWS
THAT THE AID WAS WITHHELD JUST
90 MINUTES AFTER THE PRESIDENT'S
PHONE CALL.
NOW THE WHITE HOUSE HAS BLASTED
THE IMPEACHMENT INVESTIGATION WZ
A ONE-SIDED SHAM, AND THEY HAVE
DECLINED TO COMMENT ON THIS
RECENT RELEASE OF DOCUMENTS,
EVA.
>> RACHEL, LAWMAKERS HAVE LEFT
WASHINGTON UNCERTAIN ABOUT THE
TIMING OF IMPEACHMENT TRIAL.
LAST NIGHT PRESIDENT TRUMP
LASHING OUT AS NANCY PELOSI FOR
NOT SENDING OVER THOSE ARTICLES
OF IMPEACHMENT OVER TO THE
SENATE?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT, EVA.
THE TIMING OF AN IMPEACHMENT
TRIAL IS NOW UP IN THE AIR, AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP WENT AFTER HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI AFTER THE
UNEXPECTED HOLDUP.
THE PRESIDENT TOOK TO THE STAGE
AT A CONSERVATIVE STUDENT
CONFERENCE IN FLORIDA AING
FLOWSY'S STRATEGY IS TO DELAY
THE NEXT STEP BECAUSE SHE HAS NO
CASE.
REPUBLICANS HAVE ACCUSED THE
HOUSE SPEAKER OF GETTING COLD
FEET, HAVING BUYER'S REMORSE TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT, BUT
PELOSI SAID SHE'S NOT READY TO
TAKE THE NEXT STEP.
SHE'S HELD OFF ON SENDING THE
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT OVER TO
THE SENATE UNTIL REPUBLICANS
REVEAL HOW A TRIAL WOULD PLAY
OUT, AND LAWMAKERS WHO WOULD
DECIDE THE PRESIDENT'S FATE ARE
ON A HOLIDAY RECESS, AND THEY
ARE AT AN IMPASSE.
EVA?
>> RACHEL SCOTT FOR US.
THANK YOU.
WHIT?
>>> NOW TO POLITICS IN IOWA
WHERE THE CANDIDATES ARE TRYING
TO MAKE THEIR MARK WITH THE
CAUCUSES JUST AROUND THE CORNER
THERE.
ABC'S STEPHANIE RAMOS IS IN DES
MOINES THIS MORNING.
STEPHANIE, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: WHIT, GOOD MORNING.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES ARE
RAMPING UP THEIR CAMPAIGN
EFFORTS HERE IN IOWA TRYING TO
GAIN THOSE PRIMARY VOTERS BEFORE
THE ALL-IMPORTANT IOWA CAUCUS.
A NUMBER OF DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES ARE
CRISSCROSSING THE STATE OF IOWA
IN HOPES OF WINNING OVER RURAL
VOTERS BEFORE THE IOWA CAUCUSES
IN FEBRUARY.
IT WAS A FEW DAYS AGO AT THE
DEMOCRATIC DEBATE IN LOS ANGELES
WHERE MOST OF THE CANDIDATES
WERE TAKING AIM AT EACH OTHER.
>> MRS. KLOBUCHAR, YOU HAD YOUR
HAND UP FIRST.
>> I DID NOT COME HERE TO LISTEN
TO THIS ARGUMENT.
>> Reporter: WE SPOKE WITH
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN
AT THIS INTIMATE RALLY IN
CRESTON WHERE HE SAYS THE VERBAL
ATTACKS WON'T HELP UNIFY THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S A GOOD
THING.
I THINK WE HAVE ENOUGH DIVISION
IN THE PARTY AS WELL.
I DON'T THINK WE HELP ANYBODY
BUT THE OTHER GUY.
I DON'T THINK IT WORKS FOR
EVERYONE.
>> Reporter: MANY OF THE OTHER
CANDIDATES FIRING SHOTS,
DIRECTLY AT SOUTH BEND, INDIANA
MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG FOR HAVING
A PRIVATE FUND-RAISER IN A WINE
CAVE HOSTED BY BILLIONAIRES.
>> WE SHOULD DECIDE WE'RE NOT
GOING TO LET BILLIONAIRES IN
WINE CAVES PICK THE NEXT
PRESIDENT.
>> Reporter: BUTTIGIEG POINTED
OUT THAT ELIZABETH WARREN
HERSELF IS A MILLIONAIRE, IS
DEFENDING CONTRIBUTIONS HIS
CAMPAIGN IS RECEIVING FROM WALL
STREET DONORS SAYING HE WELCOMES
ANY DONATION BIG OR SMALL.
>> IF YOU ARE WEALTHY AND YOU
WANT A DIFFERENT PRESIDENT, I'LL
ACCEPT THAT.
>> Reporter: SENATOR KLOBUCHAR
WHILE MAKING HER ROUNDS SAYS,
IT'S ABOUT EVERYONE HAVING A
FAIR CHANCE TO RUN FOR OFFICE.
>> THE BIGGER ISSUE HERE IS
CAMPAIGN FINANCE REFORM.
I FIND A BIG IMBALANCE THAT
PEOPLE WHO HAVE BIGGER BANK
ACCOUNTS CAN RUN THEIR OWN ADS
ALL THE TIME AND ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: THE NEXT DEBATE IS
SCHEDULED FOR JANUARY 14th.
IT IS THE ONLY 2020 DEBATE
BEFORE THE IOWA CAUCUSES, AND
THE DNC IS RAISING THE CRITERIA
TO PARTICIPATE.
CANDIDATES MUST EARN AT LEAST 5%
IN FOUR POLLS OR 7% IN TWO
DIFFERENT POLLS CONDUCTED IN
IOWA, NEW HAMPSHIRE, NEVADA OR
SOUTH CAROLINA.
DAN?
>> WE'RE DOWN TO THE WIRE HERE.
IOWA NOT FAR AWAY.
THANKS SO MUCH, STEPHANIE.
APPRECIATE IT.
SO MUCH TO DISCUSS HERE.
SO LET'S BRING IN OUR RINGER,
MARTHA RADDATZ IN WASHINGTON
WHERE SHE'LL BE HOSTING "THIS
WEEK" LATER THIS MORNING.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
YOU SPENT TIME IN BATTLEGROUND
STATES THIS WEEK.
I'M CURIOUS.
DOES THIS DEMOCRATIC DEBATE
ABOUT MONEY AND POLITICS AND
WHETHER PETE BUTTIGIEG SPENT
TIME IN A WINE CAVE, DOES THAT
CUT THROUGH FOR REGULAR VOTERS?
>> I GOT TO SAY, DAN, I DIDN'T
HEAR ANYONE BRING UP WINE CAVES,
BUT THAT IS REALLY SORT OF AN
EVOCATIVE IMAGE TO SOME PEOPLE,
THINKING OF PETE BUTTIGIEG
THINKING ABOUT THERE IN THAT
WINE CAVE.
CLEARLY CAMPAIGN SPENDING IS AN
ISSUE.
WE HAVE HEARD BERNIE SANDERS AND
ELIZABETH WARREN TALK ABOUT
BILLIONAIRES OVER AND OVER AND
OVER.
SO THERE IS CLEARLY SOME
RESPONSE TO THAT, BUT VOTERS OUT
THERE ARE THINKING OF FAR
DIFFERENT THINGS.
THEY'RE REALLY THINKING ABOUT
HEALTH CARE.
THAT IS THE ANSWER I GOT MORE
THAN ANY OTHER.
WHAT ISSUES ARE IMPORTANT TO
YOU?
HEALTH CARE, HEALTH CARE, HEALTH
CARE.
>> AND IMPEACHMENT NOT CUTTING
THROUGH THEN?
>> IMPEACHMENT, YOU KNOW, I'M
SURPRISED.
THERE WERE SO MANY PEOPLE WHO
WERE ABSOLUTELY RIVETED TO THE
SCREEN, BUT THOSE WERE MAINLY
DEMOCRATS.
THE REPUBLICANS WERE ECHOING
DONALD TRUMP'S WORDS IN MANY,
MANY WAYS SAYING IT WAS A WASTE
OF TIME, SAYING IT WAS A SHAM.
THEY WOULD SAY IT OVER AND OVER.
I THINK -- I GET THE SENSE FROM
TALKING TO THOSE VOTERS IN
BATTLEGROUND STATES THAT THEY
JUST WANT TO MOVE ON AND GET
BACK TO THE ISSUES OUTSIDE OF
IMPEACHMENT.
SOME DEMOCRATS SAY THEY WERE
EVEN WORRIED THAT IT WOULD HELP
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> BUT THE ISSUE IS NOT GOING
AWAY.
YOU HAVE TWO PROMINENT SENATORS
ON YOUR SHOW THIS MORNING.
BOTH OF THEM WOULD SERVE AS
JURORS IF THERE WAS A TRIAL IN
THE SENATE.
WHERE DO THINGS STAND RIGHT NOW?
ARE WE GOING TO HAVE A TRIAL?
WHEN IS IT LIKELY TO HAPPEN?
WILL THERE BE WITNESSES?
WHAT DO WE KNOW?
>> I WOULD SAY JUST WHAT RACHEL
SAID.
AT THIS POINT IT IS UNCLEAR
WHETHER THAT TRIAL WILL TAKE
PLACE, BUT PEOPLE ARE PRETTY
CERTAIN IT WILL TAKE PLACE AT
SOME POINT.
PROBABLY SOMETIME IN JANUARY.
>> MARTHA, ALWAYS GREAT TO TALK
TO YOU ON A SUNDAY MORNING.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I WANT TO REMIND EVERYBODY SHE
HAS A BIG SHOW COMING UP THIS
MORNING.
SHE'LL SIT DOWN WITH GOP SENATOR
RONN JOHNSON AND DOUG JONES
ABOUT WHAT WE CAN EXPECT FROM AN
IMPEACHMENT TRIAL.
AND THE ROUND TABLE TAKES THIS
ON BEFORE THE CAUCUSES.
THAT'S COMING UP LATER THIS
MORNING ON ABC.
OVER TO YOU.
>>> IN IOWA, POLICE HAVE CHARGED
A WOMAN FOR ATTEMPTED MURDER
AFTER THEY SAY SHE RAN OVER A
14-YEAR-OLD GIRL ON PURPOSE
BECAUSE SHE WAS MEXICAN.
42-YEAR-OLD NICOLE POOLE
FRANKLIN HAS ALLEGEDLY ADMITTED
TO POLICE SHE INTENTIONALLY
VEERED OFF THE ROAD TO HIT THE
GIRL.
THE TEEN SUFFERED SOME INJURIES
BUT WAS ABLE TO RETURN TO SCHOOL
AFTER A WEEK.
AUTHORITIES ARE DECIDING WHETHER
OR NOT TO CHARGE FRANKLIN WITH A
HATE CRIME.
>>> NOW TO A DRAMATIC SCENE
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
RESIDENTS COMING TO THE
RESCUE AFTER A SMALL PLANE MADE
A HARROWING CRASH LANDING NEAR
BOSTON.
>> DISPATCHING A SMALL AIRCRAFT
CRASH.
PLANE IS IN WATER IN THE LAKE
STREET POND.
UNKNOWN INJURIES.
>> Reporter: TERRIFYING MOMENTS
IN MASSACHUSETTS WHEN THIS SMALL
PLANE CAME CRASHING DOWN ONTO AN
ICY POND IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
THE PILOT MANAGING TO ESCAPE.
NEIGHBORS THEN RUSHING IN TO
HELP.
>> THE ENGINE WAS SOUNDING LIKE
IT WAS REALLY JUST PUTTING
ALONG.
COULDN'T GET ALTITUDE.
>> Reporter: WITNESSES SAY THE
PILOT WAS ATTEMPTING AN
EMERGENCY LANDING SATURDAY ON
THE SHEET OF ICE THAT FORMED ON
TOP OF THE POND WHEN ONE OF THE
PLANE'S WINGS CLIPPED THE
SURFACE.
>> WE HAVE AN AIRCRAFT IN THE
WATER.
>> Reporter: THE PILOT
SCRAMBLING TO STAND ON TOP OF
THE PLANE AS THE AIRCRAFT SANK
INTO THE FREEZING WATER.
>> ONE PARTY ON THE WING OF THE
PLANE.
>> HE WAS PANICKING.
HE WAS WORRIED HE COULDN'T SWIM.
>> Reporter: WITH NO TIME TO
SPARE, JOHN KEEGAN WHO WORKED
THE WHOLE ORDEAL, GRABBED
HIS NEIGHBOR'S CANOE, MOUNTING
HIS OWN RESCUE TO REACH THE
DESPERATE PILOT.
>> HIS LANDING GREER GOT RIPPED
OFF.
THE FRONT OF THE PLANE WAS
CRUSHED.
>> Reporter: KEEGAN IN HIS
BORROWED CANOE, REACHING THE
PILOT JUST IN TIME.
>> HOPEFULLY THAT'S IT FOR
CHRISTMAS EXCITEMENT.
I'LL REMEMBER IT.
SO WILL EVERYBODY AROUND HERE.
>> EMERGENCY MEDICAL TECHNICIANS
WERE WAITING FOR THAT PILOT ONCE
HE REACHED SHORE, BUT HE REFUSED
TREATMENT INDICATING HE WAS
LIKELY OKAY.
>> A TOUGH MASSACHUSETTS MESS.
THANK YOU, WHIT.
>>> RIGHT NOW BOEING'S TROUBLED
STARLINER SPACECRAFT IS BACK ON
ITS WAY TO EARTH.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE AN
UNMANNED TEST ON ITS WAY TO THE
SPACE STATION, BUT IT DIDN'T GET
THERE.
TREVOR AULT IS HERE WITH MUCH OR
ON THAT.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, DAN.
THESE WERE BIG PLANS FOR THE
BOEING STARLINER THAT WERE
FOILED PRETTY SOON AFTER IT GOT
INTO SPACE, AND ACCORDING TO
N
NASA, IT'S BECAUSE A MISSION
ELAPSED TIMING ANOMALY LED TO AN
ORBITAL INSERTION.
IT SOUNDS COMPLICATED.
WHAT IT ESSENTIALLY MEANS IS ONE
OF THE CLOCKS WAS WRONG, SO THEY
DECIDED TO BRING IT BACK HOME.
THIS MORNING, THE BOEING
STARLINER HEADING BACK DOWN TO
EARTH, UNFORTUNATELY AHEAD OF
SCHEDULE.
>> AND LIFTOFF.
THE RISE OF STARLINER.
>> Reporter: JUST TWO DAYS AGO,
THE UNMANNED CAPSULE HAD A
PICTURE-PERFECT LAUNCH FROM CAPE
CANAVERAL BOUND FOR THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION, BUT
IT NEVER MADE IT THERE.
WHILE THE REASON WHY COULD BE
CALLED ROCKET SCIENCE, THE
SIMPLE VERSION IS THAT THERE WAS
A PROBLEM WITH THE CLOCK.
>> THAT ANOMALY RESULTED IN THE
VEHICLE BELIEVING THAT THE TIME
WAS DIFFERENT THAN IT ACTUALLY
WAS.
>> Reporter: THAT ERROR IN
TIMING MEANT THE STARLINER
DIDN'T FIRE ITS ROCKETS AT THE
RIGHT TIME TO GET INTO THE
CORRECT ORBIT, AND BOEING
ENGINEERS TRYING TO LAUNCH THEM
MANUALLY COULDN'T GET THE SIGNAL
THROUGH, SO THAT TRIP TO THE
SPACE STATION WITH FOOD,
CHRISTMAS REPRESENTS FOR THE
ASTRONAUTS AND ROSIE THE RO
ROCKETEER ON BOARD HAD TO BE
SCRAPPED.
>> IF ASTRONAUTS WERE ON BOARD,
THEY WOULD HAVE HAD TO TAKE OVER
THE SEQUENCE, AND NOT MAKE THE
ERRORS THAT WERE MADE.
>> Reporter: THERE WERE HOPE
THIS STARLINER'S TREK WOULD HAVE
BEEN A HISTORIC STEP IN NASA'S
COMMERCIAL CREW PROGRAM WHICH
THE AGENCY SAYS AIMS TO GET
AMERICAN ASTRONAUTS BACK INTO
SPACE BY WORKING WITH PRIVATE
COMPANIES LIKE BOEING AND
SPACEX.
ELON MUSK OFFERED A SUPPORTIVE
OLIVE BRANCH TWEETING, ORBIT IS
HARD AND WISHING THE BOEING TEAM
WELL ON THE LANDING.
>> I THINK THE 2020 WILL BE THE
ROARING '20s FOR SPACE TRAVEL.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A VERY
EXCITING DECADE COMING UP.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE THERE
WASN'T A TOTAL FAILURE.
THAT DUMBNY -- DUMMY ON BOARD,
ROSIE THE ROCKETEER GATHERED A
LOT OF DATA, BUT THE PLAN HAS
BEEN TO SEND ASTRONAUTS UP IN
THE COMING YEAR, AND WE DON'T
KNOW IF THIS WILL SLOW DOWN THIS
PLAN.
>> ARE THEY BLAMING THIS ON THE
DUMMY?
THAT'S HOW I WOULD DO IT.
>> THEY'RE NOT PASSING BLAME I'M
SURE JUST YET.
>> ROSIE.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
>>> TIME NOW FOR A CHECK OF
THE WEATHER, AND GREG DUTRA IS
IN FOR ROB.
HOW YOU DOING THIS MORNING?
>> IM A DOING GREAT, BUT
TRAVELERS WILL HAVE A PROBLEM.
MAJOR TRAVEL HUBS TODAY NOT ONLY
ON THE EAST COAST, BUT WEST
COAST AFFECTED BY DUAL SYSTEMS.
LET'S START IN THE SOUTHEAST
HERE.
ATLANTA OF COURSE, A MAJOR
TRAVEL HUB.
THE WHOLE STATE OF GEORGIA HAS
RAIN OVER IT.
SAME DEAL IN FLORIDA, SAME DEAL
IN MISSISSIPPI, AND ALL THE WAY
NORTH HERE INTO SOUTH CAROLINA,
AND THAT IS WHERE WE TRACK THIS
STORM TODAY, BUT BEFORE WE GET
INTO THIS EVENING, THERE'S A
CHANCE OF SEVERE STORMS IN SOUTH
FLORIDA.
THEY CALL IT THE SUN COAST.
NOT SO MUCH TODAY.
LATER ON, THE EVENING ON MONDAY,
THE STORM FINALLY PULLS OFF OF
THE COAST AND BRINGS DRIER AIR
IN FOR CHRISTMAS.
THAT IS A GOOD LITTLE PIT OF
NEWS, BUT LOOK AT THE RAINFALL.
TO
TOTAL SPOTS THAT HAVE TROUBLE
WITH FLOODING LIKE
CHARLESTON, THEY HAVE 3 TO
6 INCHES OF RAIN, ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO SAVANNAH, GEORGIA, AND
1 TO 3 INCHES FOR JUST ABOUT
EVERYWHERE ELSE IN THE
SOUTHEAST.
HERE'S ANOTHER DOSE OF GOOD
NEWS.
CHRISTMAS IN CHICAGO IS GOING TO
BE WARMER THAN HALLOWEEN WAS.
INCHES OF SNOW ON HALLOWEEN.
NEAR 50 DEGREES ON CHRISTMAS.
LET'S TAKE A
>>> WELL, HAPPY SUNDAY.
METEOROLOGIST ALEX LIGGETT
HERE.
AT A WHERE WE FINALLY SEE A
LITTLE BIT OF MORE MILD AIR
ACROSS THE REGION, INTO THE
UPPER 40S, UNDER PARTLY CLOUDY
SKIES, THE NATIONAL MENORAH
LIGHTING IS AT 4:00 THIS
EVENING AT THE WHITE HOUSEb&,
ACTUALLY 45 DEGREES UNDER
PARTLY SUNNY SKIES, BACK INTO
THE
>>> A BEAUTIFUL NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS HERE FOR A GOOD CHUNK OF
THE U.S., BUT REALLY SOME
PROBLEMS ELSEWHERE.
ESPECIALLY IN THE SOUTHEAST, AND
WE'LL TALK ABOUT
THAT WEST COAST STORM TOO.
>>> CHRISTMAS CAME EARLY FOR A
WAITRESS IN OHIO.
SIX FRIENDS GOT TOGETHER TO
SURPRISE THEIR FAVORITE SERVER
AT THEIR LOCAL WAFFLE HOUSE BY
GIVING HER A $600 TIP AS PART OF
A HOLIDAY MOVEMENT DUBBED SHOCK
AND CLAUS WHERE GROUPS GO OUT
AND LEAVE $100 PER PERSON TIPS
TO WORKERS.
AND IT GETS BETTER.
A COUPLE THAT SAW WHAT WAS
HAPPENING WANTED IN ON THE
ACTION AND GAVE THE WAITRESS
ANOTHER $200.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
I LOVE IT.
>> I ALSO LOVE WAFFLE HOUSE.
>> IT NEVER HAPPENED TO ME WHEN
I WAS A WAITER AT THE OLIVE
GARDEN.
IT'S A NEW TREND.
>> THAT MAY BE A WHOLE DIFFERENT
ISSUE.
>> MAYBE IT WAS MY SERVICE.
>> YOU WEREN'T FAST ENOUGH WITH
THE BREAD STICKS.
>> WHERE'S MY SALAD?
>>> JANAI IS HERE WITH ANOTHER
SURPRISE CHRISTMAS GIFT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> SO THIS ONE WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE A PRANK, BUT IT SORT OF
BACKFIRED AND TURNED INTO A MUCH
APPRECIATED SNACK.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
>> BANANA.
BANANA!
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> BANANA.
>> THE JOY OF LITTLE KIDS.
SO A MOM TRIED TO PRANK HER
2-YEAR-OLD BY GIVING HER WHAT
SHE THOUGHT WOULD BE THE WORST
CHRISTMAS EVER.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
LITTLE ARIA LOVED HER WRAPPED
BANANA.
SHE DIDN'T THINK IT WAS BAD AT
ALL.
GUESS THE JOKE'S ON MOM.
>> I THINK BANANAS ARE HAVING A
MOMENT.
>> WITH KIDS, YOU CAN WRAP
ANYTHING.
THEY'RE JUST EXCITED TO OPEN IT.
>> SHE WAS HUNGRY.
>> THANK YOU, JANAI.
APPRECIATE IT.
>>> WE'LL SWITCH GEARS AND TELL
YOU WHAT'S COMING UP ON THE
SHOW.
A MOTHER STRANGLED.
NEW DETAILS THIS MORNING FROM
TEXAS ABOUT THE SUSPECT WHO HAS
BEEN CHARGED AS INVESTIGATORS
LOOK AT THIS AS A POSSIBLE CASE
OF BABY SNATCHING.
>>> 'TIS THE SEASON FOR WEIGHT
GAIN.
HOW YOU CAN INDULGE WITHOUT
PAYING FOR IT LATER.
STAY WITH US.
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY WEATHERTECH.
THE ULTIMATE AMERICAN-MADE
VEHICLE PROTECTION.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Can you heal dry
skin in a day?
Aveeno® with prebiotic
triple oat complex
balances skin's microbiome.
So skin looks like this
and you feel like this.
Aveeno® Skin Relief.
Get Skin Healthy™
Dad, we need to talk about
something important.
You don't need to go
anywhere dad,
this is your home.
The best home to be in
is your own.
Home Instead offers
personalized in-home services
for your loved ones.
Home Instead Senior Care.
To us, it's personal.
The Epson EcoTank.
No more buying cartridges.
Home Instead Senior Care.
Look at all this ink
it comes with.
Big ink tanks.
Lots of ink.
No more cartridges.
Incredible amount of ink.
The Epson EcoTank.
Just fill and chill.
If you're 65 or older,
even if you're healthy,
you may be at increased risk
for pneumococcal pneumonia -
a potentially serious
bacterial lung disease
that can disrupt
your life for weeks.
In severe cases,
pneumococcal pneumonia
can put you in the hospital.
It can hit quickly,
without warning,
making you miss out
on what matters most.
Just one dose of the
PREVNAR 13® vaccine
can help protect you from
pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's not a yearly shot.
PREVNAR 13® is approved
for adults to help prevent
infections from 13 strains
of the bacteria that cause
pneumococcal pneumonia.
Don't get PREVNAR 13®
if you have had a severe
allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
Adults with weakened
immune systems
may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side
effects were pain,
redness and swelling
at the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever,
chills, and rash.
Ask about prevention.
Ask your doctor or
pharmacist about PREVNAR 13®.
If your mouth is made to amaze,
Let Philips Sonicare
give its care a raise.
Get healthier gums
in 2 weeks guaranteed.
Give it Philips Sonicare.
Next level clean,
next level care.
There's always a way
to make life better.
Philips Sonicare
There's always a way
to make life better.
♪
So Josh, you going for our
Drive Safe and Save discount?
Yup, using the app.
Driving safe. Heh.
You wanna go? Wanna go bro?
Hey, uh, do not mess
with my discount.
Woooo!
You could save up to 30%.
Let's go!
Nice to meet you,
go get 'em tiger!
Woooo!
Sounds like you've got this?
Yeah. Definitely.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe and Save™
from State Farm.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
>>> WELL, HELLO, AND GOOD
MORNING, WASHINGTON.
METEOROLOGIST ALEX LIGGETT
HERE, INTO THE TEENS,
TEMPERATURES WILL MODERATE SOME
TODAY INTO THE UPPER 40s UNDER
PARTLY CLOUDY SKIES, THE
OVERNIGHT HAS ANOTHER COOL
NIGHT AHEAD, WITH THAT BEING
SAID SOME SLIGHTLY MORE MILD
AIR INTO THE FORECAST, MID-20S
AND SUBURBS THE LOWER 30s
DOWNTOWN.
LOOKING AHEAD THROUGH THE LOWER
PORTIONS OF THE WEEK, 50
DEGREES UNDER THE PARLY CLOUDY
SKIES, 50 DEGREES AS WELL SO
THIS IS JUST THAT SAME EXACT
FORECAST ALL THE WAY THROUGH
CHRISTMAS DAY WITH DRY
CONDITIONS SO UNFORTUNATELY, NO
WHITE CHRISTMAS IS EXPECTED
THIS TIME AROUND, LOOKING
AHEAD, FRIDAY, THE START UP
NEXT WEEKEND, LOOKS LIKE THE
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
ON THIS SUNDAY MORNING.
YESTERDAY, WE HAD FUN HERE WITH
OUR UGLY CHRISTMAS SWEATERS WITH
ROB THERE.
THERE HE IS, TAKING HOME THE
PRIZE AFTER HE PULLED OUT ALL
THE STOPS AND HIS SWEATER.
PULLED THE SWEATER OFF.
>>> COMING UP IN "POP," JANAI
HAS AN UPDATE ON A FAMOUS UGLY
SWEATER THAT MADE HEADLINES LAST
YEAR, AND WHO IS WEARING IT THIS
YEAR.
>> I THINK ROB TOOK THE MORNING
OFF BECAUSE HE KNEW WE WERE
GOING TO MAKE FUN OF HIM.
>> EXACTLY.
>> FOR THOSE ANACONDAS HE GOT.
>> DOES ANYTHING SURPRISE ME ON
THIS SHOW?
I'M TRULY SHOCKED.
>> STILL SURPRISING.
>> WHAT HAS HAPPENED?
SPEECHLESS.
GOOD TIMES.
>>> NOW TO SOME OF THE OTHER BIG
STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING THIS
MORNING.
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW, IT IS
CRUNCH TIME.
THE HOLIDAY HUSSLE IS ON.
MILLIONS EXPECTED TO HIT THE
ROADS AND THE SKIES TO GET WHERE
THEY NEED TO BE.
WHILE OTHERS WILL MAKE THEIR
WAYS TO THE MALLS AND MARKETS
SCRAMBLING FOR LAST-MINUTE
GIFTS.
THIS WHILE TWO STORMS ON TWO
DIFFERENT COASTS WILL BRITAIN
TORRENTIAL RAIN AND WIND AND
EVEN A SEVERE WEATHER THREAT FOR
SOUTHERN FLORIDA.
>>> NOW THE INVESTIGATION INTO
WHAT CAUSED A BRIDGE TO
COLLAPSE, SENDING A FREIGHT
TRAIN OFF THE BRIDGE OVER THE
POTOMAC RIVER IN WEST VIRGINIA.
FIVE CARS TOPPLING OVER,
INCLUDING TWO OF THEM THAT
LANDED IN THE WATER.
FORTUNATELY THE TRAIN WAS EMPTY
SO NOBODY GOT HURT HERE.
>>> AND FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE
THE FRENCH REVOLUTION, MIDNIGHT
MASS WILL NOT BE CELEBRATED AT
PARIS' NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL.
THE CHURCH HAS BEEN OFF LIMITS
TO PARISHIONERS SINCE THAT FIRE.
>> SO MUCH HISTORY AND
ARCHITECTURE.
THEY ARE DETERMINED TO REBUILD.
>>> WE START THOUGH THIS HALF
HOUR WITH NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN
THE INVESTIGATION INTO WHAT
COULD BE A DISTURBING CASE OF
BABY SNATCHING.
A NEW MOTHER FOUND DEAD, AND WE
ARE LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
WOMAN'S CLOSE FRIEND NOW FACING
CHARGES.
ABC'S KAYLEE HARTUNG HAS MORE
FROM AUSTIN, TEXAS.
KAYLEE, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, WHIT.
DURING THAT MASSIVE WEEK-LONG
SEARCH FOR HEIDI BROUSSARD AND
HER BABY, THE WOMAN NOW BEHIND
BARS HERE IN AUSTIN WAS IN PLAIN
SIGHT.
ONE OF HEIDI'S BEST FRIENDS FOR
MORE THAN 20 YEARS EVEN HELPING
WITH THE SEARCH.
STUNNING NEW INFORMATION
EMERGING ABOUT THIS WOMAN,
33-YEAR-OLD MAGEN FIERAMUSCA
CHARGED WITH KIDNAPPING HER
CLOSE FRIEND HEIDI BROUSSARD AND
HER NEWBORN BABY.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW SINCERE
SHE SOUNDED.
>> Reporter: TO MILLER, ONE OF
THE LEAD SEARCHERS IN THE
DISAPPEARANCE NOW IN SHOCK
SAYING HE SPOKE TO FIERAMUSCA
JUST DAYS BEFORE HER ARREST.
>> I WAS JUST KIND OF SCRATCHING
MY HEAD TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW
IN THE WORLD COULD THIS PERSON
SOUND SO CONVINCING.
>> Reporter: MILLER SHARING WHAT
HE SAW AS THE DEATH OF
FIERAMUSCA AND BROUSSARD'S
FRIENDSHIP.
>> MAGEN WAS WITH HEIDI WHEN SHE
HAD THE BABY.
THAT'S HOW CLOSE OF FRIENDS THEY
WERE.
THEY WERE FRIENDS WHEN SHANE AND
HEIDI GOT TOGETHER TEN YEARS
AGO.
>> Reporter: CARESSA NOLTE WHO
SAYS SHE'S A MUTUAL FRIEND OF
THE TWO WOMEN REACTING TO THE
DEVASTATING DISCOVERY OF THE
STRANGLED BODY INSIDE
FIERAMUSCA'S CAR.
LIVE WHILE SPEAKING ON A
CRIMINAL JUSTICE BROADCAST.
>> OH MY GOD.
OH MY GOD.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT'S MAGEN, HER BEST FRIEND
THAT MET HER AT CHURCH CAMP WITH
ME.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THEY'RE
NOW INVESTIGATING IF FIERAMUSCA
WAS PLOTTING TO STEAL HER BEST
FRIEND'S BABY AND PASS IT OFF AS
HER OWN.
FIERAMUSCA'S FACING TWO CHARGES
OF KIDNAPPING AND ONE CHARGE OF
TAMPERING WITH A HUMAN CORPSE.
THERE ARE STILL NO MURDER
CHARGES FOR BROUSSARD'S DEATH,
AND IN THE MEANTIME, THE BABY
BELIEVED TO BE MARGOT IS IN THE
CARE OF CHILD PROTECTIVE
SERVICES AS THEY WORK TO
DETERMINE WHO WILL GET CUSTODY
OF THAT LITTLE GIRL.
DAN?
>> AS WE HAVE BEEN SAYING, SO
MANY UNANSWERED QUESTIONS STILL
IN THIS CASE.
KAYLEE, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> WE'LL SWITCH GEARS NOW AND
GET THE WEATHER FROM GREG DUTRA
FROM OUR CHICAGO STATION WLS, IN
FOR ROB THIS MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT TWO STORM
SYSTEMS, RIGHT?
THE ONE ON THE SOUTHEAST COAST,
AND NOW THE ONE ON THE WEST
COAST.
THAT HAS BROUGHT A LOT OF RAIN.
CHECK OUT THIS WATERFALL FLOWING
LIKE CRAZY, AND THIS IS IN
WASHINGTON, AND THIS STORM
SYSTEM IS HEADED OFF TO THE
SOUTH, AND WILL IMPACT MORE
MAJOR TRAVEL HUBS AS IT MAKES
ITS WAY THROUGH SAN FRANCISCO
BAY, AND DOWN INTO LOS ANGELES.
FLOOD ALERTS UP.
NO BIG SURPRISE HERE IN THE
SIERRA NEVADAS AS WE GOT WINTER
STORM WARNINGS TOO, AND AS THIS
MOVES TO THE SOUTH, ONE TO TWO
INCHES OF RAIN EXPECTED AT
L.A.X.
>>> HELLO, AND HAPPY SUNDAY.
THE FIRST FULL DAY OF WINTER IS
HERE, REACHING THE UPPER
>>> THE WEATHER REPORT SPONSORED
BY WALGREENS.
>> THAT WILL BE USEFUL THIS WEEK
WHEN PEOPLE NEED CHRISTMAS
PRESENTS LAST MINUTE.
THEY'RE OPEN LAST MINUTE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> OR COUGH MEDICATION WHEN YOU
ARE AROUND THE FAMILY.
SICKNESS TRAVELS AROUND.
>> GETTING SICK.
>> THANK YOU, WHIT.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> COME ON NOW.
>> A SHOT WITH THE TWO OF US
TOGETHER.
WHO'S WHO?
>> WHO'S WHO?
>> EXACTLY.
>> WHAT COLOR SUIT AM I WEARING
TODAY?
>> RAISE YOUR HAND TO KNOW WHICH
ONE YOU ARE.
>>> COMING UP ON "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA," THE HEROES THAT MADE
US STAND UP AND TAKE NOTICE THIS
YEAR, FACING PERSONAL AND
PROFESSIONAL BATTLES.
>> BY THE WAY, WE'RE DOING
23ANDME DNA TESTS.
LONG LOST TWIN RIGHT HERE.
>>> ALSO EDDIE MURPHY MAKES HIS
RETURN TO "SNL" AFTER THREE
DECADES.
"GMA" BACK IN A MOME Honey, can?
Guess who's early?
Good thing Walgreens is right
around the corner
with last minute holiday
supplies.
Get in.  Get out. Get jolly.
with last minute holiday
supplies.
[Boy gasps]
For real cold and flu
protection
With Lysol, you can help
protect them from a real cold.
Lysol Disinfectant Spray
kills the #1 cause of the cold
and Clorox wipes don't.
Lysol.
What it takes
to protect.
♪ ♪ ♪
There are rising reports of a
Zombie outbreak across the area.
The National Guard-
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
Enjoy the great taste
of Dunkin' at home.
When you have pain...
Sometimes you just
want to stay in.
You want relief.
Fast.
Only ThermaCare Ultra Pain
Relieving Cream
has 4 active ingredients
to fight pain
4 different ways.
Get powerful relief today,
with ThermaCare.
I can't believe it.
That Sophie opened up a
wormhole through time?
(Speaking Japanese) Where am I?
(Woman Speaking French)
Are you crazy/nuts?
Cyclist: Pip! Pip!
(Woman Speaking French)
I'm here, look at me. It's
completely your fault.
(Man Speaking French)
OK? It's me. It's my fault?
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
(Pterodactyl screech)
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
>>> AND THE COUNTDOWN IS ON TO
THE NEW YEAR AND A NEW DECADE
DEPENDING ON HOW YOU DO THE
MATH, AND THIS MORNING WE'RE
LOOKING BACK AT SOME OF THE
HEROES OF 2019 AND THEIR MOMENTS
OF STRENGTH THAT MADE GLOBAL
HEADLINES.
HERE'S MORE NOW FROM ROBIN
ROBERTS.
>> STEPS UP SLOWLY.
RAPINOE'S SHOT.
GOAL.
>> Reporter: THIS YEAR, THE U.S.
WOMEN'S NATIONAL TEAM SHATTERED
RECORDS WITH THEIR FOURTH WORLD
CUP VICTORY.
WOMEN ARE CHANGING THE GAME ON
AND OFF THE FIELD.
[ CHANTING "EQUAL PAY" ]
>> IT'S QUITE SIMPLE FROM OUR
PERSPECTIVE.
WE WANT TO BE PAID EQUALLY.
>> THEY'RE BRINGING UP A VERY
VALID AND LONG OVERDUE ISSUE.
>> THE WOMEN'S GAME HAS PROVED
TIME AND TIME AGAIN THAT WE'RE
WORTHY OF THE INVESTMENT.
>> Reporter: IN MARCH, THE
PLAYERS SUED THE U.S. SOCCER
FEDERATION FOR GENDER
DISCRIMINATION, AND THEY
CONTINUE TO SPEAK OUT.
>> I THINK THERE'S A PART IN
THIS FOR EVERYBODY TO DO.
>> THOSE WOMEN BANDED TOGETHER,
AND THEY ADVOCATED FOR
THEMSELVES, AND THAT IS THE BEST
LESSON YOU CAN TEACH, "A,"
ANYBODY, BUT, "B," A WOMAN.
>> STEP OUTSIDE YOURSELF.
BE MORE.
BE BETTER.
BE BIGGER THAN YOU HAVE EVER
BEEN BEFORE.
>> Reporter: FROM FIGHTING FOR
EQUAL PAY, TO A VERY DIFFERENT
BATTLE FOR LEGENDARY "JEOPARDY!"
HOST, ALEX TREBEK.
>> JUST LIKE 15,000 OTHER PEOPLE
IN THE UNITED STATES EACH YEAR,
THIS WEEK I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
STAGE 4 PANCREATIC CANCER, BUT
I'M GOING TO FIGHT THIS.
>> EVEN THOUGH THE RATES ARE SO
DAUNTING, SHARING HOPE WITH
OTHER PEOPLE I THINK IS, LIKE, A
VERY BEAUTIFUL THING TO DO, AND
HOPEFULLY GIVES SOMEONE ELSE
THAT LITTLE EXTRA KICK AND FIGHT
IN THEIR STEP.
>> BLESS YOU FOR BEING SO HONEST
AND TALKING ABOUT THE BAD AS
WELL AS THE GOOD.
>> YEAH.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
SAYING, HEY.
I'M REALLY DEPRESSED TODAY, AND
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY.
WHY AM I CRYING TODAY?
>> HE'S BEING OPEN AND HONEST
AND HE'S OUT THERE TRYING TO
BATTLE THIS DISEASE, BUT YOU
KNOW WHAT?
HE HASN'T MISSED A DAY OF WORK.
THAT'S AMAZING.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS THAT I HOPE
THAT WE TAKE FROM 2019 INTO 2020
IS VULNERABILITY.
>> DID YOU COME UP WITH THE
RIGHT ONE?
NO.
WHAT IS, WE LOVE YOU, ALEX.
THAT'S VERY KIND.
THANK YOU.
>> THE MOMENT THAT YOU SHARE
WHAT YOU ARE GOING THROUGH, NOT
ONLY DO YOU CONNECT WITH OTHER
PEOPLE, BUT YOU GET STRONGER AS
WELL BECAUSE OF ALL THE LOVE
THAT'S COMING TOWARDS YOU.
>> IT'S A COSTUME PARTY.
YOU PROBABLY WON'T WANT TO COME.
>> Reporter: LIKE ALEX TREBEK,
ACTRESS SELMA BLAIR EMBRACED THE
LOVE WHILE DOCUMENTING HER NEW
NORMAL, LIVING WITH MULTIPLE
SCLEROSIS.
>> I WAS A LITTLE SCARED OF
TALKING, AND EVEN MY NEUROLOGIST
SAID, NO.
THIS WILL BRING A LOT OF
AWARENESS BECAUSE NO ONE HAS THE
ENERGY TO TALK WHEN THEY'RE IN
FLARE-UP, BUT I DO BECAUSE I
LOVE A CAMERA.
>> EVERY TIME SELMA BLAIR CRACKS
A JOKE ABOUT HER SITUATION, YOU
FIND A LITTLE BIT MORE EMPATHY,
BUT YOU ALSO SEE A STRENGTH
PEEKING THROUGH THAT IS
INSPIRING TO ALL OF US.
>> SHE IS INCREDIBLE, AND THAT
IS JUST A PREVIEW OF THE
TWO-HOUR SPECIAL.
THAT'S ANCHORED BY ROBIN
ROBERTS, STARTING AT 9:00 P.M.
EASTERN TONIGHT RIGHT HERE ON
ABC.
>>> STILL AHEAD ON "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA," HOW TO CELEBRATE THIS
SEASON WITHOUT PACKING ON THE
POUNDS.
OUR DR. ASHTON DISHING OUT THE
LOW CALORIE ADVICE.
>> WHAT FUN IS THAT?R?chin,
but maybe not for people
with rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "UNJECTION™".
XELJANZ XR, a once-daily pill
for adults with moderate
to severe RA for whom
methotrexate
did not work well enough.
XELJANZ XR can reduce
pain, swelling
and further joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections like TB;
don't start XELJANZ if
you have an infection.
Taking a higher than recommended
dose of XELJANZ for RA
can increase risk of death.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections,
cancers including lymphoma, and
blood clots have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
and changes in lab results.
Tell your doctor if you've
been somewhere
fungal infections are common,
or if you've had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles. Fine for some.
But for you, one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about
XELJANZ XR.
An "UNJECTION™".
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
Thanks, Stef!
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Surprise!
No, I'm not gonna
get a date in this.
We had a lot of great
dates in this car.
Ugh, no. No, ew.
[Sneezing]
We had a lot of great
dates in♪♪his car.
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
♪
>>> IN TODAY'S WEEKEND DOWNLOAD
FOR MANY OF US, SELF-CONTROL
GOES OUT THE WINDOW.
THERE ARE WAYS TO INDULGE
WITHOUT SACRIFICING YOUR
WAISTLINE.
WE HAVE DR. ASHTON.
SHE JOINS US THIS MORNING WITH
ADVICE.
WE DON'T WANT TO FEEL DEPRIVED.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONLY
PERSON AT THE EVENT NOT EATING
THE THINGS, BUT YOU DON'T WANT
TO FEEL BAD ABOUT YOURSELF, AND
GUILTY AFTERWARDS FOR OVERDOING
IT.
HOW DO YOU DO THIS?
>> I THINK THE THING, EVA, IS
THIS IS A TOUGH SEASON.
IT'S KICKED OFF BY THANKSGIVING
AND WE HAVE A LOT OF EVENTS, A
LOT OF GET-TOGETHERS, PARTIES
AND WORK PARTIES AND IT IS HARD.
THE ADVICE I HAVE FOR PEOPLE IS
WORRY ABOUT THE REST OF THE YEAR
MORE THAN YOU WORRY ABOUT ONE
WEEK, ONE SEASON, ONE PARTY.
IF MOST OF THINGS ARE IN TRACK
FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR, YOU'RE
REALLY NOT GOING TO DERAIL
YOURSELF THAT MUCH IN ONE WEEK
OR ONE SEASON.
>> SO PART OF THE PROBLEM WITH
THE HOLIDAY FOODS IS THEY ARE
REALLY BAD FOR YOU.
THERE'S A LOT OF SUGAR.
THERE'S A LOT OF SALT.
THERE'S A LOT OF CALORIES.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DO YOU PICK AND CHOOSE?
>> HERE'S A LITTLE HACK I THINK
PEOPLE CAN TRY, AND PARTICULARLY
EFFECTIVE.
THEY WOEFUL -- WON'T FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE DEPRIVING THEMSELVES.
LET'S SAY YOU'RE CRAVING EGGNOG
OR CRAVING COOKIES.
HAVE A LITTLE, BUT HAVE A
LITTLE.
HAVE A MINI VERSION.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE THE
SERVING SIZE IN FRONT OF YOU.
YOU WERE EYEING THESE COOKIES.
THIS IS HOW THEY COME, BUT YOU
COULD GRAB SOMETHING HALF THE
SIZE SO YOU CAN HAVE YOUR CAKE
AND EAT IT TOO.
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT I CAN STOP
WHEN I TAKE A BITE.
THE PROBLEM FOR MANY OF US IS
THEY ARE LOADED WITH A LOT OF
CALORIES.
THE TRADITIONAL FOODS THAT YOU
FEEL LIKE YOU MUST EAT FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
>> I WOULD SAY LOOK FOR THINGS
YOU'RE EATING THE REST OF THE
YEAR.
YOU CAN STAY HEALTHY.
THIS IS MY GO-TO DESSERT BECAUSE
YOU GET THE SWEET, AND THE
ANTIOXIDANTS AND I'LL FINISH
THIS BOWL WHEN WE GOT OFF THE
AIR.
>> AND YOU DON'T FEEL BAD ABOUT
IT.
>> NO.
HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
>> THANK YOU, DR. ASHTON.
>>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
"POP NEWS." ASHTON.
"POP NEWS."
I have the power to lower
my blood sugar and A1C.
Because I can still
make my own insulin.
And Trulicity activates
my body to release it
like it's supposed to.
Trulicity is for people
with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
Trulicity isn't for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity
if you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if you have an
allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects
may include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea or insulin
increases low blood sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting, belly pain,
and decreased appetite,
which lead to dehydration and
may worsen kidney problems.
I have it within me
to lower my A1C.
Ask your doctor about Trulicity.
This is the Epson
EcoTank color printer.
No more buying cartridges.
Big ink tanks.
Lots of ink.
Print about...
this many pages.
The Epson EcoTank.
Just fill and chill.
[Coughs] Kim is now
demonstrating her congestion.
Save it, slimeball.
I've upgraded to Mucinex.
We still have 12 hours
to Australia.
Mucinex lasts 12 hours,
so I'm good.
Now move-
Kim nooooo!!
Mucinex has a patented tablet
that lasts 3x longer,
for 12 hours.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
I'm Tom Steyer and I approve
this message.
Climate is the number 1
priority.
I would declare a state of
emergency on Day 1.
Congress has never passed an
important climate bill, ever.
This is a problem that continues
to get worse.
I've spent a decade fighting and
beating oil companies...
Stopping pipelines...
Stopping fossil fuel plants,
ensuring clean energy across the
country.
How are we going to pull this
country together?
We take on the biggest challenge
in history,
we save the world and do it
together.
(Thud)
(Crash)
(Grunting)
(Whistle)
Play it cool
and escape heartburn fast
with TUMS Chewy Bites
Cooling Sensation.
♪ Tum tu-tu-tum tums ♪
In a world where everything
gets a sequel.
It's finally time for...
GEICO Sequels!
Classic GEICO heroes, starring
in six new commercials,
with jaw-dropping
savings.
Vote for your favorites at:
geico.com/sequels
Ahhh, which way do I go?!
I don't know, I'm voting
for our sequels.
With GEICO, the savings
keep on going
to a screen near you.
Not the leg!
You dang woodchucks!
GEICO Sequels.
Vote and enter to win today!
♪
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY GEICO.
15 MINUTES COULD SAVE YOU 15% OR
MORE ON CAR INSURANCE.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME FOR "POP NEWS."
JANAI IS HERE.
TRY NOT TO BE DISTRACTED BY THE
TWO WHITS OVER THERE.
>> AND ONE OF THEM WAS DANCING.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE.
>> IT WAS DEFINITELY HIM.
>> TIME FOR "POP NEWS," AND
WE'RE STARTING WITH SOMETHING
REALLY GOOD.
EDDIE MURPHY'S RETURN
TO "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" AFTER
35 YEARS, AND IT WAS HILARIOUS.
MURPHY PULLING OUT A REAL TOUR
DE FORCE RECOLLECTING SKITS LIKE
MR. ROBINSON'S NEIGHBORHOOD,
BUCKWHEAT AND GUMBY.
ALSO GETTING SOME HELP FROM A
REAL COMEDIAN FOR US, TRACY
MORGAN, DAVID CHAPPELLE AND
CHRIS ROCK DURING HIS MONOLOGUE.
>> WHAT A MOMENT WE'RE HAVING.
WHAT A MOMENT WE'RE HAVING.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING AT HALF OF
NETFLIX'S BUDGET RIGHT HERE ON
STAGE.
>> THANKS, NETFLIX.
>> NOT ME.
NOT ME.
I MADE ALL MY MEANS ON THE ROAD.
>> YOU MEAN TOURING?
>> NO, I GOT HIT BY A TRUCK.
>> YEAH.
DEFINITELY GOING TO WATCH THAT.
>> THE BRAIN POWER.
THOSE FOUR COMEDIANS ARE SO
AMAZE.
-- AMAZING.
>> YES, HILARIOUS.
>> TOGETHER IS INCREDIBLE.
>> AND LIZZO WAS LAST NIGHT'S
MUSICAL GUEST.
>> OH WOW.
>>> NOW TO A ROYAL MINI MIXER.
PRINCE GEORGE STEALING THE SHOW
AS FOUR GENERATIONS OF BRITISH
ROYALTY GOT TOGETHER TO PREPARE
CHRISTMAS PUDDING FOR THE ROYAL
BRITISH LEGION.
6-YEAR-OLD GEORGE EVEN MANAGING
NOT TO GET HIS SHIRT DIRTY.
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
HE CLEARLY GETS HIS BAKING
SKILLS FROM HIS MOM, KATE
MIDDLETON.
SHE REVEALED SHE MAKES BIRTHDAY
CAKES FOR THEIR KIDS FROM
SCRATCH.
ROYALS ARE JUST LIKE THEM.
>> YOU EVER WATCH "THE CROWN"?
EVERY TIME I SEE PICTURES OF THE
ROYALS NOW, I THINK OF "THE
CROWN."
>> I'M SURE THEY WOULD LOVE
THAT.
>> MY APOLOGIES.
>> EXACTLY WHAT THEY WERE GOING
FOR.
>>> SO NOW FOR THE UGLY
CHRISTMAS SWEATER, THE SEQUEL.
YOU MAY REMEMBER LAST CHRISTMAS
PALS HUGH JACKMAN AND JAKE
GYLLENHAAL TRICKED RYAN REYNOLDS
INTO WEARING THIS OUTFIT BY
TELLING HIM EVERYONE WAS GOING
TO WEAR AN UGLY CHRISTMAS
SWEATER.
REMEMBER, THEY DIDN'T.
FLASH FORWARD TO THIS YEAR, AND
HUGH REVIVING THE JOKE DONNING
THE SWEATER HIMSELF POSTING, I
CAN'T BELIEVE I AGREED TO WEAR
THE MATCHING UNDERWEAR TOO.
#THESWEATERRETURNS.
BUT THE JOKE THAT KEEPS ON
GIVING IS GIVING EVEN MORE.
REYNOLDS SHOWING IN THIS VIDEO,
HE GIFTED IDENTICAL SWEATERS TO
SICK CHILDREN IN THE HOSPITALS
FOR THE HOLIDAYS IN PARTNERSHIP
WITH THE SICK KIDS FOUNDATION.
A GREAT GIFT THERE, AND LOOK AT
THIS.
COME BACK OUT TO US, AND WE HAVE
ALL GOT FOOD.
>>> THIS IS BECAUSE TONIGHT
MARKS THE START OF HANUKKAH.
TRADITIONAL FOODS INCLUDE POTATO
LATKES AND JELLY DOUGHNUTS.
WISH OUR FRIENDS A HAPPY
HANUKKAH.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS LOT-KEYS,
BUT I WAS TOTALLY WRONG.
>> DID YOU FIND THAT OUT?
>> YES, I CONSULTED THE GOOGLE.
>> THE GOOGLE.
>> YOU WORK THE GOOGLE ON THE
INTERNET MACHINE.
IT NEVER LIES.
OH YEAH.
GOING IN.
>> I SHOULD MAKE THESE FOR MY
SON TONIGHT.
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
JANAI, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
GREAT "POP NEWS."
GREG, GREAT TO HAVE YOU.
>> GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> SORRY WE MADE OF YOU ALL
MORNING.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
I'M FED.
I'M FINE.
>> YOU'RE FED.
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND, EVERYBODY.
STAY TUNED FOR MARTHA.
♪
>>> 7 IS ON YOUR SIDE RIGHT NOW
WITH LIVE AND LOCAL NEWS FROM
WASHINGTON.
>>> GOOD MORNING, WASHINGTON.
METEOROLOGIST ALEX LIGGETT IS
HERE ON THIS BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
WE DO HAVE COLD TEMPERATURES
WITH A NICE SUNRISE, CHECK OUT
OUR CAMERAS, WHENEVER YOU WANT
ON WJLA.com.
THERE'S A BUNCH AND THEY LOOK
GREAT THIS MORNING, 48 DEGREES
UNDER PARTLY CLOUDY SKIES, JUST
A FEW CLOUDS, NOT QUITE AS COLD
WITH NO TEENS FOR THE MORNING,
26 IS THE OUTLYING SUBURBS, A
CHILLY START TO YOUR MONDAY.
NOW WE ARE WATCHING THIS BIG
SYSTEM IMPACTING THE SOUTHEAST
WITH THE AREAS UPWARDS OF 8 TO
10 INCHES OF RAIN AROUND
CHARLESTON, GEORGIA, SO YOUR
TRAVEL CONDITIONS ARE NOT GOOD
AS YOU GO THROUGH TODAY,
TONIGHT, AND MONDAY.
WE ARE STILL SEEING THIS
LINGERING PRECIPITATION FROM
THE CAROLINAS AND GEORGIA, HIGH
PRESSURE ON THE EASTERN
SEABOARD TOWARDS TUESDAY,
OVERALL, IT LOOKS LIKE SOME
GREAT CONDITIONS BY THEN, 2 TO
3 INCHES THROUGH SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA, HIGHER TEMPERATURES
ARE LOCALIZED FOR PORTIONS OF
GEORGIA AS WELL WITHOUT
WIDESPREAD HEAVY RAINFALL
EVENT, THOUGH AROUND YOUR WE DO
NOT ANTICIPATE ANY RAINFALL,
48, 50 DEGREES ON TUESDAY AND
WEDNESDAY, SO VERY DRY AND MILD
ACROSS THE REGION WITH TYPICAL
HIGHS INTO THE MID-40S, LOW 50s
FOR THURSDAY, FRIDAY AND
SATURDAY AND I DO BELIEVE THAT
THE NEXT CHANCE OF RAIN WILL
COME OVER THE WEEKEND.