>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
AS WE JOIN YOU THIS TUESDAY
MORNING MILLIONS ARE WAKING UP
TO A NEW STORM THREAT, AS THE
DEADLY SYSTEM BARRELS EAST.
>>> MULTIPLE TORNADOES TEAR
THROUGH THE SOUTH, KILLING AT
LEAST THREE PEOPLE, LEVELING
HOMES.
THIS SCHOOL COMPLETELY
DESTROYED.
ONE TWISTER LEFT A TRAIL OF
DESTRUCTION MORE THAN 60 MILES
LONG.
THE SAME SYSTEM NOW BRINGING
HEAVY SNOW AND RAIN.
NEW ALERTS THIS MORNING FROM THE
GULF TO NEW ENGLAND.
>>> IMPEACHMENT END GAME
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP BRACES FOR
THAT HISTORIC VOTE EXPECTED
TOMORROW.
WHAT OUR NEW POLL REVEALS ABOUT
THE NATION AND IMPEACHMENT.
>>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT --
A 14-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT IN THE
MURDER OF TESSA MAJORS JUMPING
OUT OF A CAR ON HIS WAY TO
SURRENDER.
THE MANHUNT THIS MORNING.
>>> MISSING MOM MYSTERY.
THE SEARCH INTENSIFYING FOR THIS
MOTHER OF TWO LAST SEEN DROPPING
HER 6-YEAR-OLD OFF AT SCHOOL.
SHE AND HER INFANT DISAPPEARING,
HER FIANCE'S PLEA AND WHAT
POLICE FOUND LEFT BEHIND.
>>> BRAZEN BURGLARY.
NEARLY $70 MILLION IN JEWELRY
STOLEN FROM THE
HEIRESS TO A FORMULA ONE
FORTUNE.
HOW THIS POST ON INSTAGRAM MAY
HAVE TIPPED OFF THE THIEVES.
>> WILL HE GET IT HERE?
YES!
>>> “BREES-ING” INTO THE RECORD
BOOKS.
SAINTS QUARTERBACK DREW BREES
MAKING HISTORY OVERNIGHT,
ROARING PAST PEYTON MANNING AND
TOM BRADY.
AND THE MOMENT HIS FAMILY
WATCHES IT ALL HAPPEN.
♪
>>> AND THE FORCE IS STRONG WITH
THIS ONE.
ALL THE STARS OUT FOR THE "STAR
WARS" PREMIERE, THE LAST FILM IN
THE EPIC SERIES.
NOW THE FIRST REVIEWS JUST IN,
AND WHAT HAPPENS WHEN KIDS GET
TO ASK THE QUESTIONS.
>>> AND GOOD MORNING AMERICA.
WHAT A SCENE, THAT "STAR WARS"
PREMIERE, THE FINAL INSTALLMENT
IN THE SKYWALKER SAGA.
>> IT'S BEEN 42 YEARS SINCE THE
FIRST "STAR WARS" HIT THE BIG
SCREEN.
LOOK WHO SHOWED UP LAST NIGHT.
SOME OF THE ORIGINALS LIKE MARK
HAMILL, AKA LUKE SKYWALKER AND
HARRISON FORD, AKA HAN SOLO.
>> GREAT TO SEE ALL THOSE FACES.
NEW STARS ALSO IN ATTENDANCE.
YOU SEE THEM THERE AND THE FIRST
REVIEWS ARE IN.
WE'LL TELL YOU ALL ABOUT IT
COMING UP.
>> THAT IS COMING UP.
>>> RIGHT NOW MILLIONS FACING
THAT WINTER STORM THREAT.
HEAVY SNOW, FREEZING RAIN FROM
THE MIDWEST TO THE NORTHEAST.
TORNADOES TURNED DEADLY IN THE
SOUTH.
ALEX PEREZ IS IN ALEXANDRIA,
LOUISIANA, WITH THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, ALEX.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD MORNING,
GEORGE.
TAKE A LOOK.
THIS WAS A SCHOOL.
I'M STANDING IN WHAT WAS A
CLASSROOM.
NOW COMPLETELY RIPPED TO SHREDS
BY THIS STORM.
YOU CAN SEE HERE'S A SCHOOL DESK
WHERE STUDENTS USED TO SIT.
SOME OF THOSE TOYS THAT STUDENTS
PLAY WITH HERE AND OVER HERE THE
REST OF THESE CHAIRS WHERE THE
STUDENTS USED TO BE COMPLETELY
UNDERNEATH ALL OF THIS DEBRIS.
ONCE THOSE STORMS ROLL THROUGH
HERE THEY QUICKLY LEFT A TRAIL
OF DESTRUCTION.
OVERNIGHT A FRIGHTENING FOOTAGE
OF A TORNADO TOUCHING DOWN IN
LOUISIANA.
ONE OF THE MANY DEADLY TORNADOES
WREAKING HAVOC ACROSS SEVERAL
STATES.
IN LOUISIANA, FORCEFUL WINDS
TURNING CARS ONTO THEIR SIDES.
THE ROOF OF THIS BUILDING
CRUSHED.
>> I THINK IT WAS ON LIKE 63
MILES AND, YOU KNOW, OFF AND ON,
OFF AND ON BUT AS IT GETS
DAYLIGHT YOU'LL SEE SOME REAL
DESTRUCTION.
>> Reporter: THIS SCHOOL RAVAGED
BY THE STORM.
THE ROOF RIPPED OFF.
NOW SCATTERED DEBRIS.
THESE VEHICLES CRUSHED.
DOWNED POWER LINES LITTERING THE
LANDSCAPE.
AUTHORITIES USHERING CHILDREN
AWAY SAFELY AS THEY WORK TO
CLEAR THE RAIN-SOAKED TERRAIN.
THE TORNADO ALSO RESULTING IN
THE DEATH OF A WOMAN TRAPPED IN
HER MOBILE HOME AS THE STORM
HIT.
>> I KNOW OF ABOUT THREE HOMES
THAT'S BEEN HIT.
>> IN MISSISSIPPI, TORNADOES
DESTROYING THIS CHURCH LEAVING
NOTHING BUT SCATTERED DEBRIS.
LIGHTNING ILLUMINATING THE
DAMAGE ON THIS HOME BELOW.
THE TORNADO DEMOLISHING THIS
ROOF, WHAT'S LEFT SCATTERED ON
THE FRONT YARD.
>> WE HAVE MULTIPLE HOMES THAT
HAVE BEEN DAMAGED.
A LARGE NUMBER OF RESIDENCES
WITHOUT POWER.
>> Reporter: IN ALABAMA,
AUTHORITIES ON THE SCENE AS
STORM DAMAGE THERE LEADING TO
TWO DEATHS AND MULTIPLE
INJURIES.
>> JUST TOTAL CHAOS.
WE HAD TO MAKE DUE THE BEST WE
COULD.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES
SCRAMBLING RELENTLESS RAIN AS
THEY WORK TO CLEAR THE AREA OF
UPROOTED TREES.
AND THE SHERIFF TELLS ME LUCKILY
ALL 18 STUDENTS WHO WERE INSIDE
OF THIS SCHOOL WERE ABLE TO GET
TO SAFETY AND THEY ARE OKAY.
NOW HE SAYS BEGINS A DIFFICULT
PROCESS OF ASSESSING THE DAMAGE
AND CLEANING ALL OF THIS UP.
MICHAEL.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE SO HAPPY
THEY'RE OKAY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, ALEX.
HERE IN THE NORTHEAST SNOW, ICE
AND RAIN LEADING TO DANGEROUS
CONDITIONS ON THE ROAD.
DOZENS OF SCHOOL DELAYS HERE IN
NEW YORK ALONE.
GIO BENITEZ IS NORTH OF US IN
DUCHESS COUNTY, NEW YORK, WITH
MORE.
GOOD MORNING, GEORGE.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU.
WE ARE SEEING THAT FREEZING RAIN
AND SNOW FROM OHIO TO NEW
ENGLAND.
WE ARE GETTING THAT FREEZING
RAIN RIGHT NOW, THAT MIX OF RAIN
AND ICE FALLING HERE.
WE KNOW IN 17 STATES RAIN, ICE
AND FLOOD WARNINGS, THEY ARE ALL
IN EFFECT RIGHT NOW THIS
MORNING.
I WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
VIDEO RIGHT NOW BECAUSE OVER THE
PAST 24 HOURS WE HAVE BEEN
SEEING ACCIDENT AFTER ACCIDENT
ESPECIALLY IN SNOWY CONDITIONS.
BUT IN THIS FREEZING RAIN, WE
ARE ALSO GOING TO BE SEEING
ACCIDENTS NOW.
HERE IN DUTCHESS COUNTY, ALL
OVER THE PLACE HERE WE ARE
SEEING THESE SHEETS OF ICE ON
THE GROUND.
WHEN YOU LOOK OUT ON THE ROAD
RIGHT NOW, YOU CAN ACTUALLY SEE
THAT BLACK ICE, THAT SLIPPERY
BLACK ICE.
IT IS INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS WHEN
YOU'RE DRIVING SO IF YOU HAVE TO
BE ON THE ROAD, JUST GIVE
YOURSELF A LITTLE EXTRA TIME.
BE CAREFUL.
GO A LITTLE SLOWER, MICHAEL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GIO, DANGEROUS OUTSIDE.
WE COME BACK INSIDE WITH GINGER.
HOW LONG DOES IT STICK AROUND
AND WHERE IS IT HEADED NEXT?
>> THIS STRETCH OF A BIG STORM
FROM LOUISIANA THROUGH A SEVERE
THUNDERSTORM WARNING JUST NOW
SOUTH OF DOTHAN, ALABAMA, UP
INTO THE NORTHEAST.
LET ME SHOW YOU THAT PINK THAT
YOU SEE ON THE RADAR.
THAT IS FREEZING RAIN.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'LL END UP WITH
THAT ICE SO PARTS OF
PENNSYLVANIA INTO CONNECTICUT
AND RHODE ISLAND.
LET ME TAKE YOU TO THE NORTHEAST
AND FOCUS ON THIS REGION, RIGHT?
WE'LL POP IT UP OUT OF THE
GROUND AND TELL YOU WHICH
HIGHWAYS SPECIFICALLY COULD BE A
PROBLEM.
WINTER STORM WARNING IN PLACE AS
GIO WAS HOLDING THAT SHEET OF
ICE, RAIN FALLS.
IT FALLS AS RAIN.
IT HITS A SURFACE SUBFREEZING.
WHAT WE DID IS TAKE THE
ADVISORIES AND TURN THEM ICY.
YOU CAN SEE THAT.
IF YOU ARE TRAVELING INTERSTATE
80 YOU'RE GOING THROUGH PARTS OF
IT.
87 AND 90 WHERE THAT MEETS YOU
INEVITABLY SEE INCH, THREE TO
FIVE INCHES HAPPENING NORTHWEST
OF THESE AREAS.
ON TOP OF ICE IT WILL BE TROUBLE
ESPECIALLY IF WE DO NOT DRY IT
OUT BECAUSE IT WILL BE SO COLD,
SOME OF THE COLDEST AIR WE'VE
SEEN, IT WILL FEEL LIKE ZERO IN
NEW YORK CITY ON THURSDAY
MORNING.
>> ROUGH TRAVEL WEEK FOR SO
MANY.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE HEAD TO WASHINGTON WHERE
THE HOUSE IS EXPECTED TO VOTE TO
IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP AS EARLY
AS TOMORROW AND NOW ON THE EVE
OF THAT HISTORIC VOTE OUR NEW
ABC NEWS/"WASHINGTON POST" POLL
SHOWS A NATION DIVIDED.
49% IN FAVOR OF IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT.
46% AGAINST.
BUT A MAJORITY BELIEVE PRESIDENT
TRUMP WAS TREATED FAIRLY BY
HOUSE INVESTIGATORS.
AND THEY EXPECT THE SENATE TO
GIVE HIM A FAIR TRIAL.
SO LET'S BRING IN OUR SENIOR
CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENT MARY
BRUCE THERE ON CAPITOL HILL
TRACKING IT ALL.
THE IN-FIGHTING ALREADY UNDER
WAY OVER WHO MIGHT BE CALLED TO
TESTIFY THERE.
>> Reporter: YES, CECILIA, THE
JOCKEYING WELL UNDER WAY.
WEEKS OF TESTIMONY TO GET TO
THIS VOTE IN THE HOUSE BUT OUR
POLL SHOWS IT ALL HAD VERY
LITTLE IMPACT.
OUR POLL SHOWS MOST AMERICANS
REMAIN RELATIVELY UNSWAYED AND
DEEPLY DIVIDED BUT THEY ARE
LOOKING AHEAD TO A FAIR TRIAL IN
THE SENATE AND SEVEN OUT OF TEN
AMERICANS IN OUR POLL SAY THEY
WOULD LIKE THE PRESIDENT TO LET
HIS TOP AIDES TESTIFY AND THAT
IS THE BIG X FACTOR.
DEMOCRATS ARE DEMANDING TO HEAR
FROM FOUR WITNESSES INCLUDING
THE PRESIDENT'S ACTING CHIEF OF
STAFF MICK MULVANEY AND FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON THEN THE PRESIDENT
PREVIOUSLY SAID HE WOULD LOVE
FOR HIS TOP AIDES TO BE ABLE TO
TESTIFY BUT REPUBLICANS DO NOT
WANT ANY WITNESSES HERE.
THEY WANT TO GET THIS OVER
QUICKLY AND SIMPLY MOVE ON.
NOW, LEADERS McCONNELL AND
SCHUMER ARE EXPECTED TO SIT DOWN
AT SOME POINT SOON AND HAMMER
OUT WHAT EXACTLY THIS TRIAL WILL
LOOK LIKE, CECILIA.
>> THEY'RE CERTAINLY WORKING ON
THAT.
MARY, ALL EYES RIGHT NOW ON
THESE DEMOCRATS.
MODERATE DEMOCRAT, PARTICULARLY
VULNERABLE IN THESE
TRUMP-LEANING DISTRICTS.
HAD HESITATED TO SAY HOW THEY
WERE GOING TO VOTE ON
IMPEACHMENT.
THEY'RE NOW MAKING THOSE VOTES
KNOWN.
>> Reporter: YEAH, CECILIA,
THESE MODERATE DEMOCRATS HAVE
BEEN UNDER INTENSE PRESSURE.
THE WHITE HOUSE AND THE
PRESIDENT'S ALLIES HAVE LAUNCHED
ESSENTIALLY A CAMPAIGN TO TRY TO
CONVINCE THEM TO BACK THE
PRESIDENT BUT NOW ONE BY ONE WE
ARE SEEING THESE DEMOCRATS
LINING UP BEHIND IMPEACHMENT.
THERE ARE NOW 17 -- AT LEAST 17
DEMOCRATS FROM TRUMP-LEANING
DISTRICTS WHO SAY THEY WILL
SUPPORT IMPEACHMENT.
ONE, CONGRESSWOMAN ELISSA
SLOTKIN GOT AN EARFUL FROM BOTH
SIDES AS SHE ANNOUNCED HER
DECISION BUT SAYS SHE HAS TO
STICK WITH HER PRINCIPLES EVEN
THOUGH SHE ADMITS IT COULD COST
HER A JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> MORE ON THIS FROM OUR CHIEF
WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT JON
KARL.
WE SAW MARY MENTION THAT NUMBER
IN THE POLL, SEVEN OUT OF TEN
AMERICANS BELIEVE THAT THERE
SHOULD BE WITNESSES, THE
PRESIDENT SHOULD SEND WITNESSES
FOR THAT SENATE TRIAL AND THE
PRESSURE COULD INCREASE NOW THAT
THE PRESIDENT'S LAWYER, RUDY
GIULIANI, IS OUT THERE GIVING
NEW INTERVIEWS, MAKING NEW
CONCESSIONS, PUTTING OUT NEW
EVIDENCE.
>> Reporter: SOME REMARKABLE
STATEMENTS BY RUDY GIULIANI JUST
SHOWING HOW INVOLVED HE WAS IN
THIS WHOLE UKRAINE SITUATION,
SPECIFICALLY REGARDING THE
FORMER AMBASSADOR TO UKRAINE,
MARIE YOVANOVITCH.
GIULIANI SAID HE SPOKE TO THE
PRESIDENT A COUPLE OF TIMES
ABOUT YOVANOVITCH, SAYING THAT
SHE WAS -- SHE SHOULD BE FIRED
ESSENTIALLY AND THAT THE
PRESIDENT PUT HIM IN TOUCH
DIRECTLY WITH THE SECRETARY OF
STATE, MIKE POMPEO, THAT HE HAD
MULTIPLE CONVERSATIONS WITH
POMPEO, THAT POMPEO REQUESTED
MORE INFORMATION, WHICH GIULIANI
PROVIDED.
KEEP IN MIND, GEORGE, RUDY
GIULIANI WAS HERE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE JUST LAST WEEK.
>> INCREDIBLE.
MEANTIME, JON, ON ANOTHER FRONT
THE PRESIDENT TAKING AIM AT THAT
PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE COMMISSION
WHICH IS CALLING INTO QUESTION
THE POSSIBILITY THAT THERE WILL
ACTUALLY BE GENERAL ELECTION
DEBATES IN THE FALL.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
SUGGESTING THAT HE MAY BYPASS
THE COMMISSION WHICH HAS HOSTED
EVERY PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE SINCE
1988 BECAUSE HE SAYS THE
COMMISSION IS FILLED WITH,
QUOTE, TRUMP HATERS AND NEVER
TRUMPERS.
GEORGE, THE PRESIDENT SAYS THIS
IS A QUOTE FROM A TWEET HE PUT
OUT AS PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES, THE DEBATES ARE UP TO
ME.
SO THIS COMMISSION HAS ALREADY
SET DATES AND LOCATIONS FOR THE
DEBATES BUT THE PRESIDENT IS
MAKING IT CLEAR THAT HE MAY BE
WILLING TO DEBATE BUT NOT
NECESSARILY WITH THAT
COMMISSION.
>> HE IS RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
THERE'S ONLY A DEBATE IF HE
SHOWS UP.
>> Reporter: THAT IS EXACTLY
RIGHT.
>> JON KARL, THANKS VERY MUCH.
MICHAEL.
>> THANK YOU, GEORGE.
>>> NOW WE GO TO BREAKING
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE MANHUNT FOR
THE KILLER OF THAT BARNARD
COLLEGE FRESHMAN.
OVERNIGHT POLICE HUNTING THROUGH
THE STREETS OF HARLEM FOR A
14-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT WHO ESCAPED.
ERIELLE RESHEF IS IN MORNINGSIDE
PARK WITH THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, ERIELLE.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING TO
YOU, MICHAEL.
THAT INTENSE MANHUNT UNDER WAY
IN HARLEM OVERNIGHT.
NOT FAR FROM WHERE WE'RE
STANDING IN THE PARK WHERE
18-YEAR-OLD BARNARD COLLEGE
FRESHMAN TESSA MAJORS WAS
STABBED TO DEATH LAST WEEK.
THE 14-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT WAS
EXPECTED TO TURN HIMSELF IN BUT
POLICE TELL US HE BOLTED FROM A
CAR AS IT CAME TO AN
INTERSECTION AND HAS BEEN
MISSING EVER SINCE.
OFFICERS FANNING OUT ACROSS
UPPER MANHATTAN IN THE DESPERATE
SEARCH FOR HIM.
POLICE WERE LED TO HIM BY A
13-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT WHO IS IN
CUSTODY.
>> ERIELLE, THAT 13-YEAR-OLD,
HE'S DUE IN COURT TODAY.
>> Reporter: HE IS DUE IN COURT
TODAY.
THAT MIDDLE SCHOOLER IS NOW
FACING CHARGES AS A JUVENILE.
WEAPONS POSSESSION, MURDER AND
ROBBERY CHARGES.
HE IS DUE IN FAMILY COURT LATER
THIS AFTERNOON WHERE THIS CASE
IS BEING HANDLED AND WE DO KNOW
THAT THAT 13-YEAR-OLD IS NOT
SUSPECTED OF BEING THE STABBER
IN THIS CASE BUT HE'S BEING HELD
WITHOUT BAIL, MICHAEL.
>> ERIELLE, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> WE TURN TO THAT BOEING
BOMBSHELL ANNOUNCING IT WILL
SUSPEND PRODUCTION OF ITS
TROUBLED 737 MAX PLANES IN
JANUARY AFTER, OF COURSE, THOSE
TWO DEADLY CRASHES.
THE DECISION EXPECTED TO SEND A
RIPPLE ACROSS THE AIRLINE
INDUSTRY AND THE ECONOMY.
DAVID KERLEY IS AT REAGAN
NATIONAL AIRPORT WITH MORE.
GOOD MORNING, DAVID.
>> GOOD MORNING, CECILIA.
STUNNING NEWS FOR THE 12,000
WORKERS AT BOEING.
FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER THE
COMPANY IS SHUTTING DOWN AN
ASSEMBLY LINE IN THE MIDST OF A
GROUNDING.
AND NEXT MONTH, JANUARY, THE
SILENCE WILL COME TO THE 737 MAX
LINE.
THIS IS THE PRODUCTION LINE
BOEING WILL SHUTTER, THE
ANNOUNCEMENT SENDING THE
COMPANY'S STOCK TUMBLING AND
RAISING CONCERNS FOR ALL THOSE
EMPLOYEES RIGHT BEFORE THE
HOLIDAYS.
>> MERRY CHRISTMAS, RIGHT?
>> Reporter: THE FASTEST SELLING
JETLINER EVER FOR BOEING
GROUNDED AFTER THAT SECOND
DEADLY CRASH NEARLY 350 KILLED
IN ALL.
BOEING CONTINUED BUILDING THE
MAX ABOUT TWO A DAY HOPING FOR
RECERTIFICATION AT LEAST BY THE
END OF THIS YEAR.
IT'S MADE SOFTWARE FIXES TO THE
SYSTEM THAT MAY HAVE CONTRIBUTED
TO THE CRASHES, BUT THE FAA
MAKING CLEAR LAST WEEK IT STILL
HAS QUESTIONS AND NO APPROVAL
WILL BE COMING THIS YEAR.
WITH NEARLY 400 OF THE BRAND-NEW
JETS STORED WHICH NEED PLENTY OF
MAINTENANCE TO KEEP THEM IN
WORKING SHAPE, BOEING DECIDED IT
COULDN'T STORE MANY MORE AND
MADE THE ANNOUNCEMENT.
QUOTE, WE HAVE DECIDED TO
PRIORITIZE THE DELIVERY OF
STORED AIRCRAFT AND TEMPORARILY
SUSPEND PRODUCTION OF THE 737
PROGRAM BEGINNING NEXT MONTH.
THE COMPANY SAYS FOR NOW IT WILL
NOT FURLOUGH NOR LAY OFF THOSE
12,000 WORKERS, KEEPING THEM ON
OTHER 737 PROJECTS OR ASSIGNING
THEM TO OTHER PRODUCTION LINES.
BUT WORKERS NOW FEELING THE
SCRUTINY THEIR COMPANY HAS FACED
FOR A YEAR.
>> AT SOME POINT BOEING HAS TO
STOP THE BLEEDING OF CASH AND
ARE THEY AT THE POINT WHERE THIS
WILL TRICKLE ALL THE WAY DOWN TO
THE WORKFORCE?
I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT.
>> Reporter: NO WORD ON HOW LONG
THIS TEMPORARY SHUTDOWN IS GOING
TO LAST BUT ON THE HEELS OF THIS
BOEING ANNOUNCEMENT SOUTHWEST
AIRLINES IS JOINING AMERICAN
AIRLINES IN CANCELING ALL MAX
FLIGHTS ALL THE WAY OUT TO
APRIL.
CECILIA.
>> HAPPENING AT SUCH A BUSY TIME
OF YEAR.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN TO AN INVESTIGATION
UNDER WAY INTO THIS ACCIDENT
NEAR SEATTLE.
A VAN SLAMMING INTO A ROSS
DEPARTMENT STORE DURING THE
HEIGHT OF HOLIDAY SHOPPING
INJURING 11 PEOPLE INCLUDING A
YOUNG CHILD.
POLICE BELIEVE THE VAN WAS
INVOLVED IN A SHOPLIFTING
INCIDENT AND IT WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE THE GETAWAY CAR.
THANKFULLY EVERYONE DID SURVIVE
AND THE SUSPECTS NOW IN CUSTODY.
>> THANK GOODNESS.
>>> WE TURN TO A HOLIDAY SHIP
AGO LETTER.
AS WE CLOSE IN ON CHRISTMAS
AMAZON IS BANNING THIRD PARTY
SELLERS FROM USING FEDEX FOR
GROUND SHIPPING AND REBECCA
JARVIS HAS THE DETAILS.
GOOD MORNING, REBECCA.
>> Reporter: HEY, GEORGE, YEAH,
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
THIS COMES AT A CRITICAL MOMENT
FOR ALL OF THOSE HOLIDAY
SHIPMENTS.
THIS IS THE KIND OF WEATHER THAT
CAN THROW YOUR ENTIRE MORNING
INTO A TAILSPIN.
IMAGINE WHAT IT MEANS FOR THE
BILLIONS OF PACKAGES TRYING TO
MAKE THEIR WAY TO AMERICA'S
DOORS ACROSS THE COUNTRY RIGHT
NOW IN THIS FINAL CRUNCH TIME
AHEAD OF CHRISTMAS.
WITH JUST ONE WEEK LEFT TO GET
THOSE GIFTS UNDER THE TREE A
POTENTIAL SPEED BUMP FOR YOUR
SPECIAL DELIVERIES.
AMAZON BEGINNING THIS WEEK
TEMPORARILY BLOCKING THIRD PARTY
SELLERS FROM USING FEDEX GROUND
SHIPPING FOR PRIME CUSTOMERS
CITING A DROP IN THE DELIVERY
PERFORMANCE.
THE RETAIL GIANT SAYS THE BAN
WILL LAST UNTIL THEY SEE
IMPROVEMENT.
FEDEX SAYS THE DECISION IMPACTS
ONLY A SMALL NUMBER OF SHIPPERS,
BUT LIMITS THE OPTIONS FOR THOSE
SMALL BUSINESSES ON SOME OF THE
HIGHEST DEMAND SHIPPING DAYS IN
HISTORY.
THE COMPANY ADMITS THEY HAVE
EXPERIENCED SOME WEATHER
CHALLENGES THIS SEASON AS WELL.
BUT SAYS OUR NETWORKS ARE
FLEXING AS DESIGN TO ACCOMMODATE
THE SURGE OF PACKAGES.
SO HOW DO YOU ENSURE YOUR
PACKAGES ARRIVE ON TIME?
FIRST KNOW THE DEADLINES.
WALMART, TARGET AND BEST BUY
ORDERS MUST BE PLACED BY EARLY
FRIDAY.
MACY'S BY NOON SATURDAY, AMAZON
AND NORDSTROM BY SUNDAY.
>> IF YOU'RE WILLING TO PAY A
LOT EXTRA, YOU COULD PRESUMABLY
SHIP SOMETHING AS LATE AS THE
23rd AND GET IT IN TIME FOR
CHRISTMAS.
THAT'S GOING TO COST YOU MORE,
THOUGH, AND YOU DO RUN THE RISK
OF UNFORESEEN DELAYS INCLUDING
WEATHER.
>> Reporter: AND FOR
PROCRASTINATORS CONSIDER APPS
LIKE SHIPT WHICH OFFERS A FREE
TWO-WEEK TRIAL FOR NEW MEMBERS,
ENOUGH TIME TO SCORE FREE SAME
DAY DELIVERY THROUGH DECEMBER
24th.
OR GIFT NOW WHICH LETS YOU
DELIVER A GIFT VIA EMAIL AND
TEXT.
THE RECIPIENT CAN CUSTOMIZE OR
EXCHANGE BEFORE IT GETS SENT.
THERE'S ALSO THE OPTION THIS
YEAR AND IT'S A NEWER ONE WHERE
YOU BUY ONLINE AND PICK UP IN
STORE.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT MACY'S IS
ALLOWING ITS CUSTOMERS TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF PLUS DOUBLE-CHECK
YOUR CREDIT CARD.
A NUMBER OF CREDIT CARDS ARE NOW
OFFERING FREE TWO-DAY SHIPPING
WITH SELECT RETAILERS.
GEORGE.
>> OKAY, REBECCA.
WE KNOW YOU'RE FOCUSED ON THE
HOLIDAY.
SEE YOU IN THE NEXT HOUR TO TALK
ABOUT REGIFTING.
>> I LIKE THAT.
CHANGE IT BEFORE YOU GET IT.
>> OPTIONS FOR OUR GIFTS.
>> OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
FIRST OF ALL I GOT TO GET IT.
THAT WOULD HELP.
YOU GUYS, WE TURN TO THAT
RECORD-SETTING NIGHT ON THE
FOOTBALL FIELD.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS WITH THIS
FIVE-YARD TOUCHDOWN PASS, THE
NEW ORLEANS SAINTS GREAT DREW
BREES BECAME THE ALL-TIME LEADER
IN PASSING TOUCHDOWNS HITTING
NUMBER 540, PAST HALL OF FAMER
PEYTON MANNING AND HE WASN'T
DONE YET.
HE ADDED A FOURTH TOUCHDOWN ON
THE NIGHT.
THERE HE GOES, JUST TO EXTEND
HIS RECORD A LITTLE BIT BUT HE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO KEEP ON GOING
BECAUSE THE MAN RIGHT BEHIND HIM
IS TOM BRADY WHO HAS 538 CAREER
TOUCHDOWNS AND BREES HAS A VERY
SPECIAL FAN IN THE STAND, HIS
WIFE AND CHILDREN.
THEY'RE THERE CHEERING HIM ON
ALONG WITH THE REST OF WHO DAT
NATION.
HE ALSO BROKE PEYTON MANNING'S
ALL-TIME PASSING YARDS RECORD A
LITTLE BIT OVER A YEAR AGO SO HE
OWNS THE RECORD BOOKS.
>> QUITE A MILESTONE.
>>> FOLLOWING A LOT OF OTHER
STORIES INCLUDING THAT MISSING
MOM MYSTERY.
A SEARCH FOR A TEXAS MOTHER AND
HER NEWBORN WHO VANISHED.
POLICE SAY WHAT WAS LEFT BEHIND
AND THE EMOTIONAL PLEA FROM HER
FIANCE.
>>> THE HEIST, $67 MILLION IN
JEWELRY REPORTEDLY STOLEN SO DID
AN INSTAGRAM POST TIP OFF THE
THIEVES?
WE'LL TELL YOU THAT BUT FIRST
LET'S HEAD BACK TO GINGER.
>> NEARLY 5 INCHES OF RAIN FELL
IN TENNESSEE.
YOUR LOCAL WEATHER IN 30
SECONDS.
>> Veronica: ANOTHER WET DAY,
BUT THIS TIME WE'RE TRACKING
RAIN SHOWERS.
WE'VE GOT A CHANCE UP UNTIL 3 TO
4:00 TODAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURE REACHED ABOUT
NOON TO 1:00.
50 TO 51 DEGREES IN DC.
COOLER CONDITIONS TO THE NORTH
AND WARMER CONDITIONS DOWN
SOUTH.
THE RAIN MOVES OUT.
WE'VE GOT COLDER AIR MOVING IN
OVERNIGHT AND WINDCHILLS IN THE
20S GOING INTO THE DAY TOMORROW.
THE HIGH FOR MID-WEEK, YOUR
WEDNESDAY 42.
THURSDAY, THE HIGH, 34.
COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON AND
DRY THROUGH THE
>>> A TUTORIAL FROM MICHAEL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪♪
Who will you make happy today?
Le Vie Est Belle.
The iconic fragrance.
Lancôme.
The must have gift
of the season.
At Macy's,
the gift destination.
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
Thanks, Stef!
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Surprise!
No, I'm not gonna
get a date in this.
We had a lot of great
dates in this car.
Ugh, no. No, ew.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
dates in this car.
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
[Sneezing]
♪♪
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
Spotlight.
And a drumroll, please.
[ hisses and snarls ]
[ bell chimes ]
Let's dance!
Try that.
Here you go.
I'll put it right here.
(gasps)
J.C. Penney.
Remember the little things.
>> VERONICA: DAMP, FOGGY TUESDAY
MORNING, AREAS OF FOG THAT WILL
BE THE CASE THROUGH THE MORNING
HOURS, NORTHWEST D.C.
TEMPERATURES COMING UP THROUGH
THE 30S TO 50 BY 10:00 THIS
MORNING.
50 DEGREES BY NOON.
RAIN CHANCES UP UNTIL THE
AFTERNOON HOURS.
THEN STARTING BLUSTERY AND MUCH
COLDER, JULIE?
>> JULIE: HERE THE MARYLAND
COLLEGE PARK TO 270, 25 MINUTES.
17 MINUTE RIDE INBOUND 5 FROM
CEDARVILLE ROAD.
OUTER LOOP TO BW PARKWAY, 19
MINUTE COMMUTE.
ACCIDENT ACTIVITY STILL IN
PLACE, SOUTHBOUND 286 NEAR HOOS
ROAD, FOLLOW POLICE DIRECTION.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
MEL?
>> MELANIE: YOU CAN GET
THE ABC 7 APP.
>> ADRIANNA:
AMERICA" BACK IN THREE MINUTES
We ordered 10,000 units.
That sounds good.
Pretty cool, huh?
They're speaking to Mom in
Japanese, and Mom hears them in
English.
♪
Can you understand me?
Yes, I can understand you.
Okay.
I have a lot of questions.
How do you guys fly? What does
Santa do in the summer?
Is Mrs. Claus a good cook?
Do you guys get presents?
Can you roller skate or ice
skate?
We are weakening our enamel
more often than we even realize.
Pronamel Repair can actively
help repair weakened enamel.
It takes minerals
and it drives it deep
into the tooth's surface.
Pronamel Repair takes it
to the next level.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
MARIAH CAREY'S HOLIDAY CLASSIC,
"ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS
YOU."
THE SUPERSTAR RETWEETING THAT
VIDEO AND CHRISTMAS IS COMING
EARLY FOR MARIAH.
THE SONG IS NOW BILLBOARD'S
NUMBER ONE SONG FOR THE FIRST
TIME EVER.
THE FIRST HOLIDAY SONG TO TOP
THE CHARTS SINCE THE CHIPMUNKS'
SONG 61 YEARS AGO.
>> STUCK IN OUR HEAD.
>> NOW STUCK IN YOUR HEAD.
THEY ALL GOT TOGETHER, VIRAL
MOMENT.
>>> A LOT OF HEADLINES INCLUDING
THAT WINTER STORM.
IT'S BARRELING EAST.
MILLIONS IN ITS PATH FROM THE
GULF TO NEW ENGLAND.
THE SYSTEM HAS LEFT A TRAIL OF
DESTRUCTION ACROSS THE SOUTH.
DOZENS OF REPORTED TORNADOES.
ALSO THIS MORNING, ONE DAY AWAY
FROM THE VOTE TO IMPEACH THE
PRESIDENT IN THE HOUSE.
THIS COMES AS A NEW ABC POLL FOR
"THE WASHINGTON POST" SHOWS THE
NATION PRETTY DIVIDED.
49% FOR, 46% AGAINST.
>>> JOE BURROW USED HIS SPEECH
TO DRAW HIS ATTENTION TO POVERTY
IN HIS HOMETOWN OF ATHENS, OHIO,
SAYING SO MANY IN NEED OF FOOD
AND SINCE THEN MORE THAN
$325,000 RAISED FOR THEIR LOCAL
FOOD PANTRY.
>> SPECIAL MOMENT.
>>> WE TURN TO THE URGENT SEARCH
FOR THAT MISSING MOTHER OF TWO
WHO MYSTERIOUSLY VANISHED ALONG
WITH HER NEWBORN DAUGHTER AFTER
DROPPING OFF HER OLDER CHILD AT
SCHOOL AND MARCUS MOORE IS IN
AUSTIN, TEXAS, WITH THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, MARCUS.
>> Reporter: CECILIA, GOOD
MORNING.
THE FBI AND THE TEXAS RANGERS
ARE NOW HELPING IN THE
INVESTIGATION INTO HEIDI
BROUSSARD AND HER YOUNG
DAUGHTER'S DISAPPEARANCE, SO FAR
THE EVIDENCE UNCOVERED ONLY ADDS
TO THIS DEEPENING MYSTERY.
POLICE SAY THIS IS THE LAST
KNOWN IMAGE OF MISSING MOM HEIDI
BROUSSARD, THE 33-YEAR-OLD
MOTHER SEEN IN THE SURVEILLANCE
PICTURE DROPPING OFF HER
6-YEAR-OLD SON AT AN AUSTIN
SCHOOL THURSDAY MORNING.
POLICE SAY SHE NEVER RETURNED TO
PICK HIM UP.
THIS MORNING, HER LOCATION IS A
MYSTERY AND THE FOCUS OF AN
INTENSE SEARCH BY AUSTIN, TEXAS,
POLICE.
POLICE HELICOPTERS EVEN HOVERING
OVER THE COUPLE'S APARTMENT
COMPLEX.
POLICE BELIEVE SHE RETURNED HOME
FROM THE SCHOOL WITH HER INFANT
DAUGHTER MARGOT IN TOW.
>> SHE WOULD NEVER DISAPPEAR.
SHE IS AN AMAZING MOM.
WE HAVE A 6-YEAR-OLD SON NAMES
SILAS.
BEAUTIFUL KID.
SHE WOULD NEVER LEAVE HIM.
>> Reporter: EVEN MORE ALARMING
HER FIANCE SAYS HER PURSE AND
WALLET WERE LEFT INSIDE HER
UNLOCKED CAR.
THE BABY'S DIAPER BAG WAS INSIDE
THE APARTMENT BUT BROUSSARD'S
KEYS AND CELL PHONE WERE GONE.
>> THERE IS NOTHING VALUABLE
MISSING.
HER PURSE AND HER WALLET AND
EVERYTHING WAS UP HERE.
HER CELL PHONE IS MISSING, IT'S
BEEN TURNED OFF.
>> Reporter: HER AUNT WRITING ON
FACEBOOK MY HEART IS SO HEAVY.
GOD, PLEASE KEEP THEM SAFE AND
BRING THEM HOME.
SHE IS A FASCINATING, WONDERFUL,
AMAZING PERSON, HAS A BUBBLY
PERSONALITY.
>> DROP HER OFF ANYWHERE.
I DON'T CARE.
MAKE SURE SHE'S SAFE, HER AND
THE BABY.
FEED THE BABY.
SHE'S ONLY 3 WEEKS OLD.
>> Reporter: SEARCH PARTIES HAVE
BEEN ORGANIZED INCLUDING ONE
GROUP PLANNING TO USE DRONES TO
SEARCH FOR THIS YOUNG MOTHER.
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT HERE IN
AUSTIN IS EXPECTED TO HOLD A
NEWS CONFERENCE LATER TODAY
WHERE WE COULD LEARN MORE IN
THEIR INVESTIGATION IN THIS
BAFFLING CASE.
MICHAEL.
>> BAFFLING, INDEED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> NOW TO THE MANHUNT UNDER WAY
AND A MULTIMILLION DOLLAR HEIST,
$67 MILLION WORTH OF JEWELRY
REPORTEDLY STOLEN FROM THE
LONDON HOME OF A FORMULA 1
RACING HEIRESS.
MAGGIE RULLI IS IN LONDON WITH
THE STORY.
GOOD MORNING, MAGGIE.
>> Reporter: WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOUR AVERAGE NEIGHBORHOOD
HERE.
THIS IS ONE OF THE MOST PRESS
TREJS MOST EXPENSIVE NEIGHBORS
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
KENSINGTON PALACE, HOME TO THE
FUTURE KING AND QUEEN IS JUST A
FEW DOORS DOWN.
NOW THE BIG QUESTION IS HOW
COULD THESE ALLEGED ROBBERS HAVE
GOTTEN PAST SUCH TOP NOTCH
SECURITY?
SHE'S A MODEL, TV HOST.
>> I'VE HAD A LIFETIME OF
PARTYING.
>> Reporter: AND HEIRESS WORTH
HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
BUT THIS MORNING TAMARA
ECCLESTON IS LEFT SHAKEN AFTER A
REPORTED $67 MILLION WORTH OF
JEWELRY WAS STOLEN OUT OF HER
LONDON HOME.
NEIGHBORS WITH PRINCE WILLIAM
AND KATE, HER 57-ROOM MANSION
SITS RIGHT ON LONDON'S COVETED
AND HIGHLY SECURE BILLIONAIRE'S
ROW.
POLICE BELIEVE THREE MEN BROKE
INTO THE BEDROOM SAFE AND
REPORTEDLY MADE OFF WITH RINGS,
EARRINGS AND AN $80,000 CARTIER
BANGLE.
IT HAPPENED JUST HOURS AFTER
TAMARA POSTED THIS PHOTO ON
INSTAGRAM SHOWING HER 5-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER BOARDING THEIR PRIVATE
JET AS THEY HEADED TO FINLAND
FOR THE HOLIDAY.
SECURITY EXPERTS WARN POSTS LIKE
THESE CAN TIP OFF ROBBERS TO
WHAT IS IN YOUR HOME AND WHEN
YOUR HOME MIGHT BE EMPTY.
KIM KARDASHIAN WAS MUGGED IN
PARIS JUST HOURS AFTER SHOWING
OFF $10 MILLION OF JEWELRY ON A
LIVE SNAPCHAT FEED.
>> ONE OF THE CHALLENGES WITH
SOCIAL MEDIA IS YOU MIGHT THINK
YOU'RE POSTING JUST A PICTURE,
JUST A PHOTO, BUT YOU'RE
ACTUALLY POSTING A LOT OF
METADATA ABOUT YOUR PICTURE.
WHERE YOU MIGHT BE OR WHO YOU
MIGHT BE WITH AND EXPOSING MORE
INFORMATION THAN YOU INTENDED
TO.
>> Reporter: AND TAMARA'S FATHER
SAYS HE THINKS THIS WAS AN
INSIDE JOB.
AS FOR NOW POLICE SAY THEY'RE
STILL INVESTIGATING AND KEEPING
AN OPEN MIND.
GUYS.
>> OKAY, MAGGIE, THANKS VERY
MUCH.
>>> THE LATEST FROM GABRIELLE
UNION.
SPEAKING ON CAMERA FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE SHE WAS FIRED FROM
"AMERICA'S GOT TALENT" AND
SENDING A MESSAGE TO BLACK WOMEN
TRYING TO MAKE IT IN
ENTERTAINMENT.
>> GABRIELLE UNION IS SPEAKING
OUT ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF
SPEAKING UP.
ON A PANEL YESTERDAY SHE DID NOT
MENTION HER RECENT TERMINATION
FROM "AMERICA'S GOT TALENT"
DIRECTLY BUT SHE DID TALK ABOUT
WHY IT'S ESSENTIAL TO BE A
LEADER AT THE WORKPLACE
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU ARE THE
ONLY, QUOTE, CHIP IN THE COOKIE.
GABRIELLE UNION SPEAKING OUT FOR
THE FIRST TIME WEEKS AFTER SHE
WAS OUSTED FROM HER SEAT ON THE
JUDGES' PANEL OF NBC'S HIT SHOW
"AMERICA'S GOT TALENT."
THE ACTRESS APPEARED IN NEW YORK
ON MONDAY AT A POWER OF
INCLUSIVITY AND THE WOMEN
LEADING THE CHARGE PANEL AND DID
NOT MINCE WORDS.
THE VIDEO SHARED ON INSTAGRAM BY
"NEW YORK" MAGAZINE'S "THE CUT."
>> DON'T FEED THE HAPPY ME
GROWTH THAT DOES THE BIDDING OF
THE STATUS QUO BECAUSE YOU'RE
AFRAID.
>> Reporter: WHILE NOT DIRECTLY
CALLING OUT NBC, THE FORMER
JUDGE WAS CANDID ABOUT THE FEAR
OF FACING POTENTIAL BACKLASH IF
SHE DID SPEAK UP.
>> DON'T ALLOW THEM TO CALL YOU
ANGRY WHEN SOMEBODY ELSE SAYING
THE SAME THING IS PASSIONATE.
IT IS SCARY, IT'S TERRIFYING.
THERE IS A SOLID CHANCE YOU MAY
LOSE YOUR JOB.
PERHAPS I SPEAK FROM EXPERIENCE.
>> Reporter: UNION WAS BOOTED
FROM THE HIT SHOW LAST MONTH
AFTER ALLEGING THE SHOW'S WORK
CULTURE WAS TOXIC.
ACCORDING TO "VARIETY" REALITY
SHOW EXECS IGNORED COMPLAINTS OF
RACISM ON THE SET AS WELL AS
UNION RECEIVING REPEATED NOTES
HER HAIR WAS TOO BLACK FOR "AGT"
AUDIENCES PROPELLING NBC TO
LAUNCH AN INTERNAL INVESTIGATION
INCLUDING A FIVE-HOUR MEETING
WITH UNION WHICH SHE CALLED
LATER PRODUCTIVE.
>> TIME TO STEP UP.
>> Reporter: THE ACTRESS ALSO
OPENED UP ABOUT HER EXPERIENCE
AS A MINORITY IN THE WORKPLACE.
>> AND I GET THAT WHEN YOU ARE
THE CHIP IN THAT COOKIE,
ESPECIALLY IN THOSE BOARDROOMS
OR THOSE OFFICE, THAT'S A LOT.
YOU GOT 87 JOBS AND YOU'VE BEEN
PAID TO DO ONE AND ALSO TRYING
TO NAVIGATE OFFICE POLITICS AND
DON'T WANT TO BE THE ONE WHO HAS
TO SAY EVERYTHING, BUT YOU'RE
THE ONE IN THERE.
FIND THOSE ALLIES AND KEEP THE
DOOR OPEN.
>> Reporter: A FORMAL
INVESTIGATION AT NBC NEWS IS
ONGOING LOOKING INTO UNION'S
ALLEGATIONS OF RACIST COMMENTS
AND A HOSTILE WORK ENVIRONMENT.
UNION HAS REBOUNDED QUICKLY.
YESTERDAY SHE LAUNCHED A NEW
HOLIDAY FASHION LINE IN
COLLABORATION WITH NEW Y
YORK & COMPANY AND USING THISES
IS A NEW PLATFORM, TERMINATION
AS MOTIVATION.
>> YOU CAN SEE THAT.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>>> COMING UP A VERY MARIAH
CAREY CHRISTMAS.
HOW "ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS
YOU" FINALLY HIT NUMBER ONE ON
THE CHARTS 25 YEARS AFTER IT WAS
RELEASED.
♪ DON'T CARE ABOUT THOSE
PRESENTS UNDERNEATH THE
CHRISTMAS TREE ♪
When we see you enter
through our doors,
We don't see who you're against,
or for,
Whether tomorrow
will be light or dark,
All we see in you, Is a spark
We see your spark in each nod,
each smile,
We see sparks in every aisle.
We see you find a hidden gem,
And buying diapers at 3am.
We see your kindness
and humanity.
The strength
of each community.
We've seen more sparks
than we can say.
About 20 million
just yesterday.
The more we look
the more we find,
The sparks that make
America shine.
Woman 1 OC:
This is my body of proof.
Man 1 VO:
Proof of less joint pain
and clearer skin.
Man 2 VO:
Proof that I can fight
psoriatic arthritis...
Woman 2 VO:
...with HUMIRA.
Woman 3 VO:
HUMIRA targets
and blocks
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes
to both joint
and skin symptoms.
It's proven
to help relieve pain,
stop further
irreversible joint damage,
and clear skin in many adults.
HUMIRA is the number one
prescribed biologic
for psoriatic arthritis.
AVO:
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Man 3 VO:
Ask your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
Woman 4 VO:
Go to HUMIRA.com
to see proof in action.
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THE SONG OF
THE SEASON.
WE'VE ALL BEEN SINGING IT FOR 25
YEARS BUT IT IS NOT UNTIL NOW
THAT MARIAH CAREY'S "ALL I WANT
FOR CHRISTMAS IS YOU" IS FINALLY
HIT NUMBER ONE ON THE CHARTS.
CHRIS CONNELLY IN LOS ANGELES.
OKAY, CHRIS, WHAT TOOK SO LONG?
>> WELL, GOOD MORNING, CECILIA.
AND, YEAH, IT SEEMS OVERDUE,
DOESN'T IT?
BECAUSE LET'S FACE IT,
RESISTANCE IS FUTILE.
BUT WHOEVER DOES YOUR POP
CULTURE HOLIDAY FAVORITE FROM
DARLENE LOVE TO THE WAITRESS,
CHIPMUNKS TO A CHARLIE BROWN
CHRISTMAS YOU KNOW THAT MARIAH
CAREY HAS GOT THIS SEASON ON
LOCK AND, YES, NOW SHE'S TOPPING
THE CHARTS.
♪ ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS
YOU ♪
♪
>>> FOR 25 YEAR ANSWER COUNTING
IT SOARED.
ITS YEARNED, IT'S BESTIRRED THE
YULETIDE SPIRIT THAT LIES WITHIN
EVEN THE GRINCHIEST OF HEARTS
♪ I JUST WANT YOU FOR MY OWN ♪
♪ MORE THAN --
>> Reporter: NOW FOR THE FIRST
TIME EVER IT'S THE NUMBER ONE
SONG IN AMERICA.
♪ BABY ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS
IS YOU ♪
>> Reporter: MARIAH CAREY'S "ALL
I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS YOU" HAS
RINIED OVER AIRWAVES SINCE ITS
1994 DEBUT AND THE MOST
DOWNLOADABLE SINGLE EVER.
A SONG THAT 24-YEAR-OLD MARIAH
CO-WROTE IN ABOUT AN HOUR.
♪ ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS ♪
>> I WANTED IT TO BE TIMELESS SO
THAT WAS THE GOAL AND I FEEL
LIKE THAT'S THE ONLY REASON --
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS WHY IT
TRANSCENDS DIFFERENT THINGS.
>> I DIDN'T WANT IT TO SOUND
LIKE SOMETHING THAT WAS NEW.
>> Reporter: IN 2018 IT WAS
PLAYED SOME 42,000 TIMES ON THE
RADIO AND STREAMED 185 MILLION
TIMES BUT FAILED TO GRAB THAT
COVETED NUMBER ONE BILLBOARD
SPOT UNTIL THIS WEEK.
♪ YOU BABY ♪
>> Reporter: CAREY CELEBRATING
THE NEWS WITH A SIMPLE TWEET
READING WE DID IT.
>> IT IS SALES AND STREAMING
COMBINED THAT PROPELLED IT TO
NUMBER ONE.
>> Reporter: THIS YEAR MARIAH
KICKING OFF THE SEASON EARLIER
THAN EVER.
>> SANTA.
>> Reporter: THE SECOND AFTER
HALLOWEEN WITH THIS INSTAGRAM
VIDEO.
>> IT'S TIME!
WHOO!
>> Reporter: AS THE WEATHER GETS
COLDER IT'S A BLAST OF WARM
EMOTION AS MARIAH BRINGS
EVERYONE A LITTLE HOLIDAY
HAPPINESS.
>> CHRISTMAS IS THE BEST.
SEE, I ACTUALLY BELIEVE THAT.
♪ ALL I WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS
YOU ♪
>> Reporter: THAT SONG IS
EVERYWHERE.
NOW, THE LAST CHRISTMAS SONG TO
HIT NUMBER ONE BEFORE MARIAH,
THE CHIPMUNK SONG BACK IN 1958.
THAT WAS 61 YEARS AGO.
ALL HAIL THE MIGHTY MARIAH,
GUYS.
>> MICHAEL HAS BEEN SERENADING
US WITH THE CHIPMUNKS SONG.
>> I NEVER GET TIRED OF MARIAH'S
SONG.
I NEWS -- I NEVER DO.
PUTS YOU IN A GOOD MOOD AND
REMINDS ME OF "LOVE ACTUALLY."
>> IT DOES.
>>> COMING UP, WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
KIDS GET TO ASK THE QUESTIONS.
WE'LL FIND OUT BECAUSE IT'S OUR
"STAR WARS" "PLAY OF THE DAY."
BE RIGHT BACK.
Great riches will find you
when Liberty Mutual
customizes your car
insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Wow. Thanks, Zoltar. How
can I ever repay you?
Maybe you
could free Zoltar?
Thanks, lady. Taxi!
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
These are real people,
not actors,
who've got their eczema
under control.
With less eczema,
you can show more skin.
So Roll Up Those Sleeves.
And help heal your skin
from within
with DUPIXENT.
DUPIXENT is the first treatment
of its kind that continuously
treats
moderate-to-severe eczema,
or atopic dermatitis,
even between flare ups.
DUPIXENT is a biologic,
and not a cream or steroid.
Many people taking DUPIXENT
saw clear or almost clear skin.
And, had
significantly less itch.
That's a difference
you can feel.
Don't use if you're
allergic to DUPIXENT.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur,
including anaphylaxis,
which is severe.
Tell your doctor about
new or worsening eye problems,
such as eye pain
or vision changes,
or a parasitic infection.
If you take asthma medicines,
don't change or stop them
without talking to your doctor.
So help heal
your skin from within,
And talk to your eczema
specialist about DUPIXENT.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Delicious high-fiber
Raisin Bran.
You sure you don't want
me to come with you?
I'm very sure.
Because I can.
(laughs)
Make good choices.
You make good choices.
I am.
Fiber is good for
DIGESTIVE HEALTH.
Good choices never
tasted so good.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran.
Get to Kohl's...
And take an extra 15 or 20% off!
Save on fleece for the family...
Throws and pillows - $15.29...
Plus - take an extra $10 off
your $50 jewelry purchase...
And save even more on fine
jewelry sets!
Plus - get Kohl's Cash!
Find new gifts at every turn -
at Kohl's.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH OUR "PLAY OF
THE DAY."
"STAR WARS" FANS ARE COUNTING
DOWN TO "THE RISE OF SKYWALKER."
THE CAST ATTENDED THE PREMIERE
LAST NIGHT BUT RIGHT BEFORE THEY
HIT THE RED CARPET JIMMY KIMMEL
GOT SOME FANS TO GRILL THE CAST
WITH SOME BIG QUESTIONS.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M WONDERING HOW THE FORCE
WORKS AND HOW IT'S SO POWERFUL.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HEY, REY, CAN YOU REALLY DO A
B
BACKFLIP OR ARE YOU JUST A LIAR?
>> U MUCHLT, UM, I'M A LIAR.
>> THIS IS FOR POE.
ARE YOU A BIG KID IN THIS MOVIE
OR ARE YOU GOING TO BE LIKE A
TINY CHARACTER?
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I ASKED
J.J. AS WELL.
>> I DON'T REALLY WATCH "STAR
WARS" ANYMORE BECAUSE I'M KIND
OF TOO OLD BUT I'LL WATCH IT.
>> GEE THANKS.
>> GOOD.
>> OH, BOY, KIDS ASK THE CRAZY
QUESTIONS.
"STAR WARS: THE RISE OF
SKYWALKER" FINALLY FLIES INTO
THEATERS ON FRIDAY AND IF THAT
KID IS TOO OLD, I'LL BE THERE.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE GOOD.
>>> COMING UP, YOUR GUIDE TO
REGIFTING.
WHEN IS IT OKAY AND WHAT'S THE
ONE GROUP YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE
THAT PRESENT TO.
THE DOs AND DON'Ts.
>>> "GMA'S" CONCERT SERIES
SPONSORED BY CARMAX.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
Count down to Christmas at the
Feel the Rush Sale at JCPenney!
Shop the season's BEST gifts...
like Levi's (for him and her)
jewelry...
and 25-35% off kitchen
electrics!
Or get an Extra 20% off NOW with
your JCPenney Credit Card.
And feel
the rush at JCPenney!
With the savings rates offered
at some banks,
your money almost
seems like it's frozen.
But not here.
With Capital One, you can open
a new savings account
in about 5 minutes
and earn five times
the national average.
Open one from here.
Or here - in a Capital One Café.
Plus, there are no fees
or minimums
on savings or checking accounts
because that's how it should be.
This is banking reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
["White Christmas" -
performed by The Drifters]
♪
(Dad)
Woah!
What do you think?
[tries speaking Korean]
Pecan Nuts?
(Woman) [yelling in Korean]
Honey, please do it well,
do it well.
(Dad)
Maple Syrup?
(Store Clerk)
No.
(Dad)
Thank you, I appreciate it.
No maple?
Alright, alright. Thank you.
(Daughter)
Come on, slowpoke!
♪
Yes!
(Dad)
Thank you.
Come on, slowpoke.
♪
(Daughter)
Merry Christmas!
(Mom)
Awe, thank you, sweetie.
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA."
I'VE HAD A LOT OF ANIMALS
PLAYING SOCCER IN THIS MOMENT
BUT NOT A TURKEY.
YEAH, THAT IS A TURKEY PLAYING
SOCCER.
OR AT LEAST TOUCHING THE BALL.
WE THOUGHT THAT WAS SO
ENTERTAINING.
BRECKENRIDGE HAD 53 INCHES OF
SNOW IN JUST SEVEN DAYS.
THAT MAKES FOR SOME GREAT
SNOWBOARDING AND SKIING.
MORE MOISTURE BUT A BIG PUSH OF
MILD AIR GOING INTO THE HOLIDAY
WEEK NEXT WEEK.
SOME WARMER THAN AVERAGE
ESPECIALLY GREAT LAKES THROUGH
TEXAS.
COMING UP HERE A HEALTH ALERT
FOR YOU ON "GMA."
THE NEW STUDY ABOUT THE LINK
BETWEEN E-CIGARETTES AND LUNG
DISEASE.
PLUS, MARVELOUS MAKEOVER.
HOW THE STAR OF "SILICON VALLEY"
TRANSFORMED INTO SUPERHERO
SHAPE.
I INTERVIEWED HIM WHEN HE HAD
THAT OUTFIT ON ON THE LEFT.
HE DID NOT LOOK LIKE THAT.
>>> THE WONDERFUL JAMIE FOXX
LIVE.
>> MELANIE: I AM MELANIE
HASTINGS.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
CHRISTMAS JUST OVER A WEEK AWAY,
POLICE IN PRINCE GEORGE'S NEED
YOUR HELP TRACKING DOWN A
SUSPECT CAUGHT STEALING A
PACKAGE FROM A PORCH.
RHODE ISLAND AVENUE AND
RIVERDALE PARK.
TRY SHIPPING PACKAGES TO YOUR
JOB.
ALSO SEND THEM TO A NEIGHBOR IF
YOU KNOW THEY'LL BE HOME WHEN
YOU WON'T BE.
>> MELANIE: WORLD SERIES MVP
AGREED TO SEVEN-YEAR DEAL WORTH
245 MILLION DOLLARS.
SHOULD KEEP HIM IN A NAT'S
JERSEY REST OF HIS CAREER.
>> VERONICA: ANOTHER DREARY
START.
WE HAVE A WHOLE LOT OF THIS, FOG
ACROSS YOUR AREA.
BUDGET EXTRA TIME.
DRIZZLE, TOO.
WE ARE GOING TO SEE LITTLE BIT
IN THE WAY OF RAIN LATE MORNING
RIGHT THROUGH YOUR AFTERNOON
HOURS.
CHECK OUT THE HOURLY
TEMPERATURES, 11:00, 51.
49 BY 2:00.
FALLING TEMPERATURES AND
FREEZING WINDS FOR YOUR
AFTERNOON COLDER AIR EXPECTED TO
MOVE IN WEDNESDAY AND THURSDAY
AND FRIDAY.
JULIE?
>> JULIE: A 60 MINUTE RIDE
INBOUND GERMANTOWN TO THE LANE
DIVIDE.
LAST 5-10 MINUTES, JUMP FROM 55
TO AN HOUR.
SOUTHBOUND 270.
CRASH REPORTED NEAR 29 AT
LOCKWOOD DRIVE.
DEFINITELY HAVING DELAYS,
TRAFFIC DELAYS OUT OF WHITE OAK.
FINALLY RIVER ROAD.
CRASH STILL BLOCKING THIS RAMP.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
BACK TO YOU.
>> MELANIE: JULIE, THANK YOU,
GET
ANY TIME WITH THE ABC 7 APP.
>> ADRIANNA: "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA" BACK IN TWO MINUTES ON
ABC 7 OR STAY WITH WJLA 24/7
NEWS FOR THE LATEST LOCAL NEWS
ON "GOOD MORNING WASHINGTON."
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
IT'S 8:00 A.M.
MULTIPLE TORNADOES KILL AT LEAST
THREE PEOPLE.
A SCHOOL DESTROYED.
ONE TWISTER LEFT A TRAIL OF
DESTRUCTION MORE THAN 60 MILES
LONG.
THE SAME SYSTEM IS NOW BRINGING
HEAVY SNOW AND FREEZING RAIN
FROM THE MIDWEST TO NEW ENGLAND.
>>> AND NEW OVERNIGHT
IMPEACHMENT SHOWDOWN AS THE
PRESIDENT BRACES FOR THAT VOTE
EXPECTED TOMORROW.
WHAT OUR NEW POLL REVEALS ABOUT
THE NATION AND IMPEACHMENT.
>>> NEW THIS MORNING, THE
GROUNDBREAKING STUDY DIRECTLY
LINKING VAPING AND RISK OF LUNG
ILLNESS.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW.
>>> ALSO THIS MORNING, THE NEW
HEADLINE ABOUT CHILI PEPPERS AND
YOUR DIET.
COULD EATING THEM REGULARLY CUT
YOUR HEART DISEASE AND STROKE
RISK IN HALF?
>>> SHOCKING BODY
TRANSFORMATION.
THE ACTOR YOU KNOW FROM "SILICON
VALLEY" AND "THE BIG SICK" AS HE
READIES TERROR A NEW ROLE.
IT TOOK A YEAR TO GET IN SUCH
GREAT SHAPE.
HOW HE DID IT AND WHAT THE
TRAINER BEHIND THE
TRANSFORMATION IS TELLING US
THIS MORNING.
♪
>>> AND OUT OF THIS GALAXY, THE
BLOCKBUSTER PREMIERE OF THE
FINAL FILM AFTER 42 YEARS OF
"STAR WARS."
HARRISON FORD AND BILLY DEE
WILLIAMS POSING TOGETHER ON THE
BLUE CARPET.
MARK HAMILL, CHEWBACCA AND THE
DROIDS ALL THERE, WHAT J.J.
ABRAMS TOLD THE AUDIENCE INSIDE
THE THEATER AND THE MOMENT JOHN
BOYEGA TOLD US WHAT HE'S TAKING
IN TO WATCH THE FINAL FILM.
OSCAR ISAAC SAYING --
>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
♪
>>> GOOD MORNING, AMERICA.
GOOD MORNING TO OSCAR, THE
TALENTED ACTOR AND YOU KNOW
WHAT, WE APPRECIATE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US ON THIS
TUESDAY MORNING.
>> YEAH.
HERE'S A COUNTDOWN FOR YOU NOT
TO SCARE YOU.
CHRISTMAS IS JUST EIGHT DAYS
AWAY.
>> OOH.
>> SOME OF THOSE GIVES YOU'RE
ABOUT TO GET MIGHT NOT HIT THE
MARK SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
WE'LL TELL YOU HOW TO REGIFT THE
RIGHT AND THE WRONG WAY.
>> THAT IS COMING UP.
>>> NEWS TO GET TO INCLUDING
THAT MAJOR STORM THAT'S BRINGING
SNOW AND RAIN TO THE NORTHEAST.
DEADLY TORNADOES IN THE SOUTH.
WANT TO GO BACK TO ALEX PEREZ IN
LOUISIANA WITH THE LATEST.
GOOD MORNING, ALEX.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD MORNING
AGAIN, GEORGE.
THIS STORM VERY QUICKLY LEFT A
PATH OF DESTRUCTION.
NOW, THIS WAS A SCHOOL, I'M
STANDING IN WHAT WAS A CLASSROOM
BUT YOU CAN SEE IT'S BEEN
COMPLETELY RIPPED TO SHREDS.
NOW, I WANT YOU TO TAKE A LOOK
AROUND ME.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU A DIFFERENT
ANGLE.
YOU CAN SEE FROM THIS WIDER SHOT
JUST HOW POWERFUL THIS STORM
WAS, COMPLETELY DESTROYING THIS
BUILDING.
NOW, THERE WERE SOME 27 REPORTED
TORNADOES ACROSS THREE STATES.
NOW HERE LUCKILY AT THIS SCHOOL
AUTHORITIES TELL US ALL 18
STUDENTS WHO WERE INSIDE WERE
ABLE TO GET TO SAFETY AND
THANKFULLY ARE ALL OKAY.
BUT THIS STORM IS NOW MOVING
EAST AND IT'S EXPECTED TO CREATE
PROBLEMS ALONG THE WAY AND,
GEORGE, THE CLEANUP HERE, WELL,
YOU CAN SEE HASN'T EVEN STARTED
YET.
ALL OF THAT STILL AHEAD FOR THIS
COMMUNITY.
GEORGE.
>> WE SURE CAN SEE THAT.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WE HEAD TO WASHINGTON NOW
WHERE THE HOUSE IS EXPECTED TO
VOTE TO IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP
AS EARLY AS TOMORROW AND NOW ON
THE EVE OF THAT HISTORIC VOTE
OUR NEW ABC NEWS/"WASHINGTON
POST" POLL SHOWS A DIVIDED
NATION.
49% IN FAVOR OF IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT.
46% AGAINST IT.
BUT A MAJORITY DO BELIEVE THE
PRESIDENT WAS TREATED FAIRLY BY
HOUSE INVESTIGATORS AND THEY
EXPECT A -- THE SENATE TO GIVE
HIM A FAIR TRIAL SO BACK OVER TO
OUR SENIOR CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MARY BRUCE THERE
ON CAPITOL HILL.
GOOD MORNING AGAIN, MARY.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING,
CECILIA.
WELL, AFTER WEEKS OF TESTIMONY
HERE AND FIERCE DEBATE, OUR POLL
SHOWS THAT AMERICANS REMAIN
RELATIVELY UNSWAYED ON THE ISSUE
OF IMPEACHMENT.
DESPITE THE STALEMATE AMERICANS
ARE LOOKING FOR A FAIR TRIAL IN
THE SENATE AND SEVEN IN TEN
AMERICANS ACCORDING TO OUR NEW
POLL SAY THEY WOULD LIKE THE
PRESIDENT TO ALLOW HIS TOP AIDES
TO TESTIFY IN THE SENATE TRIAL.
THAT IS THE BIG POINT OF
CONTENTION HERE RIGHT NOW.
DEMOCRATS ARE DEMANDING TO HERE
FROM FOUR LIVE WITNESSES
INCLUDING HIS CHIEF OF STAFF
MICK MULVANEY AND FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER JOHN
BOLTON BUT THAT IS NOT WHAT
REPUBLICANS WANT.
THEY DON'T WANT TO HEAR FROM ANY
WITNESSES AT ALL LOOKING FOR A
QUICK TRIAL SO THAT THEY CAN
SIMPLY MOVE ON FROM ALL OF THIS.
NOW THE LEADERS IN THE SENATE,
LEADER McCONNELL AND SCHUMER ARE
EXPECTED TO SIT DOWN SOMETIME
SOON AND TRY TO HAMMER OUT
EXACTLY WHAT THE TRIAL IS GOING
TO LOOK LIKE.
CECILIA.
>> WE ARE JUST HOURS AWAY FROM A
BIG DAY.
MARY, THANKS A LOT.
>>> CECILIA, NOW TO THE FIRST
LONG-TERM STUDY LINKING VAPING
WITH AN INCREASED RISK OF LUNG
DISEASE FINDING PEOPLE WHO USE
E-CIGARETTES ARE 30% MORE LIKELY
TO DEVELOP CHRONIC LUNG DISEASES
INCLUDING ASTHMA, BRONCHITIS AND
EMPHYSEMA THAN PEOPLE WHO DON'T
VAPE.
THE STUDY FINDING MANY PEOPLE
VAPE AND SMOKE REGULAR
CIGARETTES WHICH MORE THAN
TRIPLES THE RISK OF DEVELOPING
LUNG DISEASES.
>> OKAY, WE'VE GOT BIG NEWS NOW
ABOUT RED HOT CHILI PEPPERS, NOT
THE BAND.
A NEW STUDY PUBLISHED IN THE
JOURNAL OF AMERICAN COLLEGE OF
CARDIOLOGY SHOWS EATING THEM
REGULARLY COULD BE LINKED TO A
LOWER RISK OF DEATH FROM HEART
DISEASE AND STROKE.
THE STUDY FOLLOWING MORE THAN
20,000 PEOPLE AND TOOK PLACE
OVER THE COURSE OF EIGHT YEARS
IN ITALY WHERE CHILI PEPPER IS A
COMMON INGREDIENT SO THIS IS
GOOD NEWS FOR THOSE OF US WHO
LIKE OUR FOOD SPICY.
>> YOU LIKE SPICY FOOD.
>> DEFINITELY.
THE HOTTER THE BETTER.
>> ON PIZZA SO ITALY THE PERFECT
PLACE TO GO.
>>> THE RADICAL TRANSFORMATION.
HOW THE STAR FROM "SILICON
VALLEY" GOT INTO SUPER SHAPE.
>> THE STAR OF "JUST MERCY" IS
HERE, JAMIE FOXX.
HE IS AWAKE.
HE WAS AWAKE.
>> HE'S STILL AWAKE.
>>> PLUS, ANDY GRAMMER IS HERE
PERFORMING ONE OF HIS BIGGEST
HITS.
EXCITED FOR ALL OF IT.
WE
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
When you've crossed Fruit of
the Loom off your list,
you know your holiday
shopping is complete.
It's time to celebrate.
♪ ♪
♪
Everything your trip needs,
for everyone you love.
Expedia.
["I Feel Love"
by Sam Smith]
for everyone you love.
Save on last minute
gifts with Target HoliDeals!
Save on Samsung TVs.
Save on Toys.
Save on Sweaters for
the Family and more.
Doors open until
10PM Christmas Eve.
Only at Target.
Mike Bloomberg's never been
afraid of tough fights,
the ones that make a true
difference in people's lives.
And Mike's won them, which is
important right this minute,
because if he could beat
America's biggest gun lobby,
helping pass background check
laws and defeat NRA backed
politicians across this
country, beat Big Coal,
helping shut down hundreds of
polluting plants
And Beat Big tobacco,
helping pass laws to save the
next generation from addiction.
All against big odds
you can beat
him.
I'm Mike Bloomberg and I
approve this message.
If there's gonna be a sticker on
your car,
it has to mean something.
So we make sure THIS means
something.
That we've done everything -
to make your shopping,
test-driving and car-buying
experience
the way it should be.
CarMax.
[music playing]
♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA" AND WE
HAVE AN EXCITED TUESDAY AUDIENCE
HERE WITH US THIS MORNING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THEY SHOULD BE EXCITED BECAUSE
WE HAVE JAMIE FOXX HERE.
THAT'S COMING UP JUST AHEAD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TOMORROW HIS "JUST MERCY"
CO-STAR MICHAEL B. JORDAN WILL
BE HERE LIVE.
WE CANNOT WAIT FOR THAT ALSO BUT
NOW CANNOT WAIT FOR SOME "POP
NEWS" WITH SARA HAINES.
>> YES, GOOD MORNING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE BEGIN WITH A "POP NEWS"
EXCLUSIVE.
WE ARE EXCITED TO ANNOUNCE THE
PERFORMERS WHO WILL BE TAKING
THE STAGE RIGHT HERE IN TIMES
SQUARE DURING DICK CLARK'S NEW
YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE WITH RYAN
SEACREST 2020.
POST MALONE WILL BE MAKING HIS
TIMES SQUARE DEBUT AND SO WILL
GLOBAL PHENOMENON BTS.
COUNTRY MUSIC SUPERSTAR SAM HUNT
IS ALSO PERFORMING AND THE ONE
AND ONLY ALANIS MORISSETTE WILL
TAKE THE STAGE, YEAH, THE CAST
OF THE HIT BROADWAY MUSICAL
"JAGGED LITTLE PILL."
>> VERY COOL.
>> NEW YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE WITH
CELEBRATIONS FROM NEW YORK CITY
TO L.A. TO NEW ORLEANS AND ALL
HAPPENS ON DECEMBER 31st AT
8:00 P.M. EASTERN RIGHT HERE ON
ABC.
THAT WAS THE EXCLUSIVE PART.
>>> AND NOW TO A GALAXY NOT SO
FAR AWAY, HOLLYWOOD.
STARS COMING OUT IN FULL FORCE
FOR THE PREMIERE OF "STAR WARS:
THE RISE OF SKYWALKER," THE BLUE
CARPET WAS FULL OF FAMILIAR
FACES LIKE MARK HAMILL,
CHEWBACCA, R2-D2.
C3PO AND CHECK OUT THIS REUNION
BETWEEN TWO SMOOTH TALKING
SMUGGLERS, HAN SOLO AND LANDO
CALRISSIAN.
>> YES.
>> AKA HARRISON FORD AND BILLY
DEE WILLIAMS, OF COURSE, STARS
DAISY RIDLEY, ADAM DRIVER ALSO
HIT THE CARPET BUT CAUGHT UP
WITH JOHN BOYEGA WHO TOLD US HOW
HE PREPARED TO TAKE IN THE
EMOTIONAL LAST INSTALLMENT OF
THIS TRILOGY.
>> I GOT MY OWN SNACKS BECAUSE I
AIN'T GOING OUT LIKE THAT.
I GOT A BIG BAG SINCE I WENT TO
7-ELEVEN AND GOT ALL MY SNACKS
AND ABOUT TO GO IN, POPCORN, I
GOT SOME HARIBOS.
ALL SORTS OF STUFF.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> I THOUGHT YOU GUYS COULD
SNACK AS WELL.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> INSIDE DIRECTOR J.J. ABRAMS
TOLD THE AUDIENCE IT WAS
TERRIFYING TO INTRODUCE THEM TO
THIS FINAL FILM BUT TURNS OUT HE
HAD NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
THE MOVIE'S ALREADY EARNING
PRAISE WITH EARLY REVIEWS
CALLING IT PHENOMENAL, HOPEFUL
AND BEAUTIFUL.
"THE RISE OF SKYWALKER" SOARS
INTO THEATERS THIS FRIDAY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> I'M CALLING THESE DELICIOUS.
>> THESE, YOU GUYS, I WIN POINTS
THROUGH THE STOMACH.
>> WANT A SWEDISH FISH.
>> I HAD NO IDEA THEY HWOULD BE
THAT MUCH OF A HIT.
>>> UNLESS YOU'RE LIVING UNDER A
ROCK ON TATOOINE, OH, MY GOSH,
I'M GOING DOWN WITH THE "STAR
WARS" FANS.
YOU'VE SEEN HOW THE INTERNET HAS
FALLEN IN LOVE WITH BABY YODA
FROM "MANDALORIAN."
THE FORCE IS STRONG AT A
HOSPITAL IN PENNSYLVANIA.
CHECK OUT THESE SWEET LITTLE
NEWBORNS DRESSED UP AS REAL-LIFE
BABY YODAS.
THEIR ONESIES SAYING, CUTE, I AM
AND MERRY, I MUST BE.
THE HOSPITAL TELLING US THAT
IT'S THEIR ANNUAL TRADITION TO
DRESS THE BABIES IN THE NURSERY
IN FESTIVE ATTIRE AROUND THE
HOLIDAYS.
THIS YEAR THE BABIES ARE, QUOTE,
OUT OF THIS GALAXY CUTE.
NOT AGREE MORE, WE COULD.
>> OH, WOW.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW, SARA.
>> WE HAVE TO ADMIT MY BABY YODA
IS BETTER THAN MY CHEWBACCA.
[ MAKING CHEWBACCA SOUNDS]
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY, NEWS PEOPLE, TAKE IT
AWAY.
>> THAT'S "POP NEWS," EVERYBODY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
ALL RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> NOW TO OUR "GMA" COVER STORY
AND THAT STUNNING TRANSFORMATION
ACTOR KUMAIL NANJIANI REVEALING
HOW HE GOT INTO SUPERHERO SHAPE
FOR MARVEL'S "THE ETERNALS
COMPLETELY MAKING OVER HIS BODY.
WILL REEVE WITH THE DETAILS.
>> THIS IS A GLOW-UP.
THROWING UP A SHIRTLESS PICTURE
ON INSTAGRAM THAT GRABBED
EVERYONE'S ATTENTION BUT THE
ACTOR WAS QUICK TO POINT OUT
THAT HE HAD MAJOR RESOURCES AND
AN ELITE TEAM TO GET HIM TO THIS
VERY SHREDDED POINT.
THIS MORNING, AN INCREDIBLE
TRANSFORMATION FROM ACTOR KUMAIL
NANJIANI KNOWN FOR HIS COMIC
TIMING IN "SILICON VALLEY."
>> IT'S ME.
>> Reporter: HIS POIGNANT HUMAN
IN "THE BIG SICK."
IS REVEALING AN INCREDIBLE
TRANSFORMATION.
THE ACTOR POSTING WHAT HE CALLED
A THIRSTY SHIRTLESS SHOWING OFF
HIS SUPERHERO BODY BUILT FOR AN
UPCOMING MARVEL MOVIE.
IT SET THE INTERNET ON FIRE WITH
TONS OF TWEETS AND MEMES BUT
NANJIANI HIMSELF DEFLECTED THE
CREDIT TO HIS TRAINERS AND
NUTRITIONISTS WRITING I WOULD
NOT HAVE BEEN ABLE TO DO THIS IF
I DIDN'T HAVE A FULL YEAR WITH
THE BEST TRAINERS AND
NUTRITIONISTS PAID FOR BY THE
BIGGEST STUDIO IN THE WORLD.
ADDING THAT HE KNEW HE NEVER
WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO CHANGE
HIS BODY IF IT WEREN'T HIS JOB
OR WITHOUT THE HELP OF CELEBRITY
TRAINER GRANT ROBERTS.
SO WHAT DID IT TAKE FOR NANJIANI
TO GET SO RIPPED?
>> IT'S A KEY ABOUT BEING VERY
INTENSE FOR THAT FIRST HOUR,
HOUR AND 15 MENS AND PROBABLY
TRAIN BETWEEN FOUR AND FIVE DAYS
A WEEK, HIGH PROTEIN DIET, ALSO
HIGH FAT HEALTHY DIET AND, OF
COURSE, YOU NEED THE CARBS FOR
THE ENERGY TO GET THROUGH THE
WORKOUT.
>> Reporter: AND HOW HARD WILL
IT BE FOR HIM TO MAINTAIN.
>> FOR MOST OF MY CLIENTS
THEY'VE ALL KEPT THE PHYSIQUE
BECAUSE THEY UNDERSTAND THE
PRINCIPLES BEHIND IT.
IT'S NOT NECESSARILY DIFFICULT
TO MAINTAIN BUT IT'S NOT EASY.
>> Reporter: EVEN THOUGH HE'S
GRABBING TONS OF ATTENTION FOR
HIS STATUS, HIS WIFE EMILY
INSISTS HE IS STILL THE SAME GUY
ON THE INSIDE TAKING TO TWITTER
TO WRITE, MY HUSBAND WORKS HARD
FOR EVERY ROLE HE TAKES.
I'M SO PROUD OF HIM.
WE SPENT THE MAJORITY OF THIS
PAST WEEKEND PLAYING BORDERLANDS
3 SO DON'T THINK HE'S CHANGED
TOO MUCH.
ROBERTS SAYS IT WASN'T ABOUT THE
HOURS LOGGED IN THE GYM FOR
NANJIANI.
IT WAS ABOUT WORKOUT INTENSITY,
EFFICIENCY AND PREPARATION.
SO MANY OF US MAKE NEW WE'RE
RESOLUTIONS TO GET IN SHAPE.
HE SAID JANUARY 1st ANOTHER DAY
ON THE CALENDAR.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT YOU PICK A DAY
TO GET STARTED AND REALIZE THIS
IS SOMETHING YOU'LL DO FOR THE
REST OF YOUR LIFE OR YOU GET ON
THE MICHAEL STRAHAN PLAN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> MICHAEL STRAHAN TRYING TO GET
ON KUMAIL'S PLAN.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO.
DR. JEN ASHTON IS HERE WITH US
NOW.
TELL US, JEN, HOW CAN WE GET
THIS BODY?
YOU'RE A NUTRITIONIST.
WHAT KIND OF FOOD PREP AND DIET
IS INVOLVED?
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IN
THE PIECE IS PEOPLE WHO LOOK
LIKE THAT ARE TRANSFORMED LIKE
THAT DON'T DIET AND WORK OUT.
THEY EAT AND THEY TRAIN.
AND IN ORDER TO BUILD MUSCLE
LIKE THAT YOU NEED TO EAT A LOT,
OF COURSE, THAT NEEDS TO BE
MOSTLY TREE TEEN A WEIGHT BASED
CALCULATION DEPENDING ON HOW
MUCH YOU WEIGH AND HOW ACTIVE
YOU ARE SO IT'S DIFFERENT FOR
EVERYBODY AND NEED HEALTHY CARBS
TO FUEL THE KIND OF HOURS IN THE
GYM THAT HE'S SPENDING SO THINGS
LIKE SWEET POTATOES TOTALLY
GOOD.
>> EAT LESS, MANY PEOPLE THINK.
WHAT KIND OF WORKOUT?
>> THERE ARE DIFFERENT
APPROACHES.
YOU HAVE TO FIND WHAT'S WORKING
FOR YOU.
IN TERMS OF TRANSFORMING LIKE
THAT TO LOSE BODY FAT, NOT ALL
CARDIO IS CREATED EQUALLY.
WE'RE CONDITIONED IN THIS
SOCIETY TO THINK YOU HAVE TO GET
ON THE TREADMILL AND -- YOU
KNOW, FOR THAT HIGH INTENSITY,
IT'S ACTUALLY THE OPPOSITE.
YOU NEED THE LONGER INTENSITY
LOWER INTENSITY LONGER DURATION
CARDIO IF YOU LOOK AT HEART RATE
ZONE TRAINING IT'S ON THE LOWER
END.
THAT'S WHEN YOU MOBILIZE MOST OF
YOUR FUEL FOR THAT WORKOUT FROM
BODY FAT STORES BUT, AGAIN, IT'S
GOING TO BE A LOT OF CARDIO AND
IT WILL BE DIFFERENT FOR
EVERYONE.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON THE
TRANSFORMATION LIKE KUMAIL'S?
>> I'M SURPRISED THEY DIDN'T USE
MICHAEL STRAHAN BEFORE AND
AFTER.
IT'S ALWAYS GOING ON.
BUT I THINK THAT
SUSTAINABILITY --
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY, DOC, IF PEOPLE COULD
ACTUALLY SEE ME BLUSH THEY WOULD
SEE I'M BLUSHING RIGHT NOW.
>> I CAN SEE IT.
I CAN ATTEST TO IT.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT
SUSTAINABILITY.
IT'S ABOUT FINDING WHAT WORKS
FOR YOU, MAKING THIS A HABIT.
MAKING THIS A LIFESTYLE.
I THINK IT IS A TESTIMONY TO THE
MIRACULOUS STUFF THE BODY CAN DO
BUT, AGAIN, IT HAS TO BE SAFE
AND HAS TO BE SUSTAINABLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, DOC, AS ALWAYS.
APPRECIATE IT.
CECILIA, OVER TO YOU.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>>> CHRISTMAS IS JUST EIGHT DAYS
AWAY AS WE'VE BEEN SAYING.
SOME GIFTS YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET
MIGHT NOT HIT THE MARK EXACTLY
SO WE'RE GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT
YOU DO.
DO YOU REGIFT, REGRET?
REBECCA JARVIS HAS ALL OF THE
ANSWERS.
GOOD MORNING, YOU'RE BACK.
WE'LL START BY TAKING AN
INFORMAL POLL IN OUR AUDIENCE.
ANYONE IN HERE RAISE YOUR HANDS
GUILTY OF REGIFTING?
[ APPLAUSE ]
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
THERE'S OUR SCIENTIFIC POLL.
IT'S COMMON.
WHY IS IT STILL SO TABOO?
>> I THINK IT'S A LITTLE SILLY
FOR THIS TO BE TABOO TO BE
COMPLETELY HONEST BECAUSE I'VE
DONE IT, CECILIA.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> WE'RE ON THE RECORD HERE.
MOST OF US HAVE AT SOME POINT
RECEIVED SOMETHING THAT WASN'T
RIGHT FOR US AND SO SOMEBODY
ELSE RECEIVED IT AND HOPEFULLY
IT WAS THE RIGHT THING FOR THEM.
>> WE'LL TALK SOME DOs AND
DON'Ts.
WHAT SHOULD YOU AVOID WHEN
REGIFTING?
>> THIS IS THE 101 OF THE
DON'Ts.
IF IT'S ALREADY BEEN OPENED, YOU
DON'T WANT TO REGIFT SOMETHING
THAT YOU HAVE OPENED THAT YOU'VE
PARTIALLY ENJOYED OR WORN.
IF IT CAME FROM SOMEBODY INSIDE
YOUR SOCIAL CIRCLE, YOU DON'T
WANT THAT FRIEND TO SEE IT ON
ANOTHER FRIEND.
OOPS.
>> AWKWARD.
>> ANYTHING HAND MADE,
CUSTOMIZED.
IF YOU'RE AUNT BETTY IS TAKE
AGENT POTTERY CLASS, YOU DON'T
WANT TO GIFT THAT POTTERY SHE
MADE FOR YOU IN THAT CLASS SAYS
REBECCA JARVIS.
EXACTLY.
IF IT'S BEEN IN YOUR CLOSET FOR
AWHILE, TIME TO, YOU KNOW, MOVE
IT TO ANOTHER PLACE.
>> OKAY, SO YOU GOT SOME TIPS
FOR THE RIGHT WAYS TO DO THIS.
>> YES.
>> WALK US THROUGH.
>> ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU GET
SOMETHING THAT YOU ALREADY HAVE
YOU PROBABLY LIKE THIS ITEM SO A
GREAT THING TO GIVE TO SOMEONE
ELSE.
IF YOU WOULD HAVE ALREADY GIVEN
THIS ITEM TO THAT PERSON.
SOMETIMES YOU GET SOMETHING,
IT'S THE PERFECT THING FOR YOU,
CECILIA, WHICH BY THE WAY WE
HAVE IN A SECOND.
UNIVERSALLY ENJOYED.
WRAP IT UP NICELY.
I KNOW YOU ARE A LOVER OF FRUIT
WHICH IS WHY I GOT THIS LITTLE
REGIFT FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
"GMA" HELPED ME WRAP IT.
THE UNIVERSAL REGIFT.
>> FRUITCAKE.
>> HERE I HAVE RED GLASSES FOR
YOU.
OVER TO YOU, GINGER.
>> I LIKE MONEY, I'M JUST
SAYING, REBECCA E, IF YOU HAVE Y
OF THAT.
"GMA" MOMENT FROM PENNSYLVANIA.
OTIS WAS WATCHING VERY, VERY
CAREFULLY, WANTS TO STUDY HOW TO
BE THE PETS OF THE YEAR NEXT
YEAR.
UH-HUH.
REMEMBER WE HAD THAT SEGMENT ON
"GMA."
LOOK HOW INTENSELY HE WAS
WATCHING THE WINNER OF OUR PET
OF THE YEAR AND SAYING NEXT YEAR
THAT IS ALL ME.
TAKE A MOMENT, PLEASE, GO TO MY
FACEBOOK PAGE AND DROP YOUR
>> Veronica: ANOTHER WET DAY,
BUT THIS TIME WE'RE TRACKING
RAIN SHOWERS.
WE'VE GOT A CHANCE UP UNTIL 3 TO
4:00 TODAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURE REACHED ABOUT
NOON TO 1:00.
50 TO 51 DEGREES IN DC.
COOLER CONDITIONS TO THE NORTH
AND WARMER CONDITIONS DOWN
SOUTH.
THE RAIN MOVES OUT.
WE'VE GOT COLDER AIR MOVING IN
OVERNIGHT AND WINDCHILLS IN THE
20S GOING INTO THE DAY TOMORROW.
THE HIGH FOR MID-WEEK, YOUR
WEDNESDAY 42.
THURSDAY, THE HIGH, 34.
COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON AND
DRY THROUGH THE
>>> WE TURN TO JOEL OSTEEN
PASTOR OF THE NATION'S LARGEST
AND ROBIN SPOKE WITH HIM ABOUT
KANYE AND HIS NEW BOOK, "THE
POWER OF FAVOR."
>> GIVES YOU AN ADVANTAGE.
SOMETHING THAT WILL OPEN DOORS
YOU CAN'T OPEN.
SOMETHING THAT WILL MAKE YOU
STAND OUT IN THE CROWD.
IT'S CALLED FAVOR.
>> THE POWER OF FAVOR, YOUR 12th
BOOK.
HOW DO YOU DEFINE FAVOR?
>> FAVOR IS DEFINED TO ME AS
GOD'S EMPOWERMENT, A BLESSING ON
YOUR LIFE THAT TAKES YOU WHERE
YOU CAN'T GO ON YOUR OWN.
SEE, I BELIEVE TALENT CAN TAKE
US SO FAR AND EDUCATION AND WHAT
FAMILY YOU COME FROM BUT THEN
YOU REACH LIMBS BUT WITH GOD'S
FAVOR, HE'LL TAKE YOU PLACES
THAT YOU NEVER DREAMED.
>> THAT WASN'T A COINCIDENCE,
THAT WAS THE FAVOR OF GOD.
>> YOU WRITE HAVING FAVOR
DOESN'T MEAN YOU WON'T HAVE
CHALLENGES.
BUT FAVOR IS WHAT'S GOING TO
KEEP THOSE CHALLENGES FROM
DEFEATING YOU.
>> HAVING FAVOR DOESN'T MEAN WE
WON'T HAVE OBSTACLES TO
OVERCOME.
WHEN YOU KNOW YOU HAVE GOD'S
FAVOR, WHEN YOU KNOW HE'S
BREATHING ON YOUR LIFE, THAT'S
WHAT GIVES YOU POWER TO
OVERCOME.
>> SOMETHING I OFTEN REFER TO
THAT YOU HAVE SAID, GET READY
FOR YOUR SUDDENLY.
GET READY FOR YOUR SUDDENLY.
EXPLAIN WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOU REALLY FEEL EVERYONE IS JUST
ONE GOOD BREAK AWAY.
>> YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN GOD IS
GOING TO OPEN A DOOR.
WHEN HE'S GOING TO TURN
SOMETHING AROUND.
ONE TOUCH OF GOD'S FAVOR WILL
TAKE YOU FURTHER THAN YOU CAN GO
IN A LIFETIME.
>> COME ON, LET'S WELCOME
MR. KANYE WEST TODAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HERE COMES THE KANYE QUESTION.
THE COLLABORATION BECAUSE HE'S
COLLABORATED WITH RIHANNA,
JAY-Z, THE LIST GOES ON AND ON
AND NOW JOEL OSTEEN.
>> GOD IS LOVE.
>> HOW DID IT COME ABOUT?
>> IT WAS INTERESTING.
KANYE HAS HAD A TURN OF EVENTS
AND I GOT A TEXT FROM HIM AND WE
STRUCK UP A CONVERSATION AND A
FRIENDSHIP AND HE WAS GOING TO
BE IN HOUSTON FOR AN EVENT.
COME BY THE CHURCH AND THAT'S
WHEN IT ALL CAME TOGETHER AND
FELT RIGHT TO ME BECAUSE I'M A
BELIEVER IN PEOPLE AND I FOUND
HIM TO BE VERY GENUINE AND JUST
A FANTASTIC PERSON.
>> HAS HE ASKED FOR YOUR ADVICE?
>> HE ASKS ME FOR ADVICE BECAUSE
THIS WORLD IS NEW TO HIM.
>> THAT SLIGHT DIFFERENCE OF
WORDING.
>>> I GOT THAT FROM SQUEAL.
>> KEEP GOD FIRST PLACE AND KEEP
LISTENING TO HIS HEART.
>> YOU AND KANYE WILL BE AT
YANKEE STADIUM NEXT YEAR.
>> I'M EXCITED, ROBIN.
IT'S GOING TO BE 50,000 PEOPLE
THERE IN THE STADIUM.
HE'S BRINGING HIS COUPLE HUNDRED
MEMBER CHOIR AND IT'S GOING TO
BE WHAT WE CALL OUR NIGHTS OF
HOPE WITH KANYE IN THE CHOIR.
OUR THIRD TIME BACK AT YANKEE
AND FEELS RIGHT.
♪ YOU'RE THE SIGN OF MY DAY ♪
>> I BELIEVE WHEN YOU HAVE FAVOR
GOD BRINGS THE RIGHT PEOPLE TO
YOU.
NEVER DREAMED IN A MILLION YEARS
KANYE AND I WOULD BE AT LAKEWOOD
TOGETHER.
>> IT'S THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
NOW, FOR A LOT OF PEOPLE IT'S A
JOYFUL TIME.
BUT FOR SOME PEOPLE, IT'S
DIFFICULT.
IT'S EMOTIONAL.
SO WHAT IS YOUR MESSAGE THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> MY MESSAGE IS TO REMEMBER
THAT GOD HAS YOU IN THE PALM OF
HIS HAND AND THAT SEASONS COME
AND SEASONS GO, I MEAN, YOU GOT
TO KNOW THIS IS NOT PERMANENT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO LAST.
THERE ARE STILL GOOD DAYS AHEAD.
I ENCOURAGE YOU TO LIVE FROM THE
PLACE OF PEACE AND FAITH AND GOD
IS IN CONTROL OF YOUR LIFE AND
STIR YOUR FAITH UP AND SEE THAT
DAY AS GOD'S GIFT TO YOU.
> 020, LOOKING AT THE YEAR
AHEAD.
HOW DO WE COME TOGETHER AS A
NATION DO YOU THINK.
>> I THINK IT STARTS
INDIVIDUALLY, ROBIN.
ONE-ON-ONE.
TREAT EVERYBODY LIKE YOU'D WANT
TO BE TREATED.
THEY MAY NOT AGREE WITH YOU BUT
TREAT PEOPLE WITH RESPECT.
BE GOOD TO SOMEBODY.
GIVE A SMILE.
I BELIEVE THE RESPECT YOU GIVE
OTHERS, IT COMES BACK TO YOU AND
IT STARTS ON A ONE-ON-ONE BASIS.
>> GOD BLESS YOU, THANK YOU SO
MUCH, JOEL.
>> GREAT BEING WITH YOU.
>>> WE GOT A COUPLE SIGNING UP
FOR YANKEE STADIUM ALREADY.
"THE POWER OF FAVOR" IS OUT
TODAY.
JAMIE FOXX IS NEXT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
STRIKING WORKERS AT A NORTHERN
VIRGINIA BUS GARAGE BACK ON THE
JOB TODAY.
CONTINUING NEGOTIATIONS WITH
TRANSDEV.
EMPLOYEES COULD RETURN ONLY IF
TRANSDEV -- WORKERS WILL NOT BE
RETALIATED AGAINST STRIKING.
>> JESSOB: POLICE IN ARLINGTON
STILL TRYING TO TRACK DOWN
SUSPECTS WHO STOLE LUXURY CARS,
EIGHT CARS WORST TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS IN A MATTER
OF A COUPLE OF HOURS.
>> ADRIANNA: TIME IS 8:27, OVER
TO VERN VERONICA JOHNSON FOR A
CHECK ON THE FORECAST
>> VERONICA: TEMPERATURES COMING
UP THROUGH THE 40S AROUND 50
DEGREES.
WARMER AIR SITTING SOUTH OF US.
AS IT COMES IN, HAVE IT EARLY IN
THE DAY, HIGH TEMPERATURE 50
DEGREES.
CHILLY AND BLUSTERY ONCE THE
RAIN EXITS OUT OF HERE, 4:00.
COLD ONE FOR THE REST OF THE
WORK WEEK, HIGHS, 30S AND 40S.
>> JULIE: STILL MONITORING A
SITUATION TRAFFIC WELL BELOW
SPEED.
INNER LOOP HEADED TO THE WILSON
BRIDGE.
ABOUT A 14 MINUTE RIDE BRANCH
AVENUE HEADED ACROSS THE BRIDGE
BACK TO ALEXANDRIA.
NO ACCIDENTS, JUST VOLUME.
OF COURSE SLOW DOWNS HEADED INTO
NORTHWEST HERE IN BETHESDA LONG
STANDING CRASH.
RIGHT SIDE IS BLOCKED OFF WITH
POLICE ACTIVITY AS THEY CONTINUE
TO CLEAR THE ACCIDENT ACTIVITY.
THAT IS OUR TRAFFIC WATCH.
BACK OVER TO YOU.
>> ADRIANNA: GET TRAFFIC,
WEATHER, AND NEWS ANY TIME WITH
THE ABC 7 APP..
♪ GOT TO BLAME IT ON THE GOOSE ♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "GMA" AND
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO ADJUST YOUR
TV SCREEN.
LOOK WHO WE HAVE WITH US, ONE OF
OUR FAVORITE GUEST, ACADEMY
AWARD WINNING ACTOR, MR. JAMIE
FOXX.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHO IS GETTING OSCAR BUZZ AGAIN
FOR HIS ROLE IN THE NEW MOVIE,
"JUST MERCY."
JAMIE, THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU, MAN.
I WAS BACK THERE DOING SOME
PUSH-UPS.
I SEEN PICTURES OF THE DUDE OUT
THERE.
I GOT ON A STANK RIGHT NOW.
I HAD TO PUT A STANK ON.
I GET YOU CALL I A MANK.
I'M COMING OUT WITH THOSE MANX.
>> A HAPPIED BELATED BIRTHDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THIS PAST FRIDAY.
IT LOOKED LIKE YOU HAD FUN AT
THE BIRTHDAY.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> WE JUST READ SCRIPTURES AND
GOT CLOSER TO JESUS, YOU KNOW.
NO, WE HAD A GREAT TIME.
OH, MAN, MICHAEL -- HALL OF
FAMER.
MICHAEL IRVIN.
MY SISTER, DEE, JUST FAMILY.
MY DAUGHTER WHO IS DOING IDEA
GOOD TIMES" COMING UP.
THERE'S TANK.
GREAT ALBUM OUT.
THAT'S SOMEONE ELSE'S FAMILY.
AND THEN THAT'S ME.
YOU KNOW, JUST A LITTLE --
JUST A LITTLE SCOOT AROUND.
>> I SAW YOU PASS ME.
YOU PASSED ME IN L.A. THE OTHER
DAY.
>> I WAS GOING TO PICK UP
GROCERIES.
I FIGURE THAT'S THE ONE TO TAKE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT I GOT THE HOOKUP.
THAT'S MY MAN R.D.
>> YOU JUST MENTIONED FAMILY AND
YOUR DAUGHTER.
CORRINE IS GOING TO BE IN "GOOD
TIMES."
AMAZING.
YOUR PERFORMANCE --
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE ALL REMEMBER IT.
EXCITED TO SEE HER IN IT.
>> I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT IT.
SHE JUST FACETIMED ME YESTERDAY
WITH TIFFANY HADDISH, KERRY
WASHINGTON, VIOLA DAVIS.
THEY DID A RUN-THROUGH AND SHE
SAID, DAD, YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE
SO PROUD OF YOUR KIDS BUT YOU BE
WORRIED.
SHE SAID, DAD, I KILLED.
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK IT OUT.
I THINK IT WILL BE LIVE ON
WEDNESDAY.
>> WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
>> DID YOU GIVE HER ANY LIVE TV
TIPS ASK WE REMEMBER YOURS IN
THAT LITTLE MOMENT THAT HAD US
ALL LAUGHING.
>> YES.
>> BECAUSE PLAYING GEORGE
JEFFERSON MEANS EVERYTHING TO ME
AS A COMEDIAN.
THAT'S THE PERSON WHO I WATCHED.
THAT'S WHO I GOT MY TIMING FROM.
WHEN IT WAS LIVE, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN'T BLOW IT AND AT THE SAME
TIME, BEING ON "THE LOVING
COLOR" WHERE THAT'S WHERE WE
LEARNED HOW TO TAKE WHATEVER
TURNS OUT WRONG, TURN IT INTO
GOLD, YOU JUST TRY TO MAKE A
LITTLE GOLD.
>> YOU DID.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT "JUST
MERCY."
>> SO GREAT.
>> YOU SAID THIS IS ONE OF THE
MOST FULFILLING PROJECTS YOU'VE
EVER WORKED ON.
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT FILM I'VE
EVER DONE.
>> WOW.
>> BRIAN STEVENSON IS A MAN WHO
IS A LAWYER WHO WORKS FEVERISHLY
ON GETTING PEOPLE EXONERATED WHO
HAVE BEEN PUT ON DEATH ROW
FALSELY ACCUSED.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN, I MEAN WHEN I
TELL YOU IN FRONT OF AND BEHIND
THE CAMERA BECAUSE HE PLAYS
BRYAN STEVENSON HAS DONE A
WONDERFUL JOB WITH THIS MOVIE.
I HOPE EVERYBODY GOES OUT AND
SEES THIS MOVIE BECAUSE IT'S
AMAZING ABOUT A MAN WHO'S
WRONGLY ACCUSED, PUT ON DEATH
ROW FOR SIX YEARS WITHOUT A
TRIAL AND ALL OF A SUDDEN AN
ANGEL WALKS IN IN THE FORM OF
BRYAN STEVENSON AND HELPS HIM
GET EXONERATED.
YOU HAVE TO SEE IT.
>> LET'S SHOW IT.
>> PUT UP WITH THESE WHITE FOLKS
AND MAKE THEM LAUGH AND TRY TO
MAKE THEM LIKE YOU, AND SAY,
YES, SIR, BUT WHEN IT'S YOUR
TURN -- NO EVIDENCE.
AND THE WITNESSES THEY GOT MADE
THE WHOLE THING UP.
AND NONE OF THAT MATTER WHEN ALL
Y'ALL THINK IS I LOOK LIKE A MAN
WHO COULD KILL SOMEBODY.
>> YEAH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> IT'S A MOST IMPORTANT FILM.
>> ONE OF THE BIGGEST CHALLENGES
YOU HAD WAS GETTING THE ALABAMA
ACCENT.
YOU'RE FROM TEXAS.
>> I'M FROM TEXAS.
>> ALL RIGHT, MA'AM.
>> WHY WAS THIS SO HARD?
>> IT WASN'T THAT IT WAS HARD.
WE WANTED TO GET THE RIGHT
ACCENT BECAUSE I HAVE SEVERAL
LIKE DEEP SOUTHERN ALL TYPES OF
SLANG, BUT MICHAEL B. JORDAN AND
THE DIRECTOR WERE GREAT IN
CRAFTING THE RIGHT TONE FOR THIS
CHARACTER SO EVERYONE COULD BE
INVOLVED IN IT AND I'LL TELL YOU
LIKE THIS, IT HAS TESTED OUT OF
THE ROOF.
TESTED 97% IN FRONT OF AN ALL
AFRICAN-AMERICAN AUDIENCE.
AND WE WERE LIKE, WE'RE HAPPY.
WE THOUGHT THAT THAT WOULD BE
THE CASE.
THEN THEY TESTED IN FRONT OF A
MOSTLY WHITE AUDIENCE.
TESTED AT A 98.
THIS IS A MOVIE AND I'LL TELL
YOU THIS -- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND I CAN'T BE MORE PROUD OF
MICHAEL B. JORDAN BECAUSE HE DID
THIS MOVIE, THE INCLUSION BEHIND
THE CAMERA, HEADS OF
DEPARTMENTS, WOMEN, YOU KNOW,
JUST IT WAS JUST AMAZING AT HOW
HE ALLOWED EVERYONE IN SO HE PUT
SO MUCH WORK INTO IT AND I TOLD
HIM BECAUSE HE DID A SPEECH IN
THE MOVIE, HE GOT A STANDING
OVATION FROM THE EXTRAS, IT WAS
GREAT.
BUT HE DIDN'T SEE THE STANDING
OVATION BECAUSE HE WAS SO CAUGHT
UP AND I WENT TO SAY, YOU KNOW,
YOU DID GREAT AND HE'S -- HE
WALKED OUT.
YOU KNOW HOW --
>> GET CAUGHT UP IN THE MOMENT.
>> I WAS LIKE, OH, HE'S -- OOH.
BUT WHEN IT GOT TO TORONTO FILM
FESTIVAL, I SAID YOU'RE GOING TO
BE SURPRISED WHEN PEOPLE SEE
THIS MOVIE AND WHEN HE WALKED
OUT, THEY ALL STOOD UP AND GAVE
HIM A STANDING OVATION SO I'M
TELLING YOU IT IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT FILM YOU'LL EVER SEEN.
BRYAN STEVENSON, I THINK
EVERYONE NEEDS TO KNOW THIS
MAN'S WORK BECAUSE ALL OF THE
TIMES WHEN WE'RE ON OUR PHONES
AND WE HAVE REVOLUTION ON OUR
SOCIAL MEDIA AND SORT OF -- WILL
START SOMETHING WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE TO GO SOMETIMES, HE'S THE
PERSON WHO IS SPEAKING, TALKING
AND WALKING ABOUT EQUAL JUSTICE
AND MAKING US UNDERSTAND WHAT
REALLY COMING TOGETHER IS ABOUT.
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, CECILIA AND
I WERE TALKING ABOUT IT THIS
MORNING.
WE'VE BOTH SEEN IT AND THINK IT
IS AN INCREDIBLY FANTASTIC WITH
A VERY IMPORTANT MESSAGE THAT
EVERYONE NEEDS TO BE SEEN.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN WILL BE HERE
TOMORROW.
THE MOVIE, "JUST MERCY" IN
SELECT THEATERS CHRISTMAS DAY.
IT OPENS NATIONWIDE JANUARY
10th.
GIVE IT UP FOR JAMIE FOXX.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
EVERYBODY.
>>> WE ARE BACK HERE IN OUR
"GMA" HOLIDAY SQUARE.
JUST HANGING OUT, NOTHING MAKES
YOU FEEL LIKE CHRISTMAS MORE
THAN A NICE COLD RAIN, OBVIOUSLY
A LOT OF FROZEN PRECIPITATION
NORTH OF US BUT IF YOU WANTED A
MILD ONE, AS FAR AS CHRISTMAS
AND THE HOLIDAYS GO, CHECK THAT
OUT.
EVEN THROUGH HANUKKAH, NORTHERN
GREAT LAKES RIGHT DOWN INTO
TEXAS,
>> Veronica: GRAB THE UMBRELLA
AND YOUR RAIN COAT TODAY, CHILLY
ON AND OFF SHOWERS TODAY GETTING
UP TO 51 DEGREES AT NOON.
THEN THE COLD FRONT MOVES
THROUGH, TURNS BLUSTERY AND
COLDER, ESPECIALLY OVERNIGHT.
THE HIGH TOMORROW, JUST 42.
SUNSHINE ON THURSDAY, THE HIGH
34.
>>> I'M HERE NOW WITH GUY PEARCE
AND JOE ALWYN, THE TWO STARS OF
FX'S "A CHRISTMAS CAROL."
WITH RM ALMOST A WEEK AWAY
THEY'RE BRINGING US A FRESH, NEW
TAKE ON THE CLASSIC HOLIDAY
TALE.
GENTLEMEN, WELCOME.
GUY, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, JOE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
"A CHRISTMAS CAROL" IS TIMELESS.
OKAY, BUT THERE HAVE BEEN DOZENS
OF ADAPT TAKES BUT NO ONE HAS
QUITE DONE THE LIKE YOU GUYS
HAVE DONE IT.
THIS A FEW WORDS WHAT CAN YOU
TELL US ABOUT THE MOVIE.
>> I THINK WITH OUR WRITER HE'S
TAKEN US TO A SLIGHTLY DARKER
PLACE THAN PERHAPS OTHER
VERSIONS MIGHT HAVE GONE TO.
>> DARKER.
>> YEAH, TO SAY THE LEAST, A
LITTLE MORE CONFRONTING PERHAPS.
>> YOU PLAY SCROOGE.
>> I DO.
>> WHICH IS AN ICONIC --
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY I WAS CAST
AS SCROOGE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> BUT HOW DID YOU GO ABOUT
REINVENTING SCROOGE.
>> I RELIED ON NICK MURPHY OUR
DIRECTOR AND STEVE OUR WRITER.
THEY TALKED ABOUT PLAYING
SCROOGE SORT OF A YOUNGER MAN,
SOMEONE MORE ROBUST IN THE PRIME
OF HIS LIFE AND PREPARED TO TAKE
ON LIFE, NOT WIZARDED UP SCARED
OLD MAN RUNNING AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING.
SO REALLY IT WAS THEIR
PERSPECTIVE THAT I JUST TOOK ON
BOARD.
>> JOE, WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT A
CLIP.
YOUR CHARACTER IS TRYING TO GET
HOME A LITTLE EARLIER TO
CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS.
SO LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
>> COOL.
>> TALKING ABOUT THESE MATTERS
WITH YOU, I ASK YOU AGAIN, IS
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT WITH YOU?
>> CHRISTMAS, IT SEEMS, INSPIRES
SUCH EMOTION.
>> GOOD.
>> AND EVIDENTLY BAD.
>> AND THERE -- YOU PLAY BOB
CRATCHETT.
>> I DO.
>> I'M CURIOUS.
YOU SAID TO YOURSELF HARD TO
FILL THE SHOES THAT WERE WORN BY
KERMIT.
>> I'VE ACTUALLY NEVER SEEN
KERMIT EITHER.
>> BUT DID YOU EVER SEE THE
VERSION WITH KERMIT?
>> MY MAIN COMPETITION IS A
FROG.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, I SHOULD.
BUT I HAVEN'T YET.
BUILDING UP TO IT.
>> TOO NERVOUS TO TAKE IT ON.
BUT IS IT HARD FOR YOU BOTH WHEN
YOU HAVE A FILM LIKE THIS, YOU
KNOW IT'S IN THE MEMORY OF
EVERYBODY WHO'S EVER WATCHED
THIS MOVIE AND FOR CHRISTMAS
WHICH IS A TRADITION, IS IT
OVERWHELMING AT TIMES OR DO YOU
THINK, I GOT TO GET IT JUST
RIGHT?
>> IT IS TO A DEGREE BUT BECAUSE
WE HAVE THESE GREAT SCRIPTS IN
FRONT OF ALWAYS WEAN KNOW THAT
THEY'RE DIFFERENT TO OTHER
VERSIONS BEFORE WE'RE RELYING ON
THAT.
ONCE YOU'RE IN THE PROCESS OF
MAKING IT THEN, YES, YOU DO SORT
OF TEND TO FORGET ABOUT THE
OTHERS.
IT'S NOT UNTIL NOW YOU'RE
SITTING AND REMINDED OF THE
OTHER VERSIONS WE GO, OH, THAT'S
RIGHT.
HOPEFULLY WE DID SOMETHING
INNOVATIVE, I THINK WE'RE OKAY,
THOUGH.
>> CHRISTMAS IS IN FULL SWING.
HOW ARE YOU TWO GOING TO
CELEBRATE?
>> WELL, I'LL PROBABLY BE NICER
TO YOU THAN SCROOGE WOULD
NORMALLY BE.
>> HE WASN'T ON SET SUPPLY
WASN'T VERY NICE.
WELL, I'LL BE BACK IN AMSTERDAM
WITH MY LITTLE BOY AND TEACHING
HIM ABOUT MAKING SNOWBALLS AND
CHRISTMAS TREES AND THINGS LIKE
THAT BUT PROBABLY PRETTY LOW
KEY.
>> IF YOU WEREN'T THEY THINK
YOU'RE NICE NOW.
HEARD THE AH.
JOE.
>> I'LL BE IN LONDON WITH FAMILY
DOING VARIOUS CHRISTMAS
TRADITIONS AND, YOU KNOW,
DRINKING TOO MUCH AND --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> EATING TOO MUCH CHRISTMAS
PUDDING?
>> JUST LIKE A LOT OF US WILL BE
DOING.
HEY, MERRY CHRISTMAS TO BOTH OF
YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
"A CHRISTMAS CAROL," CHECK IT
OUT.
IT PREMIERES THURSDAY ON FX,
GINGER.
>> I AM SO HAPPY TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO THIS SEGMENT.
FAMILIES ARE GATHERING TO EAT
AND CELEBRATE SO WE'RE
PARTNERING WITH WELLS FARGO TO
MAKE IT GAIT -- GREAT FOR
EVERYONE.
TIFFANI THIESSEN HERE.
HOW DID YOU GET INVOLVED.
>> I GOT INVOLVED.
WORKING WITH FEEDING AMERICA FOR
AWHILE BUT I DIDN'T REALIZE ONE
IN SEVEN PEOPLE ACTUALLY TURN TO
FOOD BANKS IN THIS TIME OF YEAR
THAT'S ALL ABOUT FOOD AND FAMILY
AND FRIENDS SO I'M GOING TO
HEAR -- I'M HERE TODAY TO SHOW
YOU A VERY EASY RECIPE WITH
NONPERISHABLE FOOD WHICH IS
SOMETHING THAT WE'RE ENCOURAGING
EVERYBODY TO LITERALLY GO TO ANY
WELLS FARGO ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND BE ABLE TO DONATE IF THEY
CAN.
>> THIS IS A RECIPE MADE BY THE
THINGS THAT ARE DONATED.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
VERY, VERY EASY, FREEZABLE.
YOU CAN MAKE AHEAD.
FEEDS A CROWD.
A FOOTBALL TEAM.
ANY OF THAT.
RIGHT?
>> TAILGATE.
>> WE HAVE ONIONS SAUTEING HERE.
JUST A FEW MINUTES WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF OIL.
WOW.
I LOVE IT.
NICE FEEDBACK.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE HAVE A LITTLE
TOMATO PASTE WHICH I LOVE TO
TOAST.
>> LIKE ONE CAN, RIGHT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> OKAY.
>> A LITTLE SALT AND PEPPER, OF
COURSE.
>> YEAH, ARE YOU LIKE NOT AFRAID
OF SALT.
>> GOSH NO.
>> I MEAN, SALT -- THE THING
ABOUT SALT, IT HEIGHTENS SWEET
AND SAVORY, YOU KNOW, SO YOU'RE
GOING TO TOAST THIS FOR A LITTLE
BIT.
>> CAN I HELP?
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> THAT IS CHILI POWDER.
CAN YOU ADJUST IT TO HOW YOU
LIKE.
ADD CHIPOTLE OR ANYTHING ELSE.
YOU GUYS ARE HOT HERE, ALL
RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M GOING IN.
>> CUMIN AND CORIANDER, GARLIC
WHICH YOU'LL WANT TO ALSO --
WOW, YOU GUYS, I LIKE THIS
FEEDBACK.
>> THAT REALLY --
>> THIS IS THE BASE THEN WE'LL
TAKE OUR -- THE MAGIC OF TV AND
PUT OUR CHICKEN STOCK OR
VEGETABLE STOCK.
I'LL JUST DO THIS PART.
>> OKAY.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> LOOK, IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> WOO.
THERE YOU GO.
>> SO LET'S --
>> WE'LL ADD LITERALLY ALL THESE
BEAN, BLACK BEAN, KIDNEY,
GARBANZO, CORN, ALL STUFF THAT
IS LITERALLY CANNED.
WE ARE WORCESTERSHIRE.
>> HOW LONG DOES THAT STAY
TOGETHER.
>> A COUPLE HOURS.
SIMMER THIS FOR A COUPLE OF
HOURS SO IT GETS THICK.
I LOVE SERVING IT WITH CORNBREAD
BUT ALSO THIS IS LIKE -- SUPER
EASY.
IF YOU'RE HAVING A BIG PARTY OR
BIG MEAL PUT OUT A HUGE, YOU
KNOW, ARRAY OF TOPPINGS, RICE,
CHIPS, SOUR CREAM, BACON,
CHEESE, WHATEVER AND TOTALLY
DISH IT UP.
IT'S SO PRETTY.
>> EVERYBODY GETS INVOLVED.
SO MUCH FUN.
SO EASY.
I THINK EVERYBODY NEEDS TO SEE
THIS.
NOW THAT WE'VE GOT YOUR CHILI
AND CORNBREAD.
YOU ARE URGING EVERYBODY TO DO
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
DONATE AT THE -- TILL THE END OF
THE YEAR.
SO EASY, GO TO ANY WELLS FARGO
BRANCH OR THEIR WEBSITE.
PUT IT RIGHT IN THE BOX.
IF YOU WANT THESE RECIPES AND
EAT LIKE TIFFANI IS RIGHT NOW,
YOU CAN FIND THEM AT
GOODMORNINGAMERICA.COM.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> ALL RIGHT, GINGER, KEKE SAYS
SAVE HER A BOWL THAT HAVE CHILI
BECAUSE IT IS TIME.
WE'LL CELEBRATE THE SEASON AND
WE'RE GOING TO BE IN FULL
HOLIDAY MODE ON THE SHOW.
>> YES, WE ARE.
WE HAVE THE BEST APPS FOR ALL
YOU LAST-MINUTE SHOPPERS LIKE
MICHAEL.
>> PLUS A SPECIAL HOLIDAY
SURPRISE FOR A BFF BACHELORETTE
PARTY.
OKAY.
>> IT'S LIKE THAT, RIGHT?
>> WE ALSO HAVE A FESTIVE
REINDEER GAME.
CALL ME RUDOLPH, THAT'S RIGHT.
CATCH US AT LUNCHTIME AND NEXT
ON "GMA," ANDY GRAMMER WILL
PERFORM LIVE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Announcer: "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA'S" HOLIDAY SQUARE
SPONSORED BY WELLS FARGO.
JOIN WELLS FARGO IN PROVIDING
MORE HOLIDAY MEALS.
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH
SINGER/SONGWRITER ANDY GRAMMER
ABOUT TO PERFORM A REALLY
POWERFUL SONG FROM HIS FOURTH
STUDIO ALBUM "NAIVE."
HIS TOP TEN HIT "DON'T GIVE UP
ON ME ♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪ I WILL FIGHT
I WILL FIGHT FOR YOU ♪
♪ I ALWAYS DO UNTIL MY HEART IS
BLACK AND BLUE ♪
♪ AND I WILL STAY
I WILL STAY WITH YOU ♪
♪ WE'LL MAKE IT TO THE OTHER
SIDE LIKE LOVERS DO ♪
♪ AND I'LL REACH MY HANDS OUT IN
THE DARK AND WAIT FOR YOURS TO
INTERLOCK ♪
♪ I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M NOT GIVIN' UP
I'M NOT GIVIN' UP, GIVIN' UP,
NO, NOT YET ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M DOWN TO MY LAST
BREATH EVEN WHEN THEY SAY
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT SO DON'T
GIVE UP ON ♪
♪ I'M NOT GIVIN' UP, I'M NOT
GIVIN' UP, GIVIN' UP, NO, NOT
ME ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN NOBODY ELSE BELIEVES
I'M NOT GOIN' DOWN THAT EASILY ♪
♪ SO DON'T GIVE UP ON ME
AND I WILL HOLD
I'LL HOLD ON TO YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT THIS WORLD WILL
THROW, IT WON'T SHAKE ME LOOSE ♪
♪ AND I'LL REACH MY HANDS OUT IN
THE DARK AND WAIT FOR YOURS TO
INTERLOCK ♪
♪ I'LL WAIT FOR YOU
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M NOT GIVIN' UP
I'M NOT GIVIN' UP, GIVIN' UP ♪
♪ NO, NOT YET EVEN WHEN I'M DOWN
TO MY LAST BREATH ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN THEY SAY THERE'S
NOTHIN' LEFT, SO DON'T GIVE UP
ON ♪
♪ I'M NOT GIVIN' UP
I'M NOT GIVIN' UP, GIVIN' UP ♪
♪ NO, NOT ME
EVEN WHEN NOBODY ELSE BELIEVES ♪
♪ I'M NOT GOIN' DOWN THAT EASILY
SO DON'T GIVE UP ON ME ♪
♪ WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH ♪
♪ I WILL FIGHT
I WILL FIGHT FOR YOU ♪
♪ I ALWAYS DO UNTIL MY HEART IS
BLACK AND BLUE ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> "GMA'S" CONCERT SERIES
SPON
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WE WANT TO THANK ANDY
GRAMMER.
THAT WAS WONDERFUL, YOU GUYS AND
ALSO WANT TO TELL YOU HE'S
PARTNERING WITH ESPN TO SUPPORT
THE V FOUNDATION FOR CANCER
RESEARCH.
DETAILS ON OUR WEBSITE.
WASHINGTON" I AM JESSOB
REISBECK.
>> ADRIANNA: AND I AM ADRIANNA
HOPKINS.
VIRGINIA GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
TWO-YEAR BUDGET PROPOSAL WILL --
BOOSTING TEACHER SALARIES BY 3%.
GOVERNOR NORTHAM PLANS TO MAKE
IT PUBLIC TODAY.
>> JESSOB: TWO-YEAR PROJECT
AIMED AT BUILDING A PIPELINE OF
GRADUATES WITH SKILLS NEEDED TO
FILL COMPUTER SCIENCE JOBS.
>> VERONICA: FEW LIGHT SHOWERS,
ST. MARYS, CALVERT COUNTY.
ALL ABOUT THE FOG.
VISIBLES STILL UNDER A MILE.
TEMPERATURES CURRENTLY, 35-38
DEGREES.
WE'LL SEE TEMPERATURES TODAY TOP
OUT IN THE UPPER 40S TO 50
DEGREES.
WEATHER FRONT WILL CROSS OUR
AREA AND LOWER 40S RAIN ENDING
5:00 P.M.  WHEN THE RAIN ENDS
COLD AIR WILL MOVE IN AND GET
BREEZY TO BLUSTERY FOR EVENING
HOURS.
TEMPERATURES TOMORROW, 42.
COLD THURSDAY, HIGH TEMPERATURE
34°.
COLDEST AIR OF THE SEASON.
BUT DRY CONDITIONS STICKING
AROUND THROUGH THE WEEKEND.
>> ADRIANNA: ALL RIGHT.
VER VE, THANK YOU.
GET TRAFFIC, WEATHER, AND NEWS
ANY TIME WITH THE ABC 7 APP..
>> JESSOB: KELLY AND RYAN NEXT
OR STAY WITH "GOOD MORNING
WASHINGTON" FOR THE 9:00 HOUR,
HAVE A GREAT TUESDAY.