MELISSA: YOU WILL BE CHECKING
SECURITY AT THE CAUCUS, DOING
CHECK WORK, HE IS IN CHARGE.
CONNELL: "BULLS AND BEARS"
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
DAVID: A FOX BUSINESS ALERT
THREE BIG STOCKS MOVING BACK
AFTER HOURS, MICROSOFT,
FACEBOOK, TESLA REPORTING AFTER
THE HOURS.
WE BREAK THE NUMBERS DOWN LATER
IN THE SHOW.
>> TODAY WE'RE FINALLY ENDING
THE NAFTA NIGHTMARE, AND SIGNING
INTO LAW NEW U.S.-MEXICO-CANADA
AGREEMENT.
USMCA IS LARGEST FAIREST, MOST
BALANCED AND MODERN TRADE
AGREEMENT EVER ACHIEVED.
DAVID: I AM DAVID ASMAN, ON
"BULLS AND BEARS," PRESIDENT
TRUMP SIGNING THE HISTORIC
U.S.-MEXICO-CANADA TRADE
AGREEMENT INTO LAW.
USMCA IT TO COVER MORE THAN 1.3
TRILLION DOLLARS OF COMMERCE.
SECOND MAJOR TRADE DEAL SECURED
BY TRUMP ADMINISTRATION THIS
YEAR, WE HAVE REACTED FROM LARRY
KUDLOW, BUT FIRST, THE PANEL.
SCOTT MARTIN, ROBERT WOLF, STEVE
FORBES AND LIZ PEEK.
WITH PRESIDENT TOUTING IMPACT
WITH THE USMCA TRADE DEAL, THE
IMPACT ON THE ECONOMY.
>> USMCA IS ESTIMATED TO ADD
ANOTHER 1.2% TO YOUR GDP AND
CREATE COUNTLESS NEW AMERICAN
JOBS AND MAKE OUR BLUE COLLAR
BOOM, WHICH IS BEYOND ANYONE'S
EXPECTATION.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN AMERICAN
HISTORY WE HAVE REPLACED A
DISASTROUS TRADE DEAL, THAT
REWARDED OUTSOURCING WITH A FAIR
AND RECIPROCAL TRADE DEAL TO
KEEP JOBS AND GROWTH HERE IN
AMERICA.
DAVID: WE'RE PLEASED TO HAVE
WHITE HOUSE ECONOMIC COUNT
DIRECTOR, LARRY KUDLOW IN A FOX
BUSINESS EXCLUSIVE.
GREAT TO SEE YOU, REGARDING
USMCA, WHAT WILL THIS TREATY DO
FOR GROWTH THAT NAFTA COULD NOT.
>> PRESIDENT OUTLINED IT VERY
WELL.
AND A LOT OF THE CHAPTERS IN
HERE ARE PATH BREAKING I HOPE
TEMPLATES FOR FUTURE TRADE
DEALS, ONE IS THE NEW ECONOMY
AND OLD ECONOMY.
IN TERMS OF MANUFACTURING
AUTOMOBILE SECTOR, WE STRUCK
MUCH BETTER BALANCE THAN THE
PRIOR DEAL.
DOMESTIC CONTENT IS HIGH ARER,
CERTAIN -- HIGHER, CERTAIN WAGE
CONTEND WILL ALSO BE HIGHER, AND
A LOT OF LABOR RIGHTS THAT NEVER
EXISTED AND A LOT OF
ENVIRONMENTAL RIGHTS THAT NEVER
EXISTED BEFORE.
ON THE NEW ECONOMY SIDE, I
CONFESS THIS MY FAVORITE,
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY PROTECTION
WILL BE MAJOR BOOST TO
TECHNOLOGY ADVANCE AND DIRECT
INVESTMENT IN UNITED STATES,
THAT IS A HUGE JOB CREATOR, ON
TOP OF THAT WE HAVE EXPANDED IN
THE DIGITAL SERVICES AREA,
TECHNOLOGY -- FINANCIAL,
BIOLOGIC, AND I THINK THIS
PRESIDENT MENTIONED IN
AGRICULTURE, BIG BREAKTHROUGHS.
NOT AN EASY THING TO DO I MIGHT
ADD, GIVING AMBASSADOR
LIGHTHIZER HUGE CREDIT.
WE MADE BIG BREAKTHROUGHS ON
THINGS LIKE DAIRY PRODUCTS AND
WHEAT.
IN TOTAL, UPPER BOUNDARY FOR
POTENTIAL FOR ECONOMY GROWTH, 1%
GDP INCREASE ABOUT 600,000 JOB,
A HUNDRED BILLION IN NEW
INVESTMENT.
THEY ARE HARD THINGS TO MODEL-A
NEW ESTIMATE BUT THEY MADE THE
THE ESTIMATE, FROM STAND POINT
OF REMBRANDT EDING SOME --
REMEDYING.
THIS WILL BE A TREMENDOUS DEAL.
>> THIS IS STEVE, ANY NEWS ON
EUROPEAN FRONT.
IS THAT GOING TO GO THE WAY OF
THE USMCA?
NO TRADE WAR, THE LAST BIG CLOUD
ON THE HEAD ON TRADE FRONT.
>> STEVE, WE HAD A VERY GOOD
BILATERAL MEETING IN DAVOS WITH
THE NEW PRESIDENT OF THE EU, A
VERY GOOD MEETING, HER TRADE
MINISTER COMMISSIONER, PHIL
HOGAN.
WE HAVE BEEN IN A LOT OF TOUCH
WITH MR. HOGAN.
SHE AND PRESIDENT TRUMP GOT A
LONG VERY WELL, THEY TALKED
ABOUT URGENCY PITTING SOME
INTENSITY BEHIND IT.
IT WILL BE UP TO AMBASSADOR
LIGHTHIZER AT HIS DISCRETION AND
WISDOM TO FOLLOW THROUGH THERE
ARE A LOT OF KEY AREAS THERE.
TRADE IS VERY IMPORTANT WITH THE
-- FUNNY.
EU TRADE IS ACTUALLY -- WELL,
E.U. TRADE IS A LITTLE BIT MORE
THAN NORTH AMERICAN TRADE, BOTH
OF THEM ARE TWICE AS BIG AS
CHINA TRADE, I DON'T KNOW IF
PEOPLE KNOW THAT.
THAT IS WHERE WE HAVE BEEN
PUSHED USMCA.
CAN WE GET IT DONE WITH THE EU?
I DON'T WANT TO FORECAST, BUT I
PG YOU WILL KIND OF SEE A
RESTARTING OF INTENSITY.
>> THIS IS LIZ PEEK, THANK YOU
FOR JOINING US.
BERNIE SANDERS IS NOT HAPPY WITH
THE USMCA.
YOU MAY HAVE HEARD, THAT HE
THINKS THERE IS A MISSING
CHAPTER, ONE THAT REALLY CORRALS
OIL AND GAS PUMPS AND PREVENTS
THEM, I AM QUOTING, DUMPING
THEIR ENVIRONMENTAL WASTE TO
MEXICO, WHAT IS HE TALKING
ABOUT?
>> THAT SAY GOOD QUESTION.
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T ANSWER THAT QUESTION
THAT ALMOST A MEDAPHYSICAL FE.
I WANT MR. SANDERS, I RESPECT
HIM BUT I COMPLETELY DISAGREE
WITH HIS POINT OF VIEW.
CLEAN BURNING FUEL WHAT ABOUT
NATURAL GAS AND EXPORTING LNG,
CANADA, UNITED STATES AND MEXICO
HAVE VIBRANT ENERGY SECTORS, AS
YOU YOU KNOW.
MR. SANDERS, SOCIALISM MODEL MAY
WIN THE PRIMARIES, I HAVE NO
IDEA, I AM NOT SMART ENOUGH TO
FORECAST BUT IT IS NOTING AND WE
WOULD ADOPTING -- OR SHOULD EVER
ADOPT.
DAVID: AND LARRY KUDLOW IS NOT A
SOCIALIST.
>> RIGHT, MY BOSS IS A FREE EN
-- ENTERPRISER.
WE DISAGREE AND REJECT WITH ALL
DUE RESPECT, LORD KNOWS, SENATOR
SANDER'S VIEW.
>> I AM A CAPITALIST AS WELL, I
APPLAUD THE USMCA.
TODAY THE CBO ANNOUNCED THEY
FORECAST THE DEFICIT OF 1
TRILLION DOLLARS THROUGH 2020.
YOU HAVE BEEN A FISCAL
CONSERVATIVE YOU KNOW FOR AS
LONG AS I HAVE KNOWN YOU, MAYBE
OVER 30 YEARS NOW.
WHAT DO YOU SAY ABOUT THE
CBOREPORT, HOW DO YOU THINK WE
CAN TAKE THIS DEFICIT ON?
>> WELL, LOOK, THE DEFICIT IS
RUNNING ABOUT 5% OF GDP .
THAT IS A MANAGEABLE NUMBER IN
MY JUDGMENT.
WE NEED STRONG ECONOMIC GROWTH,
TO WORK OUR WAY THROUGH THE
DEFICIT, ALSO WOULD BE NICE TO
LIMIT SPENDING.
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS GET THE
SPENDING RESTRAINTS YOU WANT,
MORE ON THAT IN FUTURE.
I WANT TO JUST SAY ABOUT THE
CBO REPORT, I HAD NOT READ IT
CAREFULLY BUT HAVE SEEN A COUPLE
MEMOS SHARED THIS MORNING THAT
SHOWS CBO REVISED SIGNIFICANTLY
HIGHER ITS REVENUE ESTIMATE,
SUCH HAS WE PAID FOR CORPORATE
TAX CUTS AND PAID FOR THE ENTIRE
1.5 TRILLION OVERALL TAX CUT,
BECAUSE THE FASTER GROWTH THAN
THEY PREDICTED.
NOMINAL GDP COMING IN A LEVEL
HIGHER THAN THEY PREDICTED,
AVERAGE TAX RATE IS COVERING THE
TAX CUT.
NOW I'LL GO THROUGH IT MYSELF
WITH A FIND TOOTH COMB, I HAVE
BEEN IN TRANSIT THE LAST 24
HOURS.
BUT I JUST FIND THAT VERY --
DAVID: GOOD POINT.
LARRY, SWITCHING TO CHINA,
GOVERNMENT ECONOMIST IN CHINA IS
WARNING THAT THAT VIRUS COULD
DRAG DOWN THAT ECONOMY, HE SAID
BELOW 5% GROWTH LEVEL.
IF YOU TRUFFLE CHINESE FIGURES
-- IF YOU TRUST CHINESE FIGURES,
WE HAVE JERRY POW WILL SAYING P,
THEY WILL CHECK YOU ON THAT
AFFECTS THEIR ECONOMY AND GUL
SAYING THEY WILL GOES ALL OF THE
OFFICES IN CHINA, HOW MUCH ARE
YOU EXPECTING TO VIRUS TO EFFECT
OUR ECONOMY.
>> VERY LITTLE, AS J POWELL SAID
TODAY, THIS IS A CHINESE
PANDEMIC.
I WANT TO NOTE, WE JUST HAD AN
OVAL OFFICE MEETING COVERING A
NUMBER OF SUBJECTS INCLUDING
THIS ONE, AT CHINA'S INVITATION,
THE U.S. SECRETARY AZAR IS
SENDING OUR BEST CDC EXPERTS TO
CHINA, TO WORK WITH THE WORLD
HEALTH ORGANIZATION.
AND THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT.
THAT IS A FIRST TIME WE MADE
THAT DECISION, WE'RE HAPPY TO DO
IT, IT PART OF OUR ENGAGEMENT
WITH CHINA, WE WANT TO HELP OUT
ANYWAY WE CAN, WE HAVE A LOT OF
VERY SMART PEOPLE THAT KNOW HOW
TO DEAL WITH PUBLIC HEALTH
ISSUES, WE'LL SEND OVER A BATCH
OF THE CDC EXPERTS.
REGARDING THE GDP ESTIMATES, I
DON'T WANT TO GO THERE, IT WILL
BE VERY DIFFICULT FOR CHINA, THE
ISSUE IS, YOU KNOW CHINESE --
THIS IS NOT GOING TO HAVE ANY
MAJOR IMPACT ON UNITED STATES I
GO BACK TO I GUESS 2003, THE
SARS EPIDEMIC, ALWAYS A LOT OF
PESSIMISM.
BUT IT IS VIRTUALLY NO IMPACT ON
OUR ECONOMY, I DON'T THINK THATS
IS A CHINESE PANDEMIC, WE'LL DO
EVERYTHING WE HAVE AS AMERICANS
AND AMERICA GOVERNMENT TO HELP
SYSTEM SELF THIS RAPIDLY.
RAPIDLY.
DAVID: SCOTT.
>> THIS SCOTT WITH THAT IMPACT
WITH CHINA.
YOU THINK THAT GIVES US, ANY
MORE LEVERAGE WITH RESPECT TO A
PHASE TWO PART OF TRADE DEAL
DONE FASTER OR EASIER WITH
CHINA?
>> WELL, LOOK.
I DON'T WANT TO MIX THE -- I
DON'T WANT TO CONFLATE THE
SUBJECTS, CHINA HAS A SERIOUS
SERIOUS PUBLIC HEALTH PROBLEM, I
GUESS THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE ARE
DYING, WE WANT TO HELP THEM WORK
THROUGH IT, OKAY?
WE WANT TO HELP THEM, NOT ABOUT
LEVERAGE AND THIS AND THAT U.S.
AND CHINA, REACHED A MAJOR
HISTORIC PHASE ONE TRIED TRADE
AGREEMENT, THEY ARE ENGAGING AS
NEVER BEFORE.
WE HAVE TO WORK THROUGH ISSUES
ON TRADE, ON THE ECONOMY.
ON HUMAN RIGHTS, ON NATIONAL
SECURITY.
AND NOW ON PUBLIC WHILE, PUBLIC
HEALTH WILL STAND ALONE THAT IS
HOW WE LOOK AT THIS.
WE WANT TO SAVE LIVES IF WE CAN
AND HELP THEM TO GET 3 THIS
VIRUS PANDEMIC SOON AS POSSIBLE,
THIS IS A STAND ALONE ISSUE, NOT
RELATED TO LEVERAGE OR ANYTHING
ELSE, WE'RE JUST TRYING TO HELP
FOLKS THIS IS A DECENT HUMAN
INSTINCT, I DON'T WANT TO OVER
THINK THAT.
DAVID: WHAT DO WE SEE TAX CUTS
PHASE 2?
>> YOU MEAN 2.0.
>>IA. YEAH WHAT?
>> I THINK SOMETIMES THIS SUMMER
DURING CAMPAIGN, WE'LL LAY IT
OUT A LOT OF CORPORATIONS ON ALL
SIDES, IT EXCITES ME, LOWER TAX
CUTS.
STEVE FORBES, INVENTED IT, I AM
FOLLOWING UP WHAT HE TAUGHT ME.
DAVID: BEST WE DO WITH FORBES IS
KEEP PACE.
>> THANK YOU LARRY.
DAVID: 3 MAJOR MOVERS AFTER
HOURS, WHAT EVERYONE WILL TALK
ABOUT TOMORROW IS NEXT.
As a struggling actor,
I need all the breaks
that I can get.
At Liberty Butchemel...
Cut.
Liberty Mu... line?
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay
for what you need.
Cut.
Liberty M...
Am I allowed to riff?
What if I come out of the water?
Liberty Biberty...
Cut. We'll dub it.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay
for what you need.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
When I was diagnosed
with Dupuytren's contracture,
I waited to get treated.
Thought surgery
was my only option.
But then I found out about
nonsurgical treatments.
It was a total
game changer.
Learn more about the condition
at FactsOnHand.com
DAVID: 3 MAJOR COMPANIES MOVING
BIG AFTER HOURS, JACKIE
DEANGELES IS FOLLOWING THE
ACTION.
TESLA IN PARTICULAR, 11% AFTER
HOURS.
REPORTER: I WILL SAVE BEST FOR
LAST WE START WITH BAD NEWS AND
RUN THROUGH FACEBOOK SHARES DOWN
IN HOURS, THIS STOCK HIT
ALL-TIME HIGH TODAY, VISITORS
WERE EXPECTING THEM TO HIT IT
OUT OF THE PARK.
IT WAS A 3 CENT BEAT, SLIGHTLY
BETTER THAN EXPECTED BUT
INVESTORS WERE LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING BIG, THEY DID NOT GET.
NOW MICROSOFT FOR A MOMENT.
WE HEAR FROM AMAZON AFTER HOURS
TOMORROW.
BUT MICROSOFT DID SEE A BEAT IN
TERMS OF QUARTER, A 19 CENT BEAT
ON EARNINGS PER SHARE, CLOUD
REVENUE WAS STRONG THAT IS WHERE
THEY COMPETE WITH AMAZON.
>> TESLA, AS YOU MENTIONED THEY
HIT IT OUT OF THE PARK
AFTER-HOURS TRADING MORE THAN
TENDERS HIGHER, TWO -- MORE THAN
10% HIGHER, 21 CENTS BETTER THAN
EXPECTED, ELON MUSK IS EXECUTING
AND SHAREHOLDERS AND INVESTORS
ARE REWARDING HIM FOR THAT
INTERESTING BECAUSE, CHINA COULD
BE AN ISSUE FOR THIS COMPANY,
THEY JUST ROLLED OUT THAT PLANT
AND STARTED DELIVERING IN CHINA,
MAKING CARS IN CHINA, THE
CORONAVIRUS IS A LITTLE BIT OF A
CONCERN, BUT MOST PEOPLE ARE
WRITING THAT OFF, SAYING
PROBABLY WILL BE A SHORT-TERM
BLIP FOR THE COMPANY.
REST OF NEWS IS POSITIVE,
GUIDANCE FOR COMPANY, 500,000
DELIVERIES, THIS IS ONE TO
WATCH, STOCK UP 120%, SINCE
REPORTED NOT SO GREAT IN OCTOBER
OF LAST YEAR.
DAVID: 650 BUCKS, AROUND 650 A
SHARE AMAZING.
>> STAGGERING.
DAVID: PRESIDENT TWEETING OUT,
WE HAVE QUOTE HOTTEST ECONOMY ON
EARTH.
SO, THESE EARNINGS, SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT CLAIM, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> I THINK THEY DO, TO SOME
DEGREE, EARNINGS NUMBERS ARE
AMAZING REVENUE NUMBERS GOOD.
BUT STOCKS ARE AT A POINTS,
SOME, JACKIE SAID, THEY ARE SET
UP FOR PERFECTION IF THEY DON'T
PUT OUT NUMBERS THAT ABOVE AND
BEYOND WALL STREET'S WILDIST
DREAMS, THE STOCKS WILL GET HIT,
BE AWARE WHILE THE ECONOMY IS
STRONG THE NUMBERS ARE GOOD,
STOCK PRICES ARE HIGH.
>> TRUE, BUT THAT IS WHY -- YOU
ARE RIGHT, WE NEED GOOD EARNINGS
RESULT TO JUSTIFY THE CURRENT
STOCK PRICES, APPLE SET TENOR
YESTERDAY WITH UNBELIEVABLY GOOD
STRONG NUMBERS, WE'VE SEEN
CONTINUED PERFORMANCE FROM
CONSUMER SPENDING, ANYTHING TO
DO WITH THE CONSUMER IS ROCKING.
THAT IS WHAT WE WANT TO SEE, ON
TES LARK I WOULD NOTE -- TESLA,
I WOULD NOTE MOST ANALYST WERE
RECOMMENDING TO SELL, IT WAS NOT
POSITIVE, I WONDER HOW MUCH THE
RESPONSE AFTER HOURS IS SHORT
COVERING.
>> I WOULD SAY THAT MAIN OF
THESE IS NOT FABRICATED ON THE
ECONOMY, LET'S LOOK AT TESLA.
TESLA IS A 110 BILLION DOLE AR
COMPANY, THEY WILL DO 500
THOUSAND DOLLARS NEXT YEAR, THEY
HAVE A GREAT YEAR.
A COUNTRY WE DO 60 MILLION PLUS.
THEY ARE NOT TRADING ON ANY
MULTIPLE OR GROWTH TRAJECTORY,
THEY ARE TRADING THAT EVERYONE
IS BETTING HE IS THE NEXT JEFF
BEZOS EOVER NEXT 10 YEARS --
>> WHAT DOES ROBERT WOLF THINK
IN.
>> I WOULD NEVER SHORT ELON
MUSK, NOT SURE I WOULD BUY BUT I
WOULD NEVER SHORT.
>> MONTHS AGO I HAD A -- WITH
CATHERINE WOOD, SHE SAID THAT
TECHNOLOGY IS MOVING SO GREAT,
NOT ONLY FOR TESLA AND ELECTRIC
CARS, SHE TOLD ME THEN SHE
PREDICTS 5 YEARS 6,000 A SHARE.
DAVID: WOE.
>> WOE.
>> WHAT DOES STEVE FORBES THINK?
>> I'LL GO FOR THE RIDE.
DAVID: SCOTT WOULD YOU BUY NOW.
>> NOT AFTER THIS MOVE, BUT, YOU
KNOW FUNNY CAN COMMENTS ABOUT
JUST ANALYST IN SOME OTHER
PEOPLE OUT THERE UPPING THAT
PRICE TARGETS NOW, NOW PEOPLE
GET ON BOARD, AS ROBERT SAID,
MUSK AS A FAITH AND CONFIDENCE
THAT I BELIEVE SHAREHOLDERS
HAVE, AND SOME DOUBTERS AND
HATERS, ARE COMING AROUND, I
JUST WOULD WAIT FOR MORE
PULLBACKS AND DIPS.
>> DON'T BET AGAINST ELON.
>> JOE BIDEN CONFRONTING AN IOWA
VOTER AFTER SPARRING OVER
CLIMATE CHANGE, TELLING HIM NOT
TO VOTE FOR JOE BIDEN, IS THAT A
GOOD STRATEGY?
MORE ON THAT COMING NEXT.
When I got my DNA results, it
opened up so many doors.
It's a lifelong adventure
finding all of these new
connections all the time.
Greater details.
Richer stories.
And now with Health insights.
Get your DNA kit at
Ancestry.com.
I'm your 70lb St. Bernard puppy,
and my lack of impulse control,
is about to become your problem.
Ahh no, come on.
I saw you eating poop earlier.
Hey!
My focus is on the road,
and that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
Who's the dummy now?
Whoof!
So get Allstate where good
drivers save 40%
for avoiding mayhem, like me.
Sorry!
He's a baby!
DAVID: JOE BIDEN RAISING
EYEBROWS ON THE CAMPAIGN TRAIL,
TELLING THEM TO VOTE FOR SOMEONE
ELSE.
>> YOU WANT TO REPLACE THE GAS
LINES, THAT NOT GOING TO WORK.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> WHOM EVER I PICK IS CAPABLE
OF BEING THE PRESIDENT, I'M AN
OLD GUY.
I AM SERIOUS.
I -- THANK GOD, I AM IN GREAT
HEALTH, I WORK OUT EVERY
MORNING.
I AM IN GOOD SHAPE, KNOCK ON
WOOD AS MAY MOTHER WOULD SAY.
AND THANK GOD I AM IN GOOD
HEALTH.
>> IS THAT A WINNING STRATEGY?
>> I THINK IT IS, THIS JOE'S NO
MALARKEY THROUGH IOWA.
HE IS A -- GENUINE GUY AND
LIKEABLE.
SO MY VIEW IS, JOE HAS TO BE WHO
JOE IT, LOOK AUTHENTIC AND NOT
GOOD AT FAKING IT HE NEVER HAS
BEEN, WE WERE CHATTING A LITTLE
BIT, LIKE McCAIN.
DAVID: STRAIGHT TALK EXPRESS.
>> I THINK WHAT IS GOING ON IN
IT POLARIZING ENVIRONMENT.
DAVID: STEVE, YOU WERE A
STRAIGHT TALKER, WHAT DO YOU
THINK ABOUT WHAT BIDEN IS DOING
NOW IN.
>> HE HAS NOT ENDORSED THE FLAT
TAX, I'M NOT THERE YET.
BUT BIDEN IS IN TROUBLE, BERNIE
IS NOW WINNING SOCIALIST PRIMARY
AGAINST ELIZABETH WARREN, THIS
WILL OPEN IT UP PROVIDE A
OPENING FOR BLOOMBERG BIDEN HAS
NOT HIS HIS STRIDE, HE COULD
LOSE IOWA, HE IS NOT AS WELL
ORGANIZED.
HE HAS TO COME UP WITH THEMES OR
HE WILL BE SHOVED ASIDE.
>> I DON'T THINK HE LOOKS SHARP,
FORGIVE ME, I THINK HIS AGE IS
MORE OF AN ISSUE THAN FOR BERNIE
SANDERS WHO ALWAYS LOOKED
COMBATIVE AND ANGRY BUT SHE
ENERGIZED.
BIDEN IS SORT OF BUMBLING ALONG,
HE NEVER GOT NUMBER TWO, IT WAS
FIRST REASON, AND MACHINE WHO
YOUNGER -- SOMEONE WHO IS
YOUNGER WHO WAS THE SECOND
REASON?
I THINK THAT HIS PROBLEM IN A
NUTSHELL, I JUST DON'T THINK SHE
VERY SHARP.
>> HE IS TRYING TO SHOW SOME
THINGS AT TIMES, REMEMBER.
HE CHALLENGED A VOTER TO DO PUSH
UPS, AND THAT CLIP ABOUT I'M
GETTING UP AND WORKING OUT.
HE TRIES TO HANG IF YOU WILL,
SO, I AGREE, IT IS A SIGN OF
SOME WEAKNESS BUT I THINK THAT
NOTION OF TALKING ABOUT A
RUNNING MATE AS WAY TO KIND OF
SAVE HIS PRESIDENCY, I WOULD SAY
EFFORT IS TOUGH.
WHEN YOU THINK BACK TO YOU
RUNNING MATES IN THE PAST ALL
BAD RUNNING MATES HAVE DONE IS
REALLY KILL A TICKET, TO RELY ON
THAT, SEEMS WEAK TO ME AS WELL,
IT SHOULD BE ABOUT JOE, AND JOE
ONLY.
>> RIGHT, AND ANNOUNCING THAT
YOU MAY ONLY SERVE ONE TIME,
THAT SHOULD BE A BIG NATIONAL
SPEECH HE WANTS TO HEAL THE
NATION, HE WILL SERVE ONE TERM,
NOT A ONE LINER IN AN IOWA
CAUCUS MEETING, THAT IS SILLY,
THAT IS WHY HIS CAMPAIGN IS IN
TROUBLE.
THEY SAY TRUMP DOES NOT HAVE
DISCIPLINE, JOBE JEB MAKES --
JOE BIDEN MAKES --
>> I DISAGREE, I TAKE GAFFES
OVER 16,000 LIVES ALL DAY.
THAT DECENT, BRINGING COUNTRY
BACK TOGETHER HE TALKS ABOUT
UNITY AND, I WOULD THINK WE
WOULD APPLAUD THAT, WE'RE IN A
POLARIZE ENVIRONMENT.
>> LET ME --
>> WHAT UNITY.
>> IN TROUBLE THAT IS NOT
ACCURATE, RIGHT NOW HE IS TIGHT
IN IOWA TODAY.
AND HE IS LEADING IN NATIONAL
POLL.
VERSUS THE PRESIDENT, HE
OUTPERFORMS THE PRESIDENT IN
ALMOST EVERY --
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF HE LOSES IOWA
AND NEW HAMPSHIRE, SOME PEOPLE
ARE SUGGESTING THAT IS POSSIBLE.
>> I WOULD HAVE CHANGED
NARRATIVE A LITTLE, I AM NOT
SHEER TO ENDORSE OR TOUT BUT I
THINK IOWA IS NOT IN HIS
BAILIWICK BUT I THINK HE WILL
OUTPERFORM,.
BERNIE BEAT HILLARY CLINTON BY
25 ON 50, THAT IS WHERE BERNIE
SANDERS AND ELIZABETH WARREN
KIND OF SADDLE UP TO.
I THINK HE WILL OUT MERFORM IN -
OUTPERFORM IN BOTH, THEN YOU GET
TO NEVADA AND SOUTH CAROLINA HE
IS STRONG.
TO BE DETERMINED.
WE WOULD ALL BE WRONG.
DAVID: REMEMBER THAT BILL
CLINTON IN 1992 LOST IOWA HE
ONLY GOT 3%.
>> OBAMA LOST NEW HAMPSHIRE.
DAVID: WHAT IS LIFE LIKE FOR
THOSE WHO REMAIN IN THE
EPICENTER OF THE CHRIS
HUNTINGTON?
WE TALK TO -- EPICENTER OF
CORONAVIRUS, WE TALK TO A MAN
WHO IS LIVES THERE, A LIVE
INTERVIEW BY SKYPE, COMING UP,
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS IT.
.
T. Rowe Price
Invest with Confidence.
Do you have concerns about mild
memory loss related to aging?
Prevagen is the number one
pharmacist-recommended
memory support brand.
You can find it in the vitamin
aisle in stores everywhere.
Prevagen. Healthier brain.
Better life.