[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: I APPRECIATE IT.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
HAVE A SEAT, THANKS FOR BEING
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HERE.
HAVE A SEAT, THANKS FOR BEING
I APPRECIATE ALL OF THE
HERE.
SCREAMING.
I APPRECIATE ALL OF THE
OH, BOY.
SCREAMING.
THE PRIMARIES ARE UNDERWAY IN
OH, BOY.
THE CAUCUSES ARE IN FULL SWING,
THE PRIMARIES ARE UNDERWAY IN
THAT DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT, I
THE CAUCUSES ARE IN FULL SWING,
DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
THAT DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT, I
SWINGING CAUCUSES...
DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT.
SWINGING CAUCUSES...
I DON'T USUALLY FOLLOW POLITICS
DOESN'T SOUND RIGHT.
TOO CLOSELY.
I DON'T USUALLY FOLLOW POLITICS
THIS YEAR I HAVE BEEN BECAUSE I
TOO CLOSELY.
THINK THIS IS PROBABLY THE MOST
THIS YEAR I HAVE BEEN BECAUSE I
IMPORTANT YEAR FOR ALL OF US TO
THINK THIS IS PROBABLY THE MOST
BE PAYING ATTENTION.
IMPORTANT YEAR FOR ALL OF US TO
[APPLAUSE]
BE PAYING ATTENTION.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING THE DEBATES
[APPLAUSE]
AND I'VE BEEN READING UP ON ALL
I'VE BEEN WATCHING THE DEBATES
THE ISSUES, I'VE BEEN GETTING MY
AND I'VE BEEN READING UP ON ALL
BIKINI BODY READY FOR THE
THE ISSUES, I'VE BEEN GETTING MY
ELECTION YEAR.
BIKINI BODY READY FOR THE
GOOD TO HAVE A BIKINI BODY FOR
ELECTION YEAR.
ELECTION SEASON.
GOOD TO HAVE A BIKINI BODY FOR
AT THE BEGINNING THERE WERE 20
ELECTION SEASON.
CANDIDATES AND HOW THEY ARE DOWN
AT THE BEGINNING THERE WERE 20
TO SIX.
CANDIDATES AND HOW THEY ARE DOWN
FOR SOME REASON HANNAH B SHOWED
TO SIX.
UP.
FOR SOME REASON HANNAH B SHOWED
I'M PICKING OF THE BACHELOR, I'M
UP.
SORRY.
I'M PICKING OF THE BACHELOR, I'M
I'M SO IMPRESSED BY PEOPLE THAT
SORRY.
RUN FOR PRESIDENT, THOUGH,
I'M SO IMPRESSED BY PEOPLE THAT
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT.
RUN FOR PRESIDENT, THOUGH,
IT'S A COMMITMENT.
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT.
IT TAKES A LOT OF HARD WORK.
IT'S A COMMITMENT.
I DON'T THINK I COULD BE
IT TAKES A LOT OF HARD WORK.
PRESIDENT.
I DON'T THINK I COULD BE
I COULDN'T LIVE IN THE SAME
PRESIDENT.
HOUSE FOR MY FOUR YEARS.
I COULDN'T LIVE IN THE SAME
I LIKE TO MOVE TOO MUCH.
HOUSE FOR MY FOUR YEARS.
PEOPLE ARE PASSIONATE ABOUT THE
I LIKE TO MOVE TOO MUCH.
CANDIDATES AND PASSION IS A GOOD
PEOPLE ARE PASSIONATE ABOUT THE
THING AND IT'S GOOD TO DEBATE
CANDIDATES AND PASSION IS A GOOD
ISSUES.
THING AND IT'S GOOD TO DEBATE
BUT IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
ISSUES.
DISCUSSIONS.
BUT IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
CALM, CIVIL, POSITIVE
DISCUSSIONS.
DISCUSSIONS BECAUSE THERE ARE
CALM, CIVIL, POSITIVE
TWO PEOPLE BEING MEAN AND
DISCUSSIONS BECAUSE THERE ARE
SOMEHOW CAMPAIGN SLOGANS HAVE
TWO PEOPLE BEING MEAN AND
GONE FROM "I LIKE IKE" TO "VOTE
SOMEHOW CAMPAIGN SLOGANS HAVE
FOR BERNIE EGGPLANT EMOJI."
GONE FROM "I LIKE IKE" TO "VOTE
WHEN I'M ONLINE I FOLLOWED THE
FOR BERNIE EGGPLANT EMOJI."
GOLDEN RULE, TREAT OTHERS THE
WHEN I'M ONLINE I FOLLOWED THE
WAY YOU WOULD WANT THEM TO TWEET
GOLDEN RULE, TREAT OTHERS THE
YOU.
WAY YOU WOULD WANT THEM TO TWEET
AND THE PROBLEM IS THAT WE ARE
YOU.
FOCUSING ON WHAT MAKES US, AND
AND THE PROBLEM IS THAT WE ARE
SET WHAT MAKES US THE SAME, WERE
FOCUSING ON WHAT MAKES US, AND
FOCUSING ON ALL THE SUPERFICIAL
SET WHAT MAKES US THE SAME, WERE
THINGS THAT MAKE US DIFFERENT.
FOCUSING ON ALL THE SUPERFICIAL
AND WE REDUCE EVERYBODY TO
THINGS THAT MAKE US DIFFERENT.
LABELS.
AND WE REDUCE EVERYBODY TO
AND WE CAN'T DO THAT.
LABELS.
SO PLEASE REMEMBER, NO LABELS.
AND WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WHETHER YOU'RE PLANNING ON
SO PLEASE REMEMBER, NO LABELS.
VOTING FOR THE OLD GUY OR THE
WHETHER YOU'RE PLANNING ON
RICH GUY OR THE GAY GUY OR THE
VOTING FOR THE OLD GUY OR THE
OTHER OLD GUY OR THE TWO LADIES
RICH GUY OR THE GAY GUY OR THE
OR THE ORANGE GUY, DON'T REDUCE
OTHER OLD GUY OR THE TWO LADIES
PEOPLE TO LABELS.
OR THE ORANGE GUY, DON'T REDUCE
[LAUGHTER]
PEOPLE TO LABELS.
NOW, PLEASE GIVE IT UP FOR MY
[LAUGHTER]
FAVORITE DANCING GUY, THIS IS
NOW, PLEASE GIVE IT UP FOR MY
tWITCH, EVERYBODY.
FAVORITE DANCING GUY, THIS IS
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
tWITCH, EVERYBODY.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: REALLY, YOU'RE
GETTING TO BE GOOD.
REALLY, I SEE THE IMPROVEMENT
EVERY DAY.
REALLY WORKING OUT THE DANCING.
THIS IS DAY TWO OF OUR CHINO
CAMPAIGN PAIR THEY ARE OUR
UNOFFICIAL SPONSOR, THEY'LL BE
OFFICIAL ONCE THEY SEND US A
CHECK.
I LOVE CHINOS.
THIS IS A MATCH MADE IN
MARKETING HEAVEN.
I EAT THEM ALL THE TIME.
I TOOK A PICTURE OF MY HOUSE
TODAY.
THIS IS HOW MUCH I EAT CHEETOS.
SHAME.
I INVENTED A BUNCH OF DIFFERENT
WAYS TO EAT CHEETOS WITHOUT
GETTING YOUR FINGERS DIRTY
INCLUDING MY PATENTED DISPENSER.
YOU'VE ALL HEARD OF A PEZ
DISPENSER, RIGHT?
SAY YOU ARE IN AN IMPORTANT
BUSINESS MEETING AND YOU CAN'T
RISK GETTING CHEETO DUST ALL
OVER YOUR BUSINESS PAPERS, IS
THAT THE TERM?
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: DELICIOUS AND
DISCRETE.
IT'S A PROTOTYPE.
WE DIDN'T KEEP WORKING ON THAT,
DID WE?
AND TO SHOW CHEETOS I MEAN
BUSINESS I GOT tWITCH EIGHT
FLAMING HOT TO CHEETO BLASTER.
DO YOU WANT TO TRY IT OUT?
>> YES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WOW.
YOU GOT SOME DISTANCE ON IT.
>> PEOPLE WERE EXCITED.
>> Ellen: WOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE A CHANCE OVER
HERE.
HE CAN BARELY MAKE IT OVER THER
THERE.
MAYBE AFTER COMMERCIAL HOW COME
OVER TO THE SIDE.
ALL RIGHT, WHILE I WAIT FOR
CHEETOS TO CALL ME, LET ME TELL
YOU ABOUT TODAY SHOW, BECAUSE
IT'S A GOOD ONE.
PETE BUTTIGIEG IS HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AS YOU PROBABLY KNOW, I HOPE YOU
KNOW, HE'S RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT.
HE WAS ACTUALLY HERE BACK IN
APRIL AND HIS HUSBAND WAS IN THE
AUDIENCE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> Ellen: YOU BEEN MARRIED FOR
ONE YEAR AND YOUR HUSBAND WOULD
BE THE FIRST GENTLEMAN WHICH
WOULD BE THE FIRST FIRST
GENTLEMAN, HOW DOES HE FEEL
ABOUT THAT?
IS HE EXCITED ABOUT THAT?
>> YEAH, HE'S RIGHT HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: HI.
>> HEY, ELLEN.
>> HE MAKES ME A BETTER
CANDIDATE BECAUSE HE MAKES ME A
BETTER PERSON.
THAT'S A GOOD MARRIAGE WORKS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: YEP.
I HOPE HE BROUGHT HIS HUSBAND
TODAY.
MAYOR PETE WILL BE OUT HERE IN A
LITTLE BIT AND IN THE MEANTIME
TALK SHOW HOST ELLEN HAS
SOMETHING ELSE SHE WANTS TO
SHARE WITH YOU.
I'VE NOTICED PEOPLE LOVE TO FILM
THEIR FRIENDS AND FAMILY WHEN
THINGS GO WRONG BUT THEY NEVER
PUT THE CAMERA DOWN AND HELP
THEM SO TODAY I'M KICKING UP A
NEW SIMS MEANT I'M CALLING "PUT
ON THE CAMERA HELP."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OKAY.
HERE'S A WOMAN WHO CAN USE A
LITTLE HELP WALKING ON ICE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
I LITERALLY CANNOT BREATHE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: JUST FILMING AT THE
WHOLE TIME.
IF SHE BREAKS HER ANKLES AT
LEAST SHE CAN ICE IT RIGHT AWAY,
THAT'S GOOD.
HERE ARE SOME KIDS WHO COULD USE
A LITTLE HELP FROM THEIR MOM.
[CRYING]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED?
[CRYING HARDER]
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
[SCREAMING]
>> WHY ARE YOU ALL IN THERE?
GET OUT?
>> Ellen: WHY IS IT CONNOR'S
FAULT?
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S A GUY WHO
COULD USE A LITTLE HELP GETTING
OUT OF A SLIDE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> HE STUCK.
>> Ellen: I'M TOLD HE'S STILL
IN THERE.
IF YOU SEE A VIDEO OR SOMEONE
SHOULD PUT DOWN THE CAMERA AND
HELP, SEND IT TO ME.
WE'LL BE BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
'S BECAUSE THERE'S GOING TO BE
ONE NOMINEE.
WHOEVER IT IS, WE'VE GOT TO
RALLY AROUND THAT NOMINEE IF WE
WANTED TO BEAT THIS PRESIDENT
AND I'M COMMITTED TO DOING THAT
AND I THINK WE ALL ARE.
>> Ellen: YAY!
I'm a Big Kid Now
I'm a Big Kid now
Went from baby bottles to
drinking from sippy cups.
Went from wearing diapers,
to rocking these fresh Pull-Ups.
We're 50 million strong.
So, put on your Pull-Ups and
help us sing this song.
New size fits smaller trainers.
♪ OH, O(announcer)C®! ♪
ceJames
lower their blood sugar.
A majority of adults
who took Ozempic®
reached an A1C under 7
and maintained it.
Here's your A1C.
Oh!
My A1C is under 7!
(announcer)
And you may lose weight.
Adults who took Ozempic® lost
on average up to 12 pounds.
I lost
almost 12 pounds!
Oh!
(announcer)
Ozempic® does not increase
the risk of major
cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
There's no increased risk.
Oh!
And I only have
to take it once a week.
Oh!
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
Ozempic® should not be
the first medicine
for treating diabetes,
or for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump
or swelling in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase
low blood sugar risk.
Common side effects are
nausea, vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain,
and constipation.
Some side effects can lead
to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
Once-weekly Ozempic® is
helping me reach
my blood sugar goal.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
You may pay as little
as $25 per prescription.
Ask your health care
provider today
about once-weekly Ozempic®.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUEST IS
THE FORMER OF SOUTH BEND,
INDIANA, WHO IS CURRENTLY
E
PETE,
HOW ARE YOU.
SO YOU WERE HERE RIGHT BEFORE
YOU ANNOUNCED, HOW LONG IS IT
BUT NOW?
>> ALMOST A YEAR.
>> Ellen: LIFE HAS CHANGED.
>> JUST A LITTLE.
>> Ellen: HAS ANYTHING
SURPRISE YOU?
>> THE PACE OF IT.
A YEAR AGO, YOU KNOW, I WAS
MAYOR BUT IT'S JUST A DIFFERENT
LIGHT.
I WAS DRIVING MY CHEVY TO WORK.
ON CHRISTMAS WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY
STAFF OBVIOUSLY CHRISTMAS DAY
AND I WANT TO START UP THE CAR
TO TAKE HER AROUND THE BLOCK AND
IT DIDN'T EVEN START BECAUSE
IT'S JUST BEEN THAT LONG SINCE
I'VE DRIVEN IT.
ALSO MY NEIL, CAMILLE SNORING
VEHICLES.
IT'S A DIFFERENT LIFE.
>> Ellen: ARE YOU WORRIED
ABOUT THE CORONAVIRUS AT ALL?
THAT'S A LOT OF HANDS ARE
SHAKING.
>> POLICY WISE AND VERY WORRIED
ABOUT THE CORONAVIRUS.
PERSONALLY SPEAKING, ANY FLU OR
COLD THAT'S GOING AROUND, AND
THE CANDIDATES SHAKE EVERYBODY'S
HANDS.
AND THEN ON TO BEAT NICE LIKE WE
JUST HAD WE SHAKE EACH OTHER'S
HANDS PRINCE I FIGURE BY NOW WE
MUST HAVE SUPER IMMUNITY TO
ANYTHING.
>> Ellen: 'S OF THE DEBATE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT GOT PRETTY
HEATED.
EVERYBODY WAS TALKING ABOUT, HOW
DID YOU FEEL ABOUT IT?
>> THE HEAT OF COMPETITION
OBVIOUSLY DRAWS OUT OUR
DIFFERENCES BUT IT'S ALSO
IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER THAT AT
THE END OF THE DAY I THINK
DEMOCRATS ARE THE SAME BROAD
VALUES AND THERE'S GOING TO BE
ONE NOMINEE.
I HOPE IT'S ME, I'M WORKING TO
MAKE SURE IT'S ME BUT WHATEVER
IT IS WE'VE GOT TO RALLY AROUND
THAT NOMINEE IF WE WANT TO
DEFEAT THIS PRESIDENT AND I'M
COMMITTED TO DOING THAT AND I
THINK WE ALL ARE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: I MEAN, YOU ARE ALL
PRETTY MUCH, YES, SAYING THAT
YOU WANT TO DEFEAT TRUMP AND
YOU'RE HOPING BUT RIGHT NOW
THERE'S SO MUCH FIGHTING AMONG
EVERYBODY.
YOU WENT AFTER BERNIE PRETTY
HARD AND YET THEY ARE SAYING
THAT BERNIE IS MOST LIKELY
LOOKING LIKE HE WOULD GO THE
FURTHEST.
DO YOU WORRY ABOUT THAT?
HOW DO YOU THEN COMPETE WITH
THAT?
>> I AM WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
THE PUNDITS ARE PREDICTING A
WORLD WERE PRETTY SOON THE ONLY
TWO LEFT STANDING ARE MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG, BECAUSE YOU HAVE SO
MANY PERSONAL RESOURCES AND
MONEY TO DO ADS AND BERNIE.
AND I RESPECT BOTH OF THEM BUT
I'M REALLY WORRIED ABOUT OUR
ABILITY TO DEFEAT DONALD TRUMP
IF THOSE ARE OUR CHOICES.
IT WE HAVE TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
SOMEBODY WHO WANTS TO BURN
THINGS DOWN IN A WAY A LOT OF
AMERICANS DON'T IDENTIFY WITH IT
AND SOMEBODY WHO THINKS HE CAN
JUST BUY THIS A PERSONAL
FORTUNE, I DON'T THINK ANY OF
THOSE CHOICES WILL MAKE IT
POSSIBLE FOR US TO DEFEAT THIS
PRESIDENT WHICH IS WHY I'M
OFFERING A DIFFERENT APPROACH
AND I THINK WHAT'S GOING TO WORK
IS INVITING AS MANY AMERICANS AS
YOU CAN INTO THIS MAJORITY THAT
WERE NOT GOING TO AGREE ON
EVERYTHING BUT I THINK MOST OF
US CAN AGREE THAT WE CAN DO A
LOT BETTER THAN A PRESIDENT
WE'VE GOT RIGHT NOW AND WE HAVE
TO CHANGE THINGS IN THIS COUNTRY
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: DO YOU FEEL, I'VE
TALKED TO A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO
FEEL LIKE THEY'VE JUST LOST HOP
HOPE.
HOW DO YOU GIVE PEOPLE THE
INCENTIVE TO VOTE AND TO KNOW
THAT THERE IS SOMETHING THAT YOU
CAN DO?
YOU SAY WE HAVE TO DO IT
TOGETHER BUT HOW DO YOU GET
PEOPLE THAT HELP?
>> HOPE IT'S WHAT IT'S ALL
ABOUT.
THERE'S A REASON THAT THEY CALL
CANDIDATES HOPEFULS.
2020 AT HOPEFUL PETE BUTTIGIEG
APPEARED ON THE SHOW TODAY.
THERE'S THAT TERMINOLOGY AND I
THINK THAT'S VERY FITTING
BECAUSE RUNNING FOR OFFICE IS AN
ACTIVE HOPE AND BY RUNNING FOR
OFFICE AND ASKING EVERYBODY ELSE
TO BE MOTIVATED BY THE HOPE THAT
OUR LIVES WILL GO BETTER
DEPENDING ON WHO'S IN CHARGE.
DEPENDING ON WHO HAS THEIR HANDS
ON THE PULLEYS AND LEVERS OF
GOVERNMENT AND VOTING IS AN ACT
OF HOPE TOO.
SO I'M ASKING EVERYBODY WHO
FEELS MOTIVATED ENOUGH TO DO
ANYTHING AT ALL RATHER THAN JUST
ACCEPT THE WAY THAT THINGS ARE
GOING, TO STEP UP AND DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT BECAUSE IT'S
UP TO US AND I THINK FOR A LOT
OF FOLKS WATCHING THAT
IMPEACHMENT TRIAL PLAY OUT WAS
EXHAUSTING AND FRUSTRATING BUT
WE ARE THE JURY NOW.
THE VERDICT IS UP TO US BECAUSE
IT'S AN ELECTION YEAR.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO CHANGE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL TAKE A BREAK.
MORE WITH PETE BUTTIGIEG AFTER
THIS.
SPEAK UP WHEN I WAS PACKING MY
BAGS FOR AFGHANISTAN
DONALD TRUMP WAS WORKING ON
SEASON SEVEN OF
"CELEBRITY APPRENTICE" ."
>> Ellen: THINK ABOUT CLOWNS
CLOWNS --
[SCREA
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
PETE BUTTIGIEG.
I WAS JUST SAYING I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU HAVE THE ENERGY BECAUSE
YOU BEEN HOME LIKE, ONCE OR
TWICE SO YOU'RE CONSTANTLY GOING
AND YOU HAVE TO BE AN EXTROVERT
TO BE ABLE TO DO THIS BECAUSE
YOU SAID YOU GET ENERGY FROM
PEOPLE.
>> I ACTUALLY THINK OF MYSELF AS
AN INTROVERT BUT I DRAW A KIND
OF PROPULSION FROM THE PEOPLE I
MEET BECAUSE WHEN YOU'RE RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT SOMEBODY COMES UP
TO YOU AND THEY SHAKE HANDS WITH
YOU AFTER YOU GIVE A SPEECH OR
WHATEVER IT IS, THEY'RE TELLING
YOU ABOUT THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IN YOUR LIVES AND YOU'RE
TAKEN THOSE STORIES ALL DAY AND
IT ENERGIZES YOU BECAUSE IT
REMINDS YOU ALL THE TIME WHAT'S
AT STAKE AND WHY IT REALLY
MATTERS.
SOMETIMES THEY TALK ABOUT
POLITICS LIKE IT'S ANOTHER SHOW,
LIKE IT'S A GAME.
AND IT'S OUR LIVES.
AND EVERY TIME YOU GET REMINDED
OF THAT IT CREATES THIS KIND OF
FUEL TO KEEP GOING.
>> Ellen: I FEEL LIKE YOU ARE
A PERFECT PERSON TO BE IN
POLITICS BECAUSE YOU'RE SUPER
SMART, BUT YOU'RE SO EVEN KEELS.
NOTHING RATTLES YOU.
YOU JUST HAVE, AND I GUESS THAT
COMES FROM ACTUALLY, YOU SERVED
IN AFGHANISTAN AND I'M SURE YOU
HAVE TO HAVE A PRETTY EVEN...
>> IT DOES GIVE YOU A CERTAIN
PERSPECTIVE.
THERE IS INCOMING IN THE FORM OF
A MEAN TO EACH AND THEN THERE IS
LIGHT, INCOMING, RIGHT?
SO YOU JUST LEARN, I THINK, TO
KEEP THINGS IN BALANCE A LITTLE
BIT.
I'M A VERY PASSIONATE PERSON BUT
DISCIPLINE IS A VERY IMPORTANT
PART OF HOW I SERVE AND HOW I
WORK.
>> Ellen: SO YOU HAVE BEEN, I
WANT TO GIVE YOU A CHANCE TO
ADDRESS THIS BECAUSE YOU'RE
HAVING A HARD TIME PULLING WITH
MINORITIES.
AND AFRICAN-AMERICAN COMMUNITIES
AND I WANT YOU TO SPEAK TO THAT.
>> I THINK IT'S GOT TO BEGIN
WITH HUMILITY.
I WILL NEVER HAVE THE EXPERIENCE
OF WALKING THROUGH A MALL OR
DOWN THE STREET AND FEELING EYES
ON ME, JUDGING ME, AND MAYBE
THINKING THAT I'M DANGEROUS JUST
BECAUSE OF THE COLOR OF MY SKIN,
THE WAY LOCKMAN EXPERIENCE.
I WILL NEVER HAVE THE EXPERIENCE
OF GOING INTO AN EMERGENCY ROOM
AND NOT BEING BELIEVED,
DESCRIBING THAT I'M IN PAIN THE
WAY SO MANY BLACK WOMEN
EXPERIENCE.
I THINK IT STARTS WITH
ACKNOWLEDGING THAT AND IF I
CAN'T KNOW FROM EXPERIENCE WHAT
THAT'S LIKE THEN HOW CAN I MAKE
MYSELF USEFUL TO THOSE WHO HAVE?
THE NEXT BEST THING I CAN DO IS
TO SHOW UP, TO LISTEN, TO LEARN,
AND TO ELEVATE THOSE VOICES SO
WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO DO IS TO
MAKE SURE THAT THOSE VOICES ARE
ELEVATED IN MY CAMPAIGN AS A WAY
TO DEMONSTRATE WHAT IT WILL BE
LIKE IN MY PRESIDENCY, TOO.
PRECISELY BECAUSE I WILL NEVER
BE ABLE TO SAY THAT I GET IT.
AT LEAST NOT FROM THE
PERSPECTIVE OF PERSONAL
EXPERIENCE.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT SOMETHING
LIKE THE DOUGLAS PLAN THAT WE
PUT FORWARD, THE FREDERICK
DOUGLASS PLAN IS AN IDEA THAT
OUR CAMPAIGN IS PUT FORWARD, A
SERIES OF PROPOSALS TO DEAL WITH
SYSTEMIC RACISM IN THIS COUNTRY.
BUT IT'S NOT, I DIDN'T SIT THERE
AND THINK IT OUT.
WE ASKED BLACK VOICES TO BUILD
THAT PLAN.
AND THE WAY I CAN MAKE MYSELF
USEFUL IS TO TRY TO DRIVE THAT
PLAN THROUGH AS PRESIDENT AND
CONTINUE TO ELEVATE THOSE VOICES
THROUGHOUT SO THAT'S A
CONVERSATION I'M SEEKING TO HAVE
WITH VOTERS OF COLOR WHO HAS
EVERY REASON TO BE SELF TYPICAL
OF POLITICIANS, ESPECIALLY NEW
FIGURES WHO COME ALONG GIVEN THE
NUMBER OF BROKEN PROMISES AND
THE WAYS THAT THAT VOTE HAS BEEN
TAKEN FOR GRANTED AGAIN AND
AGAIN AND AGAIN AND THE ONLY WAY
TO EARN IT IS TO GO OUT THERE
A 37-YEAR-OLD GAY GUY KISSINGO,G
HIS HAS BEEN ON STAGE NEXT TO
MR. MANN DONALD TRUMP.
HOW DO YOU WANT TO RESPOND TO
THAT?
>> [LAUGHTER]
I GUESS HE JUST HAS A DIFFERENT
IDEA OF WHAT MAKES A MAN THAN I
DO.
LOOK, I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE
LECTURES ON FAMILY VALUES FROM
THE LIKES OF RUSH LIMBAUGH, OR
ANYBODY WHO SUPPORTS
DONALD TRUMP, FRANKLY.
WHEN I WAS PACKING MY BAGS FOR
AFGHANISTAN DONALD TRUMP WAS
WORKING ON SEASON SEVEN OF
CELEBRITY AND PRACTICE.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
I'M JUST DONE WITH THAT KIND OF
TALK.
AND SINCE WHEN IS STRENGTH ABOUT
THE CHEST POUNDING ON THE
LOUDMOUTH GUY AT THE END OF THE
BAR?
THE STRONGEST PEOPLE I KNOW ARE
NOT THE LOUDEST PEOPLE.
THEY ARE THE ONES WITH THE
DEEPEST SENSE OF WHO THEY ARE
AND WHAT THEY VALUE AND WHAT
THEY CARE ABOUT AND ONE OF THOSE
PEOPLE, BY THE WAY, ONE OF THE
STRONG AS PEOPLE I KNOW IS MY
HUSBAND, BRAD PITT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I KNEW CHEST    CHASTD
LIKE THAT.
>> I'M SORRY, I FORGOT MY OSCAR.
>> Ellen: WERE TO PUT YOU IN
THE HOT SEAT, AND WOULD ASK A
LOT OF QUESTIONS AND YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO ANSWER THEM
REALLY COME UP WITH A PASS WHICH
IS HARD FOR POLITICIANS TO DO
BUT I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
WE WILL BE BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WHAT'S ONE THING YOU
FORGOT TO DO MORE OFTEN THAN
ANYTHING ELSE?
>> LAUNDRY, DISHES...
>> THE THING ABOUT CLOWNS --
>>> I'M PAT LAWSON.
A QUICK LOOK AT THE STORIES
WE'RE WORKING RIGHT NOW.
A THIRD SUSPECT ARRESTED IN THE
MURDER OF A LOCAL DETECTIVE'S
SON.
AND COVERING THE LATEST TWIST IN
THE CASE AT 4.
>>> THEN, WHILE YOU'RE SITTING
IN TRAFFIC THEY FOUND 50,000
DRIVERS ACCUSED OF CHEATING HOV
LANES.
WHY IT'S SO TOUGH TO SPOT THEM.
THOSE STORIES PLUS THE WEEKEND
WEATHER COMING UP NEXT AT 4:00.
.
But on a Papadia,
cheese is what's holding the
whole operation together.
Get one now for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
I bet you've never seen a
sandwich do yoga before.
Ommmmmmmmmmmmm.
Introducing the new Papadias,
for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG AND THIS IS
A SEGMENT WE ARE GOING TO CALL,
AND WE'LL DO IT WITH ALL THE
CANDIDATES, I'M HAVING ALL THE
OTHER CANDIDATES ON AND WE'LL
PLAY THIS GAME WITH ALL OF THEM.
IT'S CALLED "CANDIDLY CANDID
CANDIDATES."
WOW, THAT WAS UPLIFTING MUSIC.
>> PRESIDENTIAL.
>> Ellen: IF YOU HAD TO PICK
ANOTHER DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATE TO
BE STUCK ON A DESERTED ISLAND
WITH WHO WOULD IT BE AND WHY?
>> I THINK OF MIND TO GO WITH
BERNIE.
>> Ellen: WHY?
>> WEEK BECAUSE WE NEVER RUN OUT
OF CONVERSATION.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE STRANGEST THING
YOU'VE HAD TO DO OR TRY ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL?
>> HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF A
BACON BALL BLT?
>> Ellen: NOPE.
>> THAT'S THE THING AT THE
IOWA STATE FAIR.
THE FOURTH OUT OF ABOUT NINE
THINGS THAT I EXPERIENCE THAT I
WILL NEVER FORGET AT THE
IOWA STATE FAIR.
>> Ellen: CAN YOU EXPLAIN TO
US WHAT'S GOING ON IN THIS VIDE
VIDEO?
>> OKAY...
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO DO THERE?
>> SO, I WAS WITH CONGRESSWOMAN
ANNIE CUSTER IN NEW HAMPSHIRE,
OFFICIALLY KNOWN AS ANY "RAISE
THE ROOF" CUSTER AND IT'S BEEN
POINTED OUT TO ME THAT THIS IS
NOT THE SAME THING AS THIS WHICH
IS WHY AS A GENERAL RULE I DO
NOT ATTEMPT TO DANCE.
>> Ellen: JUDGE JUDY WILL BE
ON MY SHOWN A COUPLE OF WEEKS
BUT SHE HAS COME OUT IN SUPPORT
OF MICHAEL BLOOMBERG.
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU WANT TO
SAY TO HER?
>> YES.
I WOULD LIKE TO FILE AN APPEAL
AND I WOULD LIKE TO ENTER
EVIDENCE THE CONTENT OF THE
LAS VEGAS DEBATE.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
[AUDIENCE REACTION]
>> Ellen: I LEARNED A LOT.
WHAT SOMETHING FROM HOME YOU
DEFINITELY WANT IN THE
WHITE HOUSE?
>> ARE DOGS, TRUMAN AND BUDDY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE THEY ARE, YEAH.
>> Ellen: I MUST KNOW THAT
CANDIDATES THIS BUT OBAMA GAVE
ME THE PRESIDENTIAL MEDAL OF
FREEDOM, WHAT WILL YOU GIVE ME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> A BIG HUG?
>> Elle: I'LL TAKE IT.
ON A SCALE OF 1-10, RATE CALL IN
JOS' IMPRESSION OF ON "SNL" ."
>> I'D GIVE IT A 6.5.
ACTUALLY WENT TO COLLEGE WITH
HIM.
SO IF YOU WOULD'VE TOLD US, WE
ARE WEREN'T VERY CLOSE BUT I
KNEW HIM.
WE WERE IN THE SAME DORM SO I
CAN JUST IMAGINE SOME SCENARIO
WHERE WE ARE PROBABLY STANDING
IN LINE NEXT TO EACH OTHER IN
THE CAFETERIA AND IF YOU COULD
HAVE TOLD US THAT HE WOULD BE
PLAYING ME ON "SNL"...
>> Ellen: WHILE MATT, THAT'S
AMAZING TO READ WHAT'S THE MOST
REBELLIOUS THING YOU DID AS A
TEENAGER.
I CAN'T IMAGINE ANYTHING BUT
COME UP WITH SOMETHING.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE, I CAN'T
IMAGINE YOU AS A TEENAGER.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'VE ALWAYS, I
CAN'T IMAGINE YOU AS A BABY.
YOU JUST SEEM LIKE YOU'RE AN OLD
SOUL, LIKE YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
THIS AGE.
>> I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS PLAYING
ELECTRIC GUITAR ISN'T REBELLIOUS
EXCEPT TRESPASS TO BE STUDYING
PIANO AND DECIDED I WAS INTO
GUITAR INSTEAD.
>> Ellen: GOD, YOUR WILD.
YOU ARE WILD.
YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO BE PLAYING
PIANO BUT YOU PLAYED ELECTRIC
GUITAR INSTEAD.
GOD.
DID YOU GET CAUGHT?
WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE TALK SHOW
HOST?
WE KNOW THAT.
WHAT IS THE ONE THING YOU FORGET
TO DO MORE --
>> I DECIDED, THIS ISN'T THAT
REBELLIOUS, BUT I HAVE A SIDE
BURN PHASE AND I THINK AS I LOOK
BACK ON IT THAT MIGHT'VE BEEN MY
IDEA OF REBELLION.
>> Ellen: HOW LONG WERE THE
SIDE BIRD'S?
>> ENOUGH.
>> Ellen: LIKE MUTTON CHOP
THINGS CUSTOMER JUST LONG
SIDEBURNS?
WHAT YEAR WAS THIS?
>> ABOUT '99, 2,000.
>> Ellen: THAT'S TOO LATE.
TO MAKE AN EXCUSE FOR.
WHAT'S ONE THING YOU FORGET TO
DO MORE OFTEN THAN ANYONE     AG
ELSE?
TO >> CHEST AND PROBABLY KNOWS
THE ANSWER MORE THAN I DO.
>> LAUNDRY, DISHES.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: WOW, THEY WERE RIGHT
THERE READY TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
PLEASE COME BACK ANY ANY TIME.
ANY TIME YOU'RE IN TOWN.
NO MATTER WHO YOU VOTE FOR,
PLEASE REMEMBER TO VOTE.
WE'LL BE BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WHAT YOU THINK HAPPENED TO
ROBIN?
YAY!
[SCREAMING]
[police siren]
Dispatch, we got a code bubly.
Are you going to get him down?
No.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
♪
Find something incredible,
from somewhere amazing.
Unique selection,
unbelievable prices.
HomeGoods.
Go Finding.
♪ ♪
Ugh...What the what?
Okay wipe
pretty-please do your thing...
nice!
Nailed it!
Huggies® Natural Care® wipes,
gentle like A HUG.
HUGG ON
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WERE ABOUT TO SEE
PEOPLE WILL LIE STRAIGHT TO MY
FACE FOR SOME CASH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
HELLO.
BEFORE THE SHOW WE FIND A FEW
PEOPLE TO PLAY, WHO ARE YOU?
IT SAYS ROBIN.
>> I WAS A RECEPTIONIST AND NOW
I'M PURSUING ACTING.
>> Ellen: AND WHO ARE YOU
PLAYING WITH?
>> AND PLAYING WITH MY MOM.
>> Ellen: IT'S NOT FAIR THAT
SHE'S IN THAT POSITION OVER
THERE.
WHERE YOU LIVE, WHAT YOU DO
QUESTION WORK >> I LIVE IN
LAGUNA BEACH AND I'M A
STAY-AT-HOME MOM TO MY 23
23-MONTH-OLD.
AND WHO ARE YOU PLAYING WITH?
>> AND PLAIN WITH MY BEST
FRIEND, KATIE.
>> Ellen: WE'LL SEE HOW LONG
THAT LASTS.
HI.
>> I'M FROM NORTHRIDGE, LOCAL.
AND I WORK AS A PROJECT MANAGER
AND I'M PLAYING WITH MY
DAUGHTER.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
HI.
THIS GAME IS VERY SIMPLE.
YOU'LL TELL ME A FUN FACT AND WE
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT IF IT'S TRUE,
IT'S DEFINITELY TRUE FOR ONE OF
YOU BUT WE'LL HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
IF IT'S TRUE FOR YOU OR YOUR
PARTNER AND IF WE CATCH YOU IN A
LIE YOU'RE OUT OF HERE.
IF WE GUESS WRONG YOU'RE SAFE.
TELL US SOMETHING AND WE ARE
GOING TO GET YOU.
TELL US.
>> WELL, ELLEN, I CAN DEAD LIFT
205 POUNDS.
>> YOU CAN DEAD LIFT 205 POUNDS?
[LAUGHTER]
>> ONE?
>> ANY TIME.
>> ANY TIME?
>> Ellen: RIGHT NOW YOU COULD
DO IT?
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN DEAD
LIFTING WEIGHT?
>> DEAD LIFTING?
SINCE ABOUT 2018.
>> Ellen: OKAY.
MARTINA?
>> I'VE BEEN WEIGHT LIFTING FOR
FIVE YEARS, SINCE HIGH SCHOOL.
AND YOU CAN DEAD LIFT
205 POUNDS?
ALL RIGHT.
WE FEEL HE GETS MARTINA.
>> NOPE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE ARE TERRIBLE AT
THIS.
>> OR THEY'RE JUST REALLY GOOD
LIARS I GUESS.
>> Ellen: LET'S KEEP GOING.
ROBIN.
>> I ALMOST DIED ON TO HER TO
MEXICO CITY PYRAMIDS.
>> HOW?
>> SO I WAS WITH MY DAD AND WE
WERE ON THE WAY AND THE BUS
DRIVER PULLED OVER AND THIS MAN
IN BLACK GOT ON THE VAN AND
STARTED FILMING ALL OF US AND
NOBODY SPOKE THE SAME LANGUAGE
THAT WE WERE ALL LOOKING AT EACH
OTHER AND THE GUY JUST FILM THE
SAW AND GOT OFF THE BUS AND IT
WAS NEVER EXPLAINED AND THEN WE
JUST KEPT DRIVING AND WE MADE
IT.
A LIFE.
>> Ellen: WHY DID YOU THINK,
THAT WAS KIND OF DRAMATIC OF YO
YOU.
HE WAS JUST FILMING YOU.
>> THERE WAS JUST A RANDOM
PERSON ON THE BUS IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE.
>> Ellen: I THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO SWITCH BACK AND FORTH.
WHY, DO YOU THINK HAPPENED TO
HER?
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY.
>> DON'T PUT THIS ON ME.
>> THEY MIGHT GO BACK AND FORTH.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
WE THINK HAPPENED TO ROBIN.
>> YES.
>> Ellen: YAY!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, BRENDA, TELL US SOMETHING.
BECAUSE SEVEN TIMES BEFORE I WAS
14.
>> Ellen: .
>> Ellen: WHY?
>> MY DAD WAS IN THE ARMY.
>> Ellen: I SEE.
>> A BRANCH OF THE MILITARY WAS
MY DAD IN?
>> ARMY.
>> Ellen: WHAT POSITION IN THE
ARMY?
YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> CAPTAIN, MAYBE?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THAT WAS
GENUINE OR NOT.
>> Ellen: I THINK SHE'S DOING
IT TO US ON PURPOSE.
TO MAKE US LOOK LIKE FULL SPEED.
AND YOU WILL NOT MAKE US LOOK
LIKE FOOLS.
IT WAS YOU, YOU MOVE SEVEN TIME
TIMES.
WHAT?
>> IS THAT YOUR FINAL ANSWER?
>> Ellen: IT IS MY FINAL
ANSWER.
[SCREAMING]
>> Ellen: YEAH!
TRYING TO FOOL US AGAIN, YOU'RE
OUT OF HERE, MARANDA.
THAT MEANS YOU ARE THE WINNERS.
YOU WIN $5,000.
YOU HAVE TO GO UP, THOUGH.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> MY TEACHERS CALLED IN SICK
TODAY AND I HEARD A RUMOR THAT
THEY MIGHT BE IN YOUR AUDIENCE.
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE THEIR NAMES
NAMES?
ANNOUNCER: People aren't talking
about Giant's all-natural
Nature's Promise Chicken.
They're not talking about
our fresh, pre-cut veggies.
Or Giant's delicious grab-and-go
salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking...
because they're eating.
Oh wow. Yum!
At Giant, we carry over
900 Nature's Promise products
that we feel good about feeding
our families, so you can, too.
The little things are Giant.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OUR NEXT GUEST IS
IT --
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
>> Ellen: IS NOT MY PHONE?
WHERE?
HELLO?
>> HI, IS THIS ELLEN?
>> Ellen: YES, WHO'S THIS?
>> MY NAME IS KELLY AUSTIN, I'M
THE PRINCIPAL AT AN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL IN FRESNO, CALIFORNIA.
>> Ellen: HI, I'M IN THE
MIDDLE OF A SHOW RIGHT NOW, WHAT
CAN I HELP YOU WITH?
>> WELL, TWO OF MY TEACHERS
CALLED IN SICK TODAY AND I HEARD
A RUMOR THAT THEY MIGHT BE IN
YOUR AUDIENCE.
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE THEIR NAMES
NAMES?
>> TO RON AND CHRISTINA NOLAN.
>> Ellen: WELCOME BUT THERE'S
TWO PEOPLE BEING VERY
EMBARRASSED RIGHT NOW.
IS THAT YOU?
YES, THEY ARE HERE.
COME DOWN HERE, BOTH OF YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI, HI, HAVE A SEAT.
I HAVE THEM DOWN HERE.
JUMPY TO SAY SAY SOMETHING TO
THEM?
>> I JUST WANT THEM BOTH TO KNOW
THAT I THINK THEY ARE ABSOLUTELY
AMAZING, THANK YOU BOTH SO MUCH
FOR GOING ABOVE AND BEYOND FOR
OUR KIDS.
YOU GUYS ENJOY YOUR SIX DAY AND
REMEMBER WE LOVE YOU.
>> Ellen: THANKS FOR CALLING!
WOW.
>> ALL MY GOODNESS.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
WE KNOW A LITTLE BIT ABOUT YOU,
ACTUALLY, THANKS FOR BEING HERE
ON YOUR SICK DAY.
>> WE WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
ANYWHERE ELSE.
OH, OH, I CAN HEAR THEM.
I GUESS YOU WANT OTHER PEOPLE TO
HEAR THEM COME UP MARY.
SO, YOU BOTH WORK AT A SCHOOL.
TELL US ABOUT THE SCHOOL YOU
WORKED FOR.
>> WE WORK FOR ROBINSON
ELEMENTARY.
IT'S A TITLE I SCHOOL, FREE AND
REDUCED LUNCH FOR EVERYONE.
YOU KNOW, THE KIDS ARE AMAZING.
THERE'S A LOT OF BROKENNESS, THE
STAFF JUST LOVES KIDS.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M HAPPY TO BE
THERE.
I'M A SIXTH-GRADE TEACHER.
>> AND I'M A RESOURCE COUNSELING
ASSISTANT.
PRETTY MUCH A MOM TO 500 KIDS
ALL DAY.
>> Ellen: AND YOU HAVE KIDS
ALSO?
THREE KIDS?
WHERE ARE THEY?
>> SOMEWHERE IN THE BACK.
>> WE AREN'T SURE.
>> Ellen: COME ON OUT, THEY
SHOULD BE HERE, RIGHT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WHO ARE YOU?
KENNEDY?
MADDOX?
ISN'T THIS COOL?
HOW ABOUT YOUR DAD.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT HE'S
GOING MORE VIRAL THAN ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT BUT I'M SO
PROUD OF HIM AND THE IMPACT THAT
HE HAS AN ON NOT ONLY US AND HIS
KIDS BUT EVERYBODY THAT WATCHES
HIS VIDEOS, HAS AN IMPACT ON
THEIR LIFE SCUM TOO.
>> Ellen: YOU STARTED DOING
SOMETHING REALLY COOL TO HELP
KIDS AT THEIR FEARS.
>> SO MANY OF MY STUDENTS
STRUGGLE WITH FEAR.
THEY LIVE IN ENVIRONMENTS WHERE
THEY ARE SCARED, THEY ARE SCARED
ABOUT THE FUTURE SO I TOLD THEM,
RIGHT DOWN ALL YOUR FEARS AND I
WILL CONQUER ALL OF MINE.
AND I PUT IT ON YOUTUBE AND THEY
LOVE WATCHING THEIR TEACHER
FREAK OUT.
>> Ellen: SO SOME OF THE FEARS
THAT THEY'VE GOTTEN OVER AND
WHAT ARE SOME OF THE PEERS
YOU'VE GOTTEN OVER?
>> I CLIMBED A 40-FOOT POLE AND
JUMPED OFF.
MY WIFE AND I RAN A 5K.
>> WHICH HE THOUGHT WAS
106 MILES.
>> MY WHOLE LEFT SIDE HURTS
STILL.
AND THE LAST ONE IS, I DID STAND
UP COMEDY FOR A RETIREMENT HOME.
>> Ellen: HOW DID THAT GO?
>> HORRIBLE.
>> Ellen: I'M GOING TO HELP
YOU WITH ONE MORE FEAR THAT I
KNOW THAT YOU HAVE WHEN WE COME
BACK, ALL RIGHT?
>> OHNO.
>> Ellen: YEP, WE'LL BE
Your mission:
Stand up to moderate
to severe rheumatoid arthritis.
And Take. It. On
with RINVOQ.
RINVOQ a once-daily pill
can dramatically
improve symptoms...
RINVOQ helps tame pain,
stiffness, swelling.
And for some...
RINVOQ can even significantly
reduce RA fatigue.
That's RINVOQ RELIEF.
With RA, your overactive
immune system
attacks your joints.
RINVOQ regulates it to
help stop the attack.
RINVOQ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious infections and blood
clots, sometimes fatal,
have occurred as
have certain cancers,
including lymphoma,
and tears in the stomach
or intestines,
and changes in lab results.
Your doctor should
monitor your bloodwork.
Tell your doctor about any
infections and if you are
or may become pregnant
while taking RINVOQ.
Ready to take on RA?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about RINVOQ relief.
RINVOQ.
Make it your mission.
Awesome!
Quickly, get the big blue bag.
Here are your groceries.
Groceries!
Teamwork makes the dream work.
I love the new myWW program,
because you get matched with
a plan tailored to you!
Whether you're a dine outer,
take outer, veggie person,
definitely-not-just-veggie
person,
bread lover,
or cheese lover...
...all you have to do is answer
personal assessment questions
and get scientifically matched
with a proven weight loss plan.
Find out which new
customized plan
can make losing weight
easier for you!
The new program from WW.
Weight Watchers reimagined.
Join today
with the WW
triple play!
Hurry,
offer ends
February 24th.
Big news America!
For a limited time, we've
changed the shape
of Honey Nut Cheerios.
Because we want people to know
they're delicious
AND can help lower cholesterol.
Heart healthy. Get it? A heart!
Can you believe they had one in
my size?!
.
>>> BREAKING NEXT AT 4:00, A
VOLK PACKED OUTSIDE A MILITARY
BASE.
MORE ABOUT THE ALARMING ARRESTS
ONLY AT NEWS 4.
>> AND TWO MORE TEENAGERS
ARRESTED IN THE MURDERED OF A
DETECTIVE'S SON.
NEW COURT DETECTIVES REVEALING
AN ALLEGED MURDER.
>> AND IT'S COLD OUT THERE.
WIERNT
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH THE
NOLAN FAMILY.
SO YOU HAVE CONQUERED SOME OF
YOUR FEARS.
YOU HAVE OTHER PEERS I KNOW,
WHAT ARE THEY?
>> YES, YES.
CLOWNS AND COTTON BALLS.
>> Ellen: I'M WITH YOU ON THE
COTTON BALLS.
>> THANK YOU, YES!
>> Ellen: I DON'T KNOW HOW
PEOPLE CAN'T STOMACH CAN TOUCH
THEM.
>> IT'S THE NOISE.
>> Ellen: DON'T EVEN TALK
ABOUT THE NOISE.
BUT CLOWNS I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE CREEPY?
>> YET.
ALL CLOWNS ARE CREEPY.
AT A HORRIBLE EXPERIENCE WHAT I
YOUNG AT A CIRCUS THAT SCARRED
ME FOR LIFE.
>> Ellen: WHAT DID THE CLOWN
DO?
>> IT WAS DANCING.
BUT IT WAS SCARY.
>> Ellen: THE THING ABOUT
CLOWNS -- GO [SCREAMING]
[APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
I WAS TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
>> Ellen: WOW.
YOU ALMOST KILLED YOUR WHOLE
FAMILY.
THAT'S WHY WE SAID THE LITTLE
AWAY, THAT WAS VERY SATISFYING.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT HOW YOU
PROTECTED YOUR FAMILY.
>> Ellen: THE THING ABOUT
CLOWNS -- GO >> I'M NEVER GOING
TO LIVE THAT DOWN.
OH, NO.
>> Ellen: OH, MAN.
>> ANYTHING ELSE?
>> Ellen: NOTHING ELSE IN
THERE, NO, THAT'S IT.
NOW I WANT TO TALK ABOUT YOUTUBE
BECAUSE YOU MET VOLUNTEERING AND
EVEN THOUGH YOU BOTH WORK AROUND
THE CLOCK YOU STILL FIND TIME TO
GET BACK TO YOUR COMMUNITY.
YOU BRING PIZZA TO YOUR STUDENTS
ON THE WEEKENDS, YOU GO TO THEIR
GAMES AND ARE ALWAYS THERE TO
SUPPORT THEM, EVEN THOUGH YOU
BOTH HAVE STUDENT LOANS TO PAY
OFF, YOU'RE STRUGGLING
YOURSELVES, YOU ALWAYS PAY
OUT-OF-POCKET FOR YOUR STUDENTS.
SO YOU'RE BASICALLY AN
INCREDIBLE FAMILY AND SINCE YOU
GO ABOVE AND BEYOND TO DO GOOD,
MY FRIENDS AT HONEY NUT CHEERIOS
SATE WHEN YOU DO GOOD YOU FEEL
GOOD AND SO THEY WANT TO GIVE
ROBINSON ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
$25,000.5,000.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: AND THEY ALSO WANT
TO GIVE YOU A $25,000.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS!
OH, MY GOD, !
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> I LOVE YOU!
>> Ellen: I
>>> BREAKING NOW AT 4:00, A
VEHICLE PACKED FULL OF WEAPONS
FOUND OUTSIDE A LOCAL MILITARY
BASE.
>> GUNS, BODY ARMOR, EVEN SMOKE
GRENADES.
DETAILS OF THE ALARMING ARREST
ONLY ON NEWS 4.
>>> THREE ARRESTS IN THE MURDER
OF A POLICE DETECTIVE'S SON.
THE NEW CONFESSION REVEALING AN
ALLEGED MOTIVE.
>> THE CHILL NOT LASTING LONG.
DETAILS ON A WEEKEND WARMUP.
>> PLUS, COLE'S LEGACY.
>> HIS LIFE WASN'T WORTHLESS.
HE HAD A PURPOSE.
>> A 4-YEAR-OLD BOY KILLED WHEN
HE PICKED UP A LOADED GUN AT DAY
CARE.
HOW HIS MOTHER IS TURNING HER
GRIEF INTO ACTION.
>> CHILDREN WILL BE SAVED AND
PEOPLE WILL BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE
FOR THEIR ACTIONS.
>>> WE COME ON AIR THIS
AFTERNOON WITH THAT BREAKING
NEWS THAT YOU'LL ONLY SEE HERE
ON NEWS 4.
>> A FORMER MEMBER OF THE OLD
GUARD ARRESTED OUTSIDE OF
FT. MYERS WAS A JAW-DROPPING
CATCH OF MILITARY WEAPONS.
>> A MAN WAS TAKEN INTO CUSTODY
DRLIER THIS WEEK.
N ARLINGTON
DEILS ABOUT THIS.
DREW?
>> Reporter: PAT, LEON, THE
ARLINGTON COUNTY POLICE
DEPARTMENT SAYS THE SUSPECT
CURTIS WELLS WAS DISCHARGED FROM
THE ARMY LAST YEAR, BUT AS YOU
MENTIONED WHILE HE WAS LISTED HE
WAS PART OF AN ELITE BATTALION
KNOWN AS THE OLD GUARD TASKED
WITH ESCORTING THE PRESIDENT,
ALL THE MORE REASON WHY TONIGHT
ARGUE-TO-BENT