♪ ♪
>> John: HELLO, EVERYBODY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH ! AS YOU CAN
SEE, ELLEN IS NOT HERE TODAY
AGAIN.
SHE SPENDING VALENTINE'S DAY
WITH THE LOVE OF HER LIFE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HER BEAUTIFUL PORSCHE.
SHE LOVES THAT CAR.
[LAUGHTER]
ALSO HER BEAUTIFUL WIFE, PORTIA,
AS WELL.
BUT YOU ARE IN GOOD HANDS
BECAUSE THIS IS ACTUALLY MY
SECOND TIME GUEST HOSTING THE
SHOW AND I'VE BEEN HERE THIS
SEASON ALMOST AS MUCH AS ELLEN
DEGENERES.
YOU KNOW, LAST TIME I WAS HERE I
WAS PROMOTING MY CHRISTMAS
ALBUM, "A LEGENDARY CHRISTMAS"
AND I WAS KIND OF HOPING IT
WOULD BE THE NEXT HUGE CHRISTMAS
ALBUM BUT THEN IN NOVEMBER,
MARIAH CAREY...
[LAUGHTER]
>> John: SHE POSTED THIS ON
INSTAGRAM TO LET EVERYONE KNOW
THAT SHE'S STILL THE QUEEN OF
CHRISTMAS.
♪ ♪
>> SANTA!
IT'S TIME!
♪ ♪
>> John: YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S RIGHT, SHE'S THE QUEEN OF
CHRISTMAS, IT'S TRUE.
BUT THERE ARE PLENTY OF OTHER
HOLIDAYS ON THE CALENDAR SO I
DECIDED I WOULD LIKE TO BE THE
KING OF ARBOR DAY.
ARBOR DAY.
YES.
[APPLAUSE]
THE ONLY ISSUE IS IT TURNS OUT I
DON'T HAVE A LOT OF SONGS ABOUT
TREES.
I HAVE ONE CALLED "GET LIFTED"
BUT I DON'T REALLY HAVE A LOT OF
SONGS ABOUT TREES.
I DO HAVE A LOT OF LOVE SONGS,
THOUGH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SO, I DECIDED TO MAKE A VIDEO TO
POSITION MYSELF TO BE THE KING
OF VALENTINE'S DAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[BABY BABBLING]
♪ ♪
>> John: CUPID!
>> HELLO, JOHN.
>> John: IT'S TIME!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> John: YES!
THAT'S THE DAVID GET A REMIX OF
MY NEW SONG,
"CONVERSATOINS IN THE DARK," AND
IT TURNS OUT THAT MY CLAIM
TO BE KING OF VALENTINE'S DAY
ACTUALLY WORKED OUT BECAUSE I
JUST SAW THIS HEADLINE,
APPARENTLY MY SONG "ALL OF ME"
IS THE NUMBER ONE SONG FOR
LOVERS.
THAT MEANS A WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE MADE LOVE WITH ME IN THE
ROOM.
[LAUGHTER]
WHEN PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR
LOVE, THEY TURNED TO ME.
SO I THOUGHT, I SHOULD HELP
SOMEONE IN THE AUDIENCE BE A
LITTLE MORE SEXY FOR THIS
VALENTINE'S DAY.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS THINK?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HOW ABOUT YOU, SIR?
COME HERE.
YOU ARE RIGHT THERE.
YES!
♪ ♪
>> John: WELCOME!
HELLO!
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
THAT'S YOUR NAME?
IT'S ALREADY PRETTY SEXY.
I FEEL LIKE IF YOU INTRODUCE
YOURSELF AS BONDS, BACKED BONDS.
>> BOND, MATCH BOND.
>> John: YES, HERE YOU ARE.
WAY.
NOW ARE YOU MARRIED?
>> I AM.
>> John: YOU HAVE KIDS?
>> I DO.
>> John: HOW MANY KIDS
QUESTION MEXICO FOUR.
>> John: YOU MAY NOT NEED ANY
HELP BEING.
PERHAPS YOU ARE A LITTLE TOO
SEXY.
MATCH BONDS.
ARE YOU RICH OR FAMOUS?
>> NO.
>> John: THIS IS GOING TO BE A
LITTLE HARDER, THEN, BUT I DO
HAVE SOME TIPS TO HELP YOU OUT.
FIRST, THEY SAY CLOSE MAKE THE
MAN.
TRUE, RIGHT?
NOTHING LOOKS BETTER THAN A
SHARP JACKET SO I GOT YOU THIS
JACKET.
HERE WE GO.
YES!
THIS IS WHAT WE CALL A SMOKING
JACKET AND IT MAKES YOU LOOK
SMOKING HOT.
>> HOW ABOUT HUGH HEFNER?
>> John: YES, YES.
AND OF COURSE YOU SHOULD ALSO
SERENADE YOUR WIFE.
I DO THAT TO MY WIFE.
YOU CAN THING MY NUMBER ONE SONG
FOR LOVERS, "ALL OF ME," OF
COURSE, OR YOU CAN SING MY NEW
SONG,
"CONVERSATIONS IN THE DARK."
LET'S HEAR YOU SING SOMETHING
SEXY.
>> OH, MAN.
HOW ABOUT ♪ ROW, ROW, ROW YOUR
BOAT ♪
I'M NOT SURE HOW SEXY THAT IT
IS.
>> John: "ROW YOUR BOAT?"
THAT'S ENOUGH SINGING FROM YOU.
GET HER THAT ALBUM, I'LL BE IN
THE ROOM WHILE YOU GUYS ARE
MAKING BABY NUMBER FIVE.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD BUT
I'M GOING ON TO HER.
I'M GOING ON TO HER, GUYS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S CALLED THE BIGGER LOVE TO
HER.
THE TICKETS ARE ON SALE TODAY!
IT'S THE PERFECT VALENTINE'S DAY
GIFT AND I WANT TO INVITE YOU
AND YOUR WIFE, MATT, TO COME SEE
THE CONCERT.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> John: AND WERE GOING TO
HAVE A GREAT TIME.
WE WILL SEE YOU THEN.
AND NOW I THINK IT'S TIME TO SET
THE MOOD.
YOU'VE GOT THE MUSIC BUT YOU
ALSO NEED SOME WINE.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> A SWEET WINE.
>> John: I RECOMMEND MY WINE.
OKAY?
NOW, THIS IS THE SEXIEST WINE ON
THE PLANET, Y'ALL.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS POOR TO
GLASSES AND THEN DRINK BOTH OF
THEM YOURSELF TO LOOSEN THINGS
UP.
AND THEN WHEN YOUR WIFE GETS
HOME FOR TWO MORE CLASSES, ONE
FOR YOU, ONE FOR YOUR WIFE, AND
THERE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL POP IT OPEN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HEY!
YOU KNOW, THAT HAPPENS EVERY
TIME YOU POP AN LVE BOTTLE OPEN.
MUSIC COMES ON, YOU GET IN THE
GROOVE.
YOU GOT THE LOOK, YOU GOT THE
GIFTS, NOT ALL YOU NEED IS SOME
MOVES.
YES!
WE'VE GOT A PERFECT DANCE
CONSULTANT FOR YOU.
WE'VE GOT tWITCH.
tWITCH IS GOING TO HELP US.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: YES!
WELL DONE, SON.
NOW, tWITCH KNOWS I DIDN'T
WANT TO BE THE ONLY SEXY GUY
AROUND HERE SO IT'S CLEAR THAT
"PEOPLE" HAVE ANNOUNCED THAT YOU
ARE THE SEXIEST DANCER ALIVE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> John: AND I HEARD THAT
"ELLEN" CREATED A LITTLE CLIP
ABOUT MY WIFE, CHRISSY, SHE'S
CALLING IT A CELEBRITY FUN FACT
CLIP.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU PUT TOGETHER.
>> I HAVE HORRIBLE FEET, NOW YOU
ARE ALL GOING TO LOOK AT MY
FEET.
>> John: WHY WOULD YOU SAY
THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW, I SAY THE WRONG
THING ALL THE TIME.
THIS IS A TERRIBLE STORY
ALREADY.
JOHN ALWAYS SAYS, IF I DIE --
>> JOHN SAYS IF YOU DIE...
>> ALL HE HAS TO DO IN THE
MORGUE, INSTEAD OF LIFTING UP
THE SHEET ON THE FACE, HE'LL
JUST DO IT THE OTHER WAY.
HE CAN TELL BY MY FEET.
[LAUGHTER]
SHALL BE LIKE "YEP, THAT'S HER."
>> YOU ALL ARE ADORABLE.
>> John: IT'S TRUE.
MY WIFE'S FEET ARE UNIQUE, YOU
KNOW?
AND I AM PERSONALLY IN LOVE WITH
HER FEET.
I LOVE HER FEET A LOT AND IN
HONOR OF VALENTINE'S DAY I ASKED
THE GOOD FOLKS ASKED ME TO TO
PUT TOGETHER A TRIBUTE TO HER
PERFECTLY UNIQUE FEATS.
PLEASE ENJOY THIS CLIP.
["ALL OF ME" PLAYING]
SICKLE MUSICAL
♪ ♪
>> John: HONESTLY, SHE IS
LITERALLY GOING TO KILL ME.
BUT I THINK THOSE FEET ARE
BEAUTIFUL AND I LOVE THEM AND I
WANT TO SAY HAPPY
VALENTINE'S DAY TO MY WIFE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> YOU LIGHT THE CANDLE AND THEN
IT TURNS INTO MASSAGE OIL.
>> John: SHE LIKES A GOOD
MASSAGE.
SPEAK I THINK SHE NEEDS A FOOT
♪ ♪
SFX [can opens]
♪ Whenever, Wherever ♪
♪ We're meant to be together ♪
[laughter]
♪ I'm at your feet ♪
♪ Whenever, Wherever ♪
(sneezing)
♪♪
Grab a Kleenex Ultra Soft tissue
and grab every moment.
Made with superior softness,
for your comfort.
Kleenex. The softest ultra
tissue.
It's tough to quit smoking
cold turkey.
So CHANTIX can help you quit
slow turkey.
Along with support, CHANTIX
is proven to help you quit.
With CHANTIX you can keep
smoking at first
and ease into quitting.
CHANTIX reduces the urge
so when the day arrives,
you'll be more ready to kiss
cigarettes goodbye.
When you try to quit smoking,
with or without CHANTIX,
you may have nicotine
withdrawal symptoms.
Stop CHANTIX and
get help right away
if you have changes
in behavior or thinking,
aggression, hostility,
depressed mood,
suicidal thoughts or actions,
seizures,
new or worse heart or blood
vessel problems, sleepwalking,
or life-threatening allergic
and skin reactions.
Decrease alcohol use.
Use caution driving
or operating machinery.
Tell your doctor if you've had
mental health problems.
The most common side effect
is nausea.
Quit smoking slow turkey.
Talk to your doctor
about CHANTIX.
So, you bought those "good
enough" paper towels?
[daughter laughs]
Not such a bargain.
There's Only One Quicker Picker
Upper.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
At Philadelphia, we know what
makes the perfect schmear
of cream cheese.
You need only the freshest
milk and cream.
That one!
And the world's best,
and possibly only, schmelier.
Philadelphia.
Schmear perfection.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: ARE FIRST TO CAST HAS
NOT ONLY WON AND OSCAR, A GOLDEN
GROW, AND AN EMMY AWARD, SHE
ALSO RUNS AN EMPIRE CALLED HOOP.
PLEASE WELCOME MY FRIEND
GWYNETH PALTROW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> John: THIS
IS MY SECOND
TIME GUEST HOSTING.
HOW AM I DOING?
>> YOU'RE KILLING IT, YOU'RE
CRUSHING IT.
IN THAT SUIT THAT SUIT.
>> John: THIS IS MY
VALENTINE'S DAY SUIT.
>> YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU'RE SO CHARMING.
ISN'T HE DOING AN AMAZING JOB?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: ENOUGH ABOUT ME.
OUR GUEST HERE IS GWYNETH AND WE
ARE SO EXCITED TO HAVE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR DOING THIS.
YOU'RE HERE ON VALENTINE'S DAY.
DO YOU LIKE TO CELEBRATE
VALENTINE'S DAY?
>> I DO.
I LOVE VALENTINE'S DAY.
I'M VERY ROMANTIC.
ARE YOU?
YOU'RE INTO IT?
>> I AM THE KING OF
VALENTINE'S DAY NOW WE JUST
FOUND OUT.
>> YOU DID.
>> John: BUT I DO HAVE A
QUESTION.
I THINK THIS HAPPENS A LOT, BUT
CHRISSY TOLD ME IT'S JUST A
HALLMARK HOLIDAY, YOU DON'T NEED
TO GET MANY PRESENTS.
IS THIS A TRAP?
>> TRAP.
OF COURSE.
YES!
>> John: WHAT YOU WILL SAY
THIS IF YOU DON'T MEAN IT?
>> I DON'T.
[LAUGHTER]
>> John: SO I SHOULD GET HER
SOMETHING CUSTOMER >>
DEFINITELY.
>> John: YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS?
>> OH, YEAH.
WE HAVE ACTUALLY, WE SELL, WE
DON'T MAKE IT BUT WE SELL THIS
CANDLE, YOU LIGHT THE CANDLE AND
THEN IT TURNS INTO MASSAGE OIL.
>> John: SHE LIKES A GOOD
MASSAGE.
>> I THINK SHE NEEDS A FOOT
[LAUGHTER]
MASSAGE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
>> John: I THINK I NEED
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SECURITY WHEN I GO HOME.
>> John: I THINK I NEED
I THINK I'M REALLY GOING TO BE
SECURITY WHEN I GO HOME.
IN TROUBLE.
I THINK I'M REALLY GOING TO BE
NOW, YOU BEEN MARRIED NOW FOR A
IN TROUBLE.
YEAR.
NOW, YOU BEEN MARRIED NOW FOR A
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YEAR.
SPEAK I THINK YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I LOVE BEING MARRIED.
SPEAK I THINK YOU!
>> John: SO BRAD IS A
I LOVE BEING MARRIED.
WONDERFUL GUY, HE'S A WRITER,
>> John: SO BRAD IS A
PRODUCER, AND YOU GUYS HAVE LIKE
WONDERFUL GUY, HE'S A WRITER,
A FAMILY COUPLE NAME NOW?
PRODUCER, AND YOU GUYS HAVE LIKE
>> WE DO.
A FAMILY COUPLE NAME NOW?
HIS LESSENING THE SPELL CHECK
>> WE DO.
AND MINUS PALTROW.
HIS LESSENING THE SPELL CHECK
SO PEOPLE STARTED CALLING US,
AND MINUS PALTROW.
THEY ARE LIKE, WHAT SHOULD IT B
SO PEOPLE STARTED CALLING US,
BE.
THEY ARE LIKE, WHAT SHOULD IT B
I THINK FALTROW SHOULD BE AT.
BE.
>> John: CHRISSY AND I CAN'T
I THINK FALTROW SHOULD BE AT.
GET IT COUPLE NAME.
>> John: CHRISSY AND I CAN'T
BUT HE WROTE "THE POLITICIAN."
GET IT COUPLE NAME.
WE ARE BIG FANS OF YOU AS AN
BUT HE WROTE "THE POLITICIAN."
ACTOR, YOU ARE A CEO WHEN YOU DO
WE ARE BIG FANS OF YOU AS AN
EVERYTHING.
ACTOR, YOU ARE A CEO WHEN YOU DO
>> HE CONVINCED ME.
EVERYTHING.
>> John: YOU SAID YOU WERE
>> HE CONVINCED ME.
GOING TO RETIRE.
>> John: YOU SAID YOU WERE
>> I WANTED TO TAKE A BIT OF A
GOING TO RETIRE.
SABBATICAL BUT HE WROTE THIS
>> I WANTED TO TAKE A BIT OF A
PART FOR ME AND HE IS VERY GOOD
SABBATICAL BUT HE WROTE THIS
IN BED SO HERE WE ARE.
PART FOR ME AND HE IS VERY GOOD
>> John: WELL, HAPPY
IN BED SO HERE WE ARE.
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> John: WELL, HAPPY
SO, ALL RIGHT, YOU ARE IN "THE
VALENTINE'S DAY.
POLITICIAN" AND IT'S COMING BACK
SO, ALL RIGHT, YOU ARE IN "THE
FOR SEASON TWO.
POLITICIAN" AND IT'S COMING BACK
>> IT'S COMING BACK FOR SEASON
FOR SEASON TWO.
TWO.
>> IT'S COMING BACK FOR SEASON
>> John: THAT'S SO EXCITING.
TWO.
NOW THIS IS ON NETFLIX, JUST
>> John: THAT'S SO EXCITING.
LIKE YOUR SHOW, "THE GOOP LAB."
NOW THIS IS ON NETFLIX, JUST
>> HAS ANYONE SEEN
LIKE YOUR SHOW, "THE GOOP LAB."
"THE GOOP LAB" AT?
>> HAS ANYONE SEEN
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
"THE GOOP LAB" AT?
>> John: WHERE EXCITING THAT
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SEASON TWO IS COMING BACK, NOW
>> John: WHERE EXCITING THAT
YOU HAVE A COUPLE OF KIDS, I
SEASON TWO IS COMING BACK, NOW
HAVE A COUPLE OF KIDS, TOO.
YOU HAVE A COUPLE OF KIDS, I
YOU HAVE A GROWN-UP BOY, I HAVE
HAVE A COUPLE OF KIDS, TOO.
A GROWN-UP WAY BUT YOURS ARE
YOU HAVE A GROWN-UP BOY, I HAVE
LITTLE OLDER THAN MINE NOW.
A GROWN-UP WAY BUT YOURS ARE
>> MINOR ALMOST 16 AND 14, I
LITTLE OLDER THAN MINE NOW.
DON'T KNOW HOW THAT HAPPENS.
>> MINOR ALMOST 16 AND 14, I
>> John: THERE'S A POINT WHEN
DON'T KNOW HOW THAT HAPPENS.
THEY STOP THINKING THEIR PARENTS
>> John: THERE'S A POINT WHEN
ARE COOL AND IT'S A LITTLE MORE
THEY STOP THINKING THEIR PARENTS
EMBARRASSING, IS IT POSSIBLE
ARE COOL AND IT'S A LITTLE MORE
THAT YOU, BEING ONE OF THE
EMBARRASSING, IS IT POSSIBLE
COOLEST WOMEN ON EARTH COULD
THAT YOU, BEING ONE OF THE
POSSIBLY EMBARRASS YOUR KIDS?
COOLEST WOMEN ON EARTH COULD
>> I MEAN COME UP MY DAUGHTER
POSSIBLY EMBARRASS YOUR KIDS?
FINDS ME MORTIFYING.
>> I MEAN COME UP MY DAUGHTER
>> John: HOW?
FINDS ME MORTIFYING.
>> BECAUSE, LIKE, IF I DO
>> John: HOW?
ANYTHING IN PUBLIC PAST JUSTICE,
>> BECAUSE, LIKE, IF I DO
NOT TALKING AND STANDING STILL,
ANYTHING IN PUBLIC PAST JUSTICE,
SHE'S LIKE, OH, MY GOD, OH, MY
NOT TALKING AND STANDING STILL,
GOD, .
SHE'S LIKE, OH, MY GOD, OH, MY
>> John: HOW OLD IS SHE NOW?
GOD, .
>> SHE'S ALMOST 16.
>> John: HOW OLD IS SHE NOW?
SHE'LL BE 16 IN MAY.
>> SHE'S ALMOST 16.
IF I DANCE, IT'S LIKE SHE TURNS
SHE'LL BE 16 IN MAY.
RED.
IF I DANCE, IT'S LIKE SHE TURNS
>> John: WE ALL HAVE THOSE NEW
RED.
DANCES.
>> John: WE ALL HAVE THOSE NEW
>> THE TICK-TOCK THEN, CAN YOU
DANCES.
DO THIS?
>> THE TICK-TOCK THEN, CAN YOU
THESE TICK-TOCK THINGS?
DO THIS?
SPEAK TO ANYONE I CAN TEACH YOU
THESE TICK-TOCK THINGS?
SOME.
SPEAK TO ANYONE I CAN TEACH YOU
>> John: YOU'LL STILL BE
SOME.
EMBARRASSING BUT AT LEAST YOU'LL
>> John: YOU'LL STILL BE
KNOW.
EMBARRASSING BUT AT LEAST YOU'LL
>> THAT'S THE STORY OF MY LIFE
KNOW.
RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT'S THE STORY OF MY LIFE
>> John: SO IS YOUR DAUGHTER
RIGHT NOW.
DRIVING ALREADY?
>> John: SO IS YOUR DAUGHTER
>> SHE HAS HER LEARNER'S PERMIT.
DRIVING ALREADY?
>> John: THAT STRESSFUL.
>> SHE HAS HER LEARNER'S PERMIT.
>> SHE DRIVES US TO SCHOOL NOW
>> John: THAT STRESSFUL.
IN THE MORNING.
>> SHE DRIVES US TO SCHOOL NOW
I KNOW, IT'S CRAZY, IT'S A
IN THE MORNING.
WEIRD.
I KNOW, IT'S CRAZY, IT'S A
>> John: ARE YOU SCARED?
WEIRD.
>> NO, SHE'S A REALLY GOOD
>> John: ARE YOU SCARED?
DRIVER.
>> NO, SHE'S A REALLY GOOD
I TRY TO BE, THE FIRST TIME I
DRIVER.
FAILED AS A MOTHER, BECAUSE SHE
I TRY TO BE, THE FIRST TIME I
WENT THROUGH A RED LIGHT AND I
FAILED AS A MOTHER, BECAUSE SHE
KIND OF YELLED AT HER.
WENT THROUGH A RED LIGHT AND I
AND THEN SHE STARTED CRYING AND
KIND OF YELLED AT HER.
IT WAS JUST TERRIBLE AND I FELT
AND THEN SHE STARTED CRYING AND
SO BAD SO I WAS LIKE, OKAY, YOU
IT WAS JUST TERRIBLE AND I FELT
KNOW WHAT?
SO BAD SO I WAS LIKE, OKAY, YOU
I'M GOING TO BE CHILL AND I'M
KNOW WHAT?
JUST GOING TO PRETEND, AND YOU
I'M GOING TO BE CHILL AND I'M
KNOW WHAT?
JUST GOING TO PRETEND, AND YOU
SHE'S NOW AN AMAZING DRIVER AND
KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'VE LEARNED FROM MY
SHE'S NOW AN AMAZING DRIVER AND
MISTAKES.
I THINK I'VE LEARNED FROM MY
>> John: OKAY.
MISTAKES.
I'VE GOT SOME TIME.
>> John: OKAY.
LUNA HAS BEEN DRIVING THIS
I'VE GOT SOME TIME.
LITTLE CONVERTIBLE AROUND THE
LUNA HAS BEEN DRIVING THIS
DRIVEWAY AT OUR HOUSE AND SHE IS
LITTLE CONVERTIBLE AROUND THE
SURVIVED SO FAR.
DRIVEWAY AT OUR HOUSE AND SHE IS
>> THAT'S GOOD.
SURVIVED SO FAR.
>> John: I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> YOU CAN SEE HOW THEY START TO
>> John: I DON'T KNOW.
TAKE ON CERTAIN ASPECTS OF YOU.
>> YOU CAN SEE HOW THEY START TO
LIKE I KIND OF HAVE ROAD RAGE IN
TAKE ON CERTAIN ASPECTS OF YOU.
THE CAR.
LIKE I KIND OF HAVE ROAD RAGE IN
>> John: CHRISSY DOES COME
THE CAR.
TOO.
>> John: CHRISSY DOES COME
>> SHE DOES?
TOO.
IT'S LIKE THE PLACE I GET OUT MY
>> SHE DOES?
ANGER.
IT'S LIKE THE PLACE I GET OUT MY
I WANT TO YELL AT SOMEONE WHERE
ANGER.
NO ONE CAN HEAR ME, YOU KNOW?
I WANT TO YELL AT SOMEONE WHERE
>> John: THE ONLY TIME ON THE
NO ONE CAN HEAR ME, YOU KNOW?
PRECIPICE WHEN I'M DRIVING.
>> John: THE ONLY TIME ON THE
I'M LIKE THE CALMEST PERSON BUT
PRECIPICE WHEN I'M DRIVING.
I'M AGGRESSIVE WHEN I'M DRIVING.
I'M LIKE THE CALMEST PERSON BUT
BUT ROAD RAGE FEELS FUTILE TO
I'M AGGRESSIVE WHEN I'M DRIVING.
ME.
BUT ROAD RAGE FEELS FUTILE TO
>> IT IS FUTILE, IT'S RIDICULOUS
ME.
BUT I NOW IS
>> IT IS FUTILE, IT'S RIDICULOUS
ELL AT PEOE.
BUT I NOW IS
>>ohn: I
ELL AT PEOE.
LIKE MOTHER LIKE DAUGHTER.
>>ohn: I
WE WILL TALK ABOUT YOUR SOLD OUT
LIKE MOTHER LIKE DAUGHTER.
AFTER THIS.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT YOUR SOLD OUT
>> ?
AFTER THIS.
OKAY.
>> ?
[CPPLAUSE]
OKAY.
>> ACTUALLY, CHRISSY WOULD
[CPPLAUSE]
REALLY, REALLY BENEFIT.
>> ACTUALLY, CHRISSY WOULD
>> John: I ASSUME YOUR HUSBAND
REALLY, REALLY BENEFIT.
IS A FAN OF THIS, TOO?
>> John: I ASSUME YOUR HUSBAND
>> MY HUSBAND CAN'T GET ENOUGH
IS A FAN OF THIS, TOO?
OF IT.
>> MY HUSBAND CAN'T GET ENOUGH
>> SHARE!
OF IT.
MADONNA!
>>> WE ALL WANT OUR KIDS TO BE
SAFE, NOW A ONCE-BANNED PRODUCT
.
WE'LL TOLL YOU WHAT YOU CAN DO
TO PROTECT YOU.
urt alternative.
Cut! Why did you eat that?
'Cause it tastes amazing.
Do you want to try it?
Delicious Almond Breeze
Almondmilk Yogurt Alternative.
Available now.
♪
I am so glad we did this.
I can't believe
we're actually here.
Notifying you quickly when we
suspect fraudulent activity.
TD Bank.
Unexpectedly Human.
RAISED IN AN ERA WHERE IT WAS
VERY MUCH ABOUT THE GUY AND
TRYING TO LOOK GOOD FOR THE GUY
AND DO WHAT THE GUY WANTED, BE
THE COOL GIRL, YOU KNOW?
>> AND SINCE YOU WERE 18 YOU
BEEN AT UNIVERSAL SEX SYMBOL.
>> WELL...
>> John: WE ARE BACK WITH
GWYNETH PALTROW, EVERYBODY.
UNIVERSAL SEX SYMBOL.
>> I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR.
>> John: ANNA "THE GOOP LAB"
YOU GUYS GET INTO SOME STUFF.
YOUR EMPLOYEES, YOU HAVE THEM
TRYING ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
>> YEAH.
THERE'S AN EPISODE ON
PSYCHEDELICS.
THERE'S A BIG GOVERNMENT FUNDED
STUDY RIGHT NOW FOR USING
PSYCHEDELICS TO HELP WITH
DEPRESSION AND PTSD.
>> John: AND YOU'RE ALLOWED TO
USE THEM?
>> IN JAMAICA YOU ARE.
SO WE SENT SOME OF THE STAFFERS
TO JAMAICA TO DO A HEALING TRIP.
SO THAT WAS FASCINATING.
SO, YEAH, I THINK MAYBE OUR HR
DEPARTMENT HAS SOME FORMS FOR
WORK.
>> John: LIKE, IF I HAPPEN TO
HAVE A REALLY BAD TRIP...
>> YEAH, OR GET NAKED ON TV,
YEAH.
>> John: THERE'S A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT ORGANS.
AND PLEASURE.
>> YEAH, AND I THINK IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT.
AS I SAID IN THAT LITTLE CLIP, I
THINK THE IDEA THAT WOMEN CAN BE
CONNECTED TO THEIR SEXUALITY.
>> John: AND DESERVE PLEASURE.
>> IT'S A NEW HARD THING FOR
SOME OF US TO UNDERSTAND SO IT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT TO ME TO MAKE
ONE OF THE EPISODES ABOUT THAT
AND ABOUT GETTING CLOSE TO
YOURSELF AND UNDERSTANDING WHAT
YOU WANT AND WHAT YOU DESERVE
AND ASKING FOR WHAT YOU WANT AS
WELL.
[APPLAUSE]
>> John: I THINK THAT'S GREAT.
I'VE BEEN A BIG FAN OF MAKING
SURE WOMEN GET PLEASURE.
[LAUGHTER]
I'VE BEEN SUPPORTIVE OF THIS
CAUSE FOR A LONG TIME.
>> YEAH, I HAD A FEELING.
>> John: BUT ANYWAY, YOU HAVE
A CANDLE OUT, A VERY SPECIAL
ONE.
>> CAN I JUST TELL YOU THE STORY
OF THE SCANDAL?
>> John: IT SMELLS LIKE, I
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT SMELLS LIKE
COME UP I DON'T KNOW BUT, WHAT
DOES IT SMELL LIKE?
>> WELL, THE CANDLE ITSELF
SMELLS LIKE ROSES BUT --
>> John: WHAT WAS THE
INSPIRATION FOR THE CANDLE?
>> WELL THE CANDLE IS CALLED
"THIS SMELLS LIKE MY VAGINA."
>> John: THIS CANDLE!"
AT SUNSET ON THE BOX.
AND WHO IS THE "MY" IN THIS
INSTANCE?
>> IT REALLY WAS, IT'S THIS
AMAZING BRAND NAMED HERETIC.
THEY CREATE ALL CLEAN FRAGRANCES
AND SO IT WAS REALLY LIKE A
FEMINIST STATEMENT.
>> John: AND IT IS SOMETHING
THAT APPLE COULD ALSO BE
EMBARRASSED BY?
>> EXACTLY.
BUT I THINK IT'S THE IDEA THAT,
AGAIN, WOMEN HAVE BEEN TAUGHT TO
HAVE A CERTAIN DEGREE OF SHAME
OR EMBARRASSMENT ABOUT THEIR
BODIES AND SO IF YOU JUST LIGHT
A CANDLE THAT SAYS "THIS SMELLS
LIKE MY VAGINA AND PUT IT ON THE
COFFEE TABLE IS A LITTLE BIT
OF A PUNK ROCK STATEMENT.
>> John: AND COLD AND FLU
SEASON IS COMING UP, DO WE HAVE
ANY GOOP PRODUCTS FOR THAT?
WHAT WE HAVE?
>> WE'VE GOT THESE INCREDIBLE
CHOOSE.
WE HAVE ONE FOR IMMUNITY WHICH
IS CALLED "PERFECT ATTENDANCE."
WHEN THAT'S FOR THE BRAIN CALLED
"NERD ALERT" AND ONE THAT'S FOR
SLEEP THAT I'M OBSESSED WITH,
IT'S CALLED "KNOCK ME OUT," I
TAKE IT EVERY NIGHT, IT'S FULL
OF MELATONIN AND ALL KINDS OF
AMAZING, NATURAL INGREDIENTS.
IT'S ALL AMAZING QUALITY.
AND YEAH, THEY ARE AMAZING.
>> John: I THINK THE COOLEST
THING ABOUT THEM IS THAT THE
AUDIENCE IS GOING TO GET THEM.
EVERYBODY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE BACK!
>> ACTUALLY, CHRISSY WOULD
REALLY, REALLY BENEFIT.
>> John: I ASSUME YOUR HUSBAND
IS A FAN OF THIS, TOO?
>> MY HUSBAND CAN'T GET ENOUGH
OF IT.
♪ ♪
>>> GOOD FRIDAY AFTERN
LEON HARRIS WITH A QUICK LOOK AT
THE STORIES WE'RE WORK
>>> AND A POPULAR WEIGHT LOSS
DRUG AND INCREASED CHA.
>>> AND SUPER STRONG TOY MAGNETS
THAT WERE BANNED SEVERAL YEARS
AGO, THEY'RE BACK ON T
WE EXPLAIN THE REASON WHY AND
WHAT YOU NEED KNOW TO OT
>>> PLUS THE COLDEST WEATHER OF
THE WINTER HITTING US NOW.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT 4:00.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: WE ARE BACK WITH
GWYNETH PALTROW, FOLKS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT COME UP WHEN IT, SINCE YOU
ARE A CEO WE THOUGHT WE'D SEE
HOW WELL YOU DO AT OUR LITTLE
GAME.
IT'S CALLED "PITCH PLEASE."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> PITCH PLEASE!
>> John: SO IN THIS GAME WE'RE
GOING TO TRY TO SELL A PRODUCT
LIKE THEY DO ON THE SHOPPING
NETWORK.
YOU WON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
SELLING.
BUT THE AUDIENCE WELL.
I'LL ASK YOU QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
PRODUCT AND YOU HAVE TO DESCRIBE
THIS PRODUCT WITH AS MUCH
CONVINCING SALES PITCH AS YOU
CAN WITHOUT ACTUALLY KNOWING
WHAT IT IS.
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
>> BEFORE WE START, BASED ON OUR
CONVERSATION, I GOT YOU A BAG OF
GOODIES FOR CHRISSY.
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> John: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WHEN YOUR WIFE TELLS YOU SHE
DOESN'T WANT SOMETHING FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY, GET HER A GOOP
BAG.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> John: LET'S TRY TO SELL
SOMETHING.
HERE'S WHAT YOU'LL BE SELLING.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> John: ARE YOU READY?
>> I'M READY.
>> John: OKAY.
FIRST QUESTION, HOW MUCH WOULD
YOU SELL IT FOR ON GOOP?
>> OH, YOU KNOW, SOMETHING THIS
AMAZING AND HIGH QUALITY --
[LAUGHTER]
>> MAYBE $75.
>> John: THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS
ABOUT RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
CAN YOU ACCESSORIZE IT, THOUGH?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THIS HONESTLY LOOKS BEST WITH
SOMETHING FEATHERY AROUND THE
FACE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> YOU KNOW, SOMETHING THAT
REALLY EXPRESSES WHO YOU ARE SO
I WOULD SAY WHEN YOU ARE
ACCESSORIZING WITH THIS AMAZING
THING JUST TO GO FOR IT.
SPARKLE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: YES, YES.
>> John: YES!
I ASSUME YOUR HUSBAND IS A FAN
OF THIS, TOO?
>> MY HUSBAND CANNOT GET ENOUGH.
THIS IS HIS FAVORITE.
>> John: I BET IT IS.
WHAT ABOUT WHEN YOU'RE ALONE,
WOULD YOU USE IT?
>> YES, BUT IT'S ALSO GOOD WITH
OTHERS.
>> John: YEP, YEP, I BET IT
IS, AND HOW MANY TIMES A DAY
WOULD YOU USE IT?
>> HONESTLY AT LEAST SIX OR
SEVEN TIMES A DAY.
>> John: WHAT TIME OF DAY IS
BEST?
>> ANYTIME!
B1 YES, ANYTIME.
>> THERE IS WRONG TIME FOR THIS.
>> John: WHAT DID YOU START
USING IT YOURSELF?
>> I MEAN PROBABLY AROUND 12
YEARS OLD?
[LAUGHTER]
>> John: OKAY.
SHOW ME THE FACE YOU MAKE WHEN
YOU USE IT.
>> OH...
[LAUGHTER]
>> John: ALL RIGHT, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN.
HERE IS WHAT GWYNETH DESCRIBED.
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S VALENTINE'S DAY!
"THE GOOP LAB" IS NOW STREAMING
ON NETFLIX AND WE WILL BE RIGHT
BACK.
THANK YOU, GWYNETH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz.
The first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those
with moderate
to severe
psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement of
their psoriasis
plaques.
Some even
saw 100%
clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
ANNOUNCER: People aren't talking
about Giant's all-natural
Nature's Promise Chicken.
They're not talking about
our fresh, pre-cut veggies.
Or Giant's delicious grab-and-go
salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking...
because they're eating.
Oh wow. Yum!
At Giant, we carry over
900 Nature's Promise products
that we feel good about feeding
our families, so you can, too.
The little things are Giant.
♪♪
At Walgreens,
we love smart savers.
Like movie savers.
Tee-time savers.
And especially
Medicare Part D savers.
So you probably know
making Walgreens your
preferred pharmacy means
up to $5 off on copays
and 100 rewards points
on prescriptions.
Because you're smart like that.
Save smartly on Med D.
Walgreens.
Trusted since 1901.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: ALL RIGHT.
YOU ALL LIKE STARBUCKS, RIGHT?
WELL, ELLEN HAS BEEN PARTNERING
WITH STARBUCKS REWARDS AND SINCE
I'M GUEST HOSTING TODAY I
THOUGHT ELLEN AND I COULD SHARE
PARTNERS, RIGHT?
YOU CAN EARN REWARDS BY USING
THE STARBUCKS APP SO EARLIER
TODAY I WENT TO STARBUCKS IN
BURBANK TO REWARD UNSUSPECTING
CUSTOMERS WITH MY TALENTS.
HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED.
♪ ♪
HAD MET, GUYS, HOW ARE YOU
DOING, I'M JOHN.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
NICE TO MEET YOU.
ARE YOU GUYS A COUPLE?
JUST BUCK'S BUDDIES?
I WROTE THAT ONE MYSELF.
I'M JUST SPREADING A LITTLE
VALENTINES CHEER AROUND HERE.
I'VE GOT MY FRIEND, HER NAME IS
LINDSAY, SHE PLAYS THE VIOLIN.
I HAVE A NEW SONG CALLED
"CONVERSATIONS IN THE DARK" AND
I WROTE A NEW VERSION.
♪ LETS HAVE CONVERSATIONS OVER
COFFEE ♪
♪ LET'S HAVE CONVERSATIONS AT
STARBUCKS ♪
♪ AT STARBUCKS ♪
♪ [LAUGHTER]
>> HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
WHAT ARE WE HAVING?
>> A VENTI GREEN TEA LEMONADE,
PLEASE.
♪ TALL FOR YOU, GROUND DAY FOR
ME ♪
♪ ITS PROPER PROPER CHINO ♪
♪ HAPPY VALENTINO'S ♪
I DON'T KNOW, JUST WORKING ON
IDEAS.
FREE VALENTINES CAKE POPS, WHO
WANTS THEM QUESTION WHAT DOES
ANYONE WANT TO CAKE POP?
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
CAKE POPS.
I'VE GOT MORE.
WHO LIKES WHIPPED CREAM?
HERE'S A STARBUCKS REWARD.
THERE WE GO.
OH, YEAH, IT'S GETTING SEXY IN
HERE.
MY PLEASURE.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME, TOO?
ON YOUR HAND?
YOU WANT SOME, TOO?
THERE YOU GO.
WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO?
JOHN LEGEND?
I HOPE SO.
THIS IS GREAT.
I BROUGHT A PIANO, GUYS.
♪ L IS FOR THE WAY YOU LOOK AT
ME ♪
♪ O IS FOR THE ONLY ONE I SEE ♪
♪ B IS VERY, VERY EXTRAORDINARY
EXTRAORDINARY ♪
♪ E IS EVEN MORE THAN ANYONE
THAT YOU ADORE ♪
♪ LOVE WAS MADE FOR ME AND
YOU ♪
THANK YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: WILL BE BACK!
>> MERYL STREEP!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CHER!"
>> MERYL STREEP!
MADONNA!
CHER!"
♪
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: WELCOME BACK TO THE
JOHN LEGEND SHOW!
LIKE ELLEN I LOVE TO PLAY GAMES
AND RIGHT NOW WE'RE GOING TO
PLAY IT ONE OF MY FAVORITE GAME
GAMES.
IT'S TIME FOR HOT HANDS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: SO, WHERE IS DESTINY?
HEY, DESTINY!
WELCOME!
HELLO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU IN OUR HOT SEAT
FOR HOT HANDS.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT HOW THIS
GAME WORKS.
WE WILL SHOW YOU A PICTURE YOU
HAVE THREE SECONDS TO GUESS WHO
IT IS.
ONCE YOU SAY THE NAME YOU HIT
THE BUTTON TO MOVE TO THE NEXT
PICTURE AND IF YOU CAN NAME TEN
PICTURES IN 30 SECONDS YOU'LL
WIN $5,000!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YES!
DESTINY, YOUR CATEGORY IS
LEGENDS.
>> I GOT THIS.
>> John: DO YOU GET IT, MY
NAME IS JOHN LEGEND.
ALL RIGHT.
GET YOUR HOT HANDS READY.
AND GO!
>> ELLEN DeGENERES!"
BEYONCE!
SKIP!"
MARIAH CAREY X?
MARILYN MONROE X?
SKIP!
MERYL STREEP!"
CHER!"
MADONNA!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: YOU GOT IT!
$5,000!
THAT IS HOW YOU PLAY HOT HANDS!
TUNE IN NEXT WEEK.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND A
New Country Crock Plant Butter
tastes like butter.
Which means it's even loved by
5 year old Cammie.
Who doesn't eat anything but
buttered noodles.
[clears throat]
Oh right...
and now plant buttered noodles.
Mmm
Even butter lovers love it.
Because of these stretch marks,
I have the most beautiful
child in the world.
My childhood memories
30 years friendship
Stories that deserve
the best care.
Dove Body Wash's new formula
with skin natural...
...moisturizers works
with your skin for lasting care.
So your skin
can keep telling stories
beautifully
New Dove Body Wash
proven lasting care for the skin
you live in.
New Dove Body Wash
Cheerios... Do I look like a
child to you?
Honey Nut Cheerios
are heart healthy
and can help lower
cholesterol.
That's why we introduced
heart shapes.
Get it?
Ummm
Did you just ummm?
No.
I'm pretty sure I heard a ummm.
♪ ♪
Ugh...What the what?
Okay wipe
pretty-please do your thing...
nice!
Nailed it!
Huggies® Natural Care® wipes,
gentle like A HUG.
HUGG ON
[police siren]
Michael, your a singer.
bubly is a sparkling water.
Sure is.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Lo necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month,
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Plus, you can get up to $200 in
Visa Prepaid Cards.
Mix and match your perfect
Fios plan.
Only on Verizon.
>> John: OUR NEXT GUEST WON
HIS FOURTH GRADE SPELLING BEE.
HE ALSO JUST LEARN TO SWIM LAST
YEAR.
HERE TO PERFORM HIS NEW SONG,
"CONVERSATIONS IN THE DARK,"
ALONG WITH HIS FRIEND, LINDSAY
STARLING, PLEASE WELCOME JOHN
LEGEND!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪ LET'S HAVE CONVERSATIONS IN
THE DARK ♪
♪ WORLD IS SLEEPING, I'M AWAKE
WITH YOU ♪
♪ WITH YOU ♪
♪ WATCH ♪
♪ MOVIES THAT WE'VE BOTH ALREADY
SEEN ♪
♪ I AIN'T EVEN LOOKING AT THE
SCREEN, IT'S TRUE ♪
♪ I GOT MY EYES ON YOU ♪
♪ AND YOU SAY THAT YOU'RE NOT
WORTH IT ♪
♪ YOU GET HUNG UP ON YOUR
FLAWS ♪
♪ WELL, IN MY EYES YOU ARE
PERFECT ♪
♪ AS YOU ARE ♪
♪ I WILL NEVER TRY TO CHANGE
YOU, CHANGE YOU ♪
♪ I WILL ALWAYS WANT THE SAME
YOU, SAME YOU ♪
♪ SWEAR ON EVERYTHING I PRAY
TO ♪
♪ THAT I WON'T BREAK YOUR
HEART ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WHEN YOU GET
LONELY, LONELY ♪
♪ KEEP THE SECRETS THAT YOU TOLD
ME, TOLD ME ♪
♪ AND YOUR LOVE IS ALL YOU OWE
ME ♪
♪ AND I WON'T BREAK YOUR HEART ♪
♪ ON ♪
♪ SUNDAY MORNINGS WE SLEEP-IN
'TIL NOON ♪
♪ WELL, I CAN SLEEP FOREVER NEXT
TO YOU ♪
♪ NEXT TO YOU ♪
♪ AND WE ♪
♪ WE GOT PLACES WE BOTH GOTTA
BE ♪
♪ BUT THERE AIN'T NOTHING I
WOULD RATHER DO ♪
♪ THEN BLOW OFF ALL MY PLANS FOR
YOU ♪
♪ AND YOU SAY THAT YOU'RE NOT
WORTH IT ♪
♪ AND GET HUNG UP ON YOUR
FLAWS ♪
♪ BUT IN MY EYES YOU ARE
PERFECT ♪
♪ AS YOU ARE ♪
♪ I WILL NEVER TRY TO CHANGE
YU, CHANGE YOU ♪
♪ I WILL ALWAYS WANT THE SAME
YOU, SAME YOU ♪
♪ SWEAR ON EVERYTHING I PRAY
TO ♪
♪ THAT I WON'T BREAK YOUR
HEART ♪
♪ WHEN NO ONE SEEMS TO NOTICE ♪
♪ AND YOUR DAYS, THEY SEEM SO
HARD ♪
♪ MY DARLING, YOU SHOULD KNOW
THIS ♪
♪ MY LOVE IS EVERYWHERE YOU
ARE ♪
♪ I WILL NEVER TRY TO CHANGE
YOU, CHANGE YOU ♪
♪ I WILL ALWAYS WANT THE SAME
YOU, SAME YOU ♪
♪ SWEAR ON EVERYTHING I PRAY
TO ♪
♪ THAT I WON'T BREAK YOUR
HEART ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE WHEN YOU GET
LONELY, LONELY ♪
♪ KEEP THE SECRETS THAT YOU TOLD
ME, TOLD ME ♪
♪ AND YOUR LOVE IS ALL YOU OWE
ME ♪
♪ AND I WON'T BREAK YOUR HEART ♪
♪ I WON'T BREAK YOUR HEART ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> John: THANK YOU!
THANK YOU LINDSAY.
ELLEN IS SO GREAT, SHE'S GIVING
AWAY TICKETS TO EVERY SHOW ON MY
TO HER.
I WANT TO THINK WHAT PALTROW AND
I WANT TO THANK ELLEN FOR
LETTING ME HOST HER SHOW AGAIN.
AS SHE ALWAYS SAYS, BE KIND TO
ONE ANOTHER.
GOOD-BYE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> RIGHT NOW AT 4:00, BUNDLE UP.
>> BUNDLE UP FOR SURE, WE'RE
TALKING THE COLDEST NUMBERS
WE'VE SEEN ALL WINTER LONG.
>> A CONSUMER ALERT IN ON A
POPULAR WEIGHT LOSS DRUG THAT
INCREASES CHANCES FOR CANCER.
>> THEN LOCAL WOMEN EMPOWERING
THE NEXT GENERATION.
>> I WANT TO HIGHLIGHT BLACK
GIRLS DOING AMAZING THINGS THAT
OTHERWISE MAY NOT GET A CHANCE
TO BE IN A MAGAZINE.
>> WHAT STARTED AS A SIMPLE IDEA
HAS MORPHED INTO AN
INTERNATIONALLY DISTRIBUTED TEEN
MAGAZINE.
>> PLUS CHILD DANGER.
>> ONCE BANNED, THEY'RE BACK ON
THE MARKET AND WHY THEY POSE A
FRIGHTENING RISK TO YOUR KIDS.
>> NEWS4 AT 4:00 STARTS NOW.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON, HAPPY
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> WE WANT TO GET RIGHT TO THE
FORECAST, BECAUSE IT'S LOOKING
LIKE A BITTER COLD DATE NIGHT
AHEAD.
>> CHIEF METEOROLOGIST DOUG
KAMMERER IS IN THE STORM CENTER.
YOU'RE TRACKING SOME OF THE
COLDEST AIR OF THE WINTER.
>> AND IT'S COMING DURING ONE OF
THE HOTTEST NIGHTS OF THE YEAR.
WHAT ARE WE DEALING WITH?
WE'VE GOT CLOUDS AND TAKE A LOOK
AT THE SATELLITE PICTURE BECAUSE
THIS TELLS THE STORY.
YOU CAN SEE THE CLOUDS FROM LAST
NIGHT MAKING THEIR WAY OUT OF
HERE.
LOOK AT THE DIRECTION COMING OUT
OF THE NORTH RIRTH RIGHT OUT OFA
ACROSS OUR REGION.
THAT IS THE COLDER AIR THAT'S
CONTINUING TO MOVE IN.
AND LOOK AT THE WINDCHILLS, 27
IN THE CITY AND 18 IN
HAGERSTOWN, ONLY 7 BACK TOWARDS
PITTSBURGH.
THE COLDER AIR CONTINUING TO
MAKE ITS WAY IN HERE.
WE ARE IN FOR WHAT I THINK WILL
BE ONE OF THE COLDEST NIGHTS
THIS YEAR, SO THE COLDEST
MORNING TOMORROW.
IF YOU ARE HEADING OUT TO
DINNER, BUNDLE UP.
STAYING IN THE 30s TOMORROW AND
THEN THE MILD AIR RETURNS
QUICKLY.
I'LL SHOW YOU JUST HOW LONG IT