Because Mike Bloomberg is the
only democrat who can take on
Trump. And Trump knows it.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪ ♪
♪♪ I'M GOING UNDER AND THIS TIME
I FEAR ♪
♪ THERE'S NO ONE TO SAVE ME ♪
♪ THIS ALL OR NOTHING REALLY GOT
A WAY ♪
♪ OF DRIVING ME CRAZY ♪
♪ I NEED SOMEBODY TO HEAL ♪
♪ SOMEBODY TO KNOW ♪
♪ SOMEBODY TO HAVE ♪
♪ SOMEBODY TO HOLD ♪
♪ IT'S EASY TO SAY ♪
♪ BUT IT'S NEVER THE SAME ♪
♪ I GUESS I KINDA LIKED THE WAY
YOU ♪
♪ NUMBED ALL THE PAIN NOW THE
DAY BLEEDS INTO NIGHTFALL ♪
♪ AND YOU'RE NOT HERE ♪
♪ TO GET ME THROUGH IT ALL ♪
♪ I LET MY GUARD DOWN ♪
♪ AND THEN YOU PULLED THE RUG ♪
♪ I WAS GETTING KINDA USED TO
BEING ♪
♪ SOMEONE YOU LOVED AND I TEND
TO CLOSE MY EYES WHEN IT ♪
♪ HURTS SOMETIMES ♪
♪ I FALL INTO YOUR ARMS ♪
♪ I'LL BE SAFE IN YOUR SOUND
'TIL I COME ♪
♪ BACK AROUND BUT NOW THE DAY
BLEEDS ♪
♪ INTO NIGHTFALL AND YOU'RE NOT
HERE ♪
♪ TO GET ME THROUGH IT ALL I LET
MY GUARD DOWN ♪
♪ AND THEN YOU PULLED THE RUG ♪
♪ I WAS GETTING KINDA USED TO
BEING SOMEONE YOU LOVED ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: WELCOME TO
"THE KELLY CLARKSON SHOW"!
HOW BEAUTIFUL IS THAT DANCE?
GIVE IT UP FOR MY DANCERS!
SO BEAUTIFUL.
"SOMEONE YOU LOVED" IS ANOTHER
ONE OF THE LOVE SONGS WE PICK TO
CELEBRATE, AND IT HAPPENS TO BE
ONE OF MY FAVORITE SONGS
RELEASED IN A VERY LONG TIME.
WEBER REQUESTED THAT SONG IS
SOMEONE I LOVE, GET IT?
THOSE OF THE JOKES WE HAVE TODAY
PAID WHERE IS EVELYN ACT?
EVELYN?
HIGH MIKE EVELYN.
I LOVE YOUR SWEATER.
>> THANK YOU, I LOVE YOU.
>> Kelly: WHAT YOU LOVE THAT
SONG?
BECAUSE I HEARD THE SONG
RECENTLY AND IT REMINDED ME OF A
BREAKUP I HAD IN NEW YORK WHERE
IT WAS GOING GREAT FOR A COUPLE
OF MONTHS AND THEN ALL OF A
SUDDEN JUST ISN'T A THING THE
NEXT DAY.
AND THAT'S FINE, I'M HAPPY NOW,
EVERYTHING HAS WORKED OUT BUT
YOU HEAR THIS SONG AND IT
REMINDS YOU OF WHEN YOU'RE
CRYING IN YOUR BEDROOM, HOLDING
YOUR TEDDY BEAR AND YOU JUST
HAVE TO KNOW --
>> Kelly: MINES USUALLY
ALCOHOL, BUT COOL.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I'M HAPPY TO KNOW THAT THERE
ARE PEOPLE WRITING SONGS ABOUT
THIS AND I JUST LOVE THE SONG.
>> Kelly: IT'S THE COOLEST
THING FOR PEOPLE TO WRITE A
SONG, I'M STILL A HUGE NERD WITH
MUSIC MYSELF, I LOVE THAT, WHERE
YOUR LIGHT, I COULD HAVE WRITTEN
THAT.
I LOVE THAT.
IT'S A REALLY GREAT SONG.
LEWIS CAPALDI, WELL DONE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVELYN.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: 'S LIKE I SAID IT'S
ALL THE FIELDS FEBRUARY.
WE'RE STILL DROPPING THE BOMBS
ALL OVER THE PLACE, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S JUST ONE PART OF THIS
AMAZING HOUR.
ALSO FROM THE NEW SHOW,
"ZOEY'S EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST,"
ONE OF MY FAVORITE
"GILMORE GIRLS" AND HUMANS ON
THE PLANET, LAUREN GRAHAM IS
HERE!
AND YOU ALL BETTER STAY SHARP
BECAUSE THE "IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"
ARE DROPPING BY AND I LOVE THEM.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: SERIOUSLY YOU COULD
BE HAVING THE WORST DAY, YOU
TURN THAT SHOW ON AND IT TURNS
RIGHT AROUND.
IT'S SO AWESOME.
ANYWAY, HERE TO SHOW US HOW TO
MAKE THE YUMMIEST SPICY PORK
BURRITO'S, CHEF ROY CHOI IS IN
OUR KITCHEN!
I'M EXCITED, I'M HUNGRY ALREADY.
AND WE WILL HEAR ABOUT THE
INSPIRE DEMOCRATS APPARENT
EFFORTS OF LILLY TARTIKOFF TO
CURE BREAST CANCER.
BUT FIRST, YOU ALL KNOW HOW
IMPORTANT MUSIC IS IN MY LIFE,
IT'S OBVIOUS AT THIS POINT AND
IT'S A VITAL PART OF MANY
STUDENTS LIVES AS WELL.
SO WHEN 13-YEAR-OLD CAME IN
PETERSON'S MEDICAL CONDITION
KEPT HER FROM PARTICIPATING IN
HER HIGH SCHOOL MARCHING BAND
SHE AND HER MOM HEATHER TOOK IT
PRETTY HARD BUT THEN, HER BAND
TEACHER DID SOMETHING INCREDIBL
INCREDIBLE.
HE BUILT A PERSONALIZED PETTY
CAB WHICH ALLOWED HER TO BE
PULLED THROUGH THE PERFORMANCES
WHILE SHE PLAYS THE DRUMS ARE
HERE TO TELL US MORE ABOUT THIS
HEARTWARMING STORY ARE HEATHER,
KAELIN, AND SCOTT.
HI!
SO, IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND, CAN
YOU TELL US MORE ABOUT YOUR
DAUGHTER'S CONDITION?
>> KAELIN WAS BORN WITH MULTIPLE
CONGENITAL BIRTH DEFECTS.
SHE HAS A HARDER TIME GETTING
AROUND, IT'S HARDER FOR HER TO
WALK AND JUST RECENTLY SHE WAS
DIAGNOSED WITH BORDERLINE
LIFE-THREATENING SCOLIOSIS ON
TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE.
>> Kelly: GOOD GOSH, ONE THING
AFTER THE OTHER.
>> ONE LITTLE JEAN WENT WRONG.
>> Kelly: SCOTT, HOW DID YOU
COME UP WITH THIS IDEA?
>> WE HAD BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS IDEA FOR ABOUT A YEAR
BEFOREHAND, BEFORE WE START
MARCHING IN SEVENTH GRADE
BECAUSE THE HARNESS AND THE
SNARE DRUM WAS FAIRLY DIFFICULT
TO MARCH WITH SO I WAS SEARCHING
AROUND FOR SOMETHING TO MOUNT
SOME SNARE DRUMS TO AND HANDED
UP FINDING A BEAT UP PEDICAB AND
I HAD A GOOD FRIEND WHO WAS A
HANDY WELDER AND SO WE MOUNTED
THE SNARE DRUMS TO THE CART AND
WERE STILL USING IT TODAY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THAT'S AWESOME!
I HAVE ONE REALLY IMPORTANT
WELDING QUESTION FOR YOU, MAYBE
YOU CAN ANSWER THIS ONE --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: JUST KIDDING, IT'S A
LOVE BOMB!
HEATHER HAS SOMETHING SHE WANTS
TO SAY TO SCOTT, GO FOR IT.
>> THANK YOU.
THE REASON THAT I RODE TO KELLY,
AND I GET EMOTIONAL --
>> Kelly: HERE'S THE THING,
WELCOME TO THE SHOW, WE ARE THE
SAME.
>> THE REASON THAT I RODE TO THE
SHOW IS KAELIN FEELS THIS IN HER
HEART AND SHE'S TOO SHY AND SHE
COULDN'T SAY IT, BUT WHAT SHE
FIRST WENT TO SCHOOL, YOUR
SENDING YOUR BABY OFF TO
SOMEWHERE ELSE AND YOU WANT
SOMEBODY TO TAKE CARE OF THEM
AND WHEN SHE GOT HER NEWEST
DIAGNOSIS SHE WAS DONE AT THE
BOTTOM.
SHE WAS HURTING.
SHE HAD TO GO TO HER TEACHER AND
SAY THAT SHE COULDN'T WORK AND
IT ABOUT KILLED HER.
AND THEN HER SUPERHERO CAME IN
HE CHANGED HER LIFE COME OUT OF
THE KINDNESS OF HIS HEART HE
GAVE HER THE ABILITY THAT SHE
DIDN'T HAVE TO DO WHAT SHE LOVED
TO DO.
HOW MUCH MORE LUCKY CAN YOU GET?
WE ARE VERY GRATEFUL AND WE LOVE
YOU FOR WHAT YOU'VE DONE FOR MY
DAUGHTER.
>> Kelly: I DON'T EVEN KNOW
YOU AND I'M THANKFUL.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: WELL, WE THOUGHT YOU
WERE PRETTY RAD, TOO.
SCOTT DOES SO MUCH FOR ALL HIS
STUDENTS WE THOUGHT HE DESERVED
SOME SPECIAL ATTENTION OF HIS
OWN SO WE ARE SENDING HIM TO THE
ALL-INCLUSIVE LUXURY RESORT
WHERE HE WILL ENJOY THE
BEAUTIFUL BEACHES OF MEXICO AND
SO MUCH MORE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE SO MUCH
FUN.
I WISH I COULD GO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
A LOT OF PEOPLE STRUGGLE WITH
THEIR OWN INDIVIDUAL THINGS AND
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE HAD PEOPLE
THAT DO STEP UP AND YOU MIGHT
THINK OH, IT'S SOMETHING SIMPLE
BUT IT WAS REALLY WROTE
MIRACULOUS AND IT MADE HER LIFE,
NOT JUST HER DAY.
SO VERY COOL.
ALL RIGHT.
SO HEATHER HAS GOT ME CRYING
ALREADY.
I CAN'T WATCH PEOPLE CRY.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THIS IF YOU
WATCH MY SHOW.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE WATCHING
CRYING, TURN NOW.
OKAY?
LET'S GET TO MY FIRST GUEST.
YOU'VE SEEN HER IN THE TV SERIES
"PARENTHOOD" AND OF COURSE
"GILMORE GIRLS"!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NOW SHE'S STARTING IN NBC'S
"ZOEY'S EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST,"
PLEASE WELCOME LAUREN GRAHAM,
Y'ALL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YOU LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL, BY THE
WAY.
HELLO.
I LOVE YOU EVERY TIME I SEE YOU,
I GET SO EXCITED.
>> I FEEL THE SAME EXACT WAY.
>> YOU DO NOT.
BUT HOW ABOUT THAT LOVE BOMB?
I WAS LIKE, OH, GOD, THE TISSUES
ARE SO FAR.
>> IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
AND I CAN'T WATCH PEOPLE CRY,
EITHER.
>> Kelly: IT'S CONTAGIOUS.
I CAN CRY ON MY OWN WITHOUT
ANYONE BUT THEN YOU ADD SOMEONE
IN THE MIX.
OKAY, WELL THE LAST TIME WE SAW
EACH OTHER I WAS SEEING YOU ON
BROADWAY.
>> IT WAS SO NICE OF YOU TO
COME.
>> Kelly: I'M A FAN, LAUREN.
LIKE, A REAL FAN.
IF I HAD MORE DAYS OFF I WOULD
FIND YOU AND GO WATCH WHATEVER
YOU ARE DOING.
BUT I THINK THAT YOU'RE JUST SO
MAGICAL.
YOU ARE GREAT ON STAGE.
LIKE YOU SEEM TO BE THAT PERSON
THAT CAN DO EVERYTHING.
DID YOU, YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I
LOOK LIKE WITHOUT ALL OF THIS.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT I LOOK LIKE
AFTER THE THEATER.
>> Kelly: DID YOU GROW UP
DURING MUSICALS?
>> I DID.
I GREW UP DOING ALL KINDS OF
COMMUNITY THEATER AND I ALWAYS
LOVED MUSICAL THEATER AND I
FINALLY GOT MY FIRST LEAD IN
HIGH SCHOOL, I WAS DOLLY IN
"HELLO DOLLY," I'M SURE ALL OF
YOU HAVE SEEN THAT.
>> Kelly: THAT'S A BIG ONE.
>> WHICH IS ONLY STRANGE BECAUSE
YEARS LATER WHEN I STARTED
WORKING PROFESSIONALLY MY FATHER
WOULD STILL TALK ABOUT "HELLO
DOLLY" AND I WAS LIKE, I WAS ON
"SEINFELD," BUT HE'S LIKE, OH,
ALL THE SONGS AND THE COSTUMES.
>> Kelly: BUT IT WAS PROBABLY
THE FIRST TIME HE REALLY SAW YOU
AND WANTS, WOW, SHE'S GOING TO
DO THIS FOR THE REST OF HER
LIFE.
IT WAS PROBABLY THAT NOSTALGIC.
>> IT'S A BIG PART OF IT.
I GOT TO SEE IT RECENTLY ON
BROADWAY WITH BETTE MIDLER.
I KNOW.
I CRIED THE WHOLE TIME BECAUSE
IT JUST REMINDED ME OF WHAT IT
FELT LIKE, IT REMINDED ME OF
THAT, WHEN I HAD A DREAM OF
MAYBE SOMEDAY GETTING TO BE ON A
STAGE AND IT HAPPENS.
>> Kelly: IT DOESN'T HAPPEN
FOR EVERYONE.
>> I DO HAPPEN BEYOND MY
EXPECTATIONS.
IT WAS FANTASTIC BUT IT WAS
REALLY MOVING.
I'M SURE PEOPLE SITTING NEXT TO
ME WERE LIKE, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
WATCHING A COMEDY?
AND I WAS LIKE, THIS IS SO
BEAUTIFUL.
THIS IS HOW I'VE BECOME, TOO.
>> Kelly: AFTER CHILDREN IT
GOT WORSE.
I FEEL EVERYTHING.
>> FOR ME, AFTER PRETENDING TO
HAVE CHILDREN IT GOT WORSE.
>> Kelly: WE HAVE MORE TO TALK
ABOUT BUT FIRST LET'S TOSS IT TO
COMMERCIAL.
EVELYN, CAN YOU TAKE IT TO
BREAK?
SPEAK OUT KELLY IS HERE TO GET
IT THROUGH IT ALL.
MORE WITH LAUREN GRAHAM IN JUST
A MINUTE.
Does scrubbing grease feel like
a workout?
Scrub less with Dawn Ultra.
It's superior grease-cleaning
formula gets to work faster.
Making easy work of tough
messes.
Dawn takes care of tough grease,
wherever it shows up.
Scrub Less, Save More...
with Dawn.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: I'M HERE WITH THE
LOVELY LAUREN GRAHAM AND THAT'S
A LOOK AT HER IN
"ZOEY'S EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST,"
WHICH YOU CAN SEE SUNDAY IS IT'S
AMAZING.
SO TELL ME WHO YOUR CHARACTERS,
WHAT IS YOUR ROLE ABOUT?
>> SO I PLAYED JANE LEAVY'S
BOSS, AND IN ADDITION TO GETTING
THIS THING I GET TO BE KIND OF
LIKE AN UNHINGED SNOWBALL WHICH
WAS REALLY FUN.
I DIDN'T WANT HER TO BE A DRAGON
LADY, BECAUSE WERE THE ONLY TWO
WOMEN IN THE OFFICE, BASICALLY,
SO I'M TOUGH ON HER BUT I WANT
HER TO DO WELL.
>> Kelly: YOUR TALK BECAUSE
YOU CARE.
THAT'S GOOD.
BUT I LIKE THAT YOU PLAY SOMEONE
NUTTY, THAT'S WAY FUN.
>> SHE'S GOING THROUGH A LOT AND
HAVING BREAKDOWNS, IT'S REALLY,
REALLY FUN.
AND THE MUSICAL ELEMENT OF THE
SHOW ALLOWS, THE IDEA IS THAT
ZOE IS HEARING PEOPLE'S REAL
THOUGHTS.
>> Kelly: BUT SHE'S HEARING
THEIR THOUGHTS AND SONG.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS INTERESTING
BECAUSE JANE WAS TALKING ABOUT
IT, SOMEONE SMILING IN THE
OFFICE, REALLY THE SONG PLAYING
IN HIS HEAD IS REALLY MELANCHOL
MELANCHOLY.
SO IT'S LIKE YOU GET A LITTLE
INSIGHT.
THE SHOW WAS INCREDIBLE.
IT'S VERY SMART.
>> I THINK IT'S INCREDIBLE, MY
FRIEND JANE IS INCREDIBLE.
SHE HAD NEVER REALLY SUNG BEFORE
AND SHE JUST NATURALLY HAS A
BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
SHE TOOK A COUPLE VOICE LESSONS.
>> Kelly: DID YOU ALL DO VOICE
LESSONS?
>> WE BOTH TRAINED WITH A
TEACHER NAMED ERICA BEECHER WHO
I WAS ALL READY WORKING WITH,
BECAUSE BASICALLY IF YOU ASKED
ME TO SING I'LL JUST SHOW UP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PAY ME.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE A
TELEVISED THING, I'LL JUST COME.
BUT I WAS DOING THIS CARTOON
CALLED "VAMP ARENA."
I'M THE MOM.
>> Kelly: OH, MY GOD, !
THAT IS INCREDIBLE, I WOULD'VE
NEVER GUESSED THAT'S YOU.
>> IT'S ALSO FUN WHEN YOU BECOME
A FIGURINE.
MY LITTLE OKSANA DOLL LIVES IN
OUR KITCHEN.
JUST WHERE DREAMS COME TRUE.
I'M ALSO A BOBBLEHEAD
"GILMORE GIRLS" ."
DREAMS HE DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD.
>> Kelly: WOULD YOU CONSIDER
DOING A "GILMORE GIRLS" MUSICAL
CUSTOMER JUST ASKING FOR A
FRIEND.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I JUST WANT TO SEE LUKE'S
DANCING.
>> I GUESS IT WAS A RUNNING JOKE
ON THE SHOW WHERE THEY ASSIGNED
ONE OF THE REPORTERS TO COVER
THE MUSIC ON THE PERSON IS LIKE,
ROLLING THEIR EYES BECAUSE IT
SEEMS SILLY BUT THEN THERE'S
DISCUSSION THAT, IT'S A BELOW
SHOW.
I ALWAYS FELT THAT THAT LANGUAGE
IN THAT KIND OF PACE AND THE
TONE OF THE SHOW IS VERY
THEATRICAL.
>> Kelly: IT'S A VERY BROAD
WAY.
>> IT IS.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A DEEP, LONG
BREATH BEFORE YOU DELIVER SOME
OF THOSE LINES, THEY GO ON AND
ON FOREVER.
SO I THINK IT'S KIND OF A GOOD
IDEA.
>> Kelly: I WOULD LOVE IT.
>> AND THEY'RE SO MUCH DANCE IN
THE SHOW.
BUT AGAIN, AS I'VE TOLD YOU, IF
YOU ASK ME TO SING I'LL JUST
SHOW UP.
SO WE CAN ACTUALLY PUT IT ON
BROADWAY OR IN YOUR GARAGE.
>> Kelly: I LOVE THAT ABOUT
YOU.
YOU'RE LIKE, I CAN BE FANCY AND
LOW-KEY.
I LOVE THAT.
I ALSO FOUND OUT THAT YOU ADOPT
A PUPPY?
>> YES.
SURE, SURE.
SHE LOOKS CUTE THERE.
I HAVE NOT SLEPT.
I HADN'T HAD A PUPPY IN A LONG
TIME.
MY LAST DOG RESCUE WAS AN ADULT
DOG AND I DON'T KNOW WHOSE IDEA
THIS WAS AND I GUESS IT WAS MINE
BUT SHE'S REALLY LOVELY AND
GREAT EXCEPT FOR LIKE TWO HOURS
OF THE DAY WHERE SHE JUST TURNS
INTO A DEMON.
>> Kelly: YOU HAVE JUST HAD
YOUR FIRST OFFICIAL REAL CHILD
AS WELL BECAUSE THAT'S HOW THAT
WORKS.
YOU'RE LIKE, HOW ARE YOU THE
SAME HUMAN?
YOU KNOW WHAT, HAVE A GLASS OF
WINE.
>> AT EIGHT IN THE MORNING?
>> Kelly: IT'S FINE.
IT'S 5:00 SOMEWHERE.
THE PUPPY TRAINING, IT DEPENDS
ON THE BREED, ALSO.
HE OR SHE?
>> SHE, HER NAME IS MO CHEE.
I LIKE RICE CAKES.
I'VE TAKEN HER TO SCHOOL.
SHE'S GOT THE FINEST TRAINERS IN
THE LAND.
BUT STILL SHE'S LIKE NOPE, GOING
IN THE KITCHEN.
>> Kelly: RIGHT WHERE YOU EAT.
SO I FOLLOW YOU ON TWITTER.
BUT YOU'RE NOT ON INSTAGRAM.
>> I'M NOT.
KIND OF FUNNY.
SPEAK WITH A WOMAN PLAYED MY MOM
ON "GILMORE GIRLS," WHO WAS IN
THE ORIGINAL CAST OF "A CHORUS
LINE" AND ALSO "DIRTY DANCING,"
I WANT TO LOOK HER UP TO FIND A
VIDEO OF HER FROM "A CHORUS
LINE" AND IT LITERALLY WHEN I
LOOKED UP I WAS 72 YEARS OLD.
I HAD SPENT SO LONG GETTING SO
DISTRACTED BECAUSE I WENT
THROUGH "A CHORUS LINE" AND THEN
I WAS WATCHING OLD CLIPS OF
OTHER MUSICALS, AND I'M A PERSON
WHO OPENS THE REFRIGERATOR DOOR
AND WALKS AWAY AND FORGETS.
I'M EASILY DISTRACTED I GUESS IS
MY POINTS AND I'M WORRIED IF I
WAS ON INSTAGRAM I WOULD NEVER
DO ANYTHING ELSE.
>> Kelly: MY KEY IS I ONLY USE
IT, I WAS AGAINST ALL THE IN THE
BEGINNING, BECAUSE I WAS LIKE,
THIS IS A LOT WHY DO PEOPLE CARE
HOW I LIKE MY COFFEE, AND I
DON'T CARE WHAT YOU'RE EATING
AND YOU'RE SKINNY AND YOU'RE
EATING SOMETHING I WANT TO YOU
BUT I CAN'T.
SO I JUST STARTED DOING IT JUST
FOR WORK.
AND IT WAS KIND OF COOL, BECAUSE
FANS GET TO SEE YOU AND GET A
LITTLE INSIGHT BUT I GET IT.
IT'S A LOT.
>> Kelly: BUT IT'S FUN.
I HAVE MET SOME WONDERFUL PEOPLE
WHO I ADMIRE AND THAT'S THE
CONNECTIVITY OF ALL OF THAT THAT
IS REALLY NICE.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN CATCH LAUREN ON
"ZOEY'S EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST"
SUNDAY NIGHTS ON NBC.
WHEN WE COME BACK, BRACE
YOURSELVES, THE "IMPRACTICAL
JOKERS" ARE HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
You ever get the urge
to go a little crazy?
You know what I'm talking
about, right Karen?
Huh?
You wanna let yourself woah,
but you can't do it here.
Or here. It hurts more
when you fight it.
But totally cool here.
Woah!
And here.
Woaaaahh!
-Oh yeah.
Woah, kid.
She gets it.
[ roars ]
Woah!!
Get it all out.
So when you're ready
to let yourself woah,
there's only one
place to go.
Universal, baby!
HUMIRA patients...
this one's for you.
The heroes who won't let
your disease hold you back.
You inspired us to make your
HUMIRA experience even better
with HUMIRA Citrate-free.
It has the same effectiveness
you know and trust,
but we removed the
citrate buffers,
there's less liquid,
and a thinner needle,
with less pain immediately
following injection.
If you haven't yet,
talk to your doctor
about HUMIRA Citrate-free.
And you can use your co-pay card
to pay as little as $5 a month.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal
infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Ask your doctor about
HUMIRA Citrate-free.
The same HUMIRA you trust
with less pain
immediately following injection.
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK.
I'M HERE WITH LAUREN GRAHAM,
EVERYBODY.
SO MY NEXT GUESTS ARE KNOWN FOR
THEIR HILARIOUS HIDDEN CAMERA
SERIES.
NOW THEY HAVE A MOVIE WITH MORE
SHENANIGANS THAN EVER.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THE ATLANTA HAWKS ARE HIRING.
>> I NEED TO USE THE RESTROOM
REALLY QUICK.
>> NO WORRIES.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SECURITY REALLY SUCKS AROUND
HERE.
>> YOU GOOD?
>> YEAH, SECURITY REALLY SUCKS,
IS ABLE TO GO SHOOT HOOPS.
SO, SECURITY IS AN ISSUE.
HE [CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: PLEASE WALK ON
"IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: I LOVE Y'ALL!
>> IT'S SO NICE TO MEET YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THIS.
I WAS HAVING THE ESTATE THE
OTHER DAY, AND MY HUSBAND TURNED
ON YOUR SHOW, BECAUSE OUR WHOLE
FAMILY, EXTENDED FAMILY,
EVERYONE I KNOW LOVES YOUR SHOW.
I DON'T HOW YOU GET AWAY WITH
IT.
I KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO THINK,
I'M NOT, BUT LITERALLY YOU TURN
MY WHOLE DAY AROUND.
LIKE I WAS HAVING THE WORST DAY.
IT'S JUST NICE WHEN YOU FEEL BAD
AND OTHER PEOPLE ARE FEELING
WORSE.
>> THIS IS TRUE.
I'M ONE OF THE MAIN MOVIE TICKET
SALES, BECAUSE I MOVIE IS COMING
OUT THEY HAVE THE WRONG JAMES
MURRAY.
>> THEY DO.
THEY PUT THE BRITISH ACTOR JAMES
MURRAY WHO IS MUCH MORE HANDSOM
HANDSOME.
>> YOU MIGHT GET MORE PEOPLE
COMING.
THAT'S ACTUALLY VERY SMART TO D
DO.
SO YOU GREW UP TOGETHER, RIGHT?
>> WE MET FRESHMAN YEAR OF
HIGH SCHOOL, SAME AGE.
>> I FEEL SORRY FOR YOUR
TEACHERS.
>> THEY BEEN ON THE SHOW, WE
DRAG THEM IN.
>> WE WENT TO AN ALL BOYS
CATHOLIC HIGH SCHOOL IN
STATEN ISLAND, NEW YORK, .
SO, YEAH.
>> Kelly: BUT WAIT.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE BACK ON
THE UNIVERSE A LOT?
>> HORRIFYING.
I HAD PTSD WALKING IN THERE.
THE SET UP HERE SHE'S REFERRING
TO IS THE WAY OUR SHOW WORKS.
HAS ANYBODY SEEN IT?
GIVE ME BIG APPLAUSE.
WE'LL START HERE AND GO LEFT,
MAKE OUR WAY TO THE FRONT, GIVE
ONE REASON WHY YOU LIKE THE
SHOW.
WE'VE GOT TIME.
>> AND IT'S A TEN HOUR SHOW,
WHERE FINE.
>> WE GO OUT IN PUBLIC AND WE
BUST AROUND WITH EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW.
WE TELL EACH OTHER WHAT TO DO.
IF YOU DON'T DO IT AT THE END OF
THE EPISODE YOU GET A PUNISHMEN
PUNISHMENT.
>> THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR
UNIVERSAL STORY IS.
>> SO THEY HAVE THE FAMOUS TRAIN
RADICALS AROUND THE WHOLE SET.
IT WAS AN AWESOME AT ALL.
>> Kelly: YOU GUYS ARE...
WORDS I CAN'T SAY ON DAYTIME.
>> WHERE THEY CAN PULL THE THING
AND STOP THE RIDE, SO WHAT THEY
MADE ME DO IS STOP THE RIDE AT
78 TIMES IN AN HOUR OF THE FIRST
TIME PEOPLE WERE FORGIVING.
POOR GUY DROPPED HIS CELL PHONE,
BUT THEN I HAD TO STOP THE RIDE
AND BE LIKE, CAN YOU REPEAT
THAT?
BY THE SEVENTH TIME THAT I
PULLED BACK, PEOPLE WERE LOOKING
ME IN THE EYE LIKE, WHEN WE GET
OFF THE RIDE I'M GOING TO FIND
YOU AND I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
THAT'S AN ACTUAL QUOTE THAT
SOMEBODY SAID TO ME.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
THANK YOU.
>> FOR US IT WAS A HOOT.
LIKE A 4-YEAR-OLD GIRL WAS
GIVING ME THE MIDDLE FINGER.
>> Kelly: I LOVE YOUR SHOW.
SO YOU JUST DID YOUR 200 EPISOD
EPISODE.
SO THAT'S AMAZING.
SO WHAT'S YOUR BEST PUNISHMENT
THAT YOU'VE EVER PULLED ON
SOMEONE?
>> IT HAD A LOT OF FUN BUT ONE
THAT DEFINITELY STANDS OUT FOR
US IS ONE OF OUR FIRST REAL
SWITCHES WERE NOBODY HAD AN IDEA
WHAT WAS GOING ON, WE TOLD MURR
HE HAD TO ENTER A WEIGHT LIFTING
COMPETITION.
SO WE PAINTED HIM WITH A TANNING
OIL.
>> WHICH WAS RIDICULOUS BECAUSE
I HAVE THE BODY OF A BABY
CARROT, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
SAYING?
>> WE GOT SOME POWER LIFTERS TO
COME BE IN THE ROOM WITH HIM,
RIGHT?
THE MONEY WENT TO HIS NEXT ROOM
HIS HIGH SCHOOL CRUSH, DANICA
McKELLAR WAS SITTING DOWN FROM
THE WONDER YEARS.
FOR A 2020 STYLE INTERVIEW.
AND HE HAD TO KEEP FLEXING IN
FRONT OF HER.
>> Kelly: YOU ARE SO SLIPPERY.
>> I DON'T NORMALLY...
>> HAVE YOU EVER MESS WITH
SOMEONE LIKE THIS?
>> NO.
FIRST OF ALL I'VE SEEN EVERY
EPISODE OF THE SHOW BECAUSE MY
STEPSON IS VERY INTO IT AND WE
WOULD WATCH IT AS A FAMILY.
I FIND IT HILARIOUS, I LOVE IT,
IT'S AMAZING EXCEPT WHEN YOU GET
TO THE PUNISHMENTS, THEY MAKE ME
SO TENSE.
REMEMBER THE SHOW, "PUNK," THEY
DID ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS AND
SHE SAID I KNOW MY FRIEND REALLY
WELL, SHE WILL NOT LIKE THIS, I
CAN'T DO IT.
SO NO, I DON'T.
>> GOOD FRIEND.
MY FRIENDS WOULD BE THE ONES
MAKING THE CALLS.
>> Kelly: YOU HAVE REAL
FRIENDS.
OKAY, SO TELL US ABOUT YOUR
FILM.
IT COMES OUT TODAY, RIGHT?
>> YEAH!
>> Kelly: STARTING THIS JAMES
MURRAY AND TELL US ABOUT IT.
WHAT'S DIFFERENT?
DO YOU DO DIFFERENT THINGS, IS
THAT WHAT YOU DID THE FILM?
>> WE GOT TO BREAK OUT OF THE
FORMAT OF THE HALF HOUR OF TV
AND WE HAD SOME REALLY BIG IDEAS
THAT WE COULDN'T SHOW ON TV
BECAUSE A BUDGET OR WHATEVER SO
WE ACTUALLY WENT BACK TO THE
DRAWING BOARD AND WENT TO HER
BIGGEST BIG IDEAS THAT WE HAD
AND PUT THEM IN THE MOVIE AND WE
WERE ABLE TO FIT IN TEN
CHALLENGES.
>> Kelly: I CANNOT WAIT TO
SEE.
>> THERE'S A MOMENT IN THE MOVIE
THAT'S SO CRAZY THAT WE HAD TO
TAKE UP $15 MILLION LIFE
INSURANCE POLICY OUT ON THE GUY
WHO DID IT.
IN CASE HE DIDN'T MAKE IT.
BUT HE MADE IT.
>> WE ARE ALL HERE.
>> MOST OF THE PLANNING OF THE
MOVIE WAS JUST LIFE INSURANCE
POLICIES.
>> Kelly: I HEARD, IS
PAULA ABDUL IN IT?
I'M SO EXCITED.
SHE SO INCREDIBLY ATHLETIC, TOO.
>> THAT WAS MY BEST DURING DAY
AFTER.
>> Kelly: "IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"
THE MOVIE IS IN THEATERS TODAY.
COMING UP NEXT WE HAVE CHEF ROY
CHOI, Y'ALL!
This is a story of the American
Dream.
It starts here, in a middle
class neighborhood with a middle
class kid named Mike.
When his father died, his mother
went to work and became the
breadwinner.
She instilled in Mike
a belief in hard work and a
drive to build a better life.
So he started a company from
scratch with an idea and endless
hours- today, that makes him the
only democrat in the race
who's created 20,000 jobs.
He's the only democrat who's run
the largest and most
diverse city in America,
rebuilding after 9-11, creating
over 450,000 jobs and expanding
health care coverage to 700,000
people.
The only democrat who's built a
grassroots movement to combat
gun violence and he's a
leader combatting climate
change.
The only democrat who's never
taken a penny from special
interests.
Now Mike is running to deliver
on the American Dream
for everyone with common sense
solutions and the ability to get
it done.
Because Mike Bloomberg is the
only democrat who can take on
Trump. And Trump knows it.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK, Y'ALL!
I'M BACK WITH LAUREN GRAHAM IN
THE "IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"!
I LOVE DORITOS.
IF ONLY THERE WAS A BETTER WAY
TO ENJOY BOTH OF THEM.
ENTER MY SHOW.
MY NEXT GUEST HAS THE ANSWERS
AND IT ALL COMES ON THE ONE
SECRET INGREDIENT.
SAY HELLO TO THE CHEF WITH THE
HOTTEST KOREAN TACO TRUCK, CHEF
ROY CHOI ! I'M SO EXCITED YOU'RE
HERE.
SO WHAT ARE WE MAKING TODAY?
>> IT'S A PRODUCT OF THE STREETS
IN LOS ANGELES.
WE CAME OUT ABOUT 11 YEARS AGO,
COMBINING TWITTER WITH TACO
TRUCKS AND WE SERVE THESE
BURRITOS AND TACOS AND WE FILLED
THE WHOLE STREETS WITH LOVE.
IT'S CRAZY.
>> AND YOU TO WORK TOGETHER,
RIGHT?
>> HE PLAYED ONE OF THE CHEFS I
FIRED ON THE SPEED EIGHT REVIVA
REVIVAL.
>> I MOVED THE COFFEE MACHINES
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
>> Kelly: YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
TOUCHED THAT COFFEE MACHINE.
>> THAT WAS MY FIRST TIME
ACTING.
>> YOU ARE INCREDIBLE.
>> AND NERVE-RACKING, I HATE IT.
>> SHUT OUT TO MY BROOKLYN 99
FAMILY, OR GOING TO ADD TO THE
HOT SHE DOES TO IT, THEY LOVE I
IT.
HIGH MATT, GUYS.
>> WE ARE GOING TO COOK, RIGHT?
BUT A LITTLE BIT OF OIL.
>> YOU JUST TOUCH IT?
IT'S NOT ON YOUR FINGERS?
>> BAM!
>> NOW ON THAT SAME AREA.
>> SAME AREA, PUT YOUR OIL AND
MEAT AND EGGS.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOSH, I'M SO HUNGRY.
ALL OF IT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> I'LL BE YOUR SOUS CHEF.
>> IS THAT WHAT THIS SAYS?
>> YES.
>> WE'RE IN TROUBLE IF WE DON'T
KNOW WHAT AN EGG IS.
>> AND YOU HAVE A SHOW, RIGHT?
>> IT'S CALLED "THE CHEF SHOW."
>> Kelly: WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I HOSTED WITH JOHN, TO HELP
HIM LEARN HOW TO COOK BUT IT WAS
KIND OF LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT, WE
BECAME BEST FRIENDS.
>> Kelly: I LOVE A BROMANCE.
>> I'M TRYING TO TELL A STORY
OVER HERE.
HE'S NOT HELPING.
HE'S NOT CARRYING ANY OF THE
WEIGHT.
>> BUT WHEN YOU MAKE THE MOVIE
YOU SPEND LIGHT, EVERYTHING WILL
DATE TOGETHER FOR LIKE A MONTH
AND THEN IT'S OVER.
SO IT'S LIKE SUMMER CAMP.
WE JUST MISSED EACH OTHER.
RETURN TO FIND WAYS TO HANG OUT.
>> Kelly: THAT THAT'S AWESOME.
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
>> JUST GET THE MEAT HOT.
YOU GUYS ARE LOOKING GOOD OVER
HERE.
>> SHOULD WE BE TALKING TO THEM
EACH TO ENCOURAGE IT OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT?
>> THIS SMELL SO GOOD.
>> PUT IT RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
>> IN THE MIDDLE.
>> MAKE SURE IT'S HORIZONTAL.
NOW YOU WANT TO ADD CHEESE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE DOING.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO ADD THESE
THREE SAUCES.
>> YES!
OKAY.
SAUCES PERIODS BECAUSE MUCH
SAUCE AS YOU LIKE.
>> WHAT'S THE PURPLE HE WON?
>> THIS IS A BLUEBERRY HABANERO.
>> CAN BE PUT THIS IN IT, TOO?
>> MY MOUTH IS WATERING, I'M SO
HAPPY.
OKAY, AND THEN WE PUT THIS IN
HERE.
AFTER THE ONIONS.
>> WOW.
THERE YOU GO.
>> LOOK HOW FANCY YOU ARE.
OKAY.
OKAY, SO WAIT.
WHEN DO WE ROLL IT OUT?
>> THAT'S SALTZ.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A --   .
>> OH, MY GOD, .
>> Kelly: WAY!
[LAUGHTER]
>> HOW DID I END UP WITH YOU?
YOU'RE TERRIBLE.
>> Kelly: I MADE MINE.
>> BEAUTIFUL.
>> Kelly: I KNOW.
THEY ARE SLOW.
>> THEY ARE SLOW.
>> I'M LOSING CHINOS.
>> CRUSH THEM, CRUSH THEM.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THERE YOU GO.
>> Kelly: THAT IS SO GOOD!
>> YOU DO THE ROLLING PART.
>> ARE YOU READY?
WHERE GOOD.
>> Kelly: CAN YOU IMAGINE THEM
AS KIDS IN ONE SCHOOL?
>> LOOK AT THAT FACE, HE LOVES
IT.
>> Kelly: I LOVE MINE.
MINE IS SO GOOD.
>> I FEEL LIKE I NEED AN ALIBI.
I WAS HERE, I WAS ON "THE KELLY
CLARKSON SHOW" THE WHOLE TIME, I
DIDN'T MURDER ANYONE.
>> Kelly: FOR MORE INFO ON ROY
CHOI, GO TO
KellyClarksonShow.com IF YOU
LIKE FOOD, THAT'S ALL I'M SAYIN
SAYING.
UP NEXT, ONE WOMAN'S EFFORT TO
RAISE MONEY AND AWARENESS FOR
BREAST CANCER.
SHE'S A REAL RAT HUMAN, Y'ALL,
YOU GOT TO STAY TUNED.
♪ ♪
[police siren]
Dispatch, we got a code bubly.
Are you going to get him down?
No.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT, I'M BACK
WITH LAUREN GRAHAM AND THE
"IMPRACTICAL JOKERS."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MY NEXT GUEST HAS MADE CANCER
AWARENESS AND FUND-RAISING HER
LIFE'S MISSION.
THROUGH HER ADVOCACY SHE'S ALSO
SUPPORTING SOME OF THE MOST
CUTTING EDGE DOCTORS ON THE
PLANET.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S TODAY'S RAT
HUMAN.
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: PLEASE WELCOME, FROM
UNITED CANCER FRIEND, LILY LILLY
TARTIKOFF.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE MET
EVERYBODY BEFORE.
>> Kelly: SO THIS IS ACTUALLY
REALLY INCREDIBLE.
YOU HAVE BEEN ABLE TO RAISE OVER
$81 MILLION.
HOW DOES ONE GET INVOLVED IN
THIS?
>> FIRST OF ALL, IT'S SO GREAT
TO BE BACK AT NBC.
IT'S HOME AWAY FROM HOME.
SO MY LATE HUSBAND HAD BEEN
DIAGNOSED AND TREATED FOR
HODGKIN'S DISEASE.
HODGKIN'S DISEASE IS A CANCER OF
THE LYMPH NODES.
WHEN HE WAS 26 YEARS OLD.
HE JUST DIDN'T LOOK RIGHT.
SOON AFTER I MARRIED HIM.
WHEN HE SET UP AN APPOINTMENT
AND DR. SLAMON MET WITH HIM AND
DETERMINED THAT HIS HODGKIN'S
DISEASE HAD COME BACK AND THEY
LAY THAT MASSIVE TRAY OF DRUGS
AND IT TOOK HOURS AND HOURS AND
HE WAS ON THE PHONE FOR HOURS
TALKING AND SCREAMING ABOUT THIS
NONTOXIC TREATMENT FOR CANCER.
AND I HAVE COURSE WAS
EAVESDROPPING.
I THINK THAT WAS PROBABLY A GOOD
THING, RIGHT?
>> Kelly: I WOULD'VE DONE THIS
AS WELL.
AND TO SEE YOU KNOW, YOUR
HUSBAND RAN THIS.
>> SO HE TOOK A YEAR AND DR.
SLAMON ADDED 15 YEARS AND I SAID
TO DR. SLAMON I AM GOING TO
RAISE THE MONEY FOR YOU.
>> Kelly: AND WHEN YOU MAKE A
PROMISE YOU FOLLOW THROUGH.
YOU DELIVER.
IT'S INSANE.
IT'S HARD FUND-RAISING.
IT'S HARD DOING THAT AND IT'S
HARD ASKING PEOPLE FOR MONEY.
YOUR EARLIEST FUND-RAISING LEAD
TO A DRUG THAT SAVES LIVES.
>> SEVEN YEARS LATER HE FINALLY
SAID YES AND I REALIZED I HAD
NEVER RAISED MONEY.
BUT BY CHANCE I MET THIS
INCREDIBLY SUCCESSFUL
BUSINESSMAN AND MODEL PRO MAN
WHO OWN REVLON.
AND WHEN I MET HIM I THOUGHT,
HE'S AT.
HE HAD NO IDEA WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
BUT I THOUGHT IF I CAN CONVINCE
HIM THAT IF HE CARED ABOUT
WOMEN'S HEALTH AND THEIR
WELL-BEING AS WELL AS THEIR
SHADE OF LIPSTICK IT WOULD BE SO
PROFOUND AND SO MEANINGFUL.
SO WE CREATED THE WOMEN'S CANCER
RESEARCH PROGRAM.
TEN FIRE AND ICE BALLS AND 38
REVLON LOCKS AND 1:30-40000
PEOPLE CAME OUT THEY WERE SO
EMPOWERED FOR THEY DON'T REALIZE
IS THEY HELPED US RAISE.
THEY HELPED US RAISE THIS MONEY
FOR THIS TARGETED THERAPY.
WE TOOK ALL THAT MONEY OVER 28
YEARS AND WE PUT IT INTO DR.
SLAMON AND HIS COLLEAGUES AND
RESEARCH.
AND THEY CAME UP WITH TWO
TARGETED THERAPIES.
IN AN TARGETED THERAPY IS ONE
THAT SHUTS DOWN THE CANCER CELLS
AND DOESN'T HARM THE GOOD,
HEALTHY ONES.
THESE BECAME FDA APPROVED.
THEY WERE WRETCHED IN MISSIONARY
AND LITERALLY HELPED 85% OF ALL
THE WOMEN WITH BREAST CANCER.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS IN 60 YEARS.
>> Kelly: IT MIGHT NOT HAVE
HAPPENED WITHOUT YOU CARRYING.
IT TAKES ONE PERSON TO REALLY
LIKE THAT FIRE AND THEN IT
CATCHES.
>> EVERYONE WATCHING THE SHOW,
EVERYONE IS AFFECTED DIRECTLY OR
INDIRECTLY BY CANCER.
SO NOW I HAD TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO RAISE A MASSIVE AMOUNT OF
MONEY.
>> Kelly: HOW PROUD WOULD
BRANDON BE OF YOU?
>> I THINK YOU WOULD STILL THINK
I'M OUT OF CONTROL.
>> Kelly: A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
OBSESSED WITH THINGS THAT ARE
UNIMPORTANT.
YOUR OBSESSION IS HELPING
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE.
>> YOU'VE RAISED $81 MILLION.
>> BUT NOT BY MYSELF.
>> CITED YOUR ADVANCE OR DONATE
CHALLENGE.
CAN YOU TELL EVERYBODY ABOUT
THAT?
>> I BASICALLY --
SPEAK OUT HE WAS OUR FIRST
ANSWER.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW LONG THIS
AMOUNT OF TIME WAS UNTIL I
STARTED MOVING.
SO TELL EVERYBODY.
SENT OUT STANCE AND DONATE,
RIGHT?
>> I REALIZED WE NEEDED TO TAP
INTO SOCIAL MEDIA BECAUSE WE
NEEDED TO REACH THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE SO WE CREATED DANCE OR
DONATE.
SO IF YOU GO ONLINE, SO WE HAD
DANCERS.
YOU HAD 600,000 PEOPLE WATCHED
YOU DANCE.
IT WAS A MASSIVE NUMBER.
I'M APOLOGIZING NOW.
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
I HAD TO GO BACK TO THE DRAWING
BOARD BECAUSE I WASN'T RAISING
MONEY.
>> YOU'RE RAISING AWARENESS.
>> BUT THAT WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
I NEEDED TO CREATE A
FUND-RAISING PAGE.
AND THIS TIME CREATE A
NOW YOU GO TO ALL YOUR FRIENDS
AND FAMILY AND YOU GET THEM TO
DONATE $5 HERE, $5 THERE.
WE WILL CURE CANCER.
>> EVERYONE IS LIKE MY HAVE TO
DONATE A HUGE AMOUNT BUT DONATE
WHAT YOU CAN.
IT'S EVERYWHERE.
SO THIS RESEARCH IS VERY
NECESSARY.
>> AND WE ARE SO GRATEFUL.
WE ARE GOING TO DO THIS.
WE ARE GOING TO GET IT DONE.
THANK YOU.
>> Kelly: AFTER THE BREAK WE
WILL MEET THE DOCTOR WHO IS
BREAKING GROUND IN CANCER
TREATMENT AND A WOMAN WHO SAID
HE SAVED HER LIFE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
I love the new myWW program,
because it's tailored to you!
...take the personal assessment
and get matched with a proven
weight loss plan.
Find out which customized
plan can make losing weight
easier for you!
myWW
Join today
with the WW
triple play!
Unexpected situation?
L'Oreal's Magic Root Cover Up.
Three seconds to flawless roots.
3...2...1...
Roots gone.
Magic Root Cover Up
by L'Oreal Paris.
Look for the turqoise one.
Young Man: Thanks for having
us this weekend Mrs. Garcy
Young Woman: Yeah, thanks Mom
Mother: Of course and
I love these flowers
Young Woman whispering: Hey, did
you bring the... the condoms?
Young Man whispering: What's up?
Young Woman whispering: Condoms
Young Man whispering: What?
Young Woman whispering: Condom
Father: Condoms Charlie.
She wants to know if
you brought any condoms.
Young Man: Yeah I brought some.
Announcer: Eargo, a virtually
invisible hearing loss
solution with high quality sound
and lifetime support.
If your a current or retired
federal employee
you could get Eargo at no cost
to you.
Simply call 800-EARGO-54
to hear more.
Eargo, hear life to the fullest.
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK.
I'M SITTING WITH LAUREN GRAHAM
AND THE "IMPRACTICAL JOKERS"
ALONG WITH LILLY TARTIKOFF, THE
FOUNDER OF THE UNITED CANCER
MOVEMENT AT TODAY'S RAT HUMAN.
AND JOINING US NOW IS THE MAN
BEHIND SOME THE MOST
GROUNDBREAKING CANCER TREATMENTS
IN DECADES.
DR. DENNIS B-17.
IT IS AN HONOR TO MEET YOU.
YOU'RE LITERALLY CHANGING LIVES.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE HOW MUCH
PRESSURE THAT MUST FEEL LIKE AS
WELL.
BUT NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT I
DIDN'T MEAN TO ADD TO IT.
BUT DR. SLAMON WHAT IS THE
BIGGEST MISCONCEPTIONS YOU THINK
PEOPLE HAVE ABOUT CANCER
CUSTOMER >> PERHAPS THE BIGGEST
MISCONCEPTION IS WHEN THE
DIAGNOSIS IT HAPPENS WHERE
PEOPLE ARE LIKE, YOU HAVE LUNG
CANCER OR COLON CANCER
BREAST CANCER AND THEY ASSUME
IT'S ONE DISEASE AND WE SHOULD
BE LEARNING THAT SINCE PEOPLE
HAVE VERY DIFFERENT OUTCOMES WE
ARE DEALING WITH A GROUP OF
DISEASES, BREAST CANCER IS NOT
ONE DISEASE, IT'S A SPECTRUM OF
DISEASE IN THE SAME IS TRUE WITH
LUNG AND SO WE MOVE AWAY FROM
THE OLD TYPE OF THERAPY WHERE WE
THROWN A BOMB AND HOPE WE KILL
MORE BAD THAN GOOD AND TARGET
WHAT'S BROKEN.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT.
TELL US ABOUT THE WORK IN YOUR
LAB?
>> WHAT WE'VE BEEN DOING IS
SETTING UP MODELS OF VARIOUS
HUMAN CANCERS.
AS LILY MENTIONED, THE MISSION
WORK STARTED WITH BREAST CANCER
PENDANTS NOW MOVED TO THE OTHER
MAJOR CANCERS WHERE WE REALLY
CANNOT USE MORE EFFECTIVE
THERAPY IS.
SO WE'VE SET UP THE MODELS AND
SET UP ROBOTICS THAT WOULD ALLOW
US TO SCREEN HUGE NUMBERS OF
CANCER CELLS, HUMAN CANCER CELLS
FOR WHAT THEIR SENSITIVITIES
MIGHT BE TO THE DIFFERENT
THERAPIES WE USE THAT ARE THE
NEW TARGETED THERAPIES.
THAT'S AT THE LAB IS ABOUT RIGHT
NOW.
>> Kelly: AND THAT LAB IS
EXPENSIVE, I'M SURE THAT'S WHERE
A LOT OF THE MONEY GOES, TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO TARGET THE
SPECIFIC CELLS.
AND THAT'S WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT
FOR A SWELL DONATE AND NOT JUST
DANCE.
BUT WE DO ACTUALLY HAVE ONE OF
YOUR PATIENTS IN THE AUDIENCE.
SAY HI TO GINGER.
SO, GINGER, HOW DID YOU MEET DR.
SLAMON?
>> I HAD STAGE IV METASTATIC
BREAST CANCER WITH A LIVER FULL
OF TUMORS AND I FINISHED TWO
ROUNDS OF CHEMOTHERAPY AND ONE
FOR THE CHECKUP AND WHAT THEY
SAID WAS THAT THEY DISCOVERED AT
THAT POINT THAT MY TUMORS WERE
COMPLETELY CHEMORESISTANCE.
SO IT DIDN'T HELP.
AND AT THAT TIME WHAT THAT MEANT
WAS, WHAT THEY SAID, YOU DON'T
NEED TO MAKE ANOTHER APPOINTMEN
APPOINTMENT, GO HOME AND GET
YOUR AFFAIRS IN ORDER.
AND I JUST CANNOT ACCEPT THAT.
>> Kelly: WAY TO GO.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD HAVE
BROKEN AT THAT POINT.
>> THAT'S HOW I'D DISCOVERED
THAT DR. SLAMON HAD A TRIAL
COMING UP THAT WOULD OPEN SOON,
IN 1995, THAT WAS THEN.
2020, I'M 75 NOW.
>> THAT IS AWESOME!
>> Kelly: IT'S SO AMAZING!
AND TO YOU, SIR.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
"WHAT I'M LIKING" ."
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
I need every sports channel
possible.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios
with internet starting at just
$39.99 per month.
Plus, you'll get up to $200 in
Visa prepaid cards
based on the plans you pick.
Eso existe? Los necesitamos.
Want internet? Pick your speed.
Want just TV? Pick the plan
that's right for you
No two households are the same,
so no two plans should be the
same.
We should get what we want.
And now, no matter what you
choose,
you get a year of Disney+ on us.
Boom! Sign me up.
I love that.
Finally, get internet and TV
your way
with internet starting at $39.99
per month -
no extra fees, no annual
contracts.
No surprises on my cable bill?
I'll take that.
Finally! Plans that just make
sense.
Mix and match your perfect Fios
plan and pay for what you want.
Only on Verizon.
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK.
THERE ARE A LOT OF TUBES THAT
MAKE UP THE INTERNET AND I'M
HERE TO TELL YOU WHAT CONTAINS
THE BEST STUFF.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THIS IS "WHAT I'M LIKING."
SO IF YOU'VE EVER WATCHED A
MAKEUP TUTORIAL ONLINE WITH THE
VOICE-OVER ALWAYS GIVES YOU A
CLEAR STEP-BY-STEP DESCRIPTION
OF WHAT'S BEING APPLIED.
AND AS WHAT USUALLY HAPPENS WHEN
BEAUTY BLOGGER POSTS VIDEOS BUT
IN A RECENT TUTORIAL SHE LET HER
DAD AND HIS FRIENDS CHIME IN AND
ADD VOICE-OVER COMMENTARY.
THE INTERNET IS GOING NUTS FOR
AND HERE YOU GO.
>> THERE SHE GO.
I DON'T KNOW WHY SHE NEEDS UP AT
THE SAME COLOR ON HER SKIN.
YOU'RE PUTTING SOME BROWN ON TOP
OF SOME BROWN.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: IT'S LIKE THE
"MYSTERY SCIENCE THEATER" OF
MAKEUP TUTORIALS.
LET'S GET HER AND HER DAD ON
SKYPE RIGHT NOW.
HEY, WHAT'S UP Y'ALL, I'M KELLY,
NICE TO SEE YOU.
Y'ALL ARE HILARIOUS, FIRST OF
ALL, WHAT DID YOU THINK OF YOUR
DAD'S NARRATION?
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS HILARIOUS.
HE STARTED IN A DIFFERENT ROOM,
SO I HAD TO BE SURPRISED WHEN I
WAS EDITING.
MY VIEWERS LOVED IT.
>> Kelly: MY FAVORITE PART IS
"SHE PUT SOME BROWN ON SOME
BROWN."
SO, FRANKIE, YOU GIVE A PRETTY
CLEAR MAN'S POINT OF VIEW WHEN
IT COMES TO MAKEUP.
>> MORE OF A FATHER'S POINT OF
VIEW.
WATCHING HIS LITTLE GIRL BECOME
A YOUNG LADY.
>> Kelly: I LOVE IT!
IT'S A NICE FATHER DAUGHTER
THING.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I'M OFFICIALLY LIKING YOUR POST
RIGHT NOW.
>> THANK YOU!
>> Kelly: THINKING TO ALL MY
GUESTS, LAUREN GRAHAM, THE
"IMPRACTICAL JOKERS," CHEF ROY
CHOI, LILLY TARTIKOFF AND DR.
SLAMON, HAVE A GREAT DAY, Y'ALL,
AND IF IT'S NOT GREAT, JUST
CHANGE IT.
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: HERE SHE IS NOW,
ELLEN DEGENERES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪