[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
I APPRECIATE IT!
BACK AT YOU!
I FEEL THE SAME WAY!
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
HAVE A SEAT, IF YOU WANT TO.
I DON'T CARE.
[LAUGHTER]
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THE CLAPPING, I SEE
YOUR WOO AND I RAISE YOU A MOUTH
WHISTLE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO THAT
THOUGH.
MARY, CAN YOU DO THAT?
DO IT.
[WHISTLING]
[APPLAUSE]
I KNEW THAT YOU COULD.
SOMEHOW I JUST THOUGHT YOU
COULD.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT AN
INTERESTING STUDY THAT CAME OUT.
IT RANKED THE DRUNKEST STATES IN
AMERICA.
HERE'S HOW THEY DID IT.
THEY RENTED FROM 1-FORGETTING
WHY YOU ARE CRYING.
THE STUDIES THAT SAID NEARLY 60%
OF AMERICANS ARE REGULAR
DRINKERS.
THE AVERAGE AMERICAN CONSUMES
2.3 GALLONS OF ALCOHOL ANNUALLY
UNLESS YOU FOLLOW POLITICS, THEN
IT IS DAILY.
ACTUALLY IT TURNS OUT THE
HEAVIEST DRINKERS ARE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
I DON'T BLAME THEM.
THE LEAST AMOUNT OF DRINKING
HAPPENS IN ARKANSAS.
THAT WAS SURPRISING TO ME, I
DON'T KNOW WHY.
BUT TO THEM I SAY, DO YOU KNOW
HOW DELICIOUS MARGARITAS ARE?
[LAUGHTER]
PEOPLE COME FROM ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY, FROM ALL OVER THE
WORLD, ACTUALLY, SO I THOUGHT IT
WOULD PUT THE STUDY TO A TEST
AND I WILL FIND OUT WHERE YOU'RE
FROM, HOW MUCH YOU DRINK.
YOU HAVE TO BE HONEST.
I DON'T NEED THESE.
AT ALL.
I HAVE QUESTIONS IN MY HEAD.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU DRINK.
HI.
>> HEY.
>> Ellen: STAND ON OUT HERE
WITH ME.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> JOSH.
>> Ellen: HI, JOSH.
WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> IN SACRAMENTO, CALIFORNIA.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: I NEED THOSE.
SACRAMENTO, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I WORK FOR A COW FARM DELETE
MATT KLE --
FIRE HOUSE.
>> Ellen: ARE YOU A
FIREFIGHTER?
>> YES.
>> Ellen: GOD BLESS YOU.
YOU ARE HERE IN CALIFORNIA, SO
WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT WE RATE
HERE IN CALIFORNIA?
>> GIVEN MYSELF AND MY FRIENDS,
PROBABLY TOP THREE.
>> Ellen: TURNS OUT CALIFORNIA
IS RANKED 34TH.
THAT SHOWS YOU HOW MUCH --
>> WE NEED TO WORK ON IT.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS YOUR DRINK
OF CHOICE?
>> COORS LIGHT.
>> Ellen: STRICTLY
COORS LIGHT?
>> TEQUILA I GET A LITTLE
EMOTIONAL.
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S NOT GOOD.
>> Ellen: WHAT HAPPENS TO YOU,
JOSH?
[LAUGHTER]
>> BAD THINGS.
>> Ellen: WHEN YOU DRINK
TEQUILA.
>> I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> Ellen: NOT GOOD ON TEQUILA.
SO COORS LIGHT.
YOU STICK TO THAT.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD FOR YOU.
HOW MUCH WOULD YOU SAY YOU DRINK
A WEEK, AND NIGHT, DAILY?
>> WE ARE GETTING PERSONAL.
HOURLY, I WOULD SAY --
>> Ellen: DO YOU DRINK EVERY
NIGHT?
>> NO.
FOUR NIGHTS A WEEK.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: FOUR NIGHTS A WEEK.
>> SOCIAL BEERS.
>> Ellen: SOCIAL BEERS JUST TO
KICK BACK.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
SIT DOWN.
[LAUGHTER]
NO, I DO BELIEVE YOU.
I DO.
THAT'S NOT BAD.
COORS LIGHT, A COUPLE OF NIGHTS
A WEEK.
HI.
[LAUGHTER]
STAND UP.
YOU CAN HANDLE A LOT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> I CAN.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> ANTHONY.
>> Ellen: WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> FLORIDA.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE FROM
FLORIDA?
>> YES, I AM.
>> Ellen: WHERE DOES FLORIDA
RANK?
>> TOP TEN AT LEAST.
>> Ellen: WE THINK THAT WE ARE
BIG DRINKERS.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF OLDER --
>> Ellen: YOU DO.
>> Ellen: 28.
YOU ARE 28.
>> I AM.
OH, WAIT.
I AM.
>> Ellen: I AM PSYCHIC AS
WELL.
I'M GOING TO TELL YOU ABOUT
YOURSELF.
NO, YOU ARE RANKED 28TH.
>> I'M DISAPPOINTED.
100% DISAPPOINTED.
>> Ellen: THEN YOU ARE
RESPONSIBLE FOR HELPING
EVERYBODY IN FLORIDA.
WHAT DO YOU DRINK?
>> TEQUILA, ACTUALLY.
>> Ellen: IT DOES NOT GET HIM,
JOSH.
>> NO, IT DOES.
BUT I DO IT ANYWAY.
>> Ellen: HOW MANY GALLONS
WOULD YOU SAY A WEEK?
I AM SUPPOSED TO ASK IN GALLONS.
>> 2 GALLONS, NO, A GALLON.
I'M KIDDING.
A HALF A GALLON.
>> Ellen: AND A HALF A GALLON
A WEEK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR TALKING TO ME.
I HAVE NOTHING FOR YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
I'M LOOKING FOR DRINKERS.
I AM LOOKING FOR A BIG DRINKERS
HERE, AND I, I THINK YOU DRINK,
STAND UP.
HI.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M GOOD, HOW ARE YOU.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS HALEY.
>> Ellen: WHERE YOU FROM?
>> TORONTO, CANADA.
>> Ellen: OH, YOU DON'T COUNT
ON HERE.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO DRINK?
>> I LIKE DRINKING TEQUILA.
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> Ellen: EXCEPT FOR JOSH.
>> JOSH IS NOT COOL ENOUGH.
>> Ellen: JOSH IS SUPER COOL!
DON'T YOU DARE SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT JOSH!
HE IS A FIREFIGHTER, [BLEEP]
DAMN IT!
[APPLAUSE]
>> SORRY!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, FOR
PLAYING, ALL OF YOU GET VODKA.
THAT'S ALL WE HAVE.
AND AN iPAD.
THANK YOU FOR PLAYING.
AND A DANCE FROM TWITCH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> OH, THE BOOTH IS BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THERE YOU ARE.
HE UP.
TO DO YOU LIKE -- IT IS A
CHEETO'S BOOTH.
IT SAYS CHEETOS, OFFICIAL
SPONSOR OF THE "ELLEN" SHOW.
AND IF YOU WANT TO REVEAL THAT.
>> OH, THERE WE GO.
SINCE WE DID THAT, CHEETOS SENDS
US MONEY.
[APPLAUSE]
CHEETOS, I LIKE YOU, BUT I CAN'T
GIVE YOU FREE ADVERTISING.
WE WILL KEEP THAT THEY ARE, BUT
YOU HAVE TO SEND ME AN ORANGE
DUSTED CHECK OF SOME SORT.
WHILE I WAIT FOR THE MONEY, I
WILL SHOW YOU A HEADLINE I SAW,
98-YEAR-OLD GIRL SCOUT HAS BEEN
SELLING COOKIES SINCE 1932.
ISN'T THAT AMAZING?
NOTHING GETS YOU THROUGH THE
GREAT DEPRESSION LIKE A THIN
MINT.
[LAUGHTER]
BUT TO CELEBRATE THIS INCREDIBLE
WOMAN, THE GIRL SCOUTS OF
AMERICA PUT OUT THIS VIDEO.
>> I AM A GIRL SCOUT.
>> LAST YEAR I RAISED MORE THAN
$2,000 FOR LOCAL CHARITIES.
>> I HELPED ORGANIZE A FOOD
DRIVE ON THANKSGIVING.
>> I OVERCHARGED MY CUSTOMERS $2
A BOX AND POCKET THE EXTRA CASH.
>> I LOVE BEING A PART OF SUCH
AN AWESOME COMMUNITY.
>> I FEEL SO ACCOMPLISHED.
>> DURING PROHIBITION I WOULD
REPLACE THE COOKIES WITH A
BOTTLE OF ALCOHOL I BREWED IN MY
BATHTUB.
A VERY LUCRATIVE.
>> I WILL BE A GIRL SCOUT
FOREVER.
>> I'VE DONE SOME THINGS.
[LAUGHTER]
UNSPEAKABLE THINGS.
>> GIRL SCOUTS OF AMERICA, MOST
OF US HAVE NOT DONE TIME FOR
ARMED ROBBERY.
[APPLAUSE]
'S BILL AND SHE.
NOW I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING
REALLY COOL THAT I SAW ON LINE,
THE BIGGEST DANCE TREND IS
CALLED THE RENEGADE.
THE MOST IMPRESSIVE THING IS
THAT A 14-YEAR-OLD FROM ATLANTA
CREATED IT.
PERFORMING IT WITH TWITCH RIGHT
NOW, PLEASE WELCOME JALAYA!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: SO MANY THINGS GOING
ON!
WHAT IS HAPPENING WITH ALL THE
ARMS?
SO YOU STARTED THIS.
YOU CAME UP WITH THIS ENTIRE
DANCE.
>> YES.
>> Ellen: HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
>> IT ONLY TOOK FIVE OR
10 MINUTES BUT A LOT OF TRIES.
IT WAS RIGHT BEFORE THE DANCE,
SO I HAD TO RUSH, BUT WHEN I
FINALLY POSTED IT.
>> Ellen: WHICH ONE OF THESE
ARM MOVEMENTS DID YOU --
SPEAK OF WHOA.
>> Ellen: YES, DO THE WHOA
RIGHT NOW.
AND THEN YOU ADD THINGS TO THE
WHOA.
IT'S CRAZY THAT PEOPLE CAN
REMEMBER ALL OF THAT.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
YOU HAVE MICHELLE OBAMA AND
LIZZO, AND KIM KARDASHIAN
TWEETING ABOUT YOU.
>> IT IS REALLY EXCITING KNOWING
THAT.
>> Ellen: THEY ARE LOVING IT.
I GOT YOU A GIFT, BECAUSE THAT
IS WHAT I LIKE TO DO AROUND
HERE.
THIS IS A JACKET, AND IT SAYS
THE ORIGINAL RENEGADE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> Ellen: PUT IT ON.
AND THEN THE COOL THING ABOUT
THIS, YOU HAVE A POCKET.
THERE IS $1,000 IN THIS POCKET
RIGHT HERE.
OH, THERE IS ANOTHER POCKET.
THERE IS ANOTHER $1,000 IN THAT
POCKET.
HERE IS ANOTHER POCKET, THERE IS
$1,000.
THERE IS A POCKET INSIDE.
THERE IS ANOTHER THOUSAND
DOLLARS.
THERE IS ANOTHER THOUSAND.
THAT IS $5,000!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> I FEEL LIKE I WAS JUST BORN,
♪ ♪
THAT'S EXACTLY --
>> I FEEL LIKE I WAS JUST BORN,
>> THERE WAS NO KNOWING.
THAT'S EXACTLY --
SHE CAME OUT OF THE WOMB
>> THERE WAS NO KNOWING.
PERFORMING.
SHE CAME OUT OF THE WOMB
SONG AND DANCE.
PERFORMING.
>> Ellen: I HAVE THE DATES
SONG AND DANCE.
WRONG, ALL THIS TIME.
>> Ellen: I HAVE THE DATES
DIDDY, COME ON OUT!
WRONG, ALL THIS TIME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DIDDY, COME ON OUT!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Announcer: TUESDAY, THE ONE
♪ ♪
AND ONLY CHER.
>> Announcer: TUESDAY, THE ONE
>> Ellen: I HOPE IT IS HER,
AND ONLY CHER.
BECAUSE THOSE CHER IMPERSONATORS
>> Ellen: I HOPE IT IS HER,
ARE VERY GOOD.
BECAUSE THOSE CHER IMPERSONATORS
>> Announcer: AND NEXT NEW
ARE VERY GOOD.
"ELLEN," --
>> Announcer: AND NEXT NEW
>> Ellen: HE SPEAKS SIX
"ELLEN," --
LANGUAGES.
>> Ellen: HE SPEAKS SIX
>> Announcer: GET READY TO
LANGUAGES.
VOTE.
[police siren]
Michael, your a singer.
bubly is a sparkling water.
Sure is.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
So I was at Marshalls
and I see this jean jacket.
I put it on,
popped the collar
and looked at the brand—
And when I saw the price tag
I was like,
oh yeah, this is—
this is a keeper
Brands that wow.
Prices
that thrill.
Marshalls. Your Surprise
Is Waiting!
I'm a Big Kid Now
Prices
I'm a Big Kid now
Went from baby bottles to
drinking from sippy cups.
Went from wearing diapers,
to rocking these fresh Pull-Ups.
We're 50 million strong.
So, put on your Pull-Ups and
help us sing this song.
New size fits smaller trainers.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUESTS ARE
ACTORS, PARENTS, SIBLINGS, AND
NOW THE HOSTS OF THEIR OWN
PODCAST.
PLEASE WELCOME KATE AND OLIVER
HUDSON!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WELCOME BACK!
♪ ♪
YOU TWO.
>> Ellen: WELCOME BACK!
I AM EXCITED TO SEE BOTH OF YOU.
YOU TWO.
THE LAST TIME YOU WERE HERE, I
I AM EXCITED TO SEE BOTH OF YOU.
WAS NOT HERE.
THE LAST TIME YOU WERE HERE, I
YOU WERE HOSTING WITHR MO>> I L.
WAS NOT HERE.
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
YOU WERE HOSTING WITHR MO>> I L.
>> Ellen: HOW HAVE YOU
I HAD A GREAT TIME.
>> I HAVE BEEN GREAT.
>> Ellen: HOW HAVE YOU
I HAVE BEEN HANGING WITH MY
>> I HAVE BEEN GREAT.
SISSY DOING OUR PODCAST, TRYING
I HAVE BEEN HANGING WITH MY
TO RAISE THREE CHILDREN.
SISSY DOING OUR PODCAST, TRYING
>> Ellen: YOU BOTH HAVE THREE
TO RAISE THREE CHILDREN.
CHILDREN?
>> Ellen: YOU BOTH HAVE THREE
>> HE RAISED HIS CHILDREN REALLY
CHILDREN?
EASILY.
>> HE RAISED HIS CHILDREN REALLY
>> IT IS WHAT I DO.
EASILY.
>> Ellen: IT IS MY BEST WORK?
>> IT IS WHAT I DO.
ARE THEY THE SAME AGES?
>> Ellen: IT IS MY BEST WORK?
>> I HAVE THE FIRST ONE, IT IS
ARE THEY THE SAME AGES?
RYDER THEN WYLDER.
>> I HAVE THE FIRST ONE, IT IS
THEN BODIE, BEING, RIO, RILEY.
RYDER THEN WYLDER.
>> THIS IS SUCH A GREAT PICTURE.
THEN BODIE, BEING, RIO, RILEY.
>> WE HAD TWO BOYS AND A GIRL.
>> THIS IS SUCH A GREAT PICTURE.
>> Ellen: IT'S VERY STRANGE.
>> WE HAD TWO BOYS AND A GIRL.
BUT THIS NEW LITTLE CHILD OF
>> Ellen: IT'S VERY STRANGE.
YOURS, NOW, COME ON.
BUT THIS NEW LITTLE CHILD OF
>> OH, STOP.
YOURS, NOW, COME ON.
YES, SHE IS.
>> OH, STOP.
SHE IS SO FUNNY.
YES, SHE IS.
SHE IS SO DEEPLY FUNNY.
SHE IS SO FUNNY.
I ACTUALLY THINK THAT SHE HAS
SHE IS SO DEEPLY FUNNY.
THE FUNNY GENE.
I ACTUALLY THINK THAT SHE HAS
>> Ellen: SHE LOOKS LIKE IT.
THE FUNNY GENE.
>> SHE LOVES JEWELRY, IF YOU
>> Ellen: SHE LOOKS LIKE IT.
WEAR ANY KIND OF NECKLACE, YOU
>> SHE LOVES JEWELRY, IF YOU
HAVE TO TAKE IT OFF, SHE WILL
WEAR ANY KIND OF NECKLACE, YOU
WEAR IT.
HAVE TO TAKE IT OFF, SHE WILL
IT IS A LITTLE.
WEAR IT.
>> SHE IS TOUGH.
IT IS A LITTLE.
SHE IS GOING TO HOLD HER OWN.
>> SHE IS TOUGH.
>> SHE LIKES THE GIRLY THINGS.
SHE IS GOING TO HOLD HER OWN.
>> Ellen: SHE DEMANDS IT FROM
>> SHE LIKES THE GIRLY THINGS.
YOU.
>> Ellen: SHE DEMANDS IT FROM
>> OFF.
YOU.
>> SHE WAS OFF.
>> OFF.
[LAUGHTER]
>> SHE WAS OFF.
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO ADORABLE.
[LAUGHTER]
THAT IS GREAT.
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO ADORABLE.
CONGRATULATIONS, WILL YOU KEEP
THAT IS GREAT.
HAVING CHILDREN UNTIL ONE OF YOU
CONGRATULATIONS, WILL YOU KEEP
WINS?
HAVING CHILDREN UNTIL ONE OF YOU
>> NO.
WINS?
>> [LAUGHS]
>> NO.
I HAVE A FEELING I WILL END UP
>> [LAUGHS]
WINNING.
I HAVE A FEELING I WILL END UP
I DON'T KNOW IF I AM DONE YET.
WINNING.
I AM IN THAT PLACE, LIKE RIGHT
I DON'T KNOW IF I AM DONE YET.
NOW RANI IS AT THE AGE WHERE YOU
I AM IN THAT PLACE, LIKE RIGHT
WANT ANOTHER BABY, BUT WHEN SHE
NOW RANI IS AT THE AGE WHERE YOU
GETS FOUR, MY LIFE IS BACK AND
WANT ANOTHER BABY, BUT WHEN SHE
THEY ARE IN IT GROOVE, DO YOU
GETS FOUR, MY LIFE IS BACK AND
GUYS KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
THEY ARE IN IT GROOVE, DO YOU
ABOUT?
GUYS KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
IT IS A WINDOW.
ABOUT?
>> Ellen: MY WINDOW IS NEVER
IT IS A WINDOW.
OPEN, EVER.
>> Ellen: MY WINDOW IS NEVER
MY WINDOW HAS NEVER BEEN OPEN AT
OPEN, EVER.
ALL.
MY WINDOW HAS NEVER BEEN OPEN AT
>> YOU HAVE NEVER HAD A WINDOW.
ALL.
>> Ellen: I DO THINK THEY ARE
>> YOU HAVE NEVER HAD A WINDOW.
ADORABLE, AND I LIKE PLAYING
>> Ellen: I DO THINK THEY ARE
WITH CHILDREN, AND THEN GOODBYE.
ADORABLE, AND I LIKE PLAYING
[LAUGHTER]
WITH CHILDREN, AND THEN GOODBYE.
>> Ellen: IT IS JUST
[LAUGHTER]
INTERESTING, YOU'RE BOTH VERY
>> Ellen: IT IS JUST
SIMILAR, YOU HAVE THREE KIDS,
INTERESTING, YOU'RE BOTH VERY
THREE KIDS, AND YOU ARE BOTH IN
SIMILAR, YOU HAVE THREE KIDS,
THE BUSINESS, IS THIS SOMETHING
THREE KIDS, AND YOU ARE BOTH IN
YOU BOTH KNEW GROWING UP BECAUSE
THE BUSINESS, IS THIS SOMETHING
YOU HAD PARENTS THAT WERE ACTORS
YOU BOTH KNEW GROWING UP BECAUSE
THAT YOU WOULD GO INTO THIS?
YOU HAD PARENTS THAT WERE ACTORS
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD DO
THAT YOU WOULD GO INTO THIS?
ANYTHING ELSE.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD DO
I FELT LIKE I WAS JUST BORN LIKE
ANYTHING ELSE.
THAT WAS EXACTLY --
I FELT LIKE I WAS JUST BORN LIKE
>> THERE WAS NO KNOWING WITH
THAT WAS EXACTLY --
KATE, IT JUST WAS.
>> THERE WAS NO KNOWING WITH
SHE CAME OUT OF THE WOMB
KATE, IT JUST WAS.
PERFORMING.
SHE CAME OUT OF THE WOMB
THE SONG AND DANCE, AND, HEY,
PERFORMING.
LOOK AT ME!
THE SONG AND DANCE, AND, HEY,
SHE CAME OUT AS ETHEL MERMAN.
LOOK AT ME!
>> Ellen: HELLO!
SHE CAME OUT AS ETHEL MERMAN.
>> HELLO, WORLD!
>> Ellen: HELLO!
>> KIND OF.
>> HELLO, WORLD!
>> IT DROVE ME CRAZY.
>> KIND OF.
THIS IS WHY OUR RELATIONSHIP AS
>> IT DROVE ME CRAZY.
CHILDREN WAS NOT VERY GREAT.
THIS IS WHY OUR RELATIONSHIP AS
>> THE ANSWER TO THE QUESTION
CHILDREN WAS NOT VERY GREAT.
IS, YOU DID NOT HAVE THAT.
>> THE ANSWER TO THE QUESTION
YOU WERE LIKE FREE STYLING, YOU
IS, YOU DID NOT HAVE THAT.
KIND OF GREW UP --
YOU WERE LIKE FREE STYLING, YOU
THAT WAS YOUR CREATIVE MOMENT.
KIND OF GREW UP --
>> THIS IS NOT WHAT I WAS HOPING
THAT WAS YOUR CREATIVE MOMENT.
TO DO WITH MY LIFE WAS BE A
>> THIS IS NOT WHAT I WAS HOPING
PROFESSIONAL FREESTYLE ARE.
TO DO WITH MY LIFE WAS BE A
BUT I MADE MOVIES.
PROFESSIONAL FREESTYLE ARE.
I LIKED TO MAKE MOVIES.
BUT I MADE MOVIES.
SHE WAS ACTING AND DOING HER
I LIKED TO MAKE MOVIES.
THING.
SHE WAS ACTING AND DOING HER
>> OLI WAS LIKE, I FEEL LIKE
THING.
THIS IS EASY.
>> OLI WAS LIKE, I FEEL LIKE
I WILL GO ON SOME AUDITIONS AND
THIS IS EASY.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
I WILL GO ON SOME AUDITIONS AND
>> IT WORKED OUT.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> AND THEN YOU FELL IN LOVE
>> IT WORKED OUT.
WITH IT.
>> AND THEN YOU FELL IN LOVE
>> Ellen: Y'ALL HUNG OUT WHEN
WITH IT.
YOU WERE YOUNGER, WERE YOU
>> Ellen: Y'ALL HUNG OUT WHEN
CLOSE?
YOU WERE YOUNGER, WERE YOU
>> WE WERE SUPER CLOSE, BUT AS
CLOSE?
WE GOT OLDER AND WE GOT INTO OUR
>> WE WERE SUPER CLOSE, BUT AS
PARTY YEARS, THINGS GOT A LITTLE
WE GOT OLDER AND WE GOT INTO OUR
CLOSER.
PARTY YEARS, THINGS GOT A LITTLE
>> ONCE WE WERE OLD ENOUGH TO
CLOSER.
LIKE EACH OTHER'S FRIENDS THINGS
>> ONCE WE WERE OLD ENOUGH TO
WERE GOOD.
LIKE EACH OTHER'S FRIENDS THINGS
>> WE WOULD THROW CRAZY HUGE
WERE GOOD.
PARTIES.
>> WE WOULD THROW CRAZY HUGE
>> BEFORE WE WERE LIKE -- WE
PARTIES.
WERE NAUGHTY WHEN OUR PARENTS
>> BEFORE WE WERE LIKE -- WE
WOULD LEAVE TOWN AND WE ALWAYS
WERE NAUGHTY WHEN OUR PARENTS
HAD PARTIES.
WOULD LEAVE TOWN AND WE ALWAYS
MOM WOULD FIND OUT ABOUT IT.
HAD PARTIES.
IF THE LAMP WAS BROKEN IT WAS
MOM WOULD FIND OUT ABOUT IT.
LIKE A REAL, IT WAS NOT GOOD.
IF THE LAMP WAS BROKEN IT WAS
>> I BROKE A LAMP ONCE, I BROKE
LIKE A REAL, IT WAS NOT GOOD.
A LAMP MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, IT
>> I BROKE A LAMP ONCE, I BROKE
SHATTERED INTO A BILLION PIECES
A LAMP MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, IT
AND I THINK RIGHT NOW IF SHE IS
SHATTERED INTO A BILLION PIECES
LISTENING, I AM SORRY.
AND I THINK RIGHT NOW IF SHE IS
BECAUSE I HAVE NOT TOLD YOU
LISTENING, I AM SORRY.
ABOUT THIS.
BECAUSE I HAVE NOT TOLD YOU
>> SHE STILL THINKS A DOG --
ABOUT THIS.
>> SHE STILL THINKS THE DOG DID
>> SHE STILL THINKS A DOG --
IT.
>> SHE STILL THINKS THE DOG DID
>> BUT WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
IT.
ONCE WE GOT OLDER AND HAD FUN
>> BUT WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
WITH OUR PARENTS, THEN OUR
ONCE WE GOT OLDER AND HAD FUN
PARENTS CAME TO OUR PARTIES AT
WITH OUR PARENTS, THEN OUR
THEIR HOUSE.
PARENTS CAME TO OUR PARTIES AT
SO WE WOULD THROW THE PARTY AND
THEIR HOUSE.
MY PARENTS WOULD JUST SHOW UP.
SO WE WOULD THROW THE PARTY AND
>> KATE WOULD INVITE THE
MY PARENTS WOULD JUST SHOW UP.
INDUSTRY, AND I WOULD INVITE THE
>> KATE WOULD INVITE THE
RIFFRAFF.
INDUSTRY, AND I WOULD INVITE THE
>> OLIVER --
RIFFRAFF.
>> SHE WOULD GET PISSED OFF AT
>> OLIVER --
ME, BECAUSE SHE WOULD BE LIKE
>> SHE WOULD GET PISSED OFF AT
WHO IS JOSE REMAND IS?
ME, BECAUSE SHE WOULD BE LIKE
AND THERE SHE IS ETHEL MERMAN
WHO IS JOSE REMAND IS?
AGAIN.
AND THERE SHE IS ETHEL MERMAN
>> WHY ARE THEY HERE, GO HOME!
AGAIN.
>> AND WE HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK.
>> WHY ARE THEY HERE, GO HOME!
>> ARE YOU GETTING CONFUSED?
>> AND WE HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK.
>> NO, NEVER.
>> ARE YOU GETTING CONFUSED?
HE BROUGHT THE RIFFRAFF, YOU
>> NO, NEVER.
BROUGHT THE INDUSTRY.
HE BROUGHT THE RIFFRAFF, YOU
>> OKAY.
BROUGHT THE INDUSTRY.
>> Ellen: I HAVE TO TAKE A
>> OKAY.
BREAK.
>> Ellen: I HAVE TO TAKE A
DON'T SUCK ME AGAIN.
BREAK.
DON'T SUCK ME IN AGAIN.
DON'T SUCK ME AGAIN.
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T SUCK ME IN AGAIN.
>> ELLEN.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO TELL
>> ELLEN.
PEOPLE THAT.
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO TELL
>> Ellen: DON'T SUCK ME INTO
PEOPLE THAT.
YOUR STORY AGAIN.
>> Ellen: DON'T SUCK ME INTO
WE WILL BE BACK.
YOUR STORY AGAIN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE BACK.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NAME A FAMOUS PERSON YOU HAVE
♪ ♪
KISSED THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
NAME A FAMOUS PERSON YOU HAVE
>> [LAUGHS]
KISSED THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
>> Ellen: I HAD THE DATES
>> [LAUGHS]
WRONG.
>> Ellen: I HAD THE DATES
ALL THIS TIME.
>>> NEXT.
YOU WANT A CAR THAT WILL KEEP
YOUR FAMILY SAFE AND NOT COST A
FORTUNE.
THE BEST CARS FOR YOUR FAMILY.
SEE THEM HERE FIRST NEXT ON NEWS
4 AT 4:00.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
KATE AND OLIVER HUDSON.
FINISH THE STORY.
>> BASICALLY I JUST ALWAYS
WANTED TO MAKE SURE EVERYTHING
WORKED OUT OKAY.
THAT'S HOW WE ARE IN THE
PODCAST.
I WANT IT TO BE ORGANIZED AND IT
IS NOT TOO CRAZY.
AND OLIVER IS LIKE, LET IT GET
CRAZY.
IT'S FINE.
SO I AM STANDING AT THE DOOR
MAKING SURE THAT PEOPLE WHO ARE
NOT SUPPOSED TO BE AT THE PARTY
ARE NOT COMING IN.
AND I'M KIND OF FREAKING OUT,
THE CONTROL FREAK IS LIKE, THIS
IS NOT OKAY.
AND I SEE SOMEONE SCALING,
LITERALLY SCALING AN 8-FOOT GATE
AT MY PARENTS HOUSE.
AND I AM GOING, I AM FREAKING
OUT.
I AM LIKE THIS PERSON.
AND THEY COME OFF, AND THEY DO A
BACK HAND SPRING THING.
I AM LIKE ABOUT TO YELL AT THIS
GUY.
AND IT IS TOM CRUISE.
[LAUGHTER]
AND I WAS LIKE, OH.
I DID NOT REALIZE YOU WERE
COMING TO MY PARTY.
>> HE WAS LIKE, I WAS NOT
INVITED.
>> HE WAS LIKE, I HEARD THERE
WAS A PARTY.
YEAH, TOM, COME ON IN.
>> Ellen: SO THAT'S HOW HE
GETS AROUND EVERYWHERE.
HE JUST SCALES THINGS.
>> YES, HE IS
"MISSION: IMPOSSIBLE."
IT WAS WILD.
I AM NOT KIDDING.
>> BY THE WAY, AT THE END OF THE
NIGHT, TOM CRUISE AND JOSE
HERNANDEZ WERE HAVING A GREAT
CONVERSATION.
>> HE WAS ALSO THE ONE SLEEPING
IN THE BUSHES THAT NIGHT, WE
WOKE UP AND HE WAS IN ONE OF
MOM'S RUGS.
>> MOM WOKE UP AND SAID, WHO IS
SLEEPING AND MY RUG?
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU MEAN IN
A RUG?
YOU ROLL UP AND SLEEP?
>> YES.
>> WE HAVE SO MUCH FUN.
>> Ellen: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
PODCAST.
IT IS "SIBLING REVELRY," EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
>> WE HAVE NEVER DONE ANYTHING
TOGETHER, CREATIVELY, AND THIS
WAS A GREAT OPPORTUNITY FOR US
TO EXPLORE THE SIBLING DYNAMIC.
AND WE WANTED TO BE CANDID WITH
OUR RELATIONSHIP.
AND IT HAS BEEN AMAZING EVEN
JUST FOR US, AND BRINGING ON
CELEBRITIES AND THEIR SIBLINGS
TO SORT OF GAIN DIFFERENT
PERSPECTIVES.
IT IS A VERY IMPORTANT
RELATIONSHIP THAT WE THINK IS
UNDEREXPLORED.
>> IT IS FUNDING, BECAUSE EVEN
WE ARE LEARNING SO MUCH ABOUT IT
AS WE GO.
WHETHER IT IS EACH OTHER, OTHER
PEOPLE.
IT DOES NOT MATTER, IT IS FUNNY,
WE THINK THAT WE KNOW PEOPLE,
BUT WHEN WE HEAR THINGS FROM
THEIR SIBLINGS PERSPECTIVE, YOU
GET A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
FEELING ABOUT WHO THEY ARE OR
WHERE THEY COME FROM.
AND WE DID NOT REALIZE OURSELVES
HOW MUCH FUN IT WOULD BE FOR US.
IT HAS BEEN ONE OF THE MOST
REWARDING THINGS.
>> HONESTLY FOR ME, IT HAS BEEN
THE MOST PROFOUND THING THAT I
HAVE DONE CREATIVELY.
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS CRAZY.
BUT IT IS JUST THE TRUTH.
WORKING WITH KATE AND BEING ABLE
TO SORT OF TALK ABOUT OUR
RELATIONSHIP CANDIDLY, FOR SOME
CRAZY REASON WHEN THE MIC IS IN
FRONT OF MY FACE, I CAN SAY
MORE.
>> Ellen: THAT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
"SIBLING REVELRY" IS AVAILABLE
ON APPLE, GOOGLE, AND EVERYWHERE
YOU CAN STREAM PODCASTS.
SO WHY DID I LIST THOSE?
IT IS EVERYWHERE.
WE WILL PLAY A GAME WITH KATE
AND OLIVER LATER IN THE SHOW!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HE THOUGHT THAT BY MAKING THE
VIDEO AND GETTING DIDDY'S
ATTENTION, THAT WE WOULD SHOW
THAT CHILDHOOD CANCER MATTERS.
AND IT WORKED PRETTY >> Ellen:
YES, IT DID WORK.
♪ ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ THEY SAY MOVE FOR ME, MOVE FOR
ME, MOVE FOR ME, AY, AY, AY ♪
>> Announcer: ALL NEW "ELLEN,"
2020 PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
>> Ellen: HE SPEAKS SEVEN
LANGUAGES.
WHAT ARE THEY?
>>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M PAT LAWSON WITH A LOOK AT
THE STORIES WE'RE LOOKING AT
TODAY.
TODAY AT 4:00 TRACY WILKINS
REVEALS THE SNAPCHAT EXCHANGE
THAT MAY HAVE LED TO THE
SHOOTING.
>>> VICTORIA'S SECRET SOLD AND
THE CEO STEPPED DOWN.
WILL THAT BE ENOUGH TO SAVE THE
STORE?
>>> AND CONSUMER REPORTS GIVES
US A PEEK AT THE TOP CARS FOR
2020.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: RECENTLY A VIDEO
WENT VIRAL THAT FEATURED AMAZING
KIDS BATTLING CANCER, THEY TRIED
TO CATCH MY FRIEND DIDDY'S
ATTENTION, AND THEY CAUGHT MINE.
WATCH.
>> READY, LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪
[KIDS RAPPING]
>> COME DANCE WITH US, P DIDDY!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: SOME OF THOSE KIDS
ARE HERE TODAY, COME ON OUT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HI, ELLEN!
>> Ellen: HI.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> YES!
>> Ellen: HI.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Ellen: THIS IS FANTASTIC, I
HEARD YOU WERE VERY EXCITED THAT
WE CALL DO.
>> YEAH!
>> Ellen: THIS IS REALLY COOL
WHAT Y'ALL ARE DOING, WHY THIS
SONG?
WHY DID YOU CHOOSE THIS SONG?
>> WE CHOSE THIS SONG BY P DIDDY
"BAD BOYS FOR LIFE," BECAUSE WE
SURVIVE WHAT WE HAVE BEEN
THROUGH.
AND WE ARE ALL BATTLING CANCER.
AND WE AIN'T GOING ANYWHERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: SO WE BROUGHT YOU
IN, YOU ARE FROM ALL DIFFERENT
PARTS OF THE COUNTRY.
HOW DO YOU LIKE LOS ANGELES?
>> SO FAR IT HAS BEEN GREAT.
I HAVE SEEN A LOT OF STUFF SO
FAR, BUT I AM EXCITED TO GO TO
LIKE UNIVERSAL, BECAUSE WE ARE
GOING TO UNIVERSAL IN A FEW D
DAYS, AND I JUST AM SO EXCITED
TO BE HERE TO SEE YOU.
BECAUSE I WATCH YOUR SHOW ALL
THE TIME, AND I LOVE YOUR "GAMES
OF GAMES" SHOW.
AND I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT Y
YOU!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THANKS!
I HATE TO PICK FAVORITES, BUT
SHE IS --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
>> THANK YOU.
>> Ellen: WHOSE IDEA WAS IT TO
MAKE THE VIDEO?
BECAUSE IT IS ONE THING TO
CHOOSE THE SONG, BUT TO PUT THE
VIDEO TOGETHER, WHOSE IDEA AND
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
>> IT WAS THE FOUNDER OF OUR
ORGANIZATION, HIS NAME IS TYSON,
HE DECIDED TO SHED LIGHT ON THE
DARK WORLD THAT IS CHILDHOOD
CANCER, SO HE THOUGHT THAT BY
MAKING THE VIDEO AND GETTING
DIDDY'S ATTENTION THAT WE WOULD
GET OUR POINT ACROSS THAT
CHILDHOOD CANCER MATTERS.
AND IT WORKED PRETTY >> Ellen:
GOT A LOT OF ATTENTION.
IT DID GET HIS ATTENTION, HE IS
IN MIAMI, BUT HE KNEW THAT YOU
ALL WOULD BE HERE.
SO HE SENT A MESSAGE TO YOU.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP, Y'ALL, IT IS
DIDDY.
I AM SO BUMMED THAT I CAN'T BE
WITH Y'ALL TODAY, I AM STUCK IN
MIAMI, BUT YOU ARE IN GREAT
HANDS WITH MY GIRL ELLEN.
AND I PROMISE THAT WE WILL BE
DANCING TOGETHER ONE DAY SOON.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
PEACE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
THAT WAS VERY SWEET.
HE IS BOUND TO THAT HE CAN'T BE
HERE.
BUT I HAVE A GIFT FOR YOU.
WE WILL TAKE A BREAK, AND WHEN
WE COME BACK, I WILL GIVE YOU A
LITTLE SOMETHING.
WE WILL BE BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: I HAD THE DATES
WRONG ALL THIS TIME.
DIDDY, COME ON OUT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
This right here is the new
Papadia.
Which, if I'm not mistaken,
is Latin for "better than a
sandwich."
Heh-even has a better pickle...
Get a new Papadia for
six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
No, no, no, no,  this ain't no
sandwich.
Because on a sandwich,
they ask you if you want cheese.
But on a Papadia,
cheese is what's holding the
whole operation together.
Get one now for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
♪♪
We're not going to make it.
Oh, we're going to make it.
Woo.
♪♪
Cheerios... Do I look like a
child to you?
Honey Nut Cheerios
are heart healthy
and can help lower
cholesterol.
That's why we introduced
heart shapes.
Get it?
Ummm
Did you just ummm?
No.
I'm pretty sure I heard a ummm.
>> Announcer: ALL NEW "ELLEN,"
2020 PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
>> Ellen: HE SPEAKS SEVEN
LANGUAGES.
WHAT ARE THEY?
>> NORWEGIAN, ARABIC, ITALIAN.
A COUPLE OTHERS.
>> Ellen: ME TOO.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK FROM THE
NONPROFIT FIGHTING ALL MONSTERS.
YOU KNOW THAT DIDDY WILL SEE
THIS AT SOME POINT.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK TO HIM AND
TELL HIM SOMETHING?
>> THANK YOU FOR POSTING THE
VIDEO AND SHARING IT.
AND WE ARE ALL BAD BOYS FOR
LIFE!
>> Ellen: THAT'S RIGHT!
WHAT IS THE DATE TODAY?
I COMPLETELY, AND --
>> IT IS THURSDAY.
>> Ellen: I WAS COMPLETELY
WRONG, WASN'T I?
I HAD THE DATES WRONG ALL THIS
TIME, DIDDY, COME ON OUT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS AWESOME!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOD!
♪ ♪
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WHAT'S UP, "ELLEN"?
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> Ellen: I LOVE THIS.
>> THANK YOU.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOD!
IS THIS REAL?
>> Ellen: SURPRISE!
>> SURPRISE.
>> Ellen: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> IT IS A PLEASURE.
IT IS A PLEASURE.
AND THINK YOU GUYS SO MUCH FOR
REACHING OUT TO ME.
AND I WAS SO TOUCHED, JUST SO
TOUCHED THAT THE SONG THAT HAS
HELP ME GET THROUGH A LOT OF
TRIALS AND TRIBULATIONS IS
FILLING YOU GUYS TO KNOW THE
POWER THAT YOU HAVE IN YOURSELF
TO BELIEVE THAT WE AIN'T GOING
NOWHERE.
Y'ALL GOT THIS?
[APPLAUSE]
WOW.
>> Ellen: I TELL YOU, DIDDY,
AS YOU KNOW, HE IS A SOLID MAN.
HE IS A STRONG MAN, AND HE SAYS
WHAT HE MEANS.
AND THE LAST TIME HE WAS HERE, I
WANT TO SHOW YOU, YEAH, EXACTLY.
SHE WAS ASKING WHAT KIND OF
TABLE THIS WAS.
THIS WAS A DIFFERENT TABLE.
LET'S SHOW EVERYBODY WHAT
HAPPENED LAST TIME.
>> I'M NOT AFRAID OF CLOWNS.
>> Ellen: I HEARD THAT YOU
WERE.
>> [SCREAMS]
[BLEEP]!
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
>> I WATCH THAT A MILLION TIMES.
>> YOU WATCH THAT A MILLION
TIMES.
IT IS FUNDING, RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: THIS MAKES ME VERY
HAPPY BECAUSE I LOVE THE SHOW,
YOU ARE BRINGING BACK "MAKING
THE BAND."
>> YES.
[APPLAUSE]
IT IS A REBOOT OF THE SHOW, BUT
WE ARE DOING IT TOTALLY
DIFFERENT, WE START OFF
AUDITIONS IN ATLANTA THIS
WEEKEND, AND YOU CAN CALL ME ON
MY LOVE LINE, 917 --
>> Ellen: 917, 176-1444.
>> YOU CAN TEXT ME YOUR
ADDITIONS THERE IF YOU CANNOT
MAKE IT, AND "MAKING THE BAND"
IS BACK.
THAT IS MY NUMBER.
TEXT ME.
THIS IS MY REAL NUMBER.
IT IS THE NUMBER THAT I HAVE
GIVEN OUT.
IT IS MY LOVE LINE BECAUSE I
WANT TO GIVE OUT LOVE EVERY DAY.
BECAUSE EVERYBODY NEEDS LOVE.
>> Ellen: EVERYBODY DOES!
[APPLAUSE]
BEFORE YOU GET TO DO SOMETHING
REALLY FUN, WHICH IS DANCE WITH
THIS GUY, MY FRIENDS AT
SHUTTERFLY KNOW THAT YOU ARE
PART OF THIS AMAZING NONPROFIT
FIGHTING ALL MONSTERS AND THEY
WANT TO FIGHT THE MONSTERS BY
DONATING $25,000!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WHOA!
>> Ellen: HEAD OVER AND DANCE!
>> LET'S GO DANCE!
♪ ♪
>> COM ON!
I SEE YOU!
♪ ♪
I'M GOING TO CATCH YOU!
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
♪ ♪
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
♪ THEY
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> OUR NEXT GUEST HAS A SONG
THAT HAS BEEN PERFORMED ALL
ACROSS THE WORLD.
HERE TO PERFORM "DANCE MONKEY,"
PLEASE WELCOME TONES AND I.
♪ ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE I'LL MAKE
YOU DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ THEY SAY OH MY GOD I SEE THE
WAY YOU SHINE ♪
♪ TAKE YOUR HAND, MY DEAR, AND
PLACE THEM BOTH IN MINE ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU STOPPED ME DEAD
WHEN I WAS PASSING BY ♪
♪ AND NOW I BEG TO SEE YOU DANCE
JUST ONE MORE TIME ♪
♪ OOH I SEE YOU, SEE YOU, SEE
YOU EVERY TIME ♪
♪ AND OH MY I, I LIKE YOUR
STYLE ♪
♪ YOU, YOU MAKE ME, MAKE ME,
MAKE ME WANNA CRY ♪
♪ AND NOW I BEG TO SEE YOU DANCE
JUST ONE MORE TIME ♪
♪ SO I SAY ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ THEY SAY MOVE FOR ME, MOVE FOR
ME, MOVE FOR ME, AY, AY, AY ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE I'LL MAKE
YOU DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ I SAID OH MY GOD I SEE YOU
WALKING BY ♪
♪ TAKE MY HANDS, MY DEAR, AND
LOOK ME IN MY EYES ♪
♪ JUST LIKE A MONKEY I'VE BEEN
DANCING MY WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ AND YOU JUST BEG TO SEE ME
DANCE JUST ONE MORE TIME ♪
♪ OOH I SEE YOU, SEE YOU, SEE
YOU EVERY TIME ♪
♪ AND OH MY I, I LIKE YOUR
STYLE ♪
♪ YOU, YOU MAKE ME, MAKE ME,
MAKE ME WANNA CRY ♪
♪ AND NOW I BEG TO SEE YOU DANCE
JUST ONE MORE TIME ♪
♪ SO I SAY ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ THEY SAY MOVE FOR ME, MOVE FOR
ME, MOVE FOR ME, AY, AY, AY ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE I'LL MAKE
YOU DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ THEY SAY ♪
♪ DANCE FOR ME, DANCE FOR ME,
DANCE FOR ME, OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THE
THINGS YOU DO BEFORE ♪
♪ THEY SAY MOVE FOR ME, MOVE FOR
ME, MOVE FOR ME, AY, AY, AY ♪
♪ AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE I'LL MAKE
YOU DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ ALL AGAIN ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: HELLO!
HI!
YOU ARE AWESOME!
GO TO "ELLEN TUBE" FOR AN
EXCLUSIVE PERFORMANCE OF
TONES AND I!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
TONES AND I, EVERYBODY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
NAME A FAMOUS PERSON YOU HAVE
KISSED THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
>> [LAUGHS]
♪♪
Woah is this the future?
This is the present,
future Bill.
Here's your order Bills.
No way!
Yes way.
Okay.
Your dry skin story changes
from one day to the next.
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
and switch.
It doubles your skin's moisture
And repairs dry skin over time.
So tomorrow
can be a different story.
Eucerin —
Recommended
and used by dermatologists.
♪♪
♪ I see a red door and
I want to paint it black ♪
♪ No colors anymore
I want them to turn black ♪
♪ I see a red door and
I want to paint it black ♪
♪ I paint the red door black ♪
♪ Dance floor black ♪
♪ I'm in my own lane ♪
♪ Unapologetic and
I do my own thing ♪
♪ Got my own brain ♪
♪ No colors anymore
I want to paint it black ♪
Free free.
Free!
Free!!
Uh...Free!
Free, free, free.
Free.
Free free!
FREE!!
That's right,
TurboTax Free is free.
Free,free free free.
I love the new myWW program,
because it's tailored to you!
...take the personal assessment
TurboTax Free is free.
and get matched with a proven
weight loss plan.
Find out which customized
plan can make losing weight
easier for you!
myWW
Join today
with the WW
triple play!
(sneezing)
(coughing)
Grab the only tissue with
coconut oil,
aloe, and vitamin E.
Nourish with Kleenex
soothing lotion.
The softest lotion tissue.
♪
Find something incredible,
from somewhere amazing.
Unique selection,
unbelievable prices.
HomeGoods.
Go Finding.
>>> MOMENTS AWAY, FIRST AT 4:00,
THE SOCIAL MEDIA EXCHANGE THAT
HELPED CRACK THE MURDER OF A
LOCAL POLICE DETECTIVE'S SON.
>>> AND THE TOP CARS FOR 2020.
SUSAN HOGAN ON THE BEST NEW
RIDES AND WHICH COULD SAVE YOUR
FAMILY SOME MONEY.
>>> I'M TRACKING A SNOWSTORM TO
OUR SOUTH.
Here's one you guys will like.
Show me Making It.
Oh! I got one.
The Best of Amy Poehler.
Amy, maybe we could
use the Voice Remote
to search for something
that you're not in.
Show me Parks and Rec.
From Netflix to
Prime Video to live TV,
Xfinity lets you
find your favorites
with the Emmy award-winning
X1 Voice Remote.
Show me The Best of
Amy Poehler, again.
This time around...
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get this great
offer from Xfinity.
You'll get double the speed
and save over $250
compared to Fios.
Plus, get $100 back.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
KATE AND OLIVER HUDSON.
YOU ARE VERY REVEALING ON YOUR
PODCAST.
WE WILL PLAY A GAME TO SEE HOW
MUCH YOU WILL REVEAL HERE.
IT IS CALLED TRUTH OR SHOT.
IF YOU DO NOT ANSWER, YOU HAVE
TO TAKE A SHOT OF KATE'S NEW
DELICIOUS VODKA.
>> AS OLIVER HE LIKES TO SAY
KING STREET, THE QUEEN OF VODKA.
>> Ellen: ANSWER HONESTLY.
TELL US SOMETHING ILLEGAL YOU
DID IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> EVERYTHING.
[LAUGHTER]
USED FAKE IDs.
>> OH, GOSH.
>> DON'T.
TAKE A SHOT.
IT'S TOO BAD.
>> I WANT TO SAY IT, BUT I'M
AFRAID THAT PEOPLE WILL THINK
POORLY OF ME.
>> Ellen: THEN TAKE A SHOT.
>> [LAUGHS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SO SMOOTH.
THE SMOOTHEST ON THE MARKET.
>> LIKE THE DAY IS LONG.
>> WHAT IS THE LAST THING YOUR
MOM DID THAT EMBARRASSED YOU?
>> OH, GOD.
SHE DID IT THIS WEEKEND.
THE LAST THING THAT MOM DID THAT
EMBARRASSED ME WAS SHE JUST
TALKED ABOUT THE FIRST TIME I
TOLD HER EYE HAD SEX.
LIKE TO SOMEONE IN FRONT OF ME.
AND THAT WAS EMBARRASSING FOR
ME.
I WAS LIKE YOU DON'T TELL PEOPLE
ABOUT ME LOSING MY VIRGINITY.
>> Ellen: I THINK YOU SHOULD
TAKE A SHOT TO JUST BECAUSE THAT
IS HORRIBLE.
>> SURE.
>> OH, YEAH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THIS WILL BE GOOD
FOR BOTH OF
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
NAME A FAMOUS PERSON YOU HAVE
KISSED THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WHO IS DRIVING ME HOME?
>> YOUR CAR SERVICE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Ellen: I THINK I KNOW THE
ANSWER, HAVE YOU EVER SMOKED
WEED WITH YOUR PARENTS?
>> YES.
>> I HAVE TOO.
[LAUGHTER]
OH, MY GOD THOUGH.
>> GOOD LINE, HEADLINE.
>> Ellen: IT WAS A FUN GAME,
AND WE SHOULD NEVER HAVE PLAYED
IT.
THAT'S IT.
YOU CAN KEEP DRINKING.
I WANT TO THANK ALL OF MY
GUESTS, I WILL
>>> FIRST AT 4:00, A SNAPCHAT
EXCHANGE HELPS CRACK THE KILLING
OF A LOCAL TEEN.
>> IT'S A VERY GOOD FAMILY.
HE WAS A NICE KID.
>> TRACEE WILKINS WITH THE NEW
COURT DOCUMENTS THAT HOPED SOLVE
THE MURDER OF A POLICE
DETECTIVE'S SON.
>> COLD TODAY EVEN COLDER
TOMORROW AND WE'RE TRACKING A
SNOWSTORM TO OUR SOUTH.
>>> NEW FINDINGS ON THE CARS
THAT WILL KEEP YOUR FAMILY SAFE
AND SAVE YOU A FEW BUCKS.
I'VE GOT THE REPORT.
>> AND TOMMY McFLY IS MAKING
MARGARITAS.
>> LET'S MAKE IT HAPPEN.
WHAT ARE THE FIRST STEPS?
>> THE SHAKERS.