[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THANK YOU!
HAVE A SEAT!
THANKS FOR ALL OF THAT.
BACK AT YOU, BY THE WAY.
THANKS FOR THE LOVE.
I GIVE LOVE BACK TO YOU.
VALENTINE'S DAY IS TOMORROW.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNOW THAT,
AND IF YOU DON'T --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT SNEAKS UP ON YOU.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE LIKE, WHAT
DO YOU MEAN IT IS TOMORROW?
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, A LOT
OF PEOPLE WAIT TILL THE LAST
MINUTE.
PLENTY OF RESTAURANTS WHERE YOU
CAN GET A RESERVATION.
YOU JUST HAVE TO DECIDE IF YOU
WANT TO EAT AT 3:30 OR 11:15.
[LAUGHTER]
SOMETIMES SINGLE PEOPLE GET DOWN
ON VALENTINE'S DAY.
I DON'T.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU MIGHT
FIND LOVE.
I KNEW THIS GUY.
A TRUE STORY.
[LAUGHTER]
HE THOUGHT HE WOULD NEVER FIND
LOVE, AND HE MEETS THIS GIRL.
SHE IS ON THE STREETS, AND SHE
IS BEAUTIFUL.
HE IS SUCCESSFUL, BY THE WAY.
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
AND A PROSTITUTE.
[LAUGHTER]
I'M THINKING OF "PRETTY WOMAN."
BUT YOU KNOW, THE POINT IS THAT
WAS A BEAUTIFUL MOVIE.
PERSONALLY I'M NOT A BIG FAN OF
VALENTINE'S DAY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
ELLEN, YOU WILL NEVER GET A MAN
THAT WAY.
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T GET ME WRONG, I LOVE
OVERPRICED FLOWERS AND TINY
LITTLE HEARTS THAT TASTE LIKE
CHALK.
I REALLY DO, BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU NEED A SPECIFIC DAY TO TELL
SOMEONE THAT YOU LOVE THEM.
YOU SHOULD CELEBRATE LOVE ALL
THE TIME!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
EVERY DAY!
BUT IF YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING
A LITTLE EXTRA SPECIAL, YOU
DON'T HAVE TO DO SOMETHING BIG.
REMEMBER LAST YEAR, KANYE DID
THAT THING FOR KIM WHERE HE WAS
A ROOM FULL OF ROSES AND KENNY G
WAS PERFORMING?
DON'T DO THAT.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU DON'T NEED TO
SPEND THAT MUCH MONEY TO SHOW
LOVE.
SECONDLY, I HIRED KENNY G FOR
PORTIA.
HE IS NOT AVAILABLE.
[LAUGHTER]
MANY THINGS YOU CAN DO TO SHOW
PEOPLE HOW MUCH THEY MEAN TO
YOU.
A SIMPLE GESTURE OF FILLING UP
THEIR CAR WITH GAS.
YOU KNOW?
IN THE TANK, NOT THE CAR.
[LAUGHTER]
BUT DON'T PUT IT IN IF IT IS AN
ELECTRIC CAR, BECAUSE THAT'S HOW
I RUINED PORTIA'S CHEVY VOLT.
MAYBE YOU CAN PICK -- LET YOUR
PARTNER PICK WHICH TV SHOW TO
WATCH.
I WILL GIVE YOU CHOICES, YOU CAN
WATCH THIS SHOW, YOU CAN WATCH
"GAMES OF GAMES," YOU CAN WATCH
"FINDING DORY," YOU CAN WATCH A
RERUN OF MY SITCOM.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S BASICALLY IT.
BE PRESENT, PUT AWAY YOUR PHONE.
HE SWITCHED TO SILENT.
TURN OFF NOTIFICATIONS.
I'M KIDDING, NOBODY IS GOING TO
DO THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
JUST BUY SOMEBODY SOME
CHOCOLATES, BECAUSE THEY WILL BE
HUNGRY AFTER DINNER AT 3:30.
I HOPE THAT HELPS.
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
AND GIVE IT UP, HE IS MY WORK
VALENTINE.
I LOVE HIM SO VERY MUCH!
THIS IS TWITCH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
TWITCH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT!
YOU SEE WHAT WE DID?
WE PUT A GIFT, BECAUSE IT IS
VALENTINE'S DAY.
KISSING BOOTH.
REMEMBER WHEN WE SOLD LEMONADE
AND WE MADE SO MUCH MONEY.
WE THOUGHT IF WE CHARGED AND
EVERYONE IN THE AUDIENCE HAD TO
PAY TO KISS YOU.
RIGHT?
>> OKAY.
OKAY.
>> Ellen: OR I HAD SOME PEOPLE
IN THE RIFFRAFF ROOM THAT REALLY
WANT TO KISS YOU, BECAUSE THEY
DID NOT MAKE IT INTO HERE.
SO I WILL BRING SOME PEOPLE FROM
THE RIFFRAFF ROOM, OKAY?
>> OKAY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
AWE
!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HOLD ON!
HOW DO I GET OUT OF HERE?
>> Ellen: MADDOX IS LIKE, HOW
DO I GET IN THERE TO DADDY?
THE WHOLE FAMILY, ALLISON, HI,
ALLISON.
THERE IS WESLEY, MADDOX.
AND DAVE, DAVE, GET OUT OF
THERE.
>> I WAS MAD SUSPICIOUS.
>> HI, EVERYBODY.
>> THIS IS AWESOME.
>> Ellen: I AM EXCITED TO MEET
WESLEY, HOW ARE YOU ENJOYING ZIA
AS A LITTLE SISTER?
>> I LIKE HER A LOT.
>> SHE IS VERY EXCITED TO BE
HERE.
IT IS HER FIRST TIME.
>> Ellen: IT IS SO GREAT.
>> GOING ON THIS BEFORE SHOW AT
THREE MONTHS OLD, OF COURSE!
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR HAVING US.
WE ARE EXCITED TO BE HERE.
BECAUSE IF IT WAS SOMEBODY ELSE
I MIGHT BE A LITTLE MAD.
>> I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED.
YOU'RE LIKE I AM BRINGING
SOMEBODY DOWN.
I WAS LIKE OH!
>> Ellen: I SAY IT ALL THE
TIME, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU ARE
WATCHING OR IF HE TELLS YOU, BUT
ALLISON, YOU LOOK FANTASTIC, AND
DANCING ALL THE WAY THROUGH YOUR
PREGNANCY, AND THEN RIGHT AFTER
YOU GAVE BIRTH.
YOU LOOK AMAZING, YOU ARE
AMAZING.
AND WHAT AN INCREDIBLE --
>> THANK YOU, I REALLY
APPRECIATE THAT.
>> Ellen: Y'ALL, START KIS
KISSING.
AND ALSO, YOU CAN CATCH TWITCH
AND ALLISON ON THE NEW SEASON OF
DISNEY'S "FAIRY TALE WEDDINGS"
WHICH PREMIERES VALENTINE'S DAY
ON DISNEY PLUS!
TWITCH, BELIEVE IT OR NOT, THERE
IS SOMEBODY WHO HAS KISSED MORE
PEOPLE ON TV THEN YOU, I AM
TALKING ABOUT "THE BACHELOR" OF
COURSE.
HE DOES A LOT OF KISSING.
LOOK AT, THEY ARE PUTTING THE
KIDS AWAY BECAUSE WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT "THE BACHELOR."
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT, SO THERE IS A LOT OF
KISSING ON "THE BACHELOR," BUT
THERE IS SOME MOUTH ACTION I
NOTICED.
I WAS VERY DISTRACTED BY ONE OF
THE WOMEN ON THE SHOW, JUST
WATCH HER MOUTH.
>> WHAT?
>> WE ARE GOING STRAIGHT TO THE
ROSE CEREMONY TONIGHT.
♪ ♪
>> I THINK THAT I HAVE GIVEN YOU
ANSWER.
>> BUT KELSEY ASKED AND YOU SAID
NO.
>> I NEVER SAID [BLEEP].
>> YOU WERE SITTING ON THE
COUCH.
>> [BLEEP].
>> I HEARD THAT FROM SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> SHE WANTS TO STAND UP AND
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF YOURSELF, YOU
GO RIGHT ON AHEAD.
>> Ellen: IT IS LIKE SHE IS --
LIKE SHE IS TRYING TO GET
BROCCOLI OUT OF HER TEETH, BUT
THERE WAS NO BROCCOLI THERE.
THERE WAS A STORY I SAW ON THE
NEWS THAT I WANT TO MENTION.
IT AFFECTS SOMEBODY ON MY STAFF.
IF YOU HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING THE
SHOW, YOU KNOW ANDY, MY PRODUCER
HAS STARTED A SLOW WALK
MOVEMENT.
HE IS ON A TREADMILL, AND HE HAS
CALLED IT SLOW WALKING, AND NOW
HE IS UP TO, WHAT IS IT, THREE
OR FOUR COFOLLOWERS?
>> IT IS A LOT MORE THAN THAT.
>> Ellen: HOW MANY DO YOU
HAVE?
>> A LOT, AND IT IS AN
INTERNATIONAL MOVEMENT.
>> Ellen: I JUST SAW THIS
HEADLINE, SO WALKERS ARE MORE
LIKELY TO AGE FASTER.
[LAUGHTER]
>> IT IS NOT REAL.
>> Ellen: IT IS FAKE NEWS?
OKAY.
SO I SAW THE VIDEO THAT YOU
POSTED THIS MORNING, MAYBE YOU
DON'T SEE YOURSELF THE WAY
EVERYBODY ELSE DOES.
>> GOOD MORNING, SLOW WALKERS.
ANDY LASSNER HERE, HAPPY
SOMEDAY.
YOU PROBABLY NOTICED HOW GOOD MY
HAIR LOOKS.
IT'S BECAUSE I GOT A HAIRCUT
TODAY.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GREAT NOW.
YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD.
OUR HAIR AND MAKEUP PEOPLE DO A
GREAT JOB.
BEFORE WE GO TO BREAK, I WANT TO
THANK MY FRIENDS AT HONEY NUT
CHEERIOS FOR SPONSORING THE
VALENTINE'S DAY SHOW, ANDY ZENOR
IS IN THE CHEERIOS SKYBOX, AND
REAL HONEYBEES ARE UP THERE TOO.
TELL US ABOUT THE HONEY NUT
CHEERIOS.
>> HONEY NUT CHEERIOS, HOW.
THEY ARE DELICIOUS.
THE SON OF A --
AND THEY BELIEVE, THAT WHEN YOU
DO GOOD, THAT YOUR HEART
FEELS --
OW.
>> Ellen: I'M GLAD YOU'RE
FEELING GOOD, ANDY, AND YOU WILL
ALL FEEL GOOD, BECAUSE YOU ARE
GETTING A SPECIAL EDITION BOX OF
HONEY NUT CHEERIOS, AND A $100
VISA GIFT CARD AS WELL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE BACK!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> I WANT TO MAKE A VIDEO FOR MY
WIFE THAT IS GOING TO MAKE HER
SMILE.
AND LOOK AT THIS MILLION DOLLAR
SMILE, HOW CAN YOU NOT?
>> Ellen: WHAT THREE ITEMS
WOULD YOU TAKE WITH YOU ON A
DESERTED ISLAND?
>> A NOTEBOOK, A PEN, AND SOME
TEQUILA.
[DING]
>> Announcer: NEXT NEW
"ELLEN."
>> Ellen: HE KNOWS SO MUCH
ABOUT MAKING LOVE, THE BIRDS AND
THE BEES TEACH THEIR KIDS ABOUT
HIM.
>> Announcer: SPEND
VALENTINE'S DAY WITH PEOPLE'S
SEXIEST MAN.
JOHN LEGEND.
>> MORE COMMONLY KNOWN AS
CHRISSY TEIGEN'S HUSBAND.
>> Announcer: PLUS
GWYNETH PALTROW WITH
VALENTINE'S DAY MESSAGES.
>> Ellen: DEAR MOM, I KNOW
YOUR HORMONES ARE CRAZY, BUT
Big news America!
For a limited time, we've
changed the shape
of Honey Nut Cheerios.
Because we want people to know
they're delicious
AND can help lower cholesterol.
Heart healthy. Get it? A heart!
Can you believe they had one in
my size?!
The good news?
Our protection lasts all day.
The bad news?
Your patience might not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
(Director's Voice)
Quiet, people!
And cue Rachael Ray.
Hey friends!
Today we're whipping up
some delicious recipes.
We've got Rustic Duck Stew
and Creamy Seafood Bisque.
So? Who's hungry?
(Barking, Meowing)
I said, WHO'S HUNGRY!?
Pets love Rachael Ray™ Nutrish®
because it's made from
kitchen-inspired recipes.
With real meat, poultry or fish.
I love good eaters.
Rachael Ray Nutrish.
Real Recipes.
Real Ingredients.
Real Good.®
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE HAVE BEEN
ENTERTAINED BY MADDOX'S DANCING
SO FAR.
GRAB YOUR TISSUES, YOU WILL NEED
THEM.
THIS VIDEO OF A HUSBAND
SERENADING HIS WIFE BEFORE SHE
WENT UNDER SURGERY FOR BRAIN
CANCER IS THE GREATEST THING YOU
WILL SEE YOU TODAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> ♪ EVERY TIME I LOOK INTO
YOUR EYES ♪
♪ I SEE IT ♪
♪ EVERY TIME I GET WITHIN YOUR
SITE ♪
♪ I FEEL IT ♪
♪ I'LL GET YOU THROUGH ♪
>> Ellen: FROM CHARLOTTE,
NORTH CAROLINA, PLEASE WELCOME
RAY AND ROSLYN SINGLETON.
♪ ♪
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> OH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: FIRST OF ALL, Y'ALL
LOOK FANTASTIC!
I HEARD YOU WERE SURPRISED THAT
WE CALLED.
>> SURPRISED IS AN
UNDERSTATEMENT OF WHAT WE WERE
WHEN YOU CALLED.
>> WHEN I GOT THE CALL, MY
IPHONE SHOWS THE ZIP CODE WHERE
IT CAME FROM AND IT SAID
BURBANK, CALIFORNIA, AND SHE
SAID I AM FROM THE "ELLEN" SHOW,
MY HEAD EXPLODED.
IT WAS THE GREATEST CALL I HAVE
EVER GOTTEN.
AND LOOK WHERE WE ARE.
>> HE CALLED ME AND SAID, HEY, I
NEED TO TELL YOU SOMETHING, ARE
YOU SITTING DOWN?
HE AND I SAID YEAH, HE SAID THE
"ELLEN" SHOW JUST CALLED.
I WAS LIKE, YOU SHOULD NOT LIE.
IT'S SO CLOSE TO SUNDAY.
YOU SHOULD NOT LIE.
HE WAS LIKE NO, THEY DID.
>> Ellen: IT IS SO CLOSE TO
SUNDAY.
>> YOU SHOULD NOT TELL FIBS.
>> Ellen: WEDNESDAYS ARE OKAY.
YOU LOOK FANTASTIC.
I MEAN, YOU LOOK FANTASTIC!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND WE SHOULD THINK THE DOCTORS,
YOU HAD SURGERY A MONTH AGO, AND
YOU SAID, I HAVE TO BE ON THE
"ELLEN" SHOW.
>> WHATEVER YOU HAVE TO DO, WRAP
IT UP.
WHATEVER YOU SAY, I COULD CARE
LESS.
ELLEN IS MORE IMPORTANT.
I AM GOING.
>> Ellen: A MONTH AGO.
AND I'M GOING TO SAY HOW ARE YOU
FEELING?
>> I FEEL AMAZING.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK AMAZING!
[APPLAUSE]
SO YOU POSTED THIS REALLY, YOU
PUT THAT TOGETHER, YOU SING TO
HER AND THEN YOU PUT THAT
WHOLE -- WE JUST SHOWED YOU A
SMALL AMOUNT OF THE WHOLE
JOURNEY THAT SHE HAS GONE
THROUGH.
AND I ASSUME THAT YOU DID THIS
AS A LOVE STORY JUST TO SHOW HER
STRENGTH OF WHAT AN AMAZING
WOMAN --
>> HONESTLY, ELLEN, IT WAS NOT
EVEN THAT.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE HER SMILE.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE MY WIFE
SMILE.
SHE WAS IN THE WAITING ROOM FOR
SURGERY FOR A LOT LONGER THAN
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE.
SO I WAS NERVOUS DOWNSTAIRS AND
I WAS PACING AND I SAID I WANT
TO MAKE A VIDEO FOR MY WIFE THAT
IS GOING TO MAKE HER SMILE AFTER
HAVING HER HEAD CUT OPEN, AND
LOOK OF THIS MILLION DOLLAR
SMILE, HOW CAN YOU NOT?
[APPLAUSE]
LOOK AT HER.
>> Ellen: I DON'T KNOW WHO TO
SUGGEST RIGHT NOW, BUT ANY ONE
OF OUR SPONSORS OR ANY SPONSOR,
THIS SMILE IS A MILLION DOLLAR
SMILE.
SHE SHOULD BE REPRESENTING SOME
COMPANY, BECAUSE THAT IS A
MILLION DOLLAR SMILE RIGHT
THERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
>> Ellen: SO YOU ARE A NAVY
VETERAN, THIS IS THE SECOND
TIME.
SO SIX YEARS AGO?
>> YES, 2013 WAS MY FIRST
SURGERY AND FIRST BOUT WITH
BRAIN CANCER THAT WAS
STAGE 3 THE FIRST TIME.
IN THE TUMOR WAS THE SIZE OF AN
ORANGE.
>> Ellen: I DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT.
TO THE SIZE OF AN ORANGE, WHAT
WERE YOUR SYMPTOMS THAT IT GOT
TO THAT POINT?
>> MIGRAINES WAS THE MOST
PROMINENT, THE MOST THAT I HAD
GOTTEN.
I HAD BLURRED VISION, AND THEN
WHEN I WOULD SLEEP SOMETIMES I
WOULD LAY ON ONE SIDE OF MY HEAD
AND I COULD HEAR A SEASHELL
NOISE FROM THE FLUID SWIMMING
AROUND IN MY BRAIN NOT GOING THE
RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> Ellen: SO YOU SAY MAYBE I
SHOULD SEE A DOCTOR.
>> MAYBE I SHOULD GET THIS
CHECKED OUT, IT WAS MY DAD WHO
SAID, BECAUSE I WAS YOUNG AND MY
DAD WAS LIKE ARE YOU GOING TO GO
TO THE DOCTOR, AND HE WAS LIKE,
YOU SHOULD GO.
AND SO I WENT, AND THEY SAID
HAVE YOU HAD ANY SYMPTOMS.
AND THEY SAID LET'S DO AN MRI,
AND THEY SAID IT IS AN ORANGE ON
YOUR BRAIN.
>> Ellen: SO YOU GET RID OF
THAT AND THEN YOU ARE CLEAR
FOR --
>> SIX YEARS.
YEARLY SCANS BETWEEN JULY AND
OCTOBER I GOT SCANNED, AND SIX
YEARS I WAS PERFECTLY HEALTHY.
>> Ellen: NO SYMPTOMS AT ALL,
AND THEN YOU GO IN FOR A ROUTINE
CHECK AND THEY FIND --
HOW BIG WAS THIS ONE?
>> ABOUT THE SIZE OF A HALF A
DOLLAR IN THE SAME LOCATION THAT
I GOT THE FIRST ONE.
SO FROM OCTOBER 10TH TO A WEEK
BEFORE SURGERY, WE WERE IN THE
DOCTOR'S OFFICE THREE OR FOUR
TIMES A WEEK DOING MRIs AND
SCANS, BLOOD WORK.
>> YOU HAVE TO WEAR THE DEVICE
FOR THREE DAYS.
>> I HAD TO WEAR THIS WONDERFUL
HEADPIECE THAT HAD LIKE THIS
WONDERFUL LITTLE BAG THAT CAME
WITH IT.
THAT MONITORED ME ALL DAY,
MONITORED MY BRAIN WAVES AND
MONITORED ME WHILE I SLEPT TO
SEE IF I WAS HAVING ANY
IRREGULAR BRAIN ACTIVITY.
I WASN'T.
I ONLY HAD THE BRAIN TUMOR, AND
THAT WAS IT.
>> Ellen: THAT'S GONE NOW?
SPEAK OF THE BRAIN TUMOR IS
GONE, AND WE START TREATMENT IN
TWO WEEKS.
RADIATION AND THEN CHEMO AFTER
THAT.
>> Ellen: YOU WILL BEAT THIS,
YOU HAVE AN AMAZING ATTITUDE,
AND YOU HAVE TO.
WE WILL TAKE A BREAK, MORE AFTER
THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> YES!
THIS IS AGGRESSIVE!
>> Ellen: AND ALSO --
>> [SCREAMS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: CYPRUS IS RIGHT!
>> RUSSIA!
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MUSIC >> Ellen: WE ARE BACK
WITH ROSLYN AND RAY SINGLETON.
THAT'S WHAT THE MICROPHONE WAS
FOR, FOR YOU TO SING.
WE WERE TALKING DURING THE BREAK
AND I SAID WHAT AN INSPIRATION
YOU WILL BE FOR SO MANY PEOPLE
OUT THERE, BECAUSE IT IS ONE
THING TO GET DIAGNOSED ONCE AND
IT IS HARD ENOUGH, BUT TO BEAT
IT AND THEN COME BACK, AND YOU
ARE NOT SAD, YOU ARE JUST HAPPY,
TELL EVERYBODY WHY YOU HAVE THIS
ATTITUDE?
>> I HAVE THIS ATTITUDE BECAUSE
I FEEL PERSONALLY THAT GOD GIVES
BATTLES TO CERTAIN PEOPLE.
JUST TO LET OTHER PEOPLE KNOW
THAT IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LIE AND SAY
BRAIN CANCER IS A BREEZE.
IT'S NOT.
BUT POSITIVE PRAYER, POSITIVE
PEOPLE --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND IT MAKES IT BETTER.
ALSO, IF THEY WOULD TELL ME THAT
I HAD TO GO THROUGH BRAIN CANCER
TO SEE YOU.
I WOULD'VE SIGNED THE LINE.
LET'S DO IT.
HONESTLY IT IS A BLESSING,
BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY PEOPLE
THAT ARE GOING THROUGH CANCER,
BREAST CANCER, BRAIN CANCER, ANY
CANCER.
ANYTHING IN LIFE, AND IT WILL BE
OKAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
JUST KEEP GOING.
>> Ellen: EVEN IF IT IS NOT
THE EXACT OUTCOME --
THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE THAT
SOMEBODY WHO WANTS TO SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU.
YOU INSPIRE A LOT OF PEOPLE AND
I KNOW YOU ARE INSPIRED BY A LOT
OF PEOPLE, SO DWYANE WADE WAS
HERE ON THE SHOW THE OTHER DAY,
AND HE LEFT THIS MESSAGE FOR
YOU.
>> WHAT'S UP, RAY, WHAT'S UP,
ROSLYN?
THIS IS DWYANE WADE, MY WIFE IS
NOT WITH ME RIGHT NOW, BUT WE
ARE SENDING OUR LOVE TO YOUR
FAMILY, WE ARE SENDING OUR LOVE
TO BOTH OF YOU, KEEP GOING.
KEEP FIGHTING THE GOOD FIGHT.
KEEP BELIEVING, AND CONTINUE TO
KEEP INSPIRING.
I'M SURE THERE ARE SO MANY
PEOPLE AROUND YOU GUYS LET YOU
ALL ARE INSPIRING EVERY DAY.
SO I AM DEFINITELY INSPIRED BY
THE STORY THAT I HAVE HEARD FROM
BOTH YOU GUYS, AND I KNOW MY
FAMILY WILL BE AS WELL.
SO FROM THE WADE FAMILY, MUCH
LOVE.
AND PLEASE, PLEASE KEEP
BELIEVING!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE ANY
PLANS FOR VALENTINE'S DAY, BUT I
WANT TO SEND YOU ANYWHERE YOU
WANT TO GO ON ME, DINNER IS ON
ME, SO FIND A NICE SIZZLER
SOMEWHERE.
>> WE GO INTO THE SIZZLER!
SPEW AND ALSO OUR FRIENDS AT
HONEY NUT CHEERIOS BELIEVE THAT
DOING GOOD MAKES YOU FEEL GOOD,
AND AS A GIFT FOR YOU, THEY WANT
TO GIVE YOU FLOWERS,
CHOCOLATES --
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Ellen: AND ALSO $25,000!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> [SCREAMS]
[LAUGHS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: CHOCOLATES AND
MONEY!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
AND YOU WERE DANCING ON BARS?
>> I WAS, I DANCE ON A BAR.
>> Ellen: FIRST TIME?
[LAUGHTER]
WHICH COUNTRY IS SHAPED LIKE A
BOOT?
TOM HANKS OR TOM CRUISE, WHO
COLLECTS VINTAGE TYPEWRITERS?
>> NEXT "ELLEN," JOHN LEGEND.
PLUS GWYNETH PALTROW ON
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> Ellen: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SPEND A LOT OF MONEY ON
VALENTINE'S DAY, I DO.
I DO, BECAUSE I AM RICH AND
>>> LEON HARRIS WITH A QUICK
LOOK AT THE STOREASE WE'RE
WORKING THIS AFTER.
THE TOP CONSUMER COMPLAI.
AND SUSAN HOGAN WILL SHOW YOU
THE FOUR STEPS TO TAKE TO MAKE
SURE YOU DON'T END UP WI
>>> AND A MAJOR CHANGE O
>>> PLUS MILE HIGH MANNE
THE SEAT RECLINING DEBATE
SHAKING TH.
THIS AFTERNOON NEWS 4 AT 4:00 AT
THE TOP OF THE HOU
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to everything
from helpful reminders...
to presorted
prescription packs.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to free
prescription savings reviews...
home delivery...
and more.
No wonder CVS customers
are better...than most
at staying on
their prescriptions...
Which tends to
make you healthier.
And what could
be better than that?
Treat yourself well at CVS.
And what could
be better than that?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MUSICAL >> Ellen: YOU KNOW OUR
FIRST GUEST FROM HER HIT SHOW
"GILMORE GIRLS" AND "PARENTHOOD"
AND NOW STARRING IN A NEW SHOW
"ZOEY'S EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST"!
TAKE A LOOK ♪ ♪
♪ I CAN'T GET NO ♪
♪ SATISFACTION ♪
♪ BECAUSE I TRY ♪
♪ AND I TRY ♪
♪ I CAN'T GET NO ♪
♪  ♪
>> Ellen: PLEASE WELCOME MY
FRIEND LAUREN GRAHAM!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> Ellen: THANK YOU FOR
DANCING!
CHAIR HEY, WE HAVE TO PUT THE
MONITORS ON, OTHERWISE THEY
CAN'T SEE.
OH, THEY ARE ON.
I WANT THEM TO SEE, THEY ARE
OVER THERE.
>> HAVE THEY KISSED IN THE
BOOTH?
>> WE HAVE.
>> WHAT IS THE POINT OF THE
KISSING BOOTH IF THERE IS NO
KISSING?
>> Ellen: WE DID NOT HAVE TO
SPEND THAT KIND OF MONEY ON THE
WORDS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> NOW WE HAVE SOME ACTION.
>> YOU TOOK A LOT OF PICTURES,
GREAT.
>> Ellen: IT IS GOOD TO SEE
YOU.
I HAVE NOT SEEN YOU IN A WHILE.
THIS IS CRAZY.
YOU CAME TO SEE ME WHEN I WAS
GETTING READY TO SHOOT MY STAND
UP SPECIAL, I WAS PUTTING IT
TOGETHER AT A SMALL PLACE HERE,
AND THEN THAT'S WHEN IT CLICKED
IN THAT YOU HAD SEEN ME DO STAND
UP BEFORE?
>> YES.
FIRST OF ALL, YOUR SPECIAL WAS
FANTASTIC!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND IT WAS REALLY EXCITING TO BE
THERE FOR A PRACTICE SHOW OR
WHATEVER IT IS CALLED, AND AS
YOU ARE TELLING THE STORY ABOUT
YOUR BIT, THE PHONE CALL TO GOD,
WHICH BECAME HUGE, IT OCCURRED
TO ME THAT EVEN THOUGH I HAVE
BEEN ON THE SHOW 29 MILLION
TIMES, I FORGOT THAT I HAD HEARD
YOU DO THAT BIT WHEN I WAS A
COCKTAIL WAITRESS AT THE IMPROV
IN CHICAGO.
AND I THINK IT WAS JUST THAT
THAT PERSON AND THIS PERSON SEEM
LIKE VERY DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE IT WAS THE SAME
MEANING, BUT IT IS THE SAME
MEANING, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE BEEN ON THE
SHOW, I KNOW YOU, AND YOU
COMPLETELY FORGOT THAT YOU SAW
ME, AND OF COURSE I DID NOT KNOW
THAT YOU WERE A WAITRESS AT THE
IMPROV IN CHICAGO EITHER.
>> IT WAS COOL.
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW WHERE YOU'RE
GOING TO END UP.
>> Ellen: THAT'S THE POINT OF
LIFE.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
SO LET'S GET TO THE IMPORTANT
STUFF.
>>> OKAY.
>> Ellen: YOU GOT A PUPPY.
AND IT IS A RESCUE DOG.
>> YES.
>> Ellen: AND IT IS GOING TO
BE --
IS THIS A RECENT PICTURE?
>> YES.
>> Ellen: IT IS THAT SMALL?
>> IT IS A LIE, THAT PHOTO.
BECAUSE LOOK AT THOSE PAWS, SHE
IS GOING TO BE BIG.
WE THINK LAB SHEPHERD, AND THEN
THEY SAID AND ROTTWEILER.
AND I'M LIKE, SHE KEEPS GETTING
SMALLER, WOW.
SO SHE IS A BIG DOG.
AND I FELL IN LOVE WITH HER ON
THE INTERNET.
WHICH I HOPE IS THE CLOSEST I
HAVE TO COME TO INTERNET DATING.
BUT I REALLY DID, THERE WAS
SOMETHING IN HER EYES AND I
DROVE -- I WAS WORKING IN
VANCOUVER AND I DROVE TO
WASHINGTON STATE TO PICK HER UP
AND I WAS NOT INTENDING TO TAKE
HER HOME, BUT ONE LOOK AND I WAS
LIKE, YOU ARE COMING WITH ME AND
I PUT HER IN THE CAR, AND NOW
SHE IS MY DOG.
>> Ellen: YOU LIVE HERE IN
L.A.?
AND YOU ARE NEIGHBORS WITH DAX
SHEPARD AND KRISTIN, RIGHT?
>> YES.
IT IS AMAZING!
IT IS SO SPECIAL.
IT IS REALLY COOL, IT IS JUST SO
FUN.
OUR NEIGHBORHOOD IS FUN.
AND DOING "PARENTHOOD" WITH HIM
WAS FUN.
HE AND PETER GO ON HIKES
TOGETHER WHICH IS ADORABLE.
AND HE HAS TWO GIRLS, AND THEY
HAVE A REAL TOUGH GUY LOOKING
LIKE A JEEP KIND OF THING, A
JEEP FOR KIDS.
BUT THOSE.
BUT THEY DRIVE AROUND THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
BUT DAX IS USUALLY OUT DOING OWN
HANDYMAN WORK.
>> Ellen: THAT IS REAL?
>> IT IS REAL.
HE HAS LIKE A CUT OFF SHIRT AND
ALL OF HIS TATTOOS, AND HE IS
LIKE REALLY THAT GUY.
>> Ellen: OH, WOW.
>> [LAUGHS]
AND THEN ONE DAY, THIS IS HOW I
KNOW THAT WE WILL BE FRIENDS
UNTIL WE DIE, HE WAS COMING UP
THE STREET AND I WAS IN A CAR
AND I WAS DRIVING DOWN THE
STREET AND HE WAVED AT ME, AND I
WAS LIKE, THAT'S BRAD PITT!
FOR WHATEVER REASON I THOUGHT HE
WAS BRAD PITT.
AND HE ROLLED DOWN THE WINDOW, I
WAS LIKE I THOUGHT YOU WERE
BRAD PITT, HE WAS LIKE I LOVE
YOU FOREVER.
>> Ellen: HE IS A CUTE GUY AND
A FUNNY GUY.
AND HIS PODCAST IS FANTASTIC.
>> I HAVE BEEN ON IT.
>> Ellen: ME TOO.
REALLY?
>> YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
THAT'S REALLY NICE TO SEE YOU.
I GUESS I SHOULD BE GOING.
>> Ellen: OUT.
BEFORE YOU GO, YOU SHOULD TELL
US ABOUT THE NEW PROGRAM.
>> OH.
PROMOTING THINGS, I AM ON THE
SHOW, IT'S INCREDIBLE.
IT'S CALLED, YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS
CALLED.
IT IS SINGING AND DANCING, AND
THE LEAD AS MY FRIEND JANE LEAVY
WHO HAPPENS TO BE IN A CREDIBLE
TRIPLE, AND THE IDEA IS THAT SHE
HITS HER HEAD, BECAUSE THAT
HAPPENS TO PEOPLE AND WHEN SHE
WAKES UP SHE HEARS PEOPLE'S
THOUGHTS IN SONGS PAIRED I DID
NOT KNOW THAT I WAS SINGING
"SATISFACTION," BUT MY CHARACTER
IS UNSATISFIED.
IF SO SHE KNOWS THAT I AM
UNSATISFIED.
>> Ellen: THAT IS FANTASTIC.
THAT MUST BE A LOT OF WORK.
>> IT IS A LOT OF WORK.
I HAD NEVER RECORDED IN A BOOTH
BEFORE.
WE WORKED WITH THE CHOREOGRAPHER
OR MANDY MOORE, NOT THE ACTOR,
THE CHOREOGRAPHER.
AND SHE HAD ME DANCING ON BARS.
IT WAS REALLY, REALLY FUN.
>> Ellen: THEY KNOW ME
ANYMORE, BECAUSE SHE WAS ON "SO
YOU THINK YOU CAN DANCE."
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> Ellen: YOU WERE DANCING ON
BARS?
>> I DO DANCE ON A BAR.
>> Ellen: FIRST TIME?
[LAUGHTER]
>> I BELIEVE IT IS, ELLEN.
BUT THEN I JUMP INTO THE ARMS OF
A YOUNG MAN TOO.
THAT I HAD NEVER DONE BEFORE.
>> Ellen: THAT IS FUN.
>> YEAH.
>> Ellen: OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, LAUREN.
WE ARE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
>> OH!
>> Ellen: I CAN ONLY TALK FOR
SOME TIME.
IN MY REAL LIFE I AM LIKE THIS
TOO.
>> YOU ARE NEW TO THIS.
>> Ellen: WE WILL PLAY A GAME
AFTER THIS.
>> OKAY FINE.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WHAT THREE ITEMS
WOULD YOU TAKE ON A DESERTED
ISLAND?
>> NOTEBOOK, PEN, AND SOME
TEQUILA.
[DING]
♪
I love this part.
[alert sound]
What's that?
Oh. A threat's been detected—
A threat's been detected? Ok,
this is not a drill everyone!
Abby! Protect the children!
It's just a
WiFi network threat,
and we have Xfinity xFi.
Oh yeah, it automatically
blocks threats
on all your devices.
Either way, Abby.
That wasn't a good look.
If it's connected,
it's protected
with xFi Advanced Security.
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
And now get
Advanced Security free
when you get
the xFi Gateway.
Switch today.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to everything
from helpful reminders...
to presorted
prescription packs.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to free
prescription savings reviews...
home delivery...
and more.
No wonder CVS customers
are better...than most
at staying on
their prescriptions...
Which tends to
make you healthier.
And what could
be better than that?
Treat yourself well at CVS.
[police siren]
And what could
Michael, your a singer.
bubly is a sparkling water.
Sure is.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
I love the new myWW program,
because you get matched with
a plan tailored to you!
Whether you're a dine outer,
take outer, veggie person,
definitely-not-just-veggie
person,
bread lover, or cheese lover...
...all you have to do is answer
personal assessment questions
and get scientifically matched
with a proven weight loss plan.
Find out which new
customized plan
can make losing weight
easier for you!
The new program from WW.
Weight Watchers reimagined
Join for free and get
three months free!
Hurry, offer ends February 17th.
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN,"
JOHN LEGEND.
PLUS GWYNETH PALTROW ON
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> Ellen: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
SPEND A LOT OF MONEY ON
VALENTINE'S DAY.
I MEAN, I DO, BECAUSE I AM RICH
AND PORTIA KNOWS THAT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, WE ARE
BACK WITH LAUREN GRAHAM.
TIME TO PLAY ONE OF OUR FAVORITE
GAMES "BURNING QUESTIONS."
♪ ♪
YES, EXACTLY.
I WILL READ A QUESTION, YOU HAVE
TO ANSWER WITH THE FIRST THING
THAT COMES TO MIND AND THEN
[DING]
HIT THE BUTTON.
VALENTINE'S DAY IS TOMORROW,
WHAT IS THE MOST ROMANTIC THING
YOU HAVE DONE FOR SOMEONE?
>> I --
[DING]
>> Ellen: AFTER.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY.
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE A PROBLEM?
>> WHAT IS THE MOST ROMANTIC
THING YOU HAVE DONE FOR SOMEONE?
YOU DO LIKE SKY WRITERS.
>> Ellen: WHENEVER SHE GOES
OUT OF TOWN AND I AM NOT WITH
HER, I CALL THE HOTEL AND THEY
PUT A HUGE HEART SHAPED THING OF
ROSE PETALS ON HER BED SO THAT
WHEN SHE WALKS INTO THE ROOM THE
WHOLE THING IS COVERED WITH
HEART-SHAPED PETALS.
>> ELLEN, YOU ARE A
KABILLIIONARE.
YOU CAN DO THESE THINGS.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS THE SCARIEST
THING YOU HAVE EVER DONE?
[DING]
>> DANCE ON THE BAR.
>> Ellen: ANSWER.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE PLAYING.
>> IT'S WHAT MAKES ME THINK OF
JEOPARDY.
ANY HAVE TO DO IT RIGHT AWAY.
IT IS JUST LIKE JEOPARDY.
>> Ellen: IT IS NOT AT ALL.
WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE THING TO
DO ALONE?
>> READ.
[DING]
I GOT HIST FOR READING.
>> Ellen: NO, THEY DID NOT
HISS YOU.
THEY'RE JUST THEM SNAKES WE KEEP
OVER THERE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE BODY
PART ON THE OPPOSITE SEX?
>> BUTT.
[DING]
>> Ellen: THAT SOUNDS LIKE YOU
REALLY LIKE IT.
IF YOU ARE FLIPPING THROUGH THE
CHANNELS AND YOU SEE YOURSELF ON
TV, WILL YOU WATCH?
>> NEVER.
[DING]
>> Ellen: WHAT THREE ITEMS
WILL YOU TAKE WITH YOU ON A
DESERTED ISLAND?
>> NOTEBOOK, PEN, AND SOME
TEQUILA.
[DING]
>> Ellen: TEQUILA!
WHAT IS THE BEST THING THAT HAS
HAPPENED TO YOU THIS WEEK SO
FAR?
>> BEING HERE.
I HAVE MISSED YOU.
>> Ellen: I HAVE MISSED YOU
TOO.
[DING]
WHO WAS THE LAST CELEBRITY THAT
YOU GOT STARSTRUCK OVER?
>> I MET DANIEL CLERIC WIN CRAIG
BACKSTAGE AT THE GOLDEN GLOBES,
AND HE LAUGHED.
AND HE WAS LIKE LAUGHING.
HE WAS SO CUTE AND NICE.
>> Ellen: HE IS NICE AND CUTE.
[DING]
WHAT IS A FASHION TREND YOU
DON'T UNDERSTAND?
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND SO MUCH OF
GENES THAT ARE HAPPENING.
THEY ARE WIDE AND CROPPED AND
HIGHWAY STATED, THAT'S NOT
HELPFUL TO ANYBODY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I AGREE.
WIDE, CROPPED --
WHAT DO YOU LIKE MOST ABOUT?
>> I JUST WENT TO THE DOCTOR, I
AM 5'9".
MY DOCTOR SAID I AM 5'8", SO I
HAVE BEEN LYING MY WHOLE LIFE
ABOUT BEING 5'9", I JUST DID NOT
KNOW.
I'M REALLY MAD ABOUT IT.
5'9" IS SO MUCH COOLER.
ISN'T IT?
[DING]
[BELLRINGING]
>> Ellen: "ZOEY'S
EXTRAORDINARY PLAYLIST" AIRS
SUNDAYS AT 9:00 ON NBC!
WATCH IT!
SHE IS ON A BAR, AND SHE DANCES!
WE WILL BE BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> CYPHER'S.
>> Ellen: SITE FOR US IS
RIGHT.
I bet you've never seen a
sandwich do yoga before.
Ommmmmmmmmmmmm.
Introducing the new Papadias,
for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
Delicious Almond Breeze
almondmilk yogurt alternative.
Cut! Why did you eat that?
'Cause it tastes amazing.
Do you want to try it?
Delicious Almond Breeze
Almondmilk Yogurt Alternative.
Available now.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz.
The first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those
with moderate
to severe
psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement of
their psoriasis
plaques.
Some even
saw 100%
clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
This right here is the new
Papadia.
Which, if I'm not mistaken,
is Latin for "better than a
sandwich."
Heh-even has a better pickle...
Get a new Papadia for
six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MUSICAL >> Ellen: LAST MONTH I
MADE A 2-YEAR-OLD KID GENIUS,
REALLY, KID GENIUS.
HE WAS AMAZING.
HARRY PYLE IS HIS NAME.
IT WAS PREEMPTED IN A BUNCH OF
CITIES, AND I WANTED TO MAKE
SURE THAT EVERYBODY HAD A CHANCE
TO SEE IT.
HERE HE IS.
OUR NEXT GUEST MIGHT BE THE
YOUNGEST, NOT JUST MIGHT BE, THE
YOUNGEST KID EXPERT WE HAVE EVER
HAD ON THE SHOW, HE CAN IDENTIFY
EVERY SINGLE FLAG IN THE WORLD
AND IS TWO YEARS OLD.
FROM LIVERPOOL, ENGLAND, PLEASE
WELCOME HARRY PILE AND HIS
PARENTS SHELLIE AND STEVE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI!
>> HI!
WE WILL TALK ABOUT COUNTRIES AND
FLAGS!
>> Ellen: COUNTRIES AND FLAGS!
YOU CAME ALL THE WAY FROM
ENGLAND, YOU WERE ON THE PLANE,
HOW WAS IT?
DON'T LOOK YET.
WE HAVE TO WAIT.
HOW WAS THE PLANE RIDE?
>> THE PLANE RIDE WENT UP DOWN.
TO >> THE PLANE RIDE WENT UP AND
DOWN AND ROUND AND ROUND.
AND HE WOULD NOT BELIEVE IT!
>> Ellen: OH, WOW.
>> THAT'S FUNNY!
>> Ellen: GOING ROUND AND
ROUND, THAT IS A WEIRD PILOT.
>> IT IS FUN!
>> Ellen: TWO YEARS OLD, WHEN
DID YOU NOTICE THAT THERE WAS
SOMETHING GOING ON?
DID I READ THIS RIGHT?
HE WAS 12 MONTHS OLD AND COULD,
END OF THE ALPHABET?
>> YES, WHEN HE WAS FIRST BORN,
WE NOTICE THAT HIS EYES WERE
REALLY BIG AND WE JOKED THAT HE
LOOKED SHOCKED, SO FROM THEM I
WOULD SAY 12 MONTHS, HE STARTED
TO IDENTIFY THE ALPHABET, HE
COULD SPELL HIS NAME, HE COULD
READ HIS NAME.
18 MONTHS HE COULD IDENTIFY
SHAPES.
>> Ellen: HE JUST READ IT ON
THE BACK!
[LAUGHTER]
HE IS TWO YEARS OLD!
NORMALLY WE CAN PUT THEM ON THE
BACK FOR ME TO KNOW WHAT IT IS!
[LAUGHTER]
OKAY!
LET'S GO RIGHT TO IT.
SO WHAT IS THIS?
>> AUSTRALIA.
>> Ellen: THAT'S RIGHT!
>> MALAYSIA.
>> Ellen: MALAYSIA IS RIGHT!
>> THE UNITED KINGDOM.
>> Ellen: UNITED KINGDOM.
>> THAT IS CYPHRUS.
>> Ellen: CYPHRUS IS RIGHT.
>> RUSSIA!
>> Ellen: RUSSIA!
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT WAS SO MUCH
EXCITEMENT?
>> THAT'S INDONESIA.
>> Ellen: THAT IS INDONESIA.
>> ST. VINCENT AND THE
GRENADINES.
>> Ellen: ST. VINCENT AND THE
GOVERNMENT GRENADINES.
>>> CAMEROON.
>> Ellen: CAMEROON.
>> THE VATICAN CITY.
>> Ellen: THE VATICAN CITY.
>> AND THAILAND.
>> Ellen: AND THAILAND!
[APPLAUSE]
DO YOU KNOW THAT YOU ARE SUPER
SMART?
>> YEAH.
>> Ellen: YOU'RE SMART ENOUGH
TO KNOW THAT.
IT REALLY IS INCREDIBLE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
YOU HAVE TO KEEP CHALLENGING
HIM, RIGHT?
WHAT IS THE NEW THING?
>> LOGOS.
HE LOVES LOGOS, ABSOLUTELY LOVES
THEM.
SO I BOUGHT SOME A LOGO BOOK AND
ALL OF THE CORPORATIONS
GLOBALLY, AND ON PAGE 300, WE
GOT TO THE PLAYBOY LOGO.
>> THAT'S PLAYBOY!
[LAUGHTER]
>> SO I LOOKED AT IT, ELLEN, AND
I THOUGHT TO MYSELF, HE SAID
DADDY, WHAT IS THIS?
I WAS LIKE CAN I SKIP THE PAGE?
YOU CAN'T DO THAT WITH HARRY.
SO I SAID IT IS THE PLAYBOY
LOGO.
HE SAID I LOVE PLAYBOY!
HE SAYS TO EVERYBODY THAT HE
LOVES PLAYBOY.
>> AMAZON!
>> AMAZON AS WELL.
>> NETFLIX.
>> Ellen: NETFLIX?
YES.
THERE IS NETFLIX!
>> I LOVE NETFLIX!
>> Ellen: WHAT IS THIS ONE?
>> WARNER BROS.!
THAT ONE IS PORSCHE.
>> Ellen: THAT IS NICE.
YOU WANT TO REMEMBER.
>> PIXAR!
>> DISNEYLAND PARIS >> Ellen:
THE REASON I AM SHOWING THIS IS
BECAUSE WE WILL SEND YOU AND
YOUR FAMILY TO DISNEYLAND
TOMORROW!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HARRY LOOK.
THANK YOU, ELLEN.
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY?
>> THANKS.
>> Ellen: YOU WILL LEARN ALL
OF THE CHARACTERS AND
EVERYTHING.
I CANNOT WAIT.
COME BACK ANYTIME!
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> WHAT IS IN THE ENVELOPE?
>> NOTHING, IT IS JUST A PROP.
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Welcome to our
Lipton tea factory.
Where these sun-soaked
tea leaves
are picked at the peak
of freshness.
For a naturally smooth taste.
And drinking Lipton
every day
can help support a
healthy heart!
Free free free
free free free free.
Free freefree
free freefree.
Free free, free free.
That's right,
TurboTax Free is free.
Free, free free free.
Free.
This is Hal.
Free, free free free.
This is Hal's heart.
It's been broken.
And put back together.
This is also Hal's heart.
And his relief,
knowing he's covered
by Blue Cross Blue Shield.
This is Hal's heart.
And it's beating
better than ever.
This is what Medicare
from Blue Cross Blue Shield
does for Hal.
And with easy access
to quality healthcare,
Imagine what
we can do for you.
This is the Benefit of Blue.
♪ ♪ ♪
Start Maxximizing Today
in store and online.
So, you bought those "good
enough" paper towels?
[daughter laughs]
Not such a bargain.
There's Only One Quicker Picker
Upper.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
I'm a Big Kid Now
I'm a Big Kid now
Went from baby bottles to
drinking from sippy cups.
Went from wearing diapers,
to rocking these fresh Pull-Ups.
We're 50 million strong.
So, put on your Pull-Ups and
help us sing this song.
New size fits smaller trainers.
To be their best kids
need good nutrition,
and practice.
Lots of practice.
Get them started right
with Carnation
Breakfast Essentials.
Now with probiotics
and key nutrients
for digestive and
immune support
to help kids be their best.
Carnation Breakfast Essentials.
CONNECTION WITH BREAKING NEXT AT
4:00 A LOCAL TEEN ARRESTED IN
CONNECTION WITH --
>> WE'RE TRACKING THE RAIN
MAKING ITS WAY OUT OF HERE BUT
THE COLD AIR IS MOVING IN.
I'LL SHOW YOU JUST HOW COLD
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: LET US PLAY THE
FASTEST GAME ON TV
"SPLIT-SECOND."
♪ ♪
LAUREN HOFF'S FIELD, WHERE ARE
YOU?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI!
ALL RIGHT, EACH OF THOSE BUTTONS
ARE FOR YOUR HANDS.
YOU WILL CHOOSE YOUR LEFT HAND
OR YOUR RIGHT HAND DEPENDING ON
YOUR ANSWER.
HERE'S HOW WE PLAY.
WE WILL PUT 60 SECONDS ON THE
CLOCK.
WE WILL SHOW YOU JENNIFER
ANISTON, REESE WITHERSPOON, I
WILL SAY SOMETHING LIKE WHICH
ONE WAS THE FIRST GUEST ON MY
TALK SHOW?
IT WAS JENNIFER ANISTON, YOU ARE
CORRECT.
YOU HIT THE BUTTON AND WE WILL
MOVE ON.
IF YOU GET FIVE CORRECT IN A
ROW, YOU WIN $10,000, DOESN'T
THAT SOUND FUN?
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
GET YOUR HANDS READY.
KIM OR KHLOE, WHICH KARDASHIAN
IS TALLER?
IT IS KHLOE, NIKE OR ADIDAS,
WHICH SLOGAN IS JUST DO IT?
CORRECCORRECT.
ITALY OR CANADA, WHICH IS SHAPED
LIKE A BOOT?
TOM HANKS OR TOM CRUISE, WHO
COLLECTS VINTAGE TYPEWRITERS?
CORRECT.
WHOSE RASH DO I MENTION ON THE
SHOW?
[BELLRINGING]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT IS $10,000!
CONGRATULATIONS.
I
>>> BREAKING NOW AT 4:00 A LOCAL
TEEN ARRESTED IN THE MURDER OF A
YOUNG VIRGINIA COUPLE.
WE'RE LIVE WITH LATE WORD FROM
INVESTIGATORS.
>> A SPIKE IN CASES OF THE
CORONAVIRUS.
WHAT DOCTORS SAY IS LIKELY
BEHIND THE JUMP.
>> AND WINTER MAKING A COMEBACK.
SOME OF THE COLDEST AIR THIS
SEASON IS MOVING IN.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT IT MEANS FOR
THE WEEKEND.
>> PLUS, MILE HIGH MANNERS.
ONE FLYER RECLINES AND THE MAN
BEHIND HER GETS TO SEAT
SMASHING.
WHO'S RIGHT WHO'S WRONG?
WE DIVE INTO THE NATIONWIDE
DEBATE.
>>> HELLO AND GOOD AFTERNOON,
EVERYONE.
WE WELCOME YOU TO NEWS4.
WE GOT A LOT TO GET TO THIS
AFTERNOON.
FIRST LET'S START UP WITH THE
FORECAST.
>> STORM TEAM 4 IS MONITORING
BIG CHANGES MOVING IN RIGHT NOW.
WHEN YOU LEFT THIS MORNING YOU
PROBABLY HAD YOUR UMBRELLA BUT
TOMORROW MORNING YOU'LL NEED THE
WINTER COAT.
>> CHIEF METEOROLOGIST DOUG
KAMMERER SAYS WE ARE IN FOR SOME
OF THE COLDEST WEATHER OF THE
SEASON.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WIND
CHILLS IN THE TEENS AND 20s
TOMORROW INTO THE DAY ON
SATURDAY AS WELL.
RIGHT NOW TRACKING THE RAIN.
STILL A LOT OF CLOUDS ACROSS THE
AREA.
WE'RE SEEING THOSE CLOUDS MOVING
ON OUT AND AND THE RAIN AS WELL.
THE ONLY AREA OF RAIN IS DOWN TO
OUR SOUTH INTO SOUTHERN
MARYLAND.
THAT'S ABOUT IT HERE.
AGAIN, MOST OF US ON THE DRY
SIDE RIGHT NOW AND THAT IS THE
WAY IT IS GOING TO BE RIGHT
THROUGH THE REST OF THE NIGHT
TONIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE THE WIDER PICTURE
SHOWING MOST OF THE RAIN MOVING
ON OUT OF HERE AND BEHIND IT
SOME COLD AIR.
OKAY?
HOW COLD?
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT THE WIND
CHILL.
RIGHT NOW 56 DEGREES