♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ I USED TO WANT TO GROW UP ♪
♪ I THOUGHT THAT I ♪
♪ COULD BE FREE ♪
>> Ellen: THANKS, EVERYBODY.
HAPPY TUESDAY.
HAVE A SEAT.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
THIS LAST AUDIENCE WE HAD.
NOT Y'ALL.
YOU SEEM LIKE LOVELY PEOPLE, THE
KIND OF PEOPLE I CAN SHARE GOOD
NEWS WITH.
LISTEN.
I HAVE SOME REALLY GOOD NEWS AND
REALLY GOOD NEWS, DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW WHAT IT IS?
>> YES!
>> Ellen: I'M NOT GOOD AT
KEEPING SECRETS.
WHEN I HAVE GOOD NEWS, I WANT TO
TELL PEOPLE.
BUT I'M TRYING TO DRAG IT OUT.
YOU RIGHT THERE.
I WANT YOU TO GUESS.
STAND UP AND GUESS WHAT IT IS.
>> ARE YOU COMING OUT AS
STRAIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: NO.
NO.
>> I KNOW.
>> Ellen: KEEP GUESSING.
>> ARE YOU MAKING A SEQUEL TO
YOUR CLASSIC.
>> Ellen: NO, THAT'S A GOOD
IDEA.
ISN'T IT ANNOYING WHEN PEOPLE
SAY YES.
I SHOULD JUST TELL YOU BECAUSE
I'M EXCITED ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE AS
EXCITED AS I AM.
I'M REALLY EXCITED.
OKAY.
>> [CHEERING]
>> Ellen: I JUST FOUND OUT
THAT MY "GAME OF GAMES" IS
COMING BACK FOR A FOURTH SEASON.
YES.
I'M SO EXCITED.
I LOVE THIS SHOW SO MUCH IT
MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
IT IS GAMES.
I LOVE GAMES.
COMBINES ALL MY FAVORITE THINGS.
PRIZES, SURPRISES.
THREE SEASONS WE'VE HAD SO MUCH
FUN.
HERE'S SOME OF THE FUN WE'VE HAD
IN THE PAST THREE SEASONS.
WELCOME TO MY "GAME OF GAMES."
IT'S A GAME SHOW THAT WENT ON
SPRING BREAK AND DRINK TOO MUCH
TEQUILA.
ALL THE GAMES ARE HERE, TESTED
AND READY TO GO.
AT LEAST THEY ARE READY TO GO.
OH, THAT'S A SHAME.
EAT.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: O.
>> WHAT IS IT?
TELL ME.
>> IT'S MY FAVORITE ICE CREAM.
>> VANILLA ICE CREAM.
>> NO.
MY MOM MAKES IT EVERY DAY.
WITH >> Ellen: WE NEED TO TALK
TO YOUR MOM.
WAYS TO SAY HELLO IN A DIFFERENT
LANGUAGE.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> Ellen: I AM FORCED TO PUSH
THIS RIGHT HERE.
TERRIBLE.
SORRY.
>> CRANBERRY!
>> Ellen: $100,000!
>> ELLEN, I LOVE YOU.
>> Ellen: I LOVE YOU TOO.
SHE'S GONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE SHE WENT.
I LOVE KNOCKING PEOPLE DOWN.
IN A LOVING WAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THERE'S A BRAND-NEW EPISODE
TONIGHT AT 8:00 ON NBC.
DID YOU KNOW THAT YOU CAN EVEN
PLAY ALONG LIVE WITH THE SHOW
USING THE "GAME OF GAMES" MAP.
WHEN YOU ARE WATCHING THE SHOW,
LOOK FOR THE PENNY ON YOUR TV
SCREEN AND SCAN IT ON YOUR
PHONE'S CAMERA AND USE IT ON THE
FREE SCRATCHER ON YOUR APPLE.
THE FIRST WINNER WAS KYLE.
HE WON $10,000 JUST FOR WATCHING
TV.
I KNOW.
GOOD FOR KYLE.
LOOK HOW TINY HE IS.
WEIRD.
TONIGHT WE ARE NOT GIVING AWAY
ONE $10,000 CHECK.
WE ARE GIVING AWAY TWO.
NO, I WANT TO GIVE AWAY THREE.
NO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M DOING THIS
BUT TONIGHT IN HONOR OF
SEASON 4, WE ARE GOING TO GIVE
FOUR PEOPLE $10,000 CHECKS.
$40,000.
RIGHT NOW I WANT TO PLAY A GAME
AND IT'S HARD TO PICK WHICH ONE
BECAUSE I LOVE THEM ALL EQUALLY.
IT'S LIKE ASKING MY FAVORITE
CHILD, WHICH IS KAREN.
I'M KIDDING.
IF I HAD A DAUGHTER, I WOULD
NAME HER ELLEN JR..
LET'S PLAY DANGER WORD.
IF YOU SEE YOUR NAME ON THE
SCREEN, COME ON DOWN.
HELLO!
HI.
>> HI.
>> Ellen: HELLO.
HI.
STAND RIGHT HERE.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> I AM JOY.
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU DO AND
WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> I WORK AT DISNEYLAND AND I
LIVE IN ORANGE COUNTY.
I AM EMILY.
I LIVE IN ANAHEIM.
I AM A TEACHER.
>> Ellen: AND YOU ARE FRIENDS?
>> I AM LISA.
I AM FROM GILBERT, ARIZONA AND
I'M HER MOTHER.
I AM SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> Ellen: EXCITED TO HAVE YOU
PAID >> I AM LAUREN.
I AM HER DAUGHTER.
I AM FROM GILBERT, ARIZONA AS
WELL.
>> Ellen: MOTHER AND DAUGHTER,
YOU AGREE.
YOU VERIFY IT.
YOU ARE GOING BE PLAYING.
WHO LIKES TO GET THE MESSIEST?
SHE VOLUNTEERED YOU.
WHO IS BETTER AT GIVING CLUES?
EMILY, YOU HAVE NO CHOICE.
YOU ARE GETTING MESSY.
SIT DOWN ON THE STOOL.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE PLAYING FOR
THE SIDE OF THE AUDIENCE THAT
YOU'RE SITTING ON SO YOU'RE
PLAYING FOR A REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY GOOD PRICE.
I CAN'T SAY WHAT IT IS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S PUT THE
AUDIENCE IN HALF.
ALL RIGHT.
>> [CHEERING]
>> Ellen: EVEN IF YOU CAME
TOGETHER, ONLY ONE SIDE IS GOING
TO GET THE PRIZE.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE NOT AS
FRIENDLY.
OKAY.
JOY AND EMILY, YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR THIS SIDE OF THE AUDIENCE.
THAT SIDE OF THE AUDIENCE.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE IS HOW WE PLAY.
YOU WILL SEE TWO WORDS, WINNING
WORD IN A DANGER WORD.
YOU HAVE TO GET YOUR PARTNER TO
SAVE THE WINNING WORD WITHOUT
SAYING THE DANGER WORD.
YOU CAN ONLY USE ONE WORD CLUES
AND IF YOU SEE THE DANGER WORD,
I'LL BE FORCED TO PUSH THIS
BUTTON AND YOU'LL BE SORRY.
OKAY.
LAUREN, YOU ARE GOING TO GO
FIRST.
YOU WANT HER TO SAY THE WINNING
WORD WITHOUT THE DANGER WORD.
ALL RIGHT.
>> EGGOS.
SYRUP.
>> BREAKFAST.
>> BURRITO.
MAKER.
>> TOASTER.
>> YOU'VE GOT THIS, EMILY.
COME ON.
YOU'VE GOT THIS.
>> BUTTER.
>> PANCAKE.
NO, NO, NO.
OH!
>> I'M SORRY, EMILY.
>> I CAN'T SEE.
>> Ellen: THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE
THE GOGGLES ON.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
TRY TO REMEMBER.
FOLLOW UP WITH THE NEXT ONE
BECAUSE THEN SHE SENT BREAKFAST
AFTER SHE SAID -- THAT WOULD
HAVE BEEN...
ALL RIGHT.
NOW WE GO TO JOY.
>> ME.
>> OUGHT.
>> LEAVES.
>> SEASON.
>> FALL.
>> EMILY!
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
I AM ASSUMING THAT YOU HAVE A
NIECE NAMED AUTUMN?
>> I DO.
>> Ellen: SHE SAID NIECE AND
POINTED TO HERSELF.
AND THEN SHE SAID SEASON.
YOU HAVE NO ONE TO BLAME BUT
YOURSELF.
LISTEN.
>> CLOSE YOUR MOUTH.
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE TO BE VERY,
VERY CAREFUL EMILY BECAUSE Y'ALL
HAVE --
THEY HAVE NO STRIKES.
ONE MORE STRIKE AND YOU'RE OUT.
THE OTHER SIDE WINS THE PRIZE.
ALL RIGHT.
STAND ON THIS.
ALL RIGHT, BE CAREFUL.
>> BALLET.
>> SHOE.
>> DRESS.
>> TUTU.
[LAUGHTER]
>> RIP.
>> DANCE.
>> LEGGING.
>> TIGHTS.
>> [SCREAMING]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M GOING TO GIVE Y'ALL A HEAD
START TO THE PARKING GARAGE.
ONCE THESE PEOPLE HEAR WHAT THEY
DID NOT WIN.
THIS SIDE OF THE AUDIENCE IS
COMING BACK FOR 12 DAYS OF
GIVEAWAYS.
>> [CHEERING]
>> Ellen: THEY ARE SO MAD AT
YOU.
WELL, WE HAD FUN.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL.
WE HAD FUN.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS WE
HAD FUN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.
Y'ALL ARE COMING BACK TOO!
>> ♪ THE MOST WONDERFUL TIME OF
THE YEAR ♪
♪ IT'S THE MOST WONDERFUL TIME
OF THE YEAR ♪
♪ >> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DID I LOOK LIKE BEFORE?
>> Ellen: REALLY BAD.
>> I WANTED THEM TO HAVE THAT
SAME JOY AND FEEL THAT SAME JOY.
>> Announcer: FRIDAY,
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE MAY
MAYOR PETE.
>> Ellen: SOME PEOPLE HAVE HAD
A HARD TIME PRONOUNCING HIS
NAME.
THAT CORRECT PRONUNCIATION IS
PETE.
>> Announcer: THAT SMILE COULD
SELL US ON MOST ANYTHING.
>> YOU DON'T GET A BODY LIKE
THIS WITHOUT HAVING ONE OF
THOSE.
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE NEVER HAD
ONE FALL OFF?
>> I HAVE ONE RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: CHRIS PRATT.
>> WHAT KIND OF BLACK MAGIC
My name is
Beatrice Dixon.
I'm the founder of
The Honey Pot.
In the beginning
it wasn't easy to,
like, start this company.
And there was a lot of times
that it almost didn't happen.
If Target didn't take
the chance on us,
we wouldn't be in all the
retailers that we're in today.
But what's really dope,
is they helped us
with the product line,
the packaging...
They really, like,
changed my life.
The reason why
it's so important
for Honey Pot to do well
is so the next black girl
that comes up
with a great idea,
she could have a
better opportunity...
That means a lot to me.
Ugh, another delay...
but...you keep bouncing
like I'm a bouncy castle!
Oh yeah!!
5 Stops, 0 Leaks.
We're crushing this commute!
Huggies Little Movers.
Our best fitting diaper
that Fits Like a Hugg.
HUGG ON
Thousands of women with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of the body,
are living in the moment
and taking IBRANCE.
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor
is for postmenopausal women
or for men with HR+/HER2-
metastatic breast cancer,
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole
significantly delayed
disease progression
versus letrozole,
and shrank tumors in
over half of patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop low
white blood cell counts
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
IBRANCE may cause severe
inflammation of the lungs
that can lead to death.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have new
or worsening symptoms,
including trouble breathing,
shortness of breath,
cough, or chest pain.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if
you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness, nausea,
sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Be in your moment.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: IT WAS FUN AND IT
WAS SAD AND THEN IT WAS FUN.
OUR FIRST GUEST IS A HOLLYWOOD
LEGEND WHOSE MOVIES HAVE MADE
OVER $5 BILLION.
HIS LATEST IS "CALL OF THE
WILD."
TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY SON WAS ALWAYS READING
ADVENTURE STORIES.
HE WAS CRAZY ABOUT THE NEWS
COMING OUT OF THE YUKON.
IT WASN'T THE COLD.
IT WAS THE MOUNTAINS.
HE SPENT ALL DAY LOOKING AT MAPS
AND PICTURES OF THE MOUNTAINS,
DREAMING ABOUT WHAT WAS ON THE
OTHER SIDE, PLACES NO ONE HAD
BEEN.
WILD PLACES.
WE COULD GO.
YOU AND ME.
>> Ellen: PLEASE WELCOME
HARRISON FORD.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI, MY FRIEND.
DID YOU ENJOY THAT GAME WE JUST
PLAYED?
>> NO.
>> Ellen: KNOW?
>> I MEAN...
THAT'S A GAME?
>> Ellen: IT'S A FUN GAME.
YOU HAVE ONE WORD CLUES.
IT'S CHALLENGING.
DO YOU LIKE GAMES.
DO YOU LIKE TO PLAY GAMES?
>> NO.
>> Ellen: WELL, THEN.
NO GAMES AT ALL?
>> YOU KNOW, I'M SORT OF FAD AT
GAMES.
>> Ellen: KNOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT.
YOU'RE A SMART MAN.
>> BUT I'M BAD AT GAMES.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE SMART ENOUGH
TO KNOW THAT.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
YOU LOOK REALLY GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DID I LOOK LIKE BEFORE?
>> Ellen: REALLY BAD.
REALLY BAD.
THE DIFFERENCE IS AMAZING.
>> I FELT MUCH BETTER.
>> Ellen: THERE'S A PICTURE OF
YOU ON A BIKE.
LOOK AT YOUR ARMS.
LOOK AT THESE ARMS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING THERE?
DO YOU WORK OUT LIKE CRAZY?
JUST TRUST ME.
THEY ARE GOOD.
>> NO, I DON'T WORK OUT LIKE
CRAZY.
I WORK OUT A BIT.
I RIDE BIKES AND I PLAY TENNIS.
>> Ellen: WILL THAT IS AN
ELECTRIC BIKE.
YES, IT IS.
>> I DON'T HAVE AN ELECTRIC
BIKE.
I SEE PEOPLE WITH ELECTRIC BIKES
AND I GO THAT'S AN ELECTRIC
BIKE.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> Ellen: WHAT'S THE GIANT
PACK ON THE FRONT?
>> IT'S NOT AN ELECTRIC BIKE.
I DON'T HAVE AN ELECTRIC BIKE.
>> Ellen: IT'S NOT?
>> IT'S NOT AN ELECTRIC BIKE.
>> Ellen: PEOPLE WERE ANGRY.
>> WAS THIS A GAME?
>> Ellen: I THOUGHT FOR SURE
IT WAS AN ELECTRIC BIKE BECAUSE
IT LOOKED LIKE IT WITH THAT BIG
THING ON THERE.
ALL RIGHT, I BELIEVE YOU.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
LIE.
>> THOSE AREN'T MY ARMS EITHER.
>> Ellen: THEY ARE YOUR ARMS
AND THEY LOOKED GOOD.
YOU CHANGE YOUR DIET OR
SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
>> PRACTICALLY NOTHING.
I EAT VEGETABLES AND FISH.
>> Ellen: THAT'S GOOD.
VERY HEALTHY FOR YOU.
>> NO DAIRY.
WHAT'S THE OTHER THING?
>> Ellen: MEAT?
>> NO DAIRY.
THERE'S ONE OTHER THING.
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Ellen: EVERYONE IS JUST
GUESSING.
>> IT'S REALLY BORING.
>> Ellen: THE FACT YOU CAN
STICK TO IT IS PRETTY IMPRESSIVE
BECAUSE IT'S HARD TO EAT REALLY,
REALLY CLEAN.
>> IT'S GOOD.
>> Ellen: DID YOU DO IT FOR
SOME KIND OF REASON ARE YOU JUST
DECIDED IT'S PROBABLY BETTER FOR
ME?
>> I JUST DECIDED I WAS TIRED OF
EATING MEAT.
I KNOW IT'S NOT REALLY GOOD FOR
THE PLANET.
>> Ellen: NO, IT'S NOT GOOD
FOR THE PLANET.
>> AND IT'S NOT REALLY GOOD FOR
ME.
>> Ellen: NO, IT'S GOOD TO NOT
EAT MEAT, I FIND.
SPEAKING OF THE ENVIRONMENT, YOU
WENT AND SPOKE AT THE U.N. IN
FRONT OF THE WHOLE BUNCH OF
PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT THE
ENVIRONMENT.
GOOD FOR YOU FOR DOING THAT.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING ALL OF US.
[APPLAUSE]
DO YOU GET NERVOUS OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT?
>> UM, NOT UNTIL I GET THERE.
I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH SENSE TO BE.
BUT I WAS IN THIS ROOM AND I WAS
ON A DAIS, WHAT THEY CALL IT, A
DAIS.
EVERYBODY ELSE WAS A HEAD OF
STATE AND I THOUGHT MAN.
THEY MADE A BIG MISTAKE HERE.
BUT THEN THEY LET ME TALK ABOUT
WHAT I WANTED TO TALK ABOUT.
WHICH WAS THE ENVIRONMENT.
>> Ellen: GOOD FOR YOU.
GOOD FOR YOU FOR DOING THAT.
I THINK IT'S VERY COOL.
SPEAK WE'VE ALL GOT TO DO THAT.
IF YOU START TALKING ABOUT IT
AND WE HAVE TO START DOING IT WE
HAVE TO INSIST THAT OUR ELECTED
OFFICIALS DO IT.
>> Ellen: YES, WE DO.
YES, WE DO.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE BACK WITH
HARRISON AFTER THIS.
>> WHAT PART OF YOUR BODY ARE
YOU THE PROUDEST OF?
>> OH, BUTT IMPLANTS.
>> Ellen: DO YOU WANT TO TELL
ME WHY YOU LIKE THIS MAN SO
MUCH?
>> GO DOWN
>>> THE ANSWER TO ALZHEIMER'S
DISEASE, A NICOTINE PATCH.
>> MY MOTHER HAD SENILE
DEMENTIA.
D AN INTEREST.
>> TELLS TELL US HOW THIS
EXPERIMENT TREATMENT CAN SLOW
DOWN MAYBE EVEN PREVENT MEMORY
LOSS.
NEXT
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
HARRISON FORD.
WE BUMPED IN BEFORE THE CLIP,
"CALL OF THE WILD."
IT'S ADAPTED FROM A VERY
WELL-KNOWN BOOK.
TELL EVERYBODY WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
>> IT'S ABOUT THAT FACT.
WE MADE IT INTO A BIGGER MOVIE.
IT'S A BOOK THAT'S BEEN AROUND
FOR 100 YEARS.
IT'S NEVER BEEN OUT OF
CIRCULATION.
IT'S A WIDELY READ BOOK.
WE HAVE DONE A MOVIE THAT'S
BASED ON IT.
IT'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
ONE OF THE INTERESTING THINGS --
OH, I SHOULD.
I WILL FILL IN.
IT'S ABOUT A DOG NAMED BUCK WHO
GOES ON AN ADVENTURE.
THE ADVENTURE IS THAT HE'S BEEN
TAKEN FROM HIS COMFORTABLE
CALIFORNIA HOME TO THE CANADIAN
YUKON TO BE IMPRESSED INTO A DOG
DOG'S LEAD TEAM TO WORK AND HE
GOES THROUGH SEVERAL OWNERS
UNTIL HE MEETS THE CHARACTER I
PLAYED.
WE BRING SOME VALUE TO EACH
OTHER.
>> Ellen: THE DOG IN THE
MOVIE, THERE IS NO DOG.
[LAUGHTER]
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU THINK THERE
IS A DOG IN THE MOVIE.
>> I SAW THE MOVIE.
THERE IS A DOG.
>> Ellen: I KNOW YOU THINK YOU
SAW A DOG FOR THERE IS NO DOG.
THERE IS A MAN DRESSED AS A DOG
WHEN YOU'RE DOING SCENES?
>> NOT DRESSED AS A DOG.
DRESSED AS A MAN WITH BALLS ON
HIM.
LITTLE WHITE BALLS.
[LAUGHTER]
AND HE'S A STAND-IN FOR THE DOG.
SO THAT WE KNOW WHERE TO LOOK
BECAUSE THERE'S NOT A DOG THERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE SOME PLACE TO
LOOK.
THE GUY WAS GREAT.
HE'S AN ACTOR, FORMER
CIRQUE DU SOLEIL GYMNAST AND HE
WAS REALLY GREAT.
>> Ellen: DID YOU HAVE TO PET
HIM?
>> WHAT YOU MEAN "HAVE TO?"
I ENJOYED PETTING HIM AND
RUBBING HIM BEHIND THE YEARS.
AND ROLLING AROUND ON THE FLOOR,
SCRATCHING HIS TUMMY.
HE LOVED IT.
>> Ellen: I BET HE DID.
>> IT WAS WEIRD FOR A WHILE
BUT...
BUT YOU GET USED TO THINGS.
>> Ellen: I WOULD LOVE TO SEE
THOSE PICTURES OF YOU RUBBING
THAT MAN'S BELLY WITH THE BALLS
ON HIM.
CAN YOU DENY, VERIFY OR
WHATEVER, "INDIANA JONES."
THEY ARE SAYING --
>> I CAN DENY.
THAT IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
>> Ellen: YOU CAN DENY THAT
IT'S NOT HAPPENING?
SO IT IS HAPPENING?
[APPLAUSE]
WHEN IS IT HAPPENING?
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU.
>> Ellen: YES, YOU CAN PRAY >>
I DON'T KNOW.
WE HOPE TO START SOON.
THIS SUMMER.
>> Ellen: THAT'S FANTASTIC.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT.
THAT'S AMAZING.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE FUN.
>> Ellen: ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> I AM EXCITED.
>> Ellen: IT'S GOING TO BE
FANTASTIC.
>> THEY ARE GREAT FUN TO MAKE.
>> Ellen: IN THE MEANTIME,
"CALL OF THE WILD" A MAN WITH
BALLS ON IT THAT LOOKS LIKE A
DOG IS IN THEATERS FRIDAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> WHAT PART OF YOUR BODY ARE
YOU THE PROUDEST OF?
>> OH.
BUTT IMPLANTS.
>> I KNOW HOW I FEEL WHEN I GET
A HAIRCUT.
I WANTED THEM TO HAVE THAT SAME
JOY AND FEEL THAT SAME JOY.
>> Announcer: THAT SMILE COULD
SELL ALMOST ANYTHING.
>> Ellen: I HEARD YOU WORK OUT
WITH HIM.
>> YOU DON'T GET A BODY LIKE
THESE WITHOUT
>>> I'M PAT LAWSON MUSE WITH A
LOOK AT THE STORIES WE ARE
WORKING THIS AFTERNOON.
NEW FEARS OF CORONAVIRUS
SPREADING.
AN AMERICAN WOMAN WHO
DISEMBARKED E CRUISE SHIP IN
CAMBODIA HAS NOW TESTED
POSITIVE. 4:00 T THREAT TO
OTHER TRAVELLERS AND THE NEW
ECONOM FALLOU COULD YOU A NICOT
HELP PEOPLE SUFFERING FROM
MEMORY LOSS.
>>> AND ELLEN'S BIG SURPRISE FOR
A LOCAL TEACHER.
WE
Man: Every student
is full of possibilities.
Just like every community.
Which is why the 2020 Census
wants to make sure
we are all counted.
Because an accurate
census count
can help inform funding
for things like
after-school programs
and education for
the next ten years.
Let's stand together.
Let's make it possible.
Shape your future. Start here.
Learn more at 2020census.gov.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: MY FRIEND JEN
ANISTON HOSTED THE SHOW A FEW
WEEKS AGO AND BECAUSE OF THE
IMPEACHMENT TRIAL NOT EVERYBODY
GOT TO SEE IT SO WE WANTED TO
SHOW A LITTLE BIT OF IT.
THIS IS JEN AND WILL FERRELL.
PLAYING "BURNING QUESTIONS."
>> I AM GOING TO READ A QUESTION
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO ANSWER THE
FIRST THING THE THAT COMES TO
YOUR MIND AND THEN YOU'RE GOING
TO HIT THE BUZZER AFTER YOU
ANSWER.
OKAY?
READY?
>> SURE.
>> HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO, GUYS.
I FEEL SEXY WHEN...
>> I HAVE PUT ON MY REFEREE
OUTFIT.
>> WHAT PART OF YOUR BODY ARE
YOU THE PROUDEST OF?
>> OH, BUTT IMPLANTS.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT WAS EASY.
>> I WON'T SAY IT.
NEXT.
FINISH THE SENTENCE.
I WISH I WERE MORE...
>> MORE BETTER AT PERFORMING
MAGIC TRICKS.
THAT WAS TERRIBLE.
>> WHAT OTHER CELEBRITIES ARE
YOU MISTAKEN FOR?
>> CHAD SMITH.
WHO WAS YOUR FIRST KISS WITH?
>> UH...
>> SHE LOVED YOU, THOUGH.
>> WHAT WAS HER NAME?
IT WAS ABBY.
GABBY?
I WILL SPLIT THE DIFFERENCE.
>> [LAUGHS]
MINE WAS WITH A YOUNG MAN NAMED
CHRISTIAN.
>> OH.
>> IF YOU ARE FLIPPING THE
CHANNELS IN ONE OF YOUR MOVIES
IS ON, WILL YOU WATCH IT?
>> 100% YES.
>> YEAH!
WHAT'S ONE THING YOU'VE TRIED
THAT YOU WILL NEVER TRY AGAIN.
>> OH, YES, SCUBA DIVING.
>> SCUBA DIVING.
>> WORTH TRYING WANTS BUT NEVER
AGAIN.
>> I DON'T NEED TO LIVE UNDER
THERE.
>> WE ARE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
DOWN THERE.
>> WHY WOULD YOU HAVE ALL THE
TANKS?
>> IT'S THEIR WORLD, NOT OURS.
BY THEY COME I'M TALKING ABOUT
SEA CREATURES.
>> IT'S THEIR WORLD.
>> THEY DON'T COME AND TRY TO
WALK AROUND ON LAND.
>> WHY WOULD THEY?
IT DOESN'T WORK OUT WELL.
WHAT'S THE WEIRDEST RUMOR YOU'VE
EVER HEARD ABOUT YOURSELF?
>> THAT I DIED IN A HANG GLIDING
ACCIDENT.
>> TRUE STORY?
>> TRUE STORY.
>> [LAUGHS]
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
>> I HAD TO CALL MY PARENTS AND
SAY DIDN'T HAPPEN.
>> THEY MUST'VE BEEN SO EXCITED
TO HEAR YOUR VOICE.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY'VE HEARD
IT YET BUT IT WAS ABOUT TO
BREAK.
YEAH.
>> OH.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> WHO'S YOUR FIRST CELEBRITY
CRUSH?
>> OH.
>> DON'T SAY GABBY ABBY.
>> SHE IS NOT A CELEBRITY.
OH, JONI ON HAPPY DAYS.
RIGHT?
IS IT WEIRD TO SAY THE MOM ON
"EIGHT IS ENOUGH?"
>> GET IT ALL OUT.
>> A LOT OF BLANK FACES OUT
THERE.
THIS GUY IS WEIRD.
>> SHAUN CASSIDY, OKAY?
WHAT IS SOMETHING YOU'VE BEEN
MEANING TO TRY BUT JUST HAVEN'T
GOTTEN AROUND TO IT?
>> READ A BOOK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE'LL BE BACK.
>> I KNOW HOW I FEEL WHEN I GET
MY HAIRCUT.
I WANTED THEM TO HAVE THAT SAME
JOY AND FEEL THAT SAME JOY SO I
WANTED TO BRING THAT TO THEM AND
I'M GLAD WE WERE ABLE TO.
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
[police siren]
Michael, your a singer.
bubly is a sparkling water.
Sure is.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
Find something incredible,
from somewhere amazing.
Unique selection,
unbelievable prices.
HomeGoods.
Go Finding.
>> Announcer: THAT SMILE COULD
SELL ALMOST ANYTHING.
>> NEVER HAD
ONE FALLOFF?
>> I HAVE ONE ON RIGHT NOW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: I LOVE THIS NEXT
STORY SO MUCH.
AFTER LEARNING HIS STUDENTS
COULDN'T AFFORD HAIRCUTS,
KINDERGARTEN TEACHER IN D.C. WAS
INSPIRED TO TREAT HIS SCHOOL TO
A DAY OF PAMPERING.
HIS VIDEOS FROM THAT DAY HAVE
RECEIVED MILLIONS OF VIEWERS.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> OH, GIRL, LET ME SEE.
OH, YES.
THAT'S GOOD.
LET ME SEE THAT.
YES.
I LOVE TO SEE THEM.
LET ME SEE THEM NAILS.
YOU HAD TO BRING THE LIPGLOSS.
OH, MY --
YOU'VE STILL GOT IT.
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YEAH.
HE SAYS HE STILL GOT IT.
>> Ellen: FROM
WASHINGTON, D.C., PLEASE WELCOME
AZEL PRATHER.
♪ ♪
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> YOU'RE AN AMAZING GUY.
YOU ARE A GOOD, GOOD MAN.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR STUDENTS AND
FAMILY ARE EXCITED THAT YOU'RE
HERE.
>> YES, WE LOVE ELLEN.
MY PARENTS, MY GRANDMA.
HI, GRANDMA.
THEY WATCH " "ELLEN."
>> Ellen: HI, GRANDMA.
THAT'S SO COOL.
TELL EVERYBODY ABOUT YOUR
SCHOOL.
>> IT'S A TITLE I SCHOOL.
350 STUDENTS.
EARLY CHILDHOOD EDUCATION.
PRE-K.
IT'S A SAFE HAVEN.
THEY GET TO COME IN AND THEY
KNOW WHEN WE ARE IN SCHOOL IT'S
A GREAT PLACE FOR THEM, SAFE
PLACE AND WE'RE GOING TO LEARN
AND HAVE FUN.
>> Ellen: IT'S A SAFE HAVEN.
YES.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S WHAT YOU HOPE ALL SCHOOLS
ARE.
NOT ALL SCHOOLS ARE THAT.
>> IT'S A DIFFERENT KIND OF
NEIGHBORHOOD.
MY KIDS GO THROUGH THINGS WE
PROBABLY COULDN'T IMAGINE.
IT'S CRIME-RIDDEN, POVERTY.
SOMETIMES AT RECESS WE MIGHT
HEAR GUNSHOTS AND HAVE GOT TO GO
INSIDE.
FOR THEM TO BE ABLE TO COME
INSIDE AND COME TO MY CLASS AND
COME TO SCHOOL AND THEY KNOW WE
ARE OKAY HERE AND WE'RE GOING TO
BE GOOD AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
SOME FUN.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO PROVIDE TO
THEM.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE PROVIDING
ALL THAT AND THEN HE DECIDED TO
ADD ON TOP OF THAT THE PAMPERING
DAY.
HOW DID THAT COME UP?
>> I KNOW MY KIDS' STORIES.
THE PARENTS WORK MULTIPLE JOBS.
THEY DON'T HAVE TIME TO TAKE
THEIR KIDS TO GET THEIR HAIR
DONE, NAILS OR HAIRCUTS.
SOMETIMES THEY DON'T HAVE THE
RESOURCES OF THE MONEY SO I
WANTED TO BRING THAT TO THEM AND
I KNOW WHAT IT DOES FOR THEM.
I KNOW HOW I FEEL WHEN I GET MY
HAIRCUT.
I WANTED THEM TO HAVE THAT SAME
JOY.
I WAS GLAD THAT WE WERE ABLE TO.
>> Ellen: HOW DID YOU PUT IT
TOGETHER?
YOU M MUST'VE REACHED OUT TO
PEOPLE.
>> I REACHED OUT TO PEOPLE IN
THE COMMUNITY AND FRIENDS AND
RESOURCES AND I HAD THEM COME
AND THEN PROVIDE AND THEY ALL
SAID YES AND THEY WERE ABLE TO
HELP ME OUT.
BRING SMILES TO MY KIDS' FACES.
>> Ellen: THE KIDS REACTIONS.
IT'S PRECIOUS.
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU CALL YOUR KIDS YOUR
FAMILY.
>> YES.
THEY ARE MY STUDENTS BUT THEY
ARE LITERALLY MY NIECES,
NEPHEWS, SONS AND DAUGHTERS,
LITTLE COUSINS.
WHATEVER THAT MEANS.
I AM BACK TO THEM AND I LOVE
BEING THAT TO THEM.
IT'S MUCH MORE THAN JUST A
TEACHER-STUDENT THING.
I CARE ABOUT THEM OUTSIDE OF
SCHOOL.
I'M GOING TO THEIR GAMES ON THE
WEEKENDS.
I AM PICKING THEM UP, I MET
CHEERLEADING OPTICIANS.
THEY CAN COME AND KICK IT WITH
ME.
THERE MY FRIENDS.
EVERY REALM THAT I CAN BE THERE
FOR MY KIDS COME I WANT TO BE
THERE.
>> Ellen: HOW LUCKY ARE THEY
TO HAVE A TEACHER LIKE YOU.
THAT'S AMAZING.
MORE WITH AZEL AFTER THIS.
WE'LL BE BACK.
I AM PARTNERING WITH HYUNDAI TO
CELEBRATE PEOPLE WHO MAKE LIFE
BETTER FOR THEIR COMMUNITIES.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH A
D.C. TEACHER, AZEL PRATHER.
YOUR STUDENT SOUND AMAZING SO I
WANTED TO MEET SOME OF THEM.
COME ON OUT, KIDS.
>> WHAT?
[LAUGHTER]
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> Ellen: HELLO THERE.
LOOK AT YOUR HAIR HOW GOOD IT
LOOKS.
>> WHY DO YOU SAY?
>> THANK YOU!
>> Ellen: YOU ARE WELCOME.
TELL ME YOUR NAME.
>> LYRIC.
>> Ellen: LYRIC.
>> AMAR.
>> Ellen: AMAR.
>> JOURNEY.
>> Ellen: DO YOU WANT TO TELL
ME WHY YOU LIKE THIS MAN SO
MUCH?
>> TELL THEM THE WHOLE LIST.
>> HE TEACHES HOW TO DANCE.
>> I DO.
>> Ellen: I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
THAT.
>> WHAT ELSE DO WE DO?
>> TO BE HAPPY EVERY DAY.
>> Ellen: THAT'S GOOD.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE HAPPY EVERY
DAY.
THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING.
IS THIS YOUR FIRST TIME TO BE ON
A PLANE?
>> YES!
>> Ellen: HOW WAS THAT?
>> FUN.
>> WHAT DID YOU LIKE ABOUT IT?
WHAT DID YOU SEE ON THE PLANE?
>> I SAW AN AIRPLANE.
>> Ellen: YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SAYING WHEN THAT CLOSE.
>> I SAW THE CITY.
>> Ellen: THIS CITY.
>> I SAW THE CLOUDS.
>> Ellen: THE CLOUDS.
SO YOU'RE STAYING AT A HOTEL.
WHAT IS THE HOTEL LIKE?
>> FUN.
>> IT'S VERY FUN.
>> Ellen: WHAT'S FUN ABOUT IT?
>> WHAT ARE YOU ALL ASKING
ABOUT?
>> Ellen: THE POOL.
YOU GOT PAMPERED.
WHAT WAS YOUR MOST FUN PART
ABOUT THAT?
>> MY HAIR.
>> MY NAILS.
>> Ellen: MY HAIR!
MY NAILS!
YOU'RE A GOOD MAN, AS I SAID.
YOU DO SO MANY THINGS.
YOU WALK THE STUDENT HOME.
YOU TAKE CARE OF THEM ON
WEEKENDS, GO TO SPORTING EVENTS,
PAY OUT OF YOUR POCKET WHICH SO
MANY TEACHERS DO, TO HELP YOUR
TEACHERS AND FAMILIES.
BUYING CLOTHES, SHOES,
GROCERIES.
YOU HELPED SANTA DELIVER
PRESENTS TO ALL THE STUDENTS AT
YOUR SCHOOL.
AND INSTEAD OF FIXING YOUR CAR
WHICH IS CURRENTLY IN THE SHOP,
YOU SPENT $7,000 TO OPEN A
FOUNDATION TO HELP YOUR
STUDENTS.
>> YEAH.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW BIG, HOW
MUCH A NONPROFIT REALLY COSTS.
BUT I KNEW BY DOING IT I WOULD
BE ABLE TO REACH MORE PEOPLE AND
MORE PEOPLE WOULD BE ABLE TO
HELP ME OUT AND DONATE.
YOU DO WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO DO.
>> Ellen: SET OF FIXING YOUR
CAR.
WELL, I AM PARTNERING WITH
HYUNDAI TO CELEBRATE PEOPLE WHO
MAKE LIFE BETTER FOR THEIR
COMMUNITIES.
THEY WANT TO MAKE YOUR LIFE EVEN
BETTER WITH A NEW HYUNDA
HYUNDAI SONATA.
>> [CHEERING]
>> OH!
OH, THAT'S CRAZY.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> WHERE YOU GOING?
>> THAT'S NICE.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: I LIKE IT TOO.
>> THAT'S NICE.
SONATA, SLEEK AND STYLISH AND I
>> Ellen: I LIKE IT TOO.
CAN PARK ITSELF WITH A TOUCH OF
SONATA, SLEEK AND STYLISH AND I
A BUTTON.
CAN PARK ITSELF WITH A TOUCH OF
WE ALSO WANT TO HELP --
A BUTTON.
>> [LAUGHS]
WE ALSO WANT TO HELP --
>> Ellen: LOOK AT THE TRUNK.
>> [LAUGHS]
SO MUCH SPACE BACK HERE.
>> Ellen: LOOK AT THE TRUNK.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
SO MUCH SPACE BACK HERE.
COME ON.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> NO.
COME ON.
>> Ellen: WE WANT TO GIVE THE
>> NO.
FOUNDATION.
>> Ellen: WE WANT TO GIVE THE
>> OH, MY GOSH!
FOUNDATION.
ELLEN, IS THIS FOR REAL?
>> OH, MY GOSH!
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
ELLEN, IS THIS FOR REAL?
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
ARE YOU FOR REAL?
THIS IS CRAZY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Ellen: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> UNDER HERE?
>> Ellen: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ARE YOU FEELING ANYTHING?
>> UNDER HERE?
>> II like this house, honey.
Oh, it's beautiful.
So you guys are welcome to use
the car while I'm at work.
I'll text you a key.
How do you text a key?
It's technology, dear.
I got this.
Better text it to me.
It has to be a
smart phone, dad.
Are you saying I gotta
dumb phone?
No. It's cool.
We'll just do it
old school.
Hyundai Digital Key;
now there's a better
way to share.
Hey, press that
button there.
Only on the
all-new Sonata.
Where's the car going?
Technology, dear.
That's technology.
♪♪
Woah is this the future?
This is the present,
future Bill.
Here's your order Bills.
No way!
Yes way.
Okay.
Sensitive skin?
Cetaphil Moisturizing Cream
with 24-hour moisture
lock formula
gives continuous
soothing relief
for dry Sensitive Skin.
Cetaphil skin is healthy skin.
Cheerios... Do I look like a
child to you?
Honey Nut Cheerios
are heart healthy
and can help lower
cholesterol.
That's why we introduced
heart shapes.
Get it?
Ummm
Did you just ummm?
No.
I'm pretty sure I heard a ummm.
(sneezing)
♪♪
Grab a Kleenex Ultra Soft tissue
and grab every moment.
Made with superior softness,
for your comfort.
Kleenex. The softest ultra
tissue.
>>> NOMTS AWAY FIRST AT 4:00 HOW
A NICOTINE PATCH COULD BE KEY IN
HELPING PEOPLE WHO SUFFER MEMORY
LOSS.
WE EXPLAIN THE PROMISING NEW
RESEARCH.
>> YOU JUST SAW ALAN SURPRISE A
LOCAL D.C. TEACHER.
WE GET THE SCOOP ON HIS
FOUNDAONTI
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
Alex isn't just at taekwondo
practice...
She's AT TAEKWONDO PRACTICE
SHOWING OFF HOW STRONG
AND CONFIDENT SHE'S
BECOMMMMMMMMMMMINGGGGGG!!!!!
Try new Yoplait Starburst.
For Big Little Wins!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: RECENTLY MARK
WAHLBERG WAS HERE TO PROMOTE HIS
NEW MOVIE "SPENCER CONFIDENTIAL"
AND TO SEE ME.
I ASKED HIM TO FILM SOMETHING
WITH THE FELLOW FITNESS
ENTHUSIAST.
I'VE PARED HIM UP WITH ANDY
LASSNER.
PLEASE ENJOY A SLOW WALKING WITH
ANDY.
>> HELLO, SLOW WALKERS.
TODAY I'M HERE WITH FELLOW
FITNESS ENTHUSIAST MARK WAH
WAHLBERG.
WHO OBVIOUSLY HAS HEARD ABOUT MY
PROGRAM AND GOT REALLY EXCITED
AND ASKED, IS THERE ANY WAY I
COULD GET IN ON THE PROGRAM.
MARK, WE ARE DOING, JUST SO YOU
KNOW.
IT'S CALLED SLOW WALKING WITH
ANDY 2020 AND WHAT I WANT PEOPLE
TO DO IS WALK FOR 20 MINUTES
SLOWLY 20 DAYS OUT OF THE MONTH.
I AM SAYING THAT IT'S BETTER TO
MOVE A LITTLE THAN TO NOT MOVE
AT ALL.
>> I COMPLETELY AGREE.
>> SO YOU ARE ENDORSING IT.
>> I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU WALK
SLOWLY BUT I DO RECOMMEND SOME
MORE INTENSITY.
>> I TOOK MY INCLINE UP TO 6.0.
OUR GOAL IS TO SORT OF GET
SWOLLEN UP LIKE YOU.
IT'S BIG I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
IT'S MORE OF A MEDITATIVE THING.
>> NO, IT'S MORE OF AN EXERCISE.
IT'S NOT A MEDITATION.
>> ENJOY THE ATMOSPHERE.
>> IT'S NOT REALLY MEDITATIVE.
HERE IS THE PROBLEM.
AS SOMEONE WHO ALWAYS HAS TO BE
FIT FOR MOVIES AND ALL THAT, YOU
UNDERSTAND WHAT IT TAKES TO HAVE
THE KIND OF DISCIPLINE THAT I
HAVE.
>> I SEE SOME SWEAT.
>> UNDER HERE?
ARE YOU FEELING ANYTHING?
>> I AM GETTING TIRED.
>> BECAUSE...
>> OF YOUR B.S.
OKAY, LISTEN.
>> DO YOU WANT IN ON THIS
PROGRAM FINANCIALLY?
WOULD YOU WANT A PIECE OF IT?
>> I THINK WE COULD PROBABLY
SELL THESE TREADMILLS FOR ABOUT
500 BUCKS EACH AND GET RID OF
THEM.
>> HE'S MAKING JOKES.
BUT YOU TAKE YOUR SHIRT OFF AND
YOU ARE [BLEEP]
MARK WAHLBERG.
I TAKE IT OFF.
IT'S NOT GREAT.
>> IT'S GETTING THERE.
BUT YOU REALIZE THAT THE
BIOLOGICAL CLOCK IS TICKING.
>> I WANT TO THANK MY GUESTS.
SLOW WALKING WITH ANDY 2020.
OUR NEW SPONSOR.
THERE'S NO RUNNING THIS PROGRAM,
MARK.
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU
GET A LITTLE BIT OF A BURN.
RIGHT NOW YOU HAVE AN EVEN
BURNED OFF A CRUMB.
>> WANT
>> WANT TO THANK MY GUEST, MARK
WAHLBERG, MY NEW CELEBRITY
SPOKESPERSON.
THAT IS A 15 INCLINE.
I'M GOING TO HAVE A HEART
ATTACK.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN I FLY OFF INTO
THE WALL?
>> I THINK IT'S JUST DRYWALL.
>> WE ARE GOOD!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: IF YOU DON'T FOLLOW
ANDY LASSNER ON HIS INSTAGRAM,
HE SLOW WALKS EVERY CIVIL DAY
AND YOU CAN FOLLOW HIM AND SLOW
WALK ALONG WITH HIM.
IT'S AN INTERESTING INSTAGRAM.
YOU SHOULD FOLLOW HIM.
I WANT TO THANK HARRISON FORD.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
BE KIND TO ONE ANOTHER.
BYE!
>>> STORM TEAM 4 RADAR TRACKING
SHOWERS THAT WILL MOVE IN ACROSS
THE AREA TONIGHT AND THEN COLD
AIR MOVES IN LATER THIS WEEK.
>>> A LOCAL SCHOOL COPING WITH
UNTHINKABLE LOSS.
>> ONE OF THE STUDENTS SAID
WYATT ISN'T HERE.
I SAID YES I KNOW.
>> HOW THERAPY DOGS ARE HELPING
EASE THE PAIN OF LOSING A
6-YEAR-OLD BOY.
>>> SETTING THE STAGE FOR
TOMORROW NIGHT'S DEMOCRATIC
DEBATE.
>>> COULD A NICOTINE PATCH HELP
PEOPLE SUFFERING MEMORY LOSS?
WE HAVE THE SURPRISING NEW
STUDY.
>>> AND GIFT CARDS GOING TO
WASTE.
WHY WE'RE LOSING BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
>>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
WELCOME IN TO NEWS4 AT 4:00.
GRAB YOUR UMBRELLA.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AS YOU CAN SEE, RAIN MOVING IN
ON STORM TEAM 4 RADAR AND THEN
WE GET A BLAST OF COLD AIR
MOVING IN BEHIND THIS MESS.
>> WE START THIS AFTERNOON WITH
CHIEF METEOROLOGIST DOUG
KAMMERER.
DOUG, WHO'S SEEING THE RAIN
RIGHT NOW?
>> WE'RE SEEING IT RIGHT NOW ON
STORM TEAM 4 RADAR, A PRETTY
GOOD DAY THE FIRST HALF OF THE
DAY.
NOW WE ARE STARTING TO SEE SOME
OF THE SHOWERS.
THAT'S ALL THEY ARE, JUST
SHOWERS.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING
DOWN IN PORTIONS OF ANNE ARUNDEL
COUNTY AROUND CHARLES COUNTY,
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY, DOWN
TOWARD CALVERT COUNTY AS WELL
AND THEN BACK TO THE NORTH
AROUND FREDRICK COUNTY,
HAGERSTOWN, SEEING SOME OF THE
HEAVIER RAIN MAKING ITS WAY ON
THROUGH.
BACK TOWARD THE WINCHESTER AREA,
ALSO.
WE'RE TRACKING ALL OF THIS.
THE WIDER PICTURE SHOWING HOW
BIG AND EXPANSIVE THE STORM
SYSTEM IS.
HOWEVER, WE STILL HAVE SOME DRY
AIR AND IT IS NOT A VERY STRONG
SYSTEM.
SO EVEN THOUGH IT LOOKS LIKE A
LOT OF MOISTURE MOVING OUR WAY
WE ARE ACTUALLY NOT GOING TO SEE
A LOT OUT OF THIS.
WE'LL SEE SHOWERS OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE HOURS.
THE BIGGEST THREAT FOR SHOWER
ACTIVITY