[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪♪ STARING MY HEART APART AS
WELL ♪
♪ TOLD ME THAT YOU DON'T KNOW ♪
♪ LOOKING LIKE SOMETHING THAT
MIGHT BE GOOD FOR YOU ♪
♪ GO ON AND HOLD THE FEELING AND
WRONG ♪
♪ GO ON BELIEVE ♪
♪ BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO WALKS
ACROSS THE FIRE FOR YOU ♪
♪ ONLY ONE WHO WALKS ACROSS THE
FIRE FOR YOU ♪
♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪♪
>> Kelly: GIVE IT UP!
♪♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪
♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NO ONE WRITES A SONG LIKE THE
INCREDIBLE MELISSA ETHERIDGE.
I'M A FAN OF HER.
NOT ONLY AS AN ARTIST, BUT A
FAN.
LET'S FIND WHO REQUESTED IT.
WHERE IS LESLIE AT?
MAN, IT'S LIKE CATHOLIC MASS.
YOU ARE GOING TO STAND AND SIT,
STAND AND SIT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING, LESLIE?
WHY DO YOU LOVE THAT SONG?
>> MELISSA ETHERIDGE AND
PARTICULARLY THIS ALBUM, YES, I
AM, WAS CRITICALLY IMPORTANT
WHEN IT CAME OUT AS A GAY WOMAN
IN THE EARLY '90s.
>> Kelly: IS THE COOLEST
THING.
MELISSA SEES THIS.
IT'S SO IMPORTANT FOR ARTIST,
IT'S IMPORTANT WHEN YOU CONTACT
SOMEONE.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST GIFT OF ALL.
I BET SHE LOVES HEARING -- NEVER
GETS OLD FOR ANY ARTIST.
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
MUSIC IS FEELING.
MUSIC IS POWERFUL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, LESLIE!
I WILL BUCKLE UP BECAUSE WE GOT
ONE HECK OF A SHOW.
FIRST, A
I LEARNED IT'S NOT REALLY THE
SITES AND ATTRACTIONS THAT MAKE
A TOWN SPECIAL BUT IT'S THE
PEOPLE AND CULTURE.
THE FURTHER CONNECTION IN THE
SHELL, I'M HIGHLIGHTING MY
FAVORITE CITIES AND AMAZING
PEOPLE TO MAKE THEM GREAT, SO
TODAY WE HAD TO MY HOME STATE OF
TEXAS, BUT OF COURSE.
AND A CITY KNOWN BY MANY NAMES.
SOME CALL IT STEEL CITY, H-TOWN,
THE ENERGY CAPITAL OF THE WORLD
BUT A CITY WITH A BIG, BIG
HEART.
IT'S A CITY WITH A DAILY
REMINDER TO BE SOMEONE.
THIS IS A GOOD NEIGHBORHOOD,
HOUSTON.
♪♪ GOOD NEIGHBORHOOD ♪♪
HOUSTON!
[MIMICS SIRENS]
LET'S GO WHERE DON AND LOUIS IS
STANDING BY WITH FOX 23.
IT LOOKS LIKE Y'ALL ARE ENJOYING
SOME GOOD FOOD.
>> YOU MAKE ME CRY.
>> Kelly: LOOK LIKE YOU WERE
ENJOYING SOME GOOD FOOD BEHIND
YOU.
THAT'S MY TEXAS PEOPLE, I LOVE
THEM.
>> LET'S GO TAKE A LOOK.
WE ARE AT EIGHT WUNDER BREWERY,
NAMED AFTER THE EIGHTH WONDER OF
THE WORLD, THE HOUSTON
ASTRODOME.
JOINED BY A FEW OF MY BEST D'S.
LET'S GIVE KELLY A HUGE HOLLER,
HOUSTON!
THIS IS ONE OF THE BEST THINGS
ABOUT HOUSTON, IT'S THE MIDDLE
OF WINTER AND WE ARE ALL JUST
KIND OF HANGING OUTSIDE IN THE
PATIO HERE.
HAVING A GOOD TIME FOR THIS
ISN'T QUITE L.A. WEATHER, BUT
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
>> Kelly: IT'S TEXAS, IT'S
AMAZING.
SPEAKING OF FOOD, YOU HAVE A BIG
BARBECUE FESTIVAL COMING UP,
RIGHT?
>> WE DO HAVE A BARBECUE
FESTIVAL COMING UP.
BUT FIRST TAKE A LOOK AT THESE
AMAZING TACOS RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS FROM LAMARCK ROAD TACO,
THE FOOD TRUCK.
THIS IS THEIR FAMOUS TRUMBO
TACO.
THE LOADED WAFFLE FRIES QUESTION
MIKE DOESN'T GET BETTER THAN
THAT.
BUT THE BARBECUE FESTIVAL?
WELL THE
WORLD TEMPERATURE BARBECUE FAST,
GOING TO BE COMPETING FROM ALL
OVER THE WORLD.
KELLY, YOU KNOW THAT NOBODY DOES
BARBECUE LIKE WE DO BARBECUE
HERE IN TEXAS.
THIS IS JON STEWART FROM BIG SIX
BARBECUE, AND YOU
WHIPPED UP SOME OF YOUR
CRAFTMATIC
>> YOU CAN FIND US AT THE AND RG
TEXAS GAME IS AN.
>> Kelly: BETTER HAVE SOME OF
THAT GOOD BARBECUE AT MY HOUSE
TONIGHT.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE SOME OF YOUR
CRAFT MAC IN OUR STUDIO AND IT
IS DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, CHEF!
I'M NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT.
HERE WE GO.
I'M TRYING IT.
OKAY, WE CAN'T TALK ABOUT
HOUSTON UNLESS TALKING ABOUT
RODEO HOUSTON.
IT'S THE LARGEST RODEO ON THE
PLANET.
IT TAKES PLACE OVER THREE WEEKS
IN MARCH.
I'VE ACTUALLY PERFORMED AT IT.
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
DONNELL LEE, WHAT CAN PEOPLE
EXPECT THIS YEAR?
>> WE CAN EXPECT A LOT OF
GOODNESS.
KELLY, MY MOM AND I SAW YOU
PERFORM AT THE RODEO.
WE ENJOYED IT.
THE BIGGEST EVENT OF THE YEAR.
LAST YEAR WE HAD TWO AND A HALF
MILLION PEOPLE ATTEND AND
ANYBODY WHO IS ANYBODY PERFORMED
AT THE RODEO, KELLY, YOU PERFORM
THERE.
I ALSO SAW BEYONCE,
TAYLOR SWIFT, ARIANA GRANDE,
JANET JACKSON, AND SO MANY MORE.
ELVIS PRESLEY EVEN PERFORMED AT
THE RODEO.
ONE OF YOUR FELLOW JUDGES, GWEN
STEFANI, WILL TAKE THE STAGE
ALONG WITH LUKE BRYAN, KEITH
URBAN, SO MANY PEOPLE TAKING TO
THE STAGE AND THIS GOES FOR
ALMOST A MONTH.
IT'S A LOT OF GOODNESS.
INCLUDES LOTS OF RODEO RIDING,
LIVESTOCK EXHIBITS, AND A WHOLE
LOT OF AMAZING FOOD.
>> TEXAS, YOU BETTER WATCH OUT,
AND HIS WOMAN IS THERE, I'M JUST
SAYING...
AND EVERY CITY HAS THEIR HEROES,
ALSO THEY STEP UP IN TIMES OF
NEED AND WE ARE FORTUNATE TO
HAVE TWO OF THEM TODAY PAIR THE
FIRST IS A TEXAS HIP-HOP LEGEND
AND THE SECOND IS KNOWN ALL OVES
COLORFUL COMMERCIALS.
ON PAPER THEY COULDN'T BE MORE
DIFFERENT BUT DURING
HURRICANE HARVEY, BOTH WENT
ABOVE AND BEYOND FOR THEIR
COMMUNITIES AND CONTINUE TO DO
SO TO THIS DAY.
SO PLEASE WELCOME WRAPPER TRAY
TRUTH AND JIM MACK AVAIL, BETTER
KNOWN AS MATTRESS MACK
DURING HURRICANE HARVEY, YOU
ACTUALLY RESCUED PEOPLE ON YOUR
BOAT, CORRECT?
>> DEFINITELY.
HARVEY WAS
SOMEBODY ASSISTED, WE WENT OUT
THERE TO RESCUE LIVES.
TO THIS DAY, MYSELF, MR. ROGERS,
WE'VE GIVEN OVER 1.5 BILLION IN
SUPPLIES.
WE HELPED OUT WITH FLORIDA,
CAROLINA WITH A HURRICANE.
ME AND MACK ALWAYS DOING STUFF.
>> MATTRESS MACK, YOU ACTUALLY
OPEN YOUR STORE -- I REMEMBER
HEARING ABOUT THIS DURING
HARVEY.
YOU OPEN YOUR STORE DURING
HARVEY FOR PEOPLE TO SLEEP ON
THE BEDS.
YOU DIDN'T CARE ABOUT LIABILITY,
DIDN'T CARE ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
A LOT OF BUSINESSES WOULD BE
FEARFUL OF THAT, SO THANK YOU
FOR CARING ABOUT HUMANITY AND
NOT YOURSELF FIRST.
>> THAT'S THE WAY TRAY AND I
WERE BOTH BROUGHT UP.
PEOPLE SAY, WHY DID YOU LET THE
PEOPLE IN QUESTION MIKE WHAT
ELSE WAS I GOING TO DO, LET MY
PEOPLE DROWNED?
WE'VE GOT TO HELP EACH OTHER.
>> Kelly: THAT'S MY HOME STATE
AND I LOVE THEM.
THEY ARE NOT THE ONLY
HOUSTONIANS MAKING A DIFFERENCE.
DONNA LEE, WE'LL CHECK IN BACK
WITH YOU LATER.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S BRING OUT OUR
FIRST GUEST!
YOU KNOW AND LOVE THEM AS THE
DOTING FATHER AND SKITTISH ON
AND ON "MODERN FAMILY."
THE SERIES WRAPS UP THIS YEAR.
>> [SPEAKING FRENCH]
>> IT WAS EASY TO FIT INTO IT
ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS LOOK GOOD
AND HAVE A LOT OF ATTITUDE.
PARIS WAS LIKE ONE BIG GAY BAR.
>> [SPEAKING FRENCH]
>> PIGEON?
>> BON APPETIT.
>> Kelly: GIVE IT UP FOR THE
DELIGHTFUL JESSE TYLER FERGUSON,
Y'ALL!
♪ ♪
HELLO!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I LOVE YOUR SHOES!
>> LOOK AT YOU, GUYS.
YOU PERCENTAGETHAT'S WHY
SOME DAYS YOU'RE GOING TO WANT
TO BALL AND DRINK A WINE
IN THE BATHROOM AND PRAY, OTHER
DAYS WILL BE GREAT.
>> I DO THOSE THINGS ALREADY,
THOUGH.
THAT'S LIKE A REGULAR DAY.
>> Kelly: YOU ARE GOING TO BE
A GREAT DAD.
LET'S GO BACK TO HOUSTON, CAN
YOU TAKE US TO BREAK?
>> MORE WITH KELLY AND JESSE
WHEN WE CAN TURN.
>> HOUSTON, WE HAVE NO PROBLEM
BECAUSE WE'LL BE BACK IN 60
SECONDS.
Hot! Hot!
No no no no no, there's no space
there! Maybe over here?
Oven mitts! Oven mitts!
Everything's stuck
in the drawers!
I'm sorry! Oh, jeez.
Hi.
Kelly Clarkson.
Try Wayfair!
Oh, OK.
It's going to help you,
with all of... this!
Yeah, here you go.
Thank you!
Oh, I like that one!
[ laugh ]
That's a lot of storage!
Perfect.
You're welcome!
I love it. How did
you do all this?
Wayfair!
Speaking of dinner,
what're we eating, guys?
New Tide POWER PODS one up the
cleaning power of liquid.
Can it one up spaghetti night?
It sure can.
Really?
Can it one up breakfast in bed?
Yeah, for sure.
Thanks, boys.
What about that?
Uhh, yep!
It can?
Yeah, even that!
I would very much like to see
that.
Me too.
Introducing new Tide Power PODS.
One up the toughest stains with
50% more cleaning power
than liquid detergent. Any
further questions?
>> THIS CLOSET IS SO BIG.
WE HAD TO GET TWO EXCAVATORS.
THIS IS CAROL AND THIS IS
PATRICIA.
THEY ARE TWINS.
>> I DO NOT KNOW WHERE HE GOT
THOSE NAMES, BUT ONLY JESSE CAN
MAKE EXCAVATORS SOUND CUTE.
>> THEY'VE GOT TO GO.
>> WE DON'T ALWAYS GET TO TEAR
DOWN THE HOUSE BUT WHEN WE DO, I
GET REALLY EXCITED.
MAKE IT OFFICIAL!
>> Kelly: I LOVE AND!
WELCOME BACK.
I'M SPEAKING WITH JESSE TYLER
FERGUSON.
THAT WAS A CLIP FROM THE NEW
EXTREME MAKEOVER
"EXTREME MAKEOVER: HOME
EDITION."
I LOVE THIS SHOW.
I FEEL A PEOPLE NEED IT RIGHT
NOW AND YOU COULDN'T BE MORE
RIGHT.
>> TIMES ARE WEIRD RIGHT NOW.
THE NEWS CYCLE IS SO HEAVY.
TO TURN ON THE TV AND WATCH
PEOPLE'S OPOSSUM'S LIVES BEING
CHANGED, NEW STARTS, I THINK WEL
NEED MORE OF THAT.
IT INSPIRED ME TO DO MORE IN MY
DAY-TO-DAY LIFE.
TAKE THE SHOW TO DO MORE GOOD.
>> Kelly: THE END OF "MODERN
FAMILY" IS COMING UP.
I KNOW IT PAVE THE WAY TO OTHER
SHOWS AND IT'S VERY COOL.
HOW MANY EPISODES DO YOU HAVE
LEFT AND ARE YOU KIND OF
INCREDIBLY SAD?
>> WE HAVE TWO MORE EPISODES TO
SHOOT AND WE ARE DONE FOREVER.
>> Kelly: FINAL?
SPEAK I JUST WANT TO MAKE Y'ALL
UNDERSTAND
>> Kelly: RIPPING THE BAND-AID
OFF.
>> IT'LL BE ON RERUNS TILL THE
END OF TIME BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
I'M FULLY DEALING WITH IT.
I'M KIND OF JUST PRETENDING IT'S
NOT HAPPENING.
I HAVE CRIED ONSET MANY TIMES.
I'LL HAVE TO SAY A LINE.
LET'S JUST ENJOY EACH OTHER
WHILE WE STILL CAN AND I'M
BAWLING.
WE ALL LOVE EACH OTHER SO MUCH
AND THANK YOU ALL FOR WATCHING
THE SHOW.
CHEERS MACK YOU'RE THE
>> Kelly: 11 YEARS STRAIGHT UP
QUESTION MIKE THAT'S A DREAM.
>> I KNOW.
>> Kelly: WE TALKED ABOUT
THIS, BUT WE DIDN'T TALK ABOUT
HAVING CHILDREN, EVERYBODY GAVE
ME EVERY BOOK, ALL THE ADVICE
AND IT WAS OVERWHELMING.
>> IT'S ALREADY HAPPENING.
I FEEL LIKE AS AN ACTOR TAKING
NOTES AND BEING COLLABORATIVE,
SAME WITH MY FRIENDS.
I LIKE THAT PIECE OF ADVICE.
I DON'T LIKE THAT PIECE OF
ADVICE.
I'M HONESTLY WELCOME TO ANY
SUGGESTIONS BECAUSE I HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT I'M DOING.
I KNOW I'M GOING TO SEE THEM
REGULARLY.
I DO KNOW THAT.
>> Kelly: MY NEXT GAS MIGHT
HAVE PARENTING ADVICE TOO.
YOU KNOW HER AS THE EMBARRASSED
WIFE OF LARRY DAVID ON "CURB
YOUR ENTHUSIASM."
YOU CAN WATCH THE NEW SEASON ON
HBO.
>> I WAS WONDERING IF YOU HAD AN
EXTRA TOOTHBRUSH?
>> I DON'T, SORRY.
>> CAN I USE YOURS?
>> NO.
>> WE ARE MARRIED BUT YOU'VE
USED TOOTHBRUSHES BEFORE.
>> THAT WAS SO LONG AGO!
>> THE MOUTH IS THE SAME IN.
>> I'D RATHER NOT.
>> I HOLD YOUR MOUTH IN HIGH
ESTEEM.
IT'S A COMPLIMENT.
>> IS A QUESTION MARK
>> Kelly: CHERYL HINES, Y'ALL
!
♪ ♪
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS!
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT.
IT'S SO LOVELY TO MEET YOU.
YOU ARE HILARIOUS, FOR ONE, AND
YOU LOOK SO CLASSICALLY AWESOME
WITH YOUR RED HEELS.
I HAVE THIS HABIT TO ME, DO
STRANGERS COME UP TO YOU AND
JUST DIEBOLD'S THE WEIRDEST
THINGS TO YOU BECAUSE OF "CURB
YOUR ENTHUSIASM?"
>> YES, BECAUSE "CURB" IS A
COMMENTARY ON SOCIAL GRACES AND
LACK THEREOF, THEY COME UP TO ME
AND THEY LIKE TO PICK SHOWS TO
ME.
WE HAVE NEVER CALLED OR TEXTED
EACH OTHER, BUT AT THE WRAP
PARTY, RAY WAS NOT THERE, BUT
THIS GUY WAS LIKE, I'VE GOT A
GREAT STORY FOR "CURB."
I GO, OH, OKAY.
I DO NOT KNOW HOW MUCH I CAN SAY
ON DAYTIME TELEVISION.
>> Kelly: WE CAN EDIT IT.
>> HE SAID MY WIFE AND I WERE
HAVING TO FACULTY'S GETTING
PREGNANT, SO I HAD TO GO GET A'S
ANKLE.
I WENT TO THE DOCTOR AND THERE
WAS NO GOOD PORN AND I WASN'T
ALLOWED TO USE LUBRICANT.
>> I'VE LITERALLY BEEN THERE.
THIS IS, LIKE, MY FIRST TIME.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
KEEP GOING.
>> HE'S TELLING YOU THE STORY
WITH ALL THESE DETAILS.
>> Kelly: HE'S A STRANGER!
TALKING ABOUT HIS SPERM!
>> I SAID, OKAY, I GOT IT,
THANK YOU.
I WANTED TO TELL LARRY AND I
LOOK AT MY PHONE AND FOR SOME
REASON MY PHONE HAD POCKET
DIALED RAY ROMANO, WHO I NEVER
TALKED TO ON THE PHONE BEFORE
AND I SAID, MY GOSH...
I HUNG UP AND I LOOK TO SEE HOW
LONG I HAD BEEN CONNECTED TO HIM
AND IT WAS, LIKE, 5 MINUTES.
I START PANICKING.
DO I CALL RAY AND TELL HIM
QUESTION MIKE MY FRIEND WAS,
LIKE, DON'T CALL.
MAYBE HE DOESN'T KNOW IT WAS
YOU.
JUST LET IT LIE.
THE NEXT MORNING, FIRST THING IN
THE MORNING, RAY ROMANO CALLED
IN AND SAID, DID YOU CALL ME IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
I DID BECAUSE THE GUY WITH THE
SPERM AND HE DIDN'T HAVE LUBE...
[LAUGHTER]
>> MY GOD...
>> I WAS CONNECTED TO YOU.
HE GOES, I DIDN'T HEAR ANY OF
THAT.
BUT HE GOES, SAY IT AGAIN BUT
MORE SLOWLY.
ANYWAY...
BECAUSE NOW HE'S GOING TO USE
IT.
>> Kelly: WHAT AN EPIC BUTT
DIAL.
IT'S LIKE A "FRIENDS" EPISODE
WITH MONICA GELLER.
I LOVE THAT YOU CHIMED IN.
"I'VE SO BEEN THERE"...
BEST PART OF TODAY.
YOU REALLY CONNECTED WITH THAT.
>> YOU GUYS, IT'S A PROCESS.
>> Kelly: BE SURE TO CATCH
JESSE ON THE FINAL EPISODE OF
"MODERN FAMILY" WHEN DAYS ON ABC
AND ON "EXTREME MAKEOVER: HOME
EDITION" ON SUNDAYS, AND WATCH
CHERYL ON "CURB YOUR
ENTHUSIASM," DO NOT GIVE HER
ADVICE ON WHAT TO DO ON THE
SHOW.
WE NEED A QUICK BREAK.
BEST WAY POSSIBLE, YOU'LL SEE
WHAT I MEAN.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
Once-weekly Ozempic® is
helping many people
with type 2 diabetes like James
lower their blood sugar.
A majority of adults
who took Ozempic®
reached an A1C under 7
and maintained it.
Here's your A1C.
Oh!
My A1C is under 7!
(announcer)
And you may lose weight.
Adults who took Ozempic® lost
on average up to 12 pounds.
I lost
almost 12 pounds!
Oh!
(announcer)
Ozempic® does not increase
the risk of major
cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
There's no increased risk.
Oh!
And I only have
to take it once a week.
Oh!
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
Ozempic® should not be
the first medicine
for treating diabetes,
or for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump
or swelling in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase
low blood sugar risk.
Common side effects are
nausea, vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain,
and constipation.
Some side effects can lead
to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
Once-weekly Ozempic® is
helping me reach
my blood sugar goal.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
You may pay as little
as $25 per prescription.
Ask your health care
provider today
about once-weekly Ozempic®.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> Kelly: WELCOME, EVERY BODY!
I'M BACK WITH MY PALS JESSE
TYLER FERGUSON AND CHERYL HINES.
GIVE IT UP FOR THEM!
SO, CHERYL AND JESSE EACH STAR
IN SHOWS THAT DEAL WITH AWKWARD
SITUATIONS.
JESSE IN THE "MODERN FAMILY" AND
CHERYL IN "CURB YOUR
ENTHUSIASM."
I ALSO HEARD CHERYL LOVES GAME
NIGHT.
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D SEE HOW THEY
AND I DEAL WITH UNCOMFORTABLE
SOCIAL SITUATIONS IN REAL LIFE.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY, OY, THAT'S
AWKWARD.
IT'S PRETTY SIMPLE TO IT WE WILL
THIS BUTTON.
AN AWKWARD SITUATION WILL APPEAR
WITH A COUPLE OF OPTIONS ON HOW
TO DEAL WITH IT.
WE EACH HAVE, RATHER, TO SAY
WHICH OPTION WE CHOOSE IN EACH
SITUATION.
I KIND OF DON'T UNDERSTAND
EITHER BUT IT'S GOING TO BE
GREAT.
WE ARE GOING TO PUSH THE BUTTON.
DOESN'T MATTER WHO PUSHES THE
BUTTON?
I'M GOING TO PUSH THE BUTTON.
>> NOW YOU PUSH THE BUTTON.
>> Kelly: YOUR BOSS CALLS YOU
BY THE WRONG NAME.
DO YOU, AA, CORRECT OR, BECOME A
NEW PERSON?
>> I JUST ROLL WITH IT.
LIKE, HEY, TINA.
>> Kelly: I LIKE THAT NAME...
>> MY REAL NAME IS JESSE TYLER
MORMAN, BUT MY THEY CALL ME
JESSE TYLER FERGUSON SO I ROLLED
WITH IT.
>> Kelly: WOULD YOU CORRECT A
PERSON?
>> I WOULD GET IT OUT OF THE
WAY.
BECAUSE PEOPLE WOULD THINK THAT
MY NAME IS
>> Kelly: SOMETIMES PEOPLE SAY
CLARKSTON.
AND THAT'S NOT...
I PUT LIKE RYAN ACTUALLY SAID
THAT WHEN I WON AMERICAN
"AMERICAN IDOL."I ROLLED WITH I.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
YOU WANT TO HIT IT?
>> I'VE GOT THIS DOWN.
>> Kelly: I THINK WE HIT IT
AND THEN IT DOES IT.
>> YOU HIT THE BUTTON?
>> Kelly: YOU DO NOT HAVE IT
DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, A PERSON EXIT A STALL
IN A PUBLIC RESTROOM WITH TOILET
PAPER HANGING.
DO YOU, A, TELL THEM, OR B,
WHISTLE WHILE THEY MAKE A QUICK
EXIT.
THAT'S WRONG!
YOU NEED TO TELL SOMEONE PEERED
WHICH ARE NOT?
>> I HAD A SITUATION...
THERE WAS A WOMAN IN THE
BATHROOM.
IT WAS A LONG PAPER TRAIL, AND I
SAID --
>> Kelly: HOW DOES THAT
HAPPEN?
>> DON'T ASK.
I SAID, EXCUSE ME, YOU GOT SOME
FOR THE PAPER HANGING.
SHE SAID, OH, CAN YOU GET IT?
AND I'M LIKE, I SAY TO THEM,
LARRY DAVID MODE, I'M LIKE, NO.
I CAN'T.
>> Kelly:
MY FRIEND WAS LIKE, YOU TOILETP.
>> Kelly: I DEFTLY WOULD'VE
SAID HARD PASS ON THAT ONE.
>> IS IT BAD I GET A LOT OF GLEE
TELLING SOMEONE, YOU'VE GOT
TOILET PAPER COMING OUT OF YOUR
PANTS?
HEY, GIRL!
>> Kelly: I'M TOTALLY THE
PERSON TO TELL YOU IF YOU HAVE A
BOOGER, ZIPPER IS DOWN.
IF THAT HAPPENED TO ME, I GET
RIGHT UP STATE FROM RESENTING AN
AWARD OR SOMETHING AND I'M,
LIKE, HAVE SPINACH -- SOME TYPE
OF SUGAR, IT'S NOT SPINACH.
I HAVE SOMETHING IN MY TEETH,
WHO DIDN'T TELL ME THAT?
I WAS ON NATIONAL TELEVISION!
THOSE ARE JERKS.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
WE!
WE HAVE ONE MORE.
I'M RON BURGUNDY.
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT, DID IT?
ALL RIGHT, RENEE HAS SOMETHING
SHE WANTS TO TELL HAS HUSBAND.
>> SURPRISE!
>> WE WENT ON A BLIND DATE, WE
GOT MARRIED.
WE HAVE OUR FIVE BEAUTIFUL
CHILDREN, THREE GRANDCHILDREN.
AND OUR SON WHO HAD TWO HEART
TRANSPLANTS AND LYMPHOMA.
AND SAT BY OUR SIDE WHEN OUR
SIDE AND TOOK HIS BREATH AND WE
SAT THERE THE HOSPITAL AND WE
WERE THERE TOGETHER.
WITH OUR FAMILY AND OUR
CHILDREN.
AND TO ME, YOU ARE ALWAYS THE
BEST PERSON WHO I KNEW, I THINK
I CAN COUNT ON YOU.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR OUR JOURNEY TO
CONTINUE WITH OUR GRANDCHILDREN
AND JUST THE MANY THINGS THAT'LL
BE GOING ON IN OUR LIFE.
I JUST LOVE YOU WITH ALL MY
HEART AND I THANK YOU SO MUCH
AND I'M GLAD -- I KNOW
I HOPE THIS WAS AN EXPERIENCE...
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THAT'S A LOT OF
HURDLES.
WOW.
YOU'VE CLEARLY GONE THROUGH A
LOT TOGETHER.
I CAN IMAGINE HOW MUCH THIS
MOMENT MIGHT MEAN FOR BOTH OF
YOU.
THAT'S A LOT OF HARDSHIP PLACED
ON NOT ONLY JUST ONE PERSON BUT
A COUPLE TO GET THROUGH.
WE WANT TO HELP RENEE AND CHUCK
AND ENJOY MORE EXPERIENCES
TOGETHER SO WE ARE SENDING THEM
TO
NESTLED ON ONE OF THE MOST
STUNNING BEACHES IN THE
CARIBBEAN.
DIRECT ACCESS TO THE OCEAN BELOW
IT, THIS EXCLUSIVE ADULT ONLY
EXPERIENCE EVEN INCLUDES BUTLER
SERVICE.
SO Y'ALL ENJOY.
EVERYBODY LOVES A LAW LOVE BOMB.
USE THE HASHTAG #LoveBomb.
YOU'LL MEET ONE INCREDIBLE
ORGANIZATION IN HOUSTON MAKING
LIVES EASIER FOR SINGLE MOMS IN
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT'S AMAZING.
STAY TUNED.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
I need every sports channel
possible.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios
with internet starting at just
$39.99 per month.
Plus, you'll get up to $200 in
Visa prepaid cards
based on the plans you pick.
Eso existe? Los necesitamos.
Want internet? Pick your speed.
Want just TV? Pick the plan
that's right for you
No two households are the same,
so no two plans should be the
same.
We should get what we want.
And now, no matter what you
choose,
you get a year of Disney+ on us.
Boom! Sign me up.
I love that.
Finally, get internet and TV
your way
with internet starting at $39.99
per month -
no extra fees, no annual
contracts.
No surprises on my cable bill?
I'll take that.
Finally! Plans that just make
sense.
Mix and match your perfect Fios
plan and pay for what you want.
Only on Verizon.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL.
WELCOME BACK.
YOU ARE LOOKING AT ONE MY
FAVORITE CITIES, HOUSTON, TEXAS.
I PERFORM THERE MANY TIMES AND
THE PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS
INCREDIBLE.
I'M HERE WITH JESSE TYLER
FERGUSON AND CHERYL HINES.
AND EVERYTHING IS BIGGER IN
TEXAS, SERIOUSLY.
HOUSTON IS ONE OF THE LARGEST
METRO AREAS IN THE COUNTRY.
CARS ARE ESSENTIAL AND NOT
HAVING ONE COULD BE
DEBILITATING, ESPECIALLY FOR
SINGLE MOTHERS.
FORTUNATELY THERE IS AN
ORGANIZATION JUST OUTSIDE
HOUSTON THAT MAKES A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> REPAIR AND GIFT VEHICLES FOR
SINGLE MOMS AND WIVES OF
DEPLOYED MILITARY.
>> THE LADIES COME TO US LOOKING
FOR AN OPPORTUNITY TO BETTER OUR
LIVES AND THEY WANT TO BETTER
THEIR CHILDREN'S LIVES AS WELL.
I GET ABOUT 30 APPLICATIONS A
DAY.
I HAVE 2500 LADIES WAITING ON
THE LIST.
IT'S ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF TO
A TWO-YEAR WEIGHT.
>> MY FAVORITE PART IS WORKING
WITH THE VOLUNTEERS HERE.
WE HAVE A WIDE VARIETY OF
VOLUNTEERS.
CHEMICAL ENGINEERS, WE HAVE
PILOTS, FIREFIGHTERS, POLICE
OFFICERS.
WE HAVE PEOPLE WORKING AT
DEALERSHIPS FOR 20 YEARS.
CERTIFIED MECHANIC.
YOUNG PEOPLE, THEY COME HERE AND
LEARN HOW TO DIP DOWN TO PREPARE
DIFFERENT THINGS AND IT'S JUST
WONDERFUL.
THIS IS THE MOST FULFILLING
THING I'VE EVER DONE IN MY LIFE.
>> THERE IS A COMMUNITY HERE,
THAT'S REALLY OUTSTANDING.
>> IT'S ABOUT PEOPLE AND PEOPLE
HELPING PEOPLE.
AND SHOWING THAT LOVE TO ONE
ANOTHER.
>> Kelly: PLEASE WELCOME
HARVEY, KARINA, AND JAMES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SO, HARVEY, YOU ARE ONE OF THE
FOUNDERS OF GOD'S GARAGE.
WHAT INSPIRED IT.
HOW DID YOU COME UP WITH THIS
IDEA?
IT'S SPECIFIC.
>> IT IS BIT I LIKE TO TELL
EVERYBODY IT STARTED WITH A
SIMPLE ACT OF KINDNESS.
THERE WAS A LADY AND A LITTLE
GIRL IN MONTGOMERY TEXAS, IT WAS
NIGHTTIME.
SHE WAS WALKING DOWN THE
HIGHWAY.
THE YOUTH PASTOR ACTUALLY SAW
HER WALKING.
HE PICKED HER UP TO TAKE HER
HOME.
HOW ARE YOU GETTING TO THE GOLD
DOWN THE GROCERY STORE, TAKING
YOUR KIDS TO SCHOOL, SHE TOLD
HIM THE TRUCK HAD BEEN IN THE
REPAIR SHOP FOR THREE MONTHS.
AND SHE DIDN'T HAVE MONEY FOR
REPAIRS.
THAT'S WHAT INSPIRED GOD'S
GARAGE.
>> Kelly: WHAT A GREAT, GREAT
THING.
CHEERS
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I'M SO HAPPY.
I HAVE NOT BEEN TO TEXAS IN A
WHILE AND YOUR ACCENT IS GIVING
ME ALL THE FIELDS.
I'M SO HAPPY AND I SLIGHTLY WANT
TO CRY.
IT'S FINE.
I MISS HOME!
KARINA, YOU WORK WITH THE WOMEN
AND WHAT YOU NOTICE ABOUT THEM?
>> LADIES COME FROM ALL
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS.
IT MAY BE GENERATION AFTER
GENERATION.
SOME OF THESE LADIES ACTUALLY
COME FROM GOOD FAMILIES BUT THEY
MADE A BAD MISTAKE.
THEY AREN'T ASKING FOR A
HANDOUT, THEY ARE ASKING FOR A
BOOST.
SHARED IT WITH ME THAT SHE
WALKED DOWN THE FREEWAY WITH HER
SMALL CHILDREN TO TAKE IT TO THE
BUS, TAKE IT TO THE DOCTOR, SHE
WOULD FEAR FOR HER LIFE AND HER
CHILDREN'S LIVES OF GETTING HIT
BY A CAR.
THEY ARE JUST LOOKING JUST A
BIT.
>> Kelly: YOU ARE THERE TO
GIVE IT TO THEM FOR THAT SO
MAGICAL.
THESE CARS, THEY ARE NOT FANCY.
>> THESE CARS ARE NOT FANCY.
PEOPLE HAD THESE CARS, NOW THEY
DECIDE TO GET IT TO THE GARAGE,
PRAISE GOD FOR THAT.
WE HAVE A GROUP OF VOLUNTEERS,
YOUNG, OLD, MIDDLE AGE PEOPLE
AND WORKS WITH THOSE CARS.
THAT TAKES 2-3 WEEKS TO PROCESS
THESE CARS BECAUSE THEY ARE
10-15 YEARS OLD.
SOME OF THEM TAKE A LITTLE BIT
OF WORK.
WITH THAT, WE JUST DO OUR DUE
DILIGENCE AND WE GO THROUGH IT
FOR THE YOUNG FOLKS, THE ONES
WHO MAY OR MAY NOT, WE GET THESE
VEHICLES DONE.
A SAFE ARRIVAL FOR THESE LADIES
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT WE WANT TO,
FOR THEM TO FEEL SAFE.
>> Kelly: CAN Y'ALL IMAGINE
BEING IN A STATE LIKE IN MEXICO,
NEW JERSEY AND YOU DON'T HAVE A
CAR?
YOU SHOULD SEE ME AT
THANKSGIVING AND CHRISTMAS WITH
ALCOHOL.
IT'S LIKE...
IT'S BAD.
BUT YOU KNOW?
>> WE COULDN'T DO OUR JOB
WITHOUT CARS.
>> BEING A PARENT, YOUR SPOTS
ABILITY IS TO TAKE CARE OF YOUR
CHILD.
DOCTORS APPOINTMENTS, SCHOOL,
GROCERY STORES.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Kelly: IT'S REALLY AMAZING
WHAT YOU ARE DOING.
COMING UP, WE HAVE A MOM FROM
HOUSTON WHO HAS BEEN ON A
WAITING LIST FOR CARS FROM GOD'S
GARAGE.
SHE THINKS SHE'S HERE TO SHARE
HER STORY.
CHECK THIS OUT THERE THERE'S
ALREADY A CAR WAITING FOR HER
BACK IN TEXAS AND WE ARE GOING
TO SURPRISE HER.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO WANT TO
MISS THIS.
(Professor)
Sound power is defined as
thought a surface
the product of sound pressure
and a component of the partial
velocity at a point.
[Sounds]
Kazoo sound
♪
(phone alarm beeps)
How do you become the YOU
you dream of being?
You just have to say yes.
Yes to finishing strong.
Yes to staying in the zone.
And yes to picture perfect
penguin cakes.
Yes.
Ugh, Yes.
And, oh boy, yes to that too,
I guess. I don't know.
More? Wow. I mean, yes...
seriously though.
Do you really want
to do all of this?
No.
(phone alarm beeps)
That's it.
No!
You NO girl!
Whoa! Someone could have
eaten that, but whatever.
Let them hear that no.
Because, no is beautiful.
At Pure Leaf, we believe
NO makes life better.
After all, it works
pretty well for our tea.
No Artificial Sweeteners.
No Artificial Flavors.
No Extra Stuff.
Pure Leaf.
No is beautiful.
This home is equipped with Gig
Speed Internet from Xfinity.
There's this game-time
Internetting room. So fun.
And then there's this work
-from-home Internetting room.
Finally, the open-concept
Internetting room.
This is not an open house.
But your front door was open,
so technically it is.
Get gig speed and the
coverage you need with Xfinity
Now that's simple,
easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get $100
back with this great offer.
Plus, get a free
upgrade to Gig speed.
That's a savings of
$360. Switch today.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT.
I'M BACK WITH JESSE TYLER
FERGUSON, CHERYL HINES!
>> GIRLS, IT'S LIKE I'M IN
TIMEOUT.
THAT'S LIKELY YOU ARE IN
>> Kelly: YOU SMELLED AND I
WANTED TO GET AWAY FROM YOU...
NO.
JOINING US ARE HARVEY, KARINA,
JAMES, THE TEAM FROM GOD'S
GARAGE THAT DONATES CARS TO
MOTHERS.
MY NEXT GUEST, Y'ALL, IS ON THE
WAITING LIST FOR ONE OF THOSE
CARS.
PLEASE WELCOME MELINDA.
YOU ARE FROM HOUSTON.
WE ARE BOTH TEXAS GIRLS.
WHAT IS IT LIKE.
WHAT IS A DAY LIKE FOR YOU?
BEING A MAMA IN THAT HE WITHOUT
A CAR?
>> THAT'S HARD WORK, YOU KNOW?
JUST HAVING TO TIME MANAGE
EVERYTHING, GOING TO COLLEGE AND
GOING TO SCHOOL.
I HAVE A THREE YEAR OLD -- I'M
SORRY, SHE'S TWO.
MY 5-YEAR-OLD ALSO HAS ADHD, AND
MY DAUGHTER IS 13.
WANTS TO BE A PART OF A LOT OF
ACTIVITIES AND STUFF AND IT'S
HARD NOT HAVING CARS.
>> Kelly: THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE
WITHOUT A CAR.
MY GOSH.
I ALSO HEARD THAT I READ LAST
NIGHT AND I WAS FEELING FOR YOU
BECAUSE YOU KIND OF HAD A HARD
START.
>> I DID.
I HAD A ROUGH BRINGING UP BUT
THANK GOD FOR MY MENTOR.
SHE WAS A MOTHER FIGURING SO I'M
THANKFUL I HAD SOME TYPE OF
GUIDANCE.
BUT THOSE OTHER PEOPLE TO LEARN
FROM AND THE LIFE CHOICES I WISH
I WOULD'VE MADE AT A YOUNG AGE.
THANK GOD THAT I'M STILL
PERSEVERING, NOT ALLOWING MY
MISTAKES DEFINE WHO I AM.
EXACTLY.
WE ALL HAVE MISTAKES, WE ALL
HAVE BAGGAGE.
>> Kelly: THIS IS INCREDIBLY
CRUEL OF THE UNIVERSE, BUT YOU
LOST TWO HOMES.
TELL US ABOUT THE FIRST ONE.
>> THE FIRST ONE HAPPENED 2015.
IT WAS A FIRE.
WE WERE STARTING TO BUILD OUR
LIFE BACK AND WE MOVED INTO A
DIFFERENT LOCATION.
AND THEN HARVEY CAME.
THAT HURRICANE, LIKE, REALLY
DESTROYED MY FOUNDATION.
BUT GOD IS SO GOOD, BECAUSE HE
BRINGS PEOPLE IN YOUR LIFE.
THE REASON I EVEN GOT IN CONTACT
WITH GOD'S GARAGE, I WAITED, I
WASN'T, LIKE, RUSHING INTO
THINGS.
BUT HE GOT TO THE POINT WHERE MY
OLDEST, I WANT HER TO HAVE --
YOU KNOW, NOT WORRYING ABOUT
WHO'S GOING TO BE THERE.
OR MY SON, HE SEES THERAPISTS, I
HAVE TO REARRANGE MY WHOLE LIFE
TO GET HIM AT THE DAY CARE.
TO TAKE HIM WHERE HE NEEDS TO
GO.
THEY DON'T LOVE THEIR JOB, YOU
HAVE TO, YOU KNOW...
>> Kelly: WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
THE RESILIENCE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: YOU ARE QUITE A
WOMAN.
I LOVE TEXAS WOMEN.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I LOVE
ABOUT TEXAS WOMEN, WE ARE THE
ONE STANDING IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE STORM SAYING, BRING ME MORE!
YOU ARE LIKE "THE TRUMAN STORM"
IN THAT STORM
I'M SURE THERE ARE SOME WOMEN,
I'M SURE, BUT WE DO HAVE A
SURPRISE FOR YOU.
SHE'S BEEN WAITING ON A CAR,
KNOWS IT'S GOING TO BE A WILD.
LET'S GO BACK TO DONNELLY
DONNA LEE.
WOULD YOU HAVE THERE?
>> I'M HERE WITH TAD, LAVINA AND
ALL THE AMAZING VOLUNTEERS FROM
GOD'S GARAGE BUT GUESS WHAT,
THEY HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
YOU GUYS READY TO DO THE BIG
REVEAL?
LET'S REVEAL IT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: TELL US ABOUT THE
CAR.
>> IT'S A 2005 NISSAN ALTIMA.
IT HAS WANTED 50,000 MILES BUT I
HAND
WE MADE SURE IT SUPER SAFE AND
RELIABLE AND IT'S GOING TO GET
YOU TO WHERE YOU NEED TO BE WITH
THIS CAR.
>> NO MORE DO YOU HAVE TO WALK,
BEG, BORROW TO GO TO PLACES FOR
YOUR CHILDREN CAN GO TO THE
DOCTOR, YOU CAN GO TO SCHOOLS
AND EVERYTHING.
GOOD THINGS ARE HAPPENING NOW.
>> THAT'S VERY TRUE.
>> Kelly: THAT'S NOT ALL.
WE HAVE ANOTHER SURPRISE.
WHETHER YOU'RE ON THE GO, AT
WORK, ANYWHERE IN BETWEEN, THEY
HAVE THE EVERYDAY NECESSITY TO
GET YOU THROUGH THE DAY AND THEY
ARE HELPING MELINDA GET GAS FOR
A WHOLE YEAR!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I'M JUST SAYING.
BECAUSE A GAS BILL IS VERY
EXPENSIVE.
THAT'S NOT IT, EITHER.
THE MISSION IS TO MAKE THE BEST
STROLLERS, JUVENILE GEAR OUT
THERE WITH FEATURES EVERY PARENT
WOULD WANT PURE THEY ARE ALSO
COMMITTED TO GIVING BACK AND
PROVIDING SAFE TRANSPORT FOR
FAMILIES, SO THEY ARE HOOKING
UP WITH TWO BABY CAR SEATS, YOU
DON'T GOT THE PAPER THAT!
WHAT DO YOU SAY!
>> THANK YOU, KELLY.
>> Kelly: THANK YOU!
>> I'M SO THANKFUL.
>> WE KNOW THERE ARE GREAT
THINGS IN YOUR FUTURE AND WE
HOPE THIS VEHICLE IS A STEP UP
TO MAKE A BETTER LIFE FOR YOU
AND YOUR CHILDREN.
>> ONCE I GET MY VOLUNTEER AND
STUFF ON COMING BACK TO GOD'S
GARAGE VOLUNTEERING.
>> Kelly: PEOPLE OUT THERE, IF
YOU HAVE A CAR YOU WANT TO
DONATE, PLEASE DO.
THIS COULD CHANGE SOMEONE'S LIFE
FOREVER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH TO GOD'S
GARAGE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK WITH A
MUSICAL PERFORMANCE FROM P.J.
MORTON.
With this one little
NexGard chew
comes the confidence,
you're doing what's right,
to protect your dog
from fleas and ticks
for a full month.
It's the #1 Vet recommended
protection.
And it's safe for puppies.
NexGard.
What one little chew can do.
Working with Mike
Bloomberg was one of
the most empowering
experiences that I've had.
It's important to talk to the
people who know him personally.
I worked for him for
8 years in City Hall.
I've been working for
Bloomberg for 27 years.
25 years.
Almost 30 years.
There's nobody that
I respect more,
and felt more
respected by.
Mike believes
excellence
is not defined by gender.
Mike builds a culture
that advances women.
I was the first woman
ever appointed
to be council
to the Mayor.
He expects excellence
out of everyone,
but he also provides
the kind of support
that allows you to
be that person.
Mike called to tell me,
you should be proud of
what you've done
and your name should be
on that project.
He has faith in you,
he believes in you.
It was about always showing
up and doing your best.
I always knew that
he had my back.
He was raised by an
extraordinary woman,
she supported him
all along the way
and that's very much
a part of who he is.
Mike supports women,
he promotes women, and
he respects women.
>> Kelly: GUYS, WELCOME BACK.
THIS GUY I GOT WITH ME RIGHT NOW
IS AN INCREDIBLE MUSICIAN WHO'S
PLAYED WITH MAROON 5 FOR THE
LAST DECADE AND WHOSE WON A
GRAMMY FOR HIS WORK ON HIS
ALBUM "PAUL."
PLEASE HELP ME WELCOMING IN P.J.
MORTON!
IT'S AWESOME TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WE GOT TO BE ON THE SAME TOUR.
I REMEMBER TELLING, WHO IS THAT
GUY?
HE'S INSANE.
YOU ARE SO TALENTED.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Kelly: YOU JUST WON YOUR
SECOND GRAMMY BECAUSE I HEARD
YOUR LITTLE GIRL WAS WITH YOU.
>> THAT MADE THE WHOLE
EXPERIENCE AMAZING.
I HAD MY LITTLE 7-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER WITH ME AND WE HAPPENED
TO WIN, BUT --
>> Kelly: IT'S JUST ALL RIGHT
FOR FOR ME.
>> IT'S TRUE BUT I GOT TO BRING
HER UP THERE AND GIVE HER THE
EXPERIENCE, THE SPEECH WITH MY
LITTLE GIRL RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
THAT MADE IT SO SPECIAL.
>> Kelly: WHAT'S THE STORY
BEHIND YOUR LATEST ALBUM.
YOU DECIDED TO CALL IT PAUL.
>> I'VE BEEN CALLED P.J. MY
WHOLE LIFE.
MY FAMILY HAS ALWAYS CALLED ME
P.J.
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE THAT I WAS
NOT TRYING TO CHASE ANYTHING BUT
THE PUREST FORM OF WHO I AM AND
I FEEL LIKE I CAME INTO THE
WORLD AS PAUL AND I FELT LIKE
IT'S THE PERFECT TITLE FOR THE
VULNERABILITIES.
>> Kelly: IT'S INTIMATE.
I LIKE YOU PERSONALIZED IT.
ESPECIALLY FOR FANS, THIS IS
REALLY HIM.
THAT'S AWESOME.
SO PERFORMING "READY" OFF HIS
ALBUM "PAUL," GIVE IT UP FOR
P.J. MORTON!
♪ ♪
>> YOU'RE READY TO HAVE A GOOD
TIME WITH ME?
♪
♪ SAY YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ GIRL, LET ME TAKE YOU ON A
JOURNEY ♪
♪ LET ME BE YOUR MAN ♪
♪ I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOME THINGS
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE ♪
♪ I KNOW IT'S JUST A THOUGHT BUT
I PROMISE THERE IS MUCH MORE ♪
♪ JUST COME WITH ME ♪
♪ I DON'T WANT TO PLAY AROUND
ANYMORE ♪
♪ I KNOW THERE'S NO DOUBT FOR
ME ♪
♪ THAT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ BABY, WON'T YOU TRY ME ♪
♪ I'M PUTTING THE BALL IN YOUR
COURT ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ GIRL, LET'S JUST ♪
♪ WE AIN'T GOT TO WAIT ♪
♪ WE CAN JUST GO STEADY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT ♪
♪ GIRL, LET'S GET READY ♪
♪ WE AIN'T GOT TO WAIT NO TIME ♪
♪ WE CAN JUST GO STEADY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT ♪
♪ OKAY, I ADMIT IT ♪
♪ GIVE ME A MINUTE TO GET IT ♪
♪ BUT NOW I'VE GOT IT ♪
♪ AND I DON'T WANT TO BE WITHOUT
IT ♪
♪ SO PLEASE DON'T LET GO ♪
♪ I PROMISE I WON'T EVER LET YOU
HURT NO MORE ♪
♪ ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS COME WITH
ME, GIRL ♪
♪ GIRL, I DON'T WANT TO PLAY
AROUND ANYMORE ♪
♪ I KNOW THERE'S NO ONE ELSE FOR
ME, THAT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ BABY, WANT TO TRY MEET ♪
♪ I'M PUTTING THE BALL IN YOUR
COURT ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ GIRL, IF YOU'RE READY ♪
♪ GET READY ♪
♪ AIN'T GOT A WASTE NO TIME ♪
♪ WE CAN JUST GO STEADY ♪
♪ YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU
WANT. ♪
♪ GIRL LET'S GET READY ♪
♪ AIN'T WASTE NO TIME ♪
♪ WE CAN GO STEADY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT ♪
♪ GIRL, LET'S GET READY ♪
♪ WE AIN'T GONNA WASTE NO TIME ♪
♪ WE CAN GO STEADY ♪
♪ WE CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YEAH.
>> Kelly: YOU HAVE THE BEST
SMILE.
THE BEST SMILE.
ONE MORE TIME FOR P.J. MORTON,
Y'ALL!
LATEST ALBUM, RIGHT OUT NOW.
WHEN WE COME BACK, TELL YOU WHAT
I'M LIKING.
GET IN ON THE BANDWAGON!
COME ON.
IT'S SO GOOD...
Young Man: Thanks for having
us this weekend Mrs. Garcy
Young Woman: Yeah, thanks Mom
Mother: Of course and
I love these flowers
Young Woman whispering: Hey, did
you bring the... the condoms?
Young Man whispering: What's up?
Young Woman whispering: Condoms
Young Man whispering: What?
Young Woman whispering: Condom
Father: Condoms Charlie.
She wants to know if
you brought any condoms.
Young Man: Yeah I brought some.
Announcer: Eargo, a virtually
invisible hearing loss
solution with high quality sound
and lifetime support.
If your a current or retired
federal employee
you could get Eargo at no cost
to you.
Simply call 800-EARGO-54
to hear more.
Eargo, hear life to the fullest.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT!
WELCOME BACK.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO BREAK DOWN
THE COOLEST OF THE COOL ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
THIS IS CALLED WHAT I'M LIKING.
WE ARE HEADING BACK TO THE GREAT
STATE OF TEXAS WHERE ONE BAKER
HAS CUSTOMIZED LITERALLY EATING
HER WORDS.
THAT'S BECAUSE SHE'S COMBINED
TWO OF THE GREATEST THINGS,
COOKIES AND INTERNET MEMES.
CHECK THIS OUT.
I'M TORN BETWEEN WANTING A SNACK
AND LOOKING LIKE ONE.
GIRL, PLEASE...
I'VE HAD MY PATIENTS TESTED, I'M
NEGATIVE.
HALEY CALLAWAY'S COOKIES ARE
SUCH A HIT.
SHE'S ATTRACTED NEARLY TWO EUROS
AND 50,000 FOLLOWERS ON
INSTAGRAM
350,000 FOLLOWERS ON INSTAGRAM.
LET'S CALL HER UP ON SKYPE RIGHT
NOW.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU ARE HILARIOUS
BUT HOW DID YOU COME UP WITH ALL
THESE LITTLE THINGS?
>> MAN...
WE ARE A FAMILY BUSINESS SO I
HAVE TWO OLDER BROTHERS REALLY
CRAZY AND SOMETIMES MY MOM OR MY
GRANDMA, THEY HAVE FUNNY IDEAS.
ALWAYS JUST MAKING FUN OF EACH
OTHER.
>> Kelly: I LOVE YOUR FAMILY
ALREADY.
HOW MUCH TIME DOES IT TAKE TO
MAKE ONE COOKIE?
>> ANYWHERE FROM 10 MINUTES FOR
SIMPLE COOKIE -- THAT'S
DEPENDING IF YOU MESS IT UP AND
START ALL OVER.
I GOT ONE THAT'S FULL OF TACOS
INSTEAD OF EMOTION, A LITTLE
CHOCO COOKIE.
>> Kelly: THAT'S MY FAVORITE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COOKIES
AND FUNNY.
I'M GOING TO LIKE YOUR POST
RIGHT NOW!
THANK YOU TO ALL MY GUESTS,
JESSE TYLER FERGUSON, CHERYL
HINES, HARVEY, KARINA, JAMES,
ALL OUR FRIENDS IN HOUSTON, AND
A BIG SHOUT OUT TO DONNA LEE
KEITH, A GREAT DAY.
♪ ♪
♪♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO WALKS
ACROSS THE FIRE FOR YOU ♪
♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO WILL
DROWN IN MY DESIRES FOR YOU ♪
♪ IT'S ONLY FAIR THAT MAKES YOU
RUN ♪
♪ THE DEMONS THAT YOU'RE HIDING
FROM ♪
♪ WHEN ALL YOUR PROMISES ARE
GONE ♪
♪ I'M THE ONLY ONE ♪♪
Working with Mike
Bloomberg was one of
the most empowering
experiences that I've had.
It's important to talk to the
people who know him personally.
I worked for him for
8 years in City Hall.
I've been working for
Bloomberg for 27 years.
25 years.
Almost 30 years.
There's nobody that
I respect more,
and felt more
respected by.
Mike believes
excellence
is not defined by gender.
Mike builds a culture
that advances women.
I was the first woman
ever appointed
to be council
to the Mayor.
He expects excellence
out of everyone,
but he also provides
the kind of support
that allows you to
be that person.
Mike called to tell me,
you should be proud of
what you've done
and your name should be
on that project.
He has faith in you,
he believes in you.
It was about always showing
up and doing your best.
I always knew that
he had my back.
He was raised by an
extraordinary woman,
she supported him
all along the way
and that's very much
a part of who he is.
Mike supports women,
he promotes women, and
he respects women.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: HERE SHE IS
NOW, ELLEN DeGENERES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪