♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
♪ ♪
I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> Ellen: THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVERYBODY.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I'M SO HAPPY. YOU WANT, REALLY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVERYBODY.
I KEEP ON SAYING THAT WE WILL
I'M SO HAPPY. YOU WANT, REALLY.
HAVE A STANDINGECTION AND AXT YD
I KEEP ON SAYING THAT WE WILL
I WANT TO ABOUT THE JOBS
HAVE A STANDINGECTION AND AXT YD
IT CAN BEUN TO LOOK BACK ON
I WANT TO ABOUT THE JOBS
WHERE YOU HAVE COME FROM.
IT CAN BEUN TO LOOK BACK ON
IT ALSO CAN BE TERRIFYING,
WHERE YOU HAVE COME FROM.
BECAUSE RECENTLY MY WRITERS
IT ALSO CAN BE TERRIFYING,
UNEARTHED A POPEYES COMMERCIAL
BECAUSE RECENTLY MY WRITERS
THAT I WAS IN WHEN I WAS 18.
UNEARTHED A POPEYES COMMERCIAL
I DON'T KNOW HOW OLD I WAS.
THAT I WAS IN WHEN I WAS 18.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW OLD I WAS.
AND THERE IS NO NEED TO SHOW IT,
I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT IT.
BUT I WAS IN THE COMMERCIAL.
AND THERE IS NO NEED TO SHOW IT,
>> WE HAVE IT.
BUT I WAS IN THE COMMERCIAL.
>> Ellen: I KNOW YOU HAVE IT,
>> WE HAVE IT.
ANDY.
>> Ellen: I KNOW YOU HAVE IT,
>> LET'S JUST SHOW IT.
ANDY.
THEY WANT TO SEE IT.
>> LET'S JUST SHOW IT.
>> Ellen: THEY DO NOT WANT TO
THEY WANT TO SEE IT.
SEE IT.
>> Ellen: THEY DO NOT WANT TO
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SEE IT.
>> ROLL IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IT'S A SURPRISE.
>> ROLL IT.
>> I CAN'T STAND IT.
>> IT'S A SURPRISE.
I HAVE TO HAVE IT.
>> I CAN'T STAND IT.
♪ THE JUNK FROM POPEYES ♪
I HAVE TO HAVE IT.
♪ FILL YOUR SUMMER REFILLS ALL
♪ THE JUNK FROM POPEYES ♪
SUMMER LONG ♪
♪ FILL YOUR SUMMER REFILLS ALL
>> Ellen: IT IS WONDERFUL, IT
SUMMER LONG ♪
IS JUST CRAZY!
>> Ellen: IT IS WONDERFUL, IT
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IS JUST CRAZY!
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
LISTEN, I DID A COMMERCIAL FOR
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
POPEYES AND NOW THERE IS A LINE
LISTEN, I DID A COMMERCIAL FOR
FOR THEIR SANDWICHES,
POPEYES AND NOW THERE IS A LINE
COINCIDENCE?
FOR THEIR SANDWICHES,
YES, IT IS.
COINCIDENCE?
I'VE DONE A LOT OF DIFFERENT
YES, IT IS.
THINGS IN MY CAREER, BUT THE
I'VE DONE A LOT OF DIFFERENT
PROBLEM IS I DO NOT REMEMBER A
THINGS IN MY CAREER, BUT THE
LOT OF THEM OR ANY OF THEM.
PROBLEM IS I DO NOT REMEMBER A
OR ANY OF THEM.
LOT OF THEM OR ANY OF THEM.
BUT THEY ARE ALL ON TAPE.
OR ANY OF THEM.
SO JUST FOR FUN, AND TO TEST MY
BUT THEY ARE ALL ON TAPE.
MEMORY, IT IS A NEW GAME WE ARE
SO JUST FOR FUN, AND TO TEST MY
CALLING "WAS I IN THAT."
MEMORY, IT IS A NEW GAME WE ARE
♪ ♪
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
IF YOU SEE YOUR NAME ON THE
SCREEN, COME ON DOWN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: HI, YOU TWO, ONE OF
YOU IS ALICIA, THE OTHER IS
DIANE.
>> I AM ALICIA.
>> Ellen: AND DIANE, YOU LIVE
IN PHOENIX.
YOU ARE BOUNCY, BOTH OF YOU.
BOUNCY AND SPONGY.
IT IS FINE.
NO RULES HERE AT ALL.
HERE'S HOW THE GAME WORKS.
WE WILL SHOW, A MOVIE, A TV
SHOW, A COMMERCIAL.
A SEGMENT WILL POP UP ON THE
SCREEN AND WE WILL GUESS IF I
HAVE BEEN IN IT.
YOU MAY THINK THIS IS UNFAIR
BECAUSE I HAVE AN ADVANTAGE, BUT
I AM MORE LIKE DORY THAN YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW.
[LAUGHTER]
I REALLY HAVE NO MEMORY.
THIS IS A FUN GAME FOR ALL OF
US.
I THINK.
LET'S SEE.
"SESAME STREET."
ALL RIGHT, ALICIA, ARE YOU GOING
TO GUESS?
I WILL LET YOU GUESS FIRST.
>> YOU WERE NOT IN THAT.
>> Ellen: NOT IN
"SESAME STREET."
>> YOU WERE IN "SESAME STREET."
>> Ellen: DID YOU SEE ME ON
IT?
>> YES.
>> Ellen: I WILL AGREE WITH
YOU.
THAT'S HOW I AM GOING TO FOLLOW
EVERYBODY ELSE'S LEAD.
YOU SAW ME?
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
I WAS ON "SESAME STREET."
>> HI, ELLEN.
HI.
>> Ellen: OH, HI, ELMO, DID
YOU HEAR THAT?
>> WHAT?
>> Ellen: ELLEN AND ELMO.
THEY ARE SORT OF THE SAME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I WAS ON "SESAME STREET."
WOW.
AND YET YOU REMEMBER THAT.
LET'S SEE ANOTHER ONE.
GOD, WHAT DO YOU THINK, ALICIA?
>> I'M GOING TO GO AGAIN WITH
NO.
>> Ellen: AND STICK WITH THE
HAVE I BEEN IN THAT?
NO.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HAVE I BEEN IN THAT?
I'M GOING TO GO WITH NO.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> Ellen: IT SOUNDS REALLY
I'M GOING TO GO WITH NO.
FAMILIAR TO ME, AND I REALLY
>> Ellen: IT SOUNDS REALLY
DON'T REMEMBER DOING COMMERCIALS
FAMILIAR TO ME, AND I REALLY
EXCEPT FOR THE RECENT ONES THAT
DON'T REMEMBER DOING COMMERCIALS
I HAVE DONE.
EXCEPT FOR THE RECENT ONES THAT
BUT I THINK I HAVE, I FEEL LIKE
I HAVE DONE.
I'VE DONE DONE THAT.
BUT I THINK I HAVE, I FEEL LIKE
LET'S SEE.
I'VE DONE DONE THAT.
HELLO, VERY FINE.
LET'S SEE.
IT IS 64 OUNCES.
HELLO, VERY FINE.
WELL, I SUPPOSE SO.
IT IS 64 OUNCES.
YOU COULD LIFT WEIGHTS WITH IT.
WELL, I SUPPOSE SO.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU COULD LIFT WEIGHTS WITH IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I HAVE DONE THAT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IS THAT COMPANY STILL AROUND?
>> Ellen: I HAVE DONE THAT.
DO WE KNOW?
IS THAT COMPANY STILL AROUND?
IT IS?
DO WE KNOW?
AND THEY LET ME GO?
IT IS?
[LAUGHTER]
AND THEY LET ME GO?
APPARENTLY I DID NOT DO A
[LAUGHTER]
GOOD JOB.
APPARENTLY I DID NOT DO A
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE ANOTHER
GOOD JOB.
ONE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE ANOTHER
ALICIA, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ONE.
NOW?
ALICIA, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
>> I'M GOING TO STICK WITH THE
NOW?
NO.
>> I'M GOING TO STICK WITH THE
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, DIANE,
NO.
HAVE I DONE THIS?
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, DIANE,
>> I THINK YOU HAVE.
HAVE I DONE THIS?
>> Ellen: I DON'T THINK SO.
>> I THINK YOU HAVE.
THIS IS THE ONE THAT I FEEL
>> Ellen: I DON'T THINK SO.
STRONGLY I DID NOT DO.
THIS IS THE ONE THAT I FEEL
>> YOU CAN DIAL 1-800 BULLET.
STRONGLY I DID NOT DO.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
>> YOU CAN DIAL 1-800 BULLET.
1-800 BULLET.
HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
YEAH, I JUST SAVED YOU SOME
1-800 BULLET.
CASH.
YEAH, I JUST SAVED YOU SOME
YOU'RE WELCOME.
CASH.
>> Ellen: YES, THAT IS DAVID
YOU'RE WELCOME.
SPADE.
>> Ellen: YES, THAT IS DAVID
THAT IS NOT ME.
SPADE.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT IS NOT ME.
PEOPLE CONFUSE DAVID SPADE AND
[APPLAUSE]
ME A LOT.
PEOPLE CONFUSE DAVID SPADE AND
BUT THAT IS NOT ME.
ME A LOT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE ANOTHER
BUT THAT IS NOT ME.
ONE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE ANOTHER
ALICIA?
ONE.
>> YES, YOU WERE ON IT.
ALICIA?
>> Ellen: YEAH?
>> YES, YOU WERE ON IT.
>> I WILL AGREE.
>> Ellen: YEAH?
>> Ellen: SOMEHOW I HAVE A
>> I WILL AGREE.
VAGUE MEMORY THAT I WAS ON IT.
>> Ellen: SOMEHOW I HAVE A
I DON'T REMEMBER IT, BUT I'M
VAGUE MEMORY THAT I WAS ON IT.
GOING TO SAY YES.
I DON'T REMEMBER IT, BUT I'M
HI.
GOING TO SAY YES.
>> HELLO.
HI.
>> Ellen: HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> HELLO.
SHE IN THERE?
>> Ellen: HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> I BELIEVE SO.
SHE IN THERE?
>> I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO LET
>> I BELIEVE SO.
ANYBODY IN THERE.
>> I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO LET
>> Ellen: WOW.
ANYBODY IN THERE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WOW.
I HAVE HAD QUITE A CAREER.
[APPLAUSE]
I HAVE DONE MORE THAN I
I HAVE HAD QUITE A CAREER.
REMEMBER.
I HAVE DONE MORE THAN I
THAT'S ALL!
REMEMBER.
[BELLRINGING]
THAT'S ALL!
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS HAVING
[BELLRINGING]
QUITE A CAREER, IT STOPS THERE.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS HAVING
TALLY UP THE POINTS, THERE ARE
QUITE A CAREER, IT STOPS THERE.
NO POINTS, OKAY, YOU'RE BOTH
TALLY UP THE POINTS, THERE ARE
GETTING A 65-INCH TCL ROKU TV!
NO POINTS, OKAY, YOU'RE BOTH
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GETTING A 65-INCH TCL ROKU TV!
ONE THING I KNOW, THANKS FOR
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
PLAYING.
ONE THING I KNOW, THANKS FOR
ONE THING I KNOW IS THAT I AM ON
PLAYING.
TIKTOK, AND THIS GUY IS AMAZING.
ONE THING I KNOW IS THAT I AM ON
PLEASE GIVE IT UP FOR AJANI!
TIKTOK, AND THIS GUY IS AMAZING.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: AMAZING!
THANK YOU.
THAT IS AJANI, EVERYBODY.
AS I MENTIONED, I FOUND AJANI ON
TIKTOK.
THERE ARE A LOT OF GREAT DANCERS
ON TIKTOK.
TIKTOK HAS PEOPLE DOING
DIFFERENT THINGS.&
AND I WANT TO RECOGNIZE WHAT I
HAVE FOUND.
IT IS A NEW SEGMENT CALLED THE
"TIKTOK TIKTOK AWARDS."
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
WE TRY NEW SEGMENTS, WE DON'T
LIKE TO PUT TOO MUCH MONEY INTO
THEM.
[LAUGHTER]
SO WE SAVE A THEME SONG FOR
THAT.
THE FIRST VIDEO IS AN AWARD FOR
BEST BABY.
[BABY SOUNDS]
>> SOPHIA.
>> YES.
>> DID YOU TAKE MY PHONE?
>> NO.
>> GIVE IT BACK!
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
THIS NEXT ONE IS BEST
DEMONSTRATION OF HOW THE FLU
GETS SPREAD.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
[AUDIENCE REACTION]
>> Ellen: WHY?
[LAUGHTER]
WHO COMES UP WITH THAT?
WHO SAYS, THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
THIS ONE IS THE AWARD FOR BEST
FIRST SCIENCE EXPERIMENT.
>> YOU KNOW, I HAVE SEEN THIS
DONE A COUPLE OF TIMES ON A
COUPLE OF DIFFERENT VIDEOS.
AND I AM NOT QUITE SURE THAT
THIS IS REAL.
AND I JUST WANT TO SEE WHAT'S
UP.
OOH!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
IT IS REAL.
AH.
IF YOU SEE A TIKTOK THAT
DESERVES AN AWARD, SEND IT TO
ME.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING I
DON'T WANT YOU TO SEND ME, KIDS.
I DON'T HAVE ANY, AND FROM TIME
TO TIME I LIKE TO REMIND MYSELF
WHY I DON'T HAVE ANY KIDS.
IT IS A SEGMENT I CALL "WHY I
DON'T HAVE KIDS."
♪ ♪
NORMALLY I SHOW YOU SOME
PICTURES, BUT TODAY I HAVE PUT
TOGETHER A BUNCH OF EVIDENCE, I
MEAN VIDEOS.
[LAUGHTER]
TODAY'S MONTAGE IS SPONSORED BY
THE NEW FX SHOW "BREEDERS"
PLEASE ENJOY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO!
NO TO YOU.
♪ ♪
>> WHAT DO YOU NEED?
>> I NEED AN ELBOW.
>> YOU NEED A NAPKIN?
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
>> YOU MADE A MESS.
IS THAT TOOTHPASTE?
NO, NO.
>> ♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU --
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I DON'T HAVE KIDS.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN WATCH THE PREMIERE OF
"BREEDERS" THIS MONDAY ON FX, IF
YOU MISS IT, YOU CAN STREAM IT
ON HULU.
THEY WANT YOU TO ENJOY A NIGHT
OUT WITH THIS $150 VISA
GIFT CARD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE BACK!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HE MEANT TO RESPOND SMILEY
♪ ♪
FACE, SMILEY FACE, SMILEY FACE,
>> HE MEANT TO RESPOND SMILEY
AND INSTEAD HE RESPONDED
FACE, SMILEY FACE, SMILEY FACE,
EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT.
AND INSTEAD HE RESPONDED
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT.
IS THIS ON?
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IS THIS ON?
♪ ♪
To be their best kids
need good nutrition,
and practice.
Lots of practice.
Get them started right
with Carnation
Breakfast Essentials.
Now with probiotics
and key nutrients
for digestive and
immune support
to help kids be their best.
Carnation Breakfast Essentials.
I like this house, honey.
Oh, it's beautiful.
So you guys are welcome to use
the car while I'm at work.
I'll text you a key.
How do you text a key?
It's technology, dear.
I got this.
Better text it to me.
It has to be a
smart phone, dad.
Are you saying I gotta
dumb phone?
No. It's cool.
We'll just do it
old school.
Hyundai Digital Key;
now there's a better
way to share.
Hey, press that
button there.
Only on the
all-new Sonata.
Where's the car going?
Technology, dear.
That's technology.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: SOMETIMES IT PAYS TO
GET MESSY, BUT NOT TODAY.
LET'S PLAY "SLOPPY SECONDS."
♪ ♪
ALL RIGHT, LAUREN AND STACY, GET
ON DOWN HERE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI.
HELLO, YOU TWO.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> STACY.
>> Ellen: WHERE YOU LIVE, WHAT
DO YOU DO?
>> IRVINE, CALIFORNIA, I AM A
MOM.
>> Ellen: HOW OLD?
>> 18, 13, TEN.
>> Ellen: THAT IS AMAZING.
AND YOU ARE?
>> I AM LAUREN, FROM SUNNY
SAN DIEGO, AND I AM A
PSYCHOTHERAPIST FOR PEOPLE WITH
MENTAL HEALTH CHALLENGES.
IT'S BEEN WONDERFUL.
DO YOU KNOW EACH OTHER?
>> NO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, WHEREVER
YOU SEE YOUR NAME, STAND BEHIND
THAT NAME, AND THEN, THIS IS
VERY FUN.
THIS IS HOW YOU PLAY THE GAME.
ABOVE YOU IS A 60 SECOND CLOCK
AND A BUCKET FILLED WITH SLIME.
WHEN I SAY GO YOU HAVE TO
COMPLETE A CHALLENGE.
THE FASTER YOU DO IT, THE
BETTER, BECAUSE THE BUCKET WILL
SPILL OVER WHEN YOUR CLOCK HIT
ZERO.
ONCE YOU HAVE COMPLETED THE
CHALLENGE, WE WILL MOVE TO
ANOTHER.
BUT WHEN WE START TO RUN OUT OF
TIME IT STARTS TRIPPING, LIKE AT
TEN SECONDS.
SO AS SOON AS YOU HAVE COMPLETED
THE TASK, YOU CAN STOP, BUT IF
YOU HAVE NOT COMPLETED, YOU HAVE
TO KEEP GOING UNTIL.
AND THE CLOCK KEEPS TICKING.
HERE IS YOUR FIRST CHALLENGE.
THE METAL THING IN FRONT OF YOU
IS CALLED A CAN OPENER, FIRST
CHALLENGE IS TO OPEN A CAN OF
SOUP AND POUR IT INTO THE BOWL,
GO.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
[CLOCK TICKING]
>> WE ARE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> DONE.
>> Ellen: STACY CAN STOP,
LAUREN CAN STOP.
OKAY, NECK AND NECK.
ONE SECOND BETWEEN YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
KRISTEN BELL IS HERE TODAY, I
HEAR THAT SHE ONLY LIKES PINK
STARBURST, YOUR SECOND CHALLENGE
IS TO OPEN THE PACK OF STARBURST
AND STACK THEM BY COLOR, GO.
>> OH, MY GOD!
[CLOCK TICKING]
>> OH, MY GOSH!
GET OUT!
>> Ellen: Y'ALL BETTER HURRY
UP, STACK THEM BY COLOR!
STACK THEM BY COLOR.
>> STACK ON TOP?
>> Ellen: YOU HAD IT RIGHT,
LAUREN.
JUST BY COLOR.
YOU CAN STOP, LAUREN.
STACY, FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO,
ONE.
[BUZZER]
>> [SCREAMS]
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: OH, MAN.
THAT IS NOT FAIR!
ALL RIGHT, STACY RAN OUT OF TIME
WHICH MEANS THAT YOU WIN, YOU
ARE GETTING A $500 TARGET
GIFT CARD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
AND YOU ARE GETTING ONE TOO.
WE WILL BE BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> SHE WILL RUN RIGHT INSIDE AND
PEE ON THE KITCHEN MAT.
IT'S LIKE SHE IS STANDING
OUTSIDE THE DOOR SAYING LET ME
IN, LET ME IN, I HAVE TO PEE.
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
IS IT HUMAN FOOD?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
>>> HOMEOWNERS SAYING THEY
TRUSTED THE WRONG PERSON FOR
HELP.
>> I AM WORKING WITH YOU SO THIS
DENY HAPPEN TOE.
>> TODAY AT 4:00.
We have a president who thinks
everything is about him.
His tweets, his golf courses,
his ego.
But I think the job is about
you.
Your healthcare, your schools,
your security, your families and
your future.
I'm Amy Klobuchar.
I'll be a president and a
commander in chief who restores
decency to the white house
and gets things done for you
That's why I approve this
message.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to everything
from helpful reminders...
to presorted
prescription packs.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: VERY FUNNY, WAY TOO
HONEST.
A LOVER OF SWATHS.
THESE ARE JUST A FEW THINGS I
CAN SAY TO DESCRIBE OUR FIRST
GUEST.
PLEASE WELCOME KRISTEN BELL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HI!
>> Ellen: HOW ARE YOU?
YOU ARE SO DOLLED UP.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING AFTER THIS?
>> I'M JUST MEETING A GIRL
GIRLFRIEND.
>> Ellen: HE DID THIS FOR ME?
>> I DID.
I CERTAINLY DON'T WEAR THINGS
LIKE THIS AT HOME.
>> Ellen: THAT'S WHY I THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING SOMEWHERE AFTER
THIS.
>> NO, JUST A ROCK CLIMBING GYM
WITH MY KIDS.
A TRUE STORY.
>> Ellen: DO YOU CLIMB THE
ROCKS AS WELL?
>> I DO NOT.
I'M AFRAID OF BACK AND NECK
INJURIES WHERE THEY ARE NOT.
>> Ellen: THAT'S THE THING
ABOUT CHILDREN.
THEY HOOKED UP TO A HARNESS OR
SOMETHING?
>> NOPE.
>> Ellen: THAT SEEMS FINE TO
YOU.
>> THEY ARE NOT OLD ENOUGH WHERE
THEY ARE NIMBLE ENOUGH TO GET UP
TO AN INJURY.
IT IS PADDED.
>> Ellen: THEY LOOK FUN AND
LIKE A FUN THING FOR KIDS TO DO.
>> THEY ARE PRETTY COOL.
>> Ellen: CAN I ASK WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOUR CHILD'S HEAD IN
THIS PICTURE, WHICH CHILD IS
THIS?
>> THAT IS THE BACK OF MY
YOUNGEST DAUGHTER'S HEAD, AND TO
THE STORY BEHIND THIS --
>> Ellen: WHAT IS HER NAME?
>> ?
>> DELTA.
>> Ellen: AND SHE IS?
>> FIVE.
SHE HAS THIS OBSESSION WITH
BATHING WITH HER STUFFED
ANIMALS.
IN MY HEAD I AM LIKE IT IS A
COOL SENSORY THING.
I WILL LET HER DO IT, BUT SHE
ROLE-PLAYS AND SHE WANTS ME TO
LEAVE THE ROOM.
NOW THAT SHE IS FIVE I'M LIKE, I
CAN START TO MAKE DINNER.
IT IS THIS MUCH WATER IN THE
BATHTUB.
SO SHE IS IN THERE AND I GO TO
GET HER OUT.
AND I GO, I DON'T THINK YOU GOT
THE CONDITIONER OUT OF YOUR
HAIR.
SHE SAYS NO, I RINSED IT.
IN 10 MINUTES LATER I AM LIKE,
WHAT DID YOU USE?
AND SHE IS LIKE, THE VASELINE!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: IS THAT THE ENTIRE
TUB OF VASELINE?
AND WHY WAS THAT IN HER REACH?
>> BECAUSE HER MOTHER LEFT HER
ALONE IN THE BATHROOM.
AND SHE LIKES SENSORY PLAY.
AND HOW YOU GET IT OUT IS THIS.
IT WAS THREE ROUNDS OF HELLO
BELLO SHAMPOO.
ONE ROUND OF CLARIFYING SHAMPOO.
TWO ROUNDS OF DISH SOAP AND THEN
WE STILL HAD TO WAIT FOR DAYS,
BECAUSE NONE OF THAT WORKED.
>> Ellen: BECAUSE DAWN IS WHAT
THEY USE WHEN THE BIRDS GET IN
THE OIL SPILLS.
HE WOULD THINK THAT WOULD DO IT.
>> IT DID CUT THE GREASE DOWN.
>> Ellen: DELTA DAWN, HOW
ABOUT THAT?
[APPLAUSE]
>> IT CUT THE GREASE A LITTLE
BIT.
IT WORKED A LITTLE BIT.
>> Ellen: WOW.
I'M SURE IT WAS SOMEWHAT COMBED
OUT.
>> NO, WE DID NOT TOUCH IT.
[LAUGHTER]
WHO DOES SHE HAVE TO IMPRESS?
>> Ellen: THAT IS TRUE.
TO START SAVING FOR THERAPY NOW.
AND THEN I LOVE THAT YOU RESCUE
DOGS.
AND YOU HAVE A ONE EYED DOG THAT
IS SO --
>> I DO, BARBARA!
BARBARA BISCUITS IS GOING TO
TURN 12 THIS YEAR.
WE GOT HER LAST YEAR.
AND SHE IS JUST A HOT MESS.
DAX CALLS HER THE OLD DIRTY GOLF
RAG.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT SHE LOOKS
LIKE.
>> Ellen: SHE LOOKS LIKE SHE
HAS VASELINE IN HER HAIR.
>> SHE WALKED RIGHT INTO THE
POOL, SHE IS BLIND IN THIS I END
THIS I ONLY HAS 20% SITE, BUT
NONE OF IT INVOLVES THE EDGE OF
THE POOL.
I SCOOPED HER RIGHT OUT.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE NOT LOOKING
GOOD AS A MOM OR A PET OWNER
RIGHT NOW.
>> I TAKE WONDERFUL CARE OF HER,
AND I TAKE CARE OF ALL OF THE
SENIOR DOGS.
>> Ellen: TO RESCUE A SENIOR
DOG IS THE BEST THING.
IT IS SO SWEET THAT YOU DID
THAT.
>> DESPITE HOW MUCH SHE PUTS US
THROUGH.
BECAUSE SHE CAME AT 11 YEARS
OLD, AND THERE IS NO TRAINING A
DOG LIKE THAT, ALSO I THINK SHE
HAS A TINY BRAIN.
SO IT IS NOT GOING TO WORK.
BUT SHE DOES NOT FIGURE OUT THAT
GOING OUTSIDE IS WHERE YOU GO TO
THE BATHROOM.
OR MAYBE SHE HAS AND SHE DOES
NOT ENJOY IT.
BUT I WILL LEAVE HER OUTSIDE FOR
LIKE FIVE HOURS, SHE WILL BE ON
THE PORCH IN THE YARD AND THEN
SHE WILL RUN RIGHT INSIDE AND
PEE ON THE KITCHEN BATHMAT.
IT IS LIKE SHE IS STANDINGAT
SHE THINKS THAT IS THE KITCHEN.
YOU HAVE ENOUGH MONEY TO DO T
THAT.
>> I GUESS I COULD.
I'VE NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
>> Ellen: THINK ABOUT IT.
I WANTED YOU TO TELL THE STORY
BECAUSE I HEARD ABOUT IT THIS
AND IND RESPONDSURFACE
EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT, EGGPLANT.
AND WHEN HE DID IT.
HE WENT --
[GASP]
IT MADE A HUGE MISTAKE.
AND HE SHOWS ME THE PHONE, AND
BY THE WAY, WHEN YOU INVOLVE AND
EGGPLANT MOJI, THE WHOLE STORY
CHANGES, BECAUSE NOW IT READS I
WILL BE THERE AT 11, CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU.
WHICH IS NOT HOW IT WAS READ OR
INTENDED TO, BUT THANKFULLY SHE
DID NOT KNOW WHAT AN EGGPLANT
MOJI MEANT.
>> Ellen: SHE DOES NOW.
WE HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK.
MORE WITH KRISTEN AFTER THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> THEY LOOK LIKE FINGERS!
>> SOUR CREAM AND CHEDDAR.
>> THEY LOOK LIKE FINGERS.
>> CHEESE IT'S.
I SAID SHE'S.
>> Ellen: WE HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOUR GROWING FAMILY.
Since my DVT blood clot
I wasn't sure...
was another around the corner?
Or could things go
a different way?
I wanted to help protect myself.
My doctor recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven to treat
and help prevent
another DVT or PE blood clot.
Almost 98 percent of patients
on ELIQUIS
didn't experience another,
and ELIQUIS has significantly
less major bleeding
than the standard treatment.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
Don't stop ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
What's around the corner
could be worth waiting for.
Ask your doctor about ELIQUIS.
There's a company that's talked
to even more real people
than me: JD Power.
448,134 to be exact.
They answered 410 questions
in 8 categories
about vehicle quality.
And when they were done,
Chevy earned more J.D. Power
Quality Awards across
Cars, Trucks and SUVs than any
other brand
over the last four years.
So on behalf of Chevrolet,
I want to say
"Thank you, real people."
You're welcome.
We're gonna need a bigger room.
Wow!
I know right? Walmart.com
has a lot of great stuff.
And now get 5% back
on the things you buy there,
with the new Capital
One Walmart Rewards Card.
Say what?
5% back.
Say that again!?
Yes!
What's in your wallet?
Yup. Nailed it!
>>> I'M PAT LAWSON MUSE.
WE ARE FOLLOWING BREAKING NEWS
RIGHT NOW.
POLICE ARRESTED A MAN ACCUSED OF
TRYING TO EXPLODE A CAR OUTSIDE
OF THE PENTAGON.
SCOTT MacFARLAND IS WORKING THE
STORY.
HE WILL HAVE THE REPORT COME UP
AT 4:00.
>>> THEN FEARS OF A GLOBAL
PANDEMIC.
CORONAVIRUS CASES SURGE, AND
STOCKS TAKE ANOTHER HIM.
WE WILL SHOW YOU THE NEW
PRECAUTIONS HERE AT HOME.
>>> PLUS HOMEOWNERS STRUGGLING
TO STAVE FOR THEIR AMERICAN
TREATMENT SAY THEY TRUSTED THE
WRONG PERSON FOR HELP.
THE CAUTIONARY TALE AT 4:00.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
KRISTEN BELL, THIS IS THE
ONE-YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF
HELLO BELLO.
IT IS DOING SO WELL.
USUALLY TAKES A COMPANY A LONG
TIME TO ESTABLISH AND DO WELL.
THIS IS DOING SO WELL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU, THANK PARENTS CANE
BETWEEN THEIR BABY IN THEIR
BUDGET AND CREATE A COMMUNITY.
AND WE HAVE GIVEN OVER AWAY A
MILLION DIAPERS IN OUR FIRST
YEAR ALONE.
TO 70 DIFFERENT ORGANIZATIONS.
SO FIRST RESPONDERS DISCOUNT TO
LAST YEAR.
[APPLAUSE]
SO ALL FIRST RESPONDERS,
MILITARY.
AND THEN WE ARE GIVING NEW AND
EXPECTANT PARENTS A FREE WEEKS
WORTH OF DIAPERS ON US.
EVERYONE IN NORTH AMERICA WHO IS
NEWLY OR EXPECTING, AND YOU JUST
PAY LIKE A DOLLAR IN SHIPPING
AND WE WILL SEND YOU A WEEK'S
WORTH OF DIAPERS.
NOT A SAMPLE PACK TO TELL YOU WE
CAN HOPE THAT WE CAN LIFT A
LITTLE BIT OF THE BURDEN OFF OF
HAVING A CHILD.
>> Ellen: THAT IS FANTASTIC,
KRISTEN, THAT IS GREAT.
YOU DO THE SERIES
"MOMSPLAINING," AND THERE IS
SOMETHING THAT I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT HAVING A CHILD, BUT WHEN
YOU BREAST-FEED, I GUESS YOU
HAVE TO BE AWARE ALL THE TIME OF
EVERYTHING.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF YOU SAW, THE
WOMAN WHO WAS JUST -- SHE HAD
SELF TANNING ON AND WAS
BREASTFEEDING.
A LOOK AT THE BABY'S FACE.
THIS IS AFTER SHE REALIZED.
[LAUGHTER]
>> OH, YEAH.
WOW.
THAT CHECKS OUT.
>> Ellen: WHAT A SHOCK WHEN
YOU ARE LIKE WHAT'S WRONG?
>> AND NOW THE BABY HAS A 5:00
SHADOW.
>> Ellen: IT LOOKS LIKE A
HOBO, GET ON A TRAIN IN A MI
MINUTE.
AND THEN HE JUST WROTE TO YOUR
FIRST CHILDREN'S BOOK WHICH IS
CALLED?
>> THE WORLD NEEDS MORE PURPLE
PEOPLE.
I WILL LET YOUYTHING OTHER THANE
BOOK AS A, ogy.
CONDITIONS!
MILK OUT IT CRUNCHY AFTER DINNE.
>> THEY LOOK LIKE FINGERS!
>> AND THEY ARE MADE OF CHEESE,
STRING CHEESE.
>> THEY ARE COUNTRY AND THEY
LOOK LIKE A FINGER, AND THEY
HAVE A CURVE LIKE A CASHEW, BUT
THEY ARE NOT A CASHEW, THEY ARE
BRIGHT ORANGE, AND THERE IS A
BIG TIGER THAT SELLS THEM.
>> A BIG WHAT?
>> TIGER, IS HE A TIGER?
>> OH, HE IS A CHEETAH!
>> OH, CHEETOS. I
AM SO COMPETITIVE.
BUT THE M I SAID THE
WORD OATMEAL AND REALIZED THE
GAME WAS
ALL OF MY WIRES STARTED CROSSING
HelloBello.com .
W B
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
WE GOT
but heo
that allows you to
be that person.
Mike called to tell me,
you should be proud of
what you've done
and your name should be
on that project.
He has faith in you,
he believes in you.
It was about always showing
up and doing your best.
I always knew that
he had my back.
He was raised by an
extraordinary woman,
she supported him
all along the way
and that's very much
a part of who he is.
Mike supports women,
he promotes women, and
he respects women.
MEET AND
HOW DID YOU MEET? YOUR GROWING .
>> OH, MY GOD!
S AND APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOSH,ss
than the standard treatment.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
Don't stop ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you hadl procedures.
What a
Ask your doctor about ELIQUIS.
There's a company that's talked
to even more real people
than me: JD Power.
448,134 to be exact.
They answered 410 questions
in 8 categories
a Nationoscle quality.hil's
we will always
be by their side.
Children's
National Hospital.
Grow Up Stronger.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
DOUG AND NICK, WE WANT YOU TO
HAVE A CHANCE TO WIN A PRIZE OR
DO SINCE YOU HAVE A BABY ON THE
WAY WE WILL PLAY "TASTE BUDS,"
YOU WILL BE BLINDFOLDED, ANDY
ZENOR AND I WILL PUT A PLATE IN
FRONT OF YOU AND YOU WILL
DESCRIBE WHAT IS ON THE PLATE
WITHOUT SAYING EXACTLY WHAT IT
IS.
WHEN YOU GET IT RIGHT, YOU WILL
HEAR A NOISE AND GO TO THE NEXT
THING.
60 SECONDS ON THE CLOCK.
LET'S PUT YOUR BLINDFOLDS ON.
>> THANK YOU.
OH, MY GOSH.
>> Ellen: HANDS BEHIND YOUR
BACK, WE WILL START WITH NICK.
OKAY.
OH, NICK.
>> I AM READY.
>> Ellen: IT IS IN FRONT OF
YOU NOW.
>> OH, I KNOW THIS.
>> I AM SO GLAD.
>> BABY'S EAT IT.
>> LITERALLY EVERYTHING.
KNOAT>> Ellen: SHALL WE PASS?
WE WILL PASS.
IT IS YOUR TURN.
WE'LL SEE HOW EASY THIS IS.
>> OH, IT IS TOMATOEY.
DON'T SAY THE FOOD!
IT IS AN ITALIAN, ITALIAN MOSHE
THING.
>> TOMATO SAUCE.
>> Ellen: YOU KIND OF SAID IT.
IT IS TOMATOEY.
>> THIS IS HARD.
>> Ellen: I KNOW, VERY HARD.
>> THEY ARE GOOD FOR YOUR HEART.
IT IS SERIAL.
THEY ARE AROUND.
>> CHEERIOS.
>> Ellen: YES, THAT IS RIGHT!
READY, GO!
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?
>> IS A HUMAN FOOD?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT IS A BOX.
IT IS NOT EDIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
>> Ellen: TAKE YOUR BLINDFOLDS
OFF.
IT IS
>>> BREAKING NOW AT 4:00.
CORONAVIRUS ALERT.
>> WHY TOP AMERICAN DOCTOR RGS
NOW SOUNDING THE ALARM.
>>> AND WE'LL TAKE YOU INSIDE
AND TELL YOU HOW THEY'RE
PREPARING AT LOCAL AIRPORTS.
>> WE'RE WORKING LIVE FOR YOU
WITH TEAM COVERAGE.
>>> A POTENTIAL PLOT FOILED
OUTSIDE THE PENTAGON.
>>> HOW POLICE STOPPED IT.
>>> SHATTERED DREAMS.
LOCAL HOMEOWNERS SAY THEY
TRUSTED THE WRONG WOMAN TO HELP
THEM SAVE THEIR HOMES.
>> I THOUGHT I WOULD SPEND MY
GOLDEN YEARS HERE, I THOUGHT I
COULD PASS THIS ON TO MY
GRANDCHILDREN.
>> I'M WORKING WITH YOU TO TELL
YOU WHAT YOU NEED TO DO TO
PROTECT YOUR HOME.
>>> TRACKINGG SEVERE WEATHER.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHEN IT MOVES
THROUGH YOUR AREA.
>> 100% CHANCE OF HURRICANES
TODAY IN D.C.
I'M TOMMY McFLY WITH MARDI GRAS
EXTRAVAGANZA.
>>> WE COME ON THE AIR THIS
AFTERNOON WITH STRONG NEW
WARNINGS ABOUT THE SPREAD OF THE
CORONAVIRUS HERE IN THE U.S.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE THIO
START PLANNING FOR THIS
SETH OFF A DOWNWARD SPIRAL ON
WALL STREET.
IT'S DOWN 855 POINTS.
AT ONE POINT IT WAS DOWN WELL
OVER 900.
>> WE'RE WORKING ON LIVE TEAM
COVERAGE WITH FAST MOVING
DEVELOPMENTS AND WE'LL SHOW YOU
HOW LOCAL AIRPORTS ARE WORKING.
>> AND WE'RE LIVE WITH