♪ NO, NO, NO ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I USED TO WANT TO GROW UP ♪
♪ I THOUGHT THAT I ♪
♪ COULD BE FREE ♪
>> Ellen: HAVE A SEAT,
EVERYBODY.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT YOU.
YOU LOOK FAMILIAR.
SOME OF YOU LOOK LIKE SOMEBODY I
SAW A WEEK AGO OR SO.
HAPPY PRESIDENTS' DAY TO YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
PRESIDENTS' DAY.
HERE'S A FUN FACT.
PRESIDENTS' DAY WAS ESTABLISHED
IN 1885 TO HONOR
GEORGE WASHINGTON ACROSS THE
POTOMAC IN SEARCH OF GREAT DEALS
ON MATTRESSES.
[LAUGHS]
WASHINGTON IS ALSO FAMOUS FOR
NEVER TELLING A LIE.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED A LITTLE
SINCE HE WAS PRESIDENT.
MOST PEOPLE HAVE THE DAY OFF BUT
NOT ME SO I THOUGHT I WOULD GIVE
MYSELF A BREAK AND HAVE MY
AUDIENCE ENTERTAINED ME.
IT'S A NEW GAME WE ARE CALLING
"CAN YOU DO THAT."
♪ ♪
>> ♪ IT'S TRICKY ♪
>> Ellen: I'M GOING TO NEED
tWITCH TO HELP ME.
COME ON OUT.
[RHYTHMIC CLAPPING]
THAT'S YOUR SET UP OVER THERE.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> Ellen: HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>>> IT'S GOOD.
IT'S HISTORICAL.
>> Ellen: LEADING IN THE POLLS
ALREADY.
tWITCH, THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
IN THE AUDIENCE WHO CLAIM THEY
HAVE A SPECIAL TALENT.
WE HAVE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
WE ARE GOING TO DECIDE IF THEY
ARE LYING OR NOT.
THAT'S WHY WE SAY "CAN YOU DO
THAT?"
ANDY.
>> HERE'S OUR FIRST GUY.
>> Ellen: HELLO, SIR.
>> HELLO.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS BRAD BYERS.
>> Ellen: WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I LIVE IN PULLMAN,
WASHINGTON, AND I AM RETIRED
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO.
>> Ellen: WONDERFUL.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WHAT CAN I DO?
>> Ellen: WHAT CAN YOU DO.
>> I CAN BALANCE A DOLLAR BILL
ON MY NOSE AND A QUARTER AT THE
SAME TIME.
>> Ellen: BUT YOU DIDN'T SAY
THAT WAS ON YOUR NOSE AT THE
SAME TIME.
A QUARTER AND A DOLLAR BILL BOTH
ON YOUR NOSE?
>> BOTH ON MY NOSE.
>> Ellen: IT SOUNDS SPECIFIC.
>> I GUESS YOU CAN DO THAT.
>> Ellen: DON'T ACT LIKE IT'S
EASY.
IT'S NOT EASY.
>> NOSES ARE SHAPED DIFFERENTLY.
>> Ellen: WE ARE GOING TO SAY
YES.
LET'S SEE IT.
[DRUMROLL]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WOW.
YOU CAN DO THAT.
THAT'S VERY GOOD.
THAT'S NOT HOW I PICTURED IT.
I THOUGHT THEY QUARTER WOULD BE
DOWN HERE IN THE DOLLAR WOULD BE
ON TOP.
>> I DON'T TAKE REQUESTS, ELLEN.
>> Ellen: THAT'S FANTASTIC.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
HI.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> FAVEN.
>> Ellen: WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
>> SAN DIEGO, CALIFORNIA.
EVERYONE IS A FAN OF THAT CITY.
>> I CAN JUGGLE A TABLE WITH MY
FEET.
>> Ellen: JUGGLE A TABLE WITH
YOUR FEET.
>> YES.
>> Ellen: SHE CAN JUGGLE A
TABLE WITH HER FEET.
WHAT SIZED TABLE?
>> PRETTY BIG.
>> Ellen: A PRETTY BIG TABLE.
>> OKAY.
>> Ellen: OKAY?
>> I'M GOING TO SAY YES.
IT DOESN'T HURT IF YOU SAY YES.
IF A DOLLAR AND A QUARTER
HAPPENED, I SAY YES.
>> Ellen: I ASSUME YOU HAVE TO
COME DOWN HERE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> SHE'S GOT THE MUSIC.
I REALLY BELIEVE IT NOW.
[APPLAUSE]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WOW!
SHE HAD NO PROTECTIVE GEAR ON
HER FACE.
IT COULD HAVE FALLEN RIGHT ON
WOW.
HER FACE.
BRAD, I BET YOU ARE NOT SO HAPPY
WOW.
WITH YOURSELF.
BRAD, I BET YOU ARE NOT SO HAPPY
[LAUGHTER]
WITH YOURSELF.
I'VE GOT A QUARTER ON MY NOSE.
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT.
ONE MORE.
>> HI, I'M MARY.
>> Ellen: HI, MARY.
WHATEVER YOU DO, IT'S GOT TO BE
REAL GOOD.
HOW DO YOU TOP THAT?
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
SHE BALANCED IT WITH NOTHING TO
COVER HER FACE AND IT COULD'VE
FALLEN.
WHAT DO YOU DO, MARY?
>> I CAN DO THE SPLITS BUT THEN
I CAN STAND UP FROM THE SPLITS
WITHOUT USING MY HANDS.
>> Ellen: OKAY.
I THINK SHE CAN DO THAT.
>> DO YOU THINK SHE CAN DO IT?
>> Ellen: YEAH.
CAN YOU DO THAT, tWITCH.
>> NOT THESE DAYS.
>> Ellen: BUT DANCERS CAN DO
IT.
>> IN YEARS PAST.
>> Ellen: IT'S REALLY HARD.
I'M NOT SAYING IT'S NOT HARD.
TONS OF MUSCLES TO DO THAT.
SURE, LET'S SEE THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
[DRUMROLL]
>> OKAY, I CAN'T DO IT.
>> Ellen: YOU CAN'T?
OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
BACK TO YOUR SEAT.
>> THIS GUY SAYS HE CAN DO IT.
THIS GUY SAYS HE CAN DO IT.
>> Ellen: HE CAN DO IT?
OH.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU COULD DO THAT.
>> AND DUDES COME UP LIKE THAT,
IT USUALLY MEANS IT'S ABOUT TO
GO DOWN.
[DRUMROLL]
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WOW.
WOW.
THAT'S AMAZING.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS PABLO.
>> Ellen: OKAY.
THANK YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
DOES SHE EVEN GET -- SHE DOESN'T
DO IT?
SHE TRIED.
FOR PLAYING, YOU'RE ALL GETTING
A ROKU TV AND IF YOU HAVE A
SPECIAL TALENT YOU LIKE TO SHARE
WITH ME, SHARE IT ON ELLENTUBE.
HERE'S SOMEONE I KNOW WHO CAN
DANCE.
IT IS tWITCH.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: YES.
I WOULD VOTE FOR YOU, tWITCH.
PUT YOURSELF ON THE BALLOT.
THANKS FOR SHAKING YOUR ARTICLES
OF IMPEACHMENT FOR US.
IT'S MONDAY.
IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE WEEK.
HONEY NUT CHEERIOS WANTS YOU TO
FEEL GOOD WITH THE SPECIAL MOOD
BOOSTER.
♪ ♪
THANK YOU, HONEY NOT CHEERIOS,
FOR THAT.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE BACK.
WHEN YOU HEARD THAT THEY WERE
CALLING 911.
>> WHAT I HEARD RIVER 4911 WAS
LIKE AMY SCHUMER IS GOING DOWN.
>> Ellen: THE LARGEST BLANK OF
ANY U.S. PRESIDENT.
>> IT'S TOO EASY.
>> Announcer: HERE COMES
EXCITEMENT.
>> Ellen: DO YOU LIKE TO PLAY
GAMES?
>> NO.
IS THIS A GAME?
>> Ellen: NO.
>> Announcer: ALL NEW "ELLEN."
HARRISON FORD AND THE RETURN OF
"INDIANA JONES"?
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DO I LOOK LIKE BEFORE?
>> Announcer: MARK WAHLBERG AN
AVERAGE ANDY.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S
Big news America!
For a limited time, we've
changed the shape
of Honey Nut Cheerios.
Because we want people to know
they're delicious
AND can help lower cholesterol.
Heart healthy. Get it? A heart!
Can you believe they had one in
my size?!
Free!
Free, free, free.
♪
That's right,
TurboTax Free is free.
Free, free free free.
From the home of never ending,
Comes Never Ending
Stuffed Pastas.
From as little
as $11.99 you get,
Never ending stuffed pastas,
sauces, and toppings.
Never ending salad
and breadsticks, of course.
Never ending generosity.
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only at Olive Garden.
[Crackling fire]
[Wood rolling]
Alexios, add toilet paper
to the shopping list.
[Chiseling on stone]
Oh, and camel milk.
And a chicken.
And moisturizer.
ALEXA: Thanks, guys.
I'll take it from here.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUEST IS
ONE OF THE MOST TALENTED PEOPLE
I KNOW AND I'M SO, SO, SO HAPPY
SHE IS THE NEW HOST OF THE SHOW
"LITTLE BIG SHOTS."
PLEASE WELCOME MY FRIEND,
MELISSA McCARTHY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HI, GUYS.
WOW.
REALLY NICE.
>> Ellen: THE LAST TIME YOU
WERE HERE, WE SENT YOU TWO TO
THE DRY CLEANERS.
IT'S YOUR DRY CLEANERS.
>> IT IS.
REMEMBER I WAS SAYING, IS IT A
GOOD IDEA BECAUSE THIS IS
ACTUALLY WHERE I GO.
WE THOUGHT IT WAS EXTRA FUNNY.
>> Ellen: ON THE GROUND.
ON THE GROUND.
SO I WAS TELLING HER WHAT TO SAY
AND I TOLD HER TO FAINT AND
EVERYONE FREAKED OUT THERE
BECAUSE SHE FAINTED SUPPOSEDLY.
THEY CALLED 911.
WHEN YOU HEARD THEY WERE CALLING
911.
>> WHAT I HEARD RIGHT BEFORE 911
IS LIKE, AMY SCHUMER IS GOING
DOWN.
AMY SCHUMER IS ON THE GROUND AND
I WAS LIKE A!
-SHE CALLED ME AMY SCHUMER WHICH
WAS MY FAVORITE PART.
WHAT A COMPLEMENT BUT SHE CALLED
ME AMY SCHUMER FOR A FIVE TIMES.
AMY SCHUMER'S ON THE GROUND!
AND THEN 911!
>> Ellen: SO THEY ARE RUSHING
TO GET AMY SCHUMER.
>> PEOPLE WERE NOT LIKING IT.
I REMEMBER OUT OF THE CORNER OF
úMYL
WAS LIKE NO, NO.
THEY PULLED THEIR SON BACK FOR
ME.
THAT LADY IS CRAZY.
AND THEN I WAS IN THERE RECENTLY
AND SOMEONE WALKED BEHIND ME
THAT WORKED THERE AND SAID TRY
TO KEEP IT UP RIGHT THIS TIME.
I JUST YELLED, IT'S ELLEN'S
FAULT!
>> Ellen: GOOD FOR YOU.
>> NOBODY SEEMED TO HEAR THAT.
THEY WERE LIKE, ELLEN CAN DO NO
WRONG.
>> Ellen: THEY LOVE YOU THERE.
>> THEY FLINCHED WHEN I CAME IN.
>> Ellen: WE'VE NEVER HAD
SOMETHING GO SO WRONG WERE 911
WAS CALLED.
IT WAS A HIGHLIGHT FOR US.
>> YOU ARE SWEET.
YOU HAD HER IN.
>> Ellen: WE GIVE HER MONEY.
YEAH, WE GIVE HER MONEY.
SO SHE CAN SEE AMY SCHUMER IN
CONCERT.
>> SHE WILL BE LIKE, WE LIKE HER
SO MUCH BETTER.
>> Ellen: SHE SAID SHE DIDN'T
KNOW IT WAS YOU BUT SHE KEPT
CALLING YOU AMY SCHUMER.
YOUR CHILDREN ARE ALWAYS -- I'M
INTERESTED IN EVERYTHING THEY
DO.
THE 10-YEAR-OLD NOW, EXPLAIN
WHAT YOU GOT HER FOR HER
BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
>> YOUR TYPICAL 10-YEAR-OLD, I
GOT HER A HONG KONG HARNESS
WHICH IS --
EVERYONE.
WHAT?
IT IS A STUNT HARNESS WHICH IS
WHAT YOU WEAR IF YOU ARE BEING
JERKED UP OR IF YOU ARE IN A
FIGHT SCENE, SEE THERE'S AN
EXPLOSION IN THE MOVIE.
IT PULLS YOU BACK.
THERE'S NINE HUGE GUYS.
THAT'S ALL SHE REALLY WANTED.
IT WAS KIND OF LIKE --
I GOT HER BABY STUNT VEST.
THAT WOMAN DOES NOT LIKE THAT I
GOT HER STUNT VEST.
THERE'S ONE GIRL OUT THERE LIKE
NO THANKS.
HER BIRTHDAY PARTY CAN REALLY
JUDGE THAT WAY.
AT HER BIRTHDAY PARTY, WE ARE
GOING TO LIKE A POWER CORD GYM.
SHE SUNSET WITH ME AND SHE'S
LIKE CAN YOU HOLD ME AND TAKE ME
UP, WHICH I DON'T.
I AM NOT THAT BAD OF A MOM.
SHE ALWAYS WANTS TO DO STUNTS
AND FLIP AROUND.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE GUYS SAFELY
AND LOVINGLY JERKED HER UP TO
THE CEILING.
SHE WAS LITERALLY, YES.
>> Ellen: SHE WANTS TO BE A
STUNT PERSON?
>> SHE'S LIKE, NOW I HAVE THREE
JOBS.
CHIROPRACTOR, ACTOR, STUNT WO
WOMAN.
SHE'S REALLY CLINGING TO ALL
THREE.
>> Ellen: SHE ALSO PLAYING
VIOLENT OR IS THAT SOMEBODY
ELSE?
>> THAT IS HER.
>> Ellen: ALSO PLAYING VIO
VIOLENT.
ZACH -- PLAYING VIOLIN.
>> ARE YOU ON THE STRING?
SHE IS JUST LEARNING.
THE FACT THAT SHE PRACTICES,
THERE ARE TIMES WHEN THE DOGS
ARE LIKE ROOOOR.
IT'S NOT AN EASY INSTRUMENT TO
LEARN.
>> Ellen: THAT WOULDN'T BE FUN
TO HEAR.
>> Ellen: DO YOU WANT TO
PRACTICE EVERY DAY?
I THINK I'VE GOT IT ONCE A WEEK.
>> MAYBE I SHOULDN'T PUSH FOR
MORE.
>> Ellen: YOUR PARENTS ARE IN
THE AUDIENCE TODAY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> MY MOM IS LIKE, YOU LIED.
>> Ellen: I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU BECAUSE I JUST LEARNED.
I DIDN'T KNOW GROWING UP THAT
YOU RESCUED CATS.
I LOVE ALL ANIMALS BUT I LOVE
CATS AND I HEARD AT ONE POINT
THERE WAS LIKE 30 CATS LIVING AT
YOUR HOUSE.
>> PROBABLY MORE.
I REMEMBER GETTING UP TO 33, 34.
>> IN THE BARN.
>> Ellen: THEY WERE OUTSIDE.
>> THAT ONLY MAKES US HALF AS
CRAZY.
BUT THANK YOU FOR CLARIFYING.
>> Ellen: PEOPLE WOULD DUMP
THEM OFF AND YOU WOULD RESCUE
THE CATS?
>> WE DID THIS, MY MOM WOULD
OFTEN GO ON THE BACK PORCH AND
THIS WAS THE CALL AND WE ALL DID
IT WHICH ONLY NOW SEEMS WEIRD.
GROWING UP, I WAS LIKE THIS IS
HOW YOU CALL 30 CATS.
BUT YOU'D GO OUT WITH THIS HUGE
-- WE WOULD HAVE TWO BIG
PICTURES OF FOOD AND WE WOULD
HAVE MILK AND WATER AND BREAD
AND YOU STAND OUTSIDE AND SAY
HERE, KI-KI-KI-KI-KITTY.
THEY WOULD ALL COME.
THEY DON'T KNOW EACH OTHER.
THEY ARE FERAL OR THEY WERE
SCARED.
MY MOM WOULD TAKE A LONG TIME.
WHILE THEY WERE EATING WAS OUR
TIME TO PET THEM AND GET THEM
FAMILIAR SO IN THE MOM WOULD PET
THEM IN TALK TO EACH ONE OF THEM
GIVE THEM NAMES AND GO AROUND
THE WHOLE CIRCLE.
SHE DID THAT.
WHEN SHE STOOD UP, SHE WAS LIKE
THAT IS A SKUNK.
IT'S TRUE.
>> Ellen: THAT'S FANTASTIC.
MORE WITH MELISSA AFTER THIS.
♪ ♪
>> HE'S EVERYONE FAVORITE GUY.
HE TRIES TO BE A BAD GUY BUT
HE'S NOT AT ALL.
[chuckles]
Beat you home.
Uh yeah, but I got dinner.
Cheers!
ANNOUNCER:
With Giant same-day pickup,
we'll do the shopping
for you
so you can do more
of what you love.
Oooooooohh
Ooooooooohh
♪
Unock the cinnaverse with
Cinnamon Toast Crunch.
>> DO YOU WANT YOUR FACE TO BE
ALL PINK?
>> YOU ARE THE ARTIST.
>> I AM AN ARTIST BECAUSE I MAKE
BEAUTIFUL THINGS.
>> YOU ARE VERY MIGHTY FOR FOUR.
YOU HAVE AN INCREDIBLY STRONG
ARM.
I GOT A REAL PIECE OF SOMETHING
IN THERE.
>> I NEED A NAP AGAIN SO I CAN
WIPE IT OFF.
IT'S PLASTIC.
>> ON MY FACE?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S A CAUTIONARY TALE.
[APPLAUSE]
IT'S A HARD SEAT OF PLASTIC.
SHE TURNS AROUND THE MAKEUP
BRUSH.
THIS SOFT BRUSH IS COMING AT ME
AND SHE SAYS WE CAN'T HAVE THAT
AND SHE TAKES THE SHARP END OF
IT.
I WAS LIKE OH, LET'S USE THE
SOFT FLUFFY SIDE.
>> Ellen: WHAT WAS HER TALENT?
>> HER TALENT WAS BEING MIGHTY
AND INCREDIBLY OUTSPOKEN.
SHE HAD A WHOLE PHILOSOPHY WHICH
IS WHY WE WENT TO THIS MOROCCAN
STORE TO GET A MAGIC CARPET.
SHE HAS THIS WHOLE THING, I
DON'T NEED A PRINCE TO GET A
RUG.
I CAN GET MY OWN RUG AND IF I
WANT TO FLY AROUND ON A MAGIC
CARPET I CAN DO IT ON MY OWN AND
HE CAN GET HIS OWN RUG AND WE
EACH HAVE OUR OWN BUT I DON'T
NEED HIM TO GET ME A MAGIC
CARPET RIDE.
4 YEARS OLD.
SHE WAS LIKE, I DON'T NEED A
PRINCE.
SHE WAS LIKE --
I WAS LIKE HOW IS IT --
SHE'S SO TINY, IF YOU ASK HER
SOMETHING, SHE IS LIKE I DON'T
NEED THAT.
I'M CAPABLE.
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO SPECIAL.
THE THING ABOUT IT, FIRST OF
ALL, I WAS SO HAPPY YOU SAID
YES.
I REALLY WANT TO DO TO HOST THE
SHOW.
IT'S A WHOLE NEW VERSION.
WE REMADE "LITTLE BIG SHOTS" AND
MELISSA IS THE HOST.
WE ALWAYS FIND AMAZING KIDS.
HOW MUCH DID YOU CRY ON THAT
SHOW?
>> OH, GOD.
IT WAS A TOPIC OF CONVERSATION
BECAUSE I WAS LIKE AT A CERTAIN
POINT, DO I SEEM NUTS AND WILL I
SCARE THE CHILDREN?
BUT THEN I WOULD LOOK AROUND AND
EVERYBODY IN THE AUDIENCE IS
CRYING AND PEOPLE WOULD COME IN,
YOUR SWEATER LOOKS WEIRD AND DON
IS CRYING.
EVERYBODY'S CRYING.
AND THEN WOULD BE LAUGHING.
THERE'S SOMETHING INCREDIBLY
POWERFUL ABOUT THESE KIDS THAT
ARE EXACTLY WHO THEY ARE.
SOMEHOW THEY HAVEN'T BEEN SHAMED
OUT OF ANYTHING.
THEY REALLY GOT SOMETHING TO SAY
AND JUST BEING ABLE I THINK TO
SHINE THE LIGHT ON KINDNESS IS
GOOD AND HAVING AN INTEREST IN
THINGS.
SO MUCH ATTENTION I THINK IS
GIVEN TO WHO SAID SOMETHING THE
NASTIEST.
WHO RIPPED SOMEONE APART ON ALL
THESE CRAZY SOCIAL MEDIA THINGS.
I THINK WE ARE FORGETTING THAT
THAT'S NOT THE GOAL.
YOU SEE KID AFTER KID COMING IN
AND THEY ARE COMPLETELY SELFLESS
AND THEY ARE FUNNY THEY ARE
CRAZY AND THEY'RE REALLY
TALENTED.
IT'S QUITE A REMINDER.
THE ADULTS, NOT ONLY THE KIDS,
WERE LIKE WE'VE GOT TO DO BE
BETTER.
I CRIED A LOT.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE GOING TO
LOVE THE SHOW.
SO MANY SPECIAL KIDS.
SO MANY DIFFERENT AREAS OF
EVERYTHING.
REALLY AMAZING.
RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE DOING LITTLE
MERMAID?
>> JUST STARTING.
I PLAY URSULA, THE SEA WITCH.
WE ARE JUST IN REHEARSALS.
IT'S BEEN A BLAST.
STEPPING INTO THE WORLD OF ROB
MARSHALL IS LIKE A FEVER DREAM.
I WENT TO LONDON FOR A WEEK AND
I'M LIKE, I DON'T GET TO GO TO
DANCE CAMP FOR A WEEK.
DO YOU WANT TO SLIDE DOWN THIS
40-FOOT CLAMSHELL?
I'M LIKE, YES.
OF COURSE I DO.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
IT'S BEEN WILDLY CREATIVE.
>> Ellen: FANTASTIC.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE IT.
WE ARE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
WE WILL PLAY AGAIN AFTER THIS.
>> [CHEERING]
>> WHAT DO WE LOVE?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SPEAK I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING
TO BE IT.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DID I LOOK LIKE BEFORE?
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN"
HARRISON FORD AND THE RETURN OF
>>> I'M PAT LAWSON
A QUICK LOOK AT THE STORIES
WE'RE .
AN EFFORT TO BAN ASSAULT WEAPONS
IN VIRGINIA FAILED.
>>> TRANSPORTATION REPORTER HAS
THE INSIDE SCOOP ON METRO'S NEXT
BIG .
THE LOOMING PARKING PROBLEMS AND
HO
>>> AND THE NEW TREND THAT COULD
STRAIGHTEN YOUR SMILE WITHOUT
COSTING YOU BI
WE'LL SEE YOU TH
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
MELISSA McCARTHY.
SINCE YOU ARE THE NEW HOST OF
"LITTLE BIG SHOTS," AND GAVE US
AN IDEA FOR A GAME CALLED
"LITTLE BIG SLINGSHOTS."
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S HOW IT WORKS.
WE'RE GOING TO USE THESE
SLINGSHOTS TO FIRE THE THOSE
BALLS OF THOSE TARGETS.
EACH TARGET IS WORTH A THOUSAND
DOLLARS TO THE CHARITY OF YOUR
JOIST.
>> LOS ANGELES
CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
>> Ellen: TO MAKE THIS GAME
MORE FUN, ANDY LASSNER, WILL YOU
COME OUT HERE?
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
AND THEN THE ARMS UP SO WE CAN
SEE THOSE TARGETS.
>> THAT'S A LITTLE WIDE.
>> Ellen: THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
PUT A TARGET ON HIM.
WE NEED ONE MORE TARGET.
OKAY.
COME ON.
YOU PLAY HOCKEY.
YOU ARE GOOD WITH THIS.
>> NOT THIS.
>> Ellen: HOW MUCH TIME ON THE
CLOCK?
ONE MINUTE.
READY?
SET.
GO.
>> OH!
NO!
, GOD
!
[LAUGHTER]
WAIT A MINUTE!
>> SEVEN, SIX, FIVE, FOUR,
THREE, TWO, ONE!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
>> [LAUGHS]
I GOT YOU A COUPLE TIMES.
>> Ellen: SUPPORTING
ORGANIZATIONS LIKE LOS ANGELES
CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
WE ARE GOING TO ROUNDED UP.
>> [LAUGHS]
OH, MY GOD.
[LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: HE IS STILL
CRAWLING.
WE ARE GOING TO ROUND IT UP TO
$10,000.
SPECIAL SNEAK PEEK OF "LITTLE
BIG SHOTS" MONDAY, FEBRUARY 24
AFTER "THE VOICE."
EVERY SUNDAY AT 8:00 ON NBC.
MELISSA IS GOING TO STICK
AROUND.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Ellen: WARREN HARDING HAD
THE LARGEST BLANK OF ANY U.S.
PRESIDENT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> IT'S TOO EASY.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Lo necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month,
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Plus, you can get up to $200 in
Visa Prepaid Cards.
Mix and match your perfect
Fios plan.
Only on Verizon.
♪ ♪
Ugh...What the what?
Okay wipe
pretty-please do your thing...
nice!
Nailed it!
Huggies® Natural Care® wipes,
gentle like A HUG.
HUGG ON
(VO)
Morning, noon, night;
indulgent, delicious,
irresistible.
Fancy Feast makes delighting
your cat delightfully easy.
Every recipe, every last detail;
another fancy way
to show your love.
Fancy Feast.
Introducing Savory Centers.
Paté with a center of gravy!
♪
Find something incredible,
from somewhere amazing.
Unique selection,
unbelievable prices.
HomeGoods.
Go Finding.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
WHAT DID I LOOK LIKE BEFORE?
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN"
HARRISON FORD AND THE RETURN OF
"INDIANA JONES"?
MARK WAHLBERG AND AVERAGE ANDY.
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
MELISSA McCARTHY IN HONOR OF
PRESIDENTS' DAY, MELISSA IS
HOSTING THE NEW SEASON OF
"LITTLE BIG SHOTS," FELT LIKE
THE BEST TIME TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO OUR FAVORITE 10-YEAR-OLD
PRESIDENTIAL EXPERT.
PLEASE WELCOME MACEY HENSLEY.
♪ ♪
HEY, MACEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> Ellen: I'M GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
>> Ellen: I'M GOOD.
SPEAK I BROUGHT SOME VALENTINES.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
ELLEN, SINCE WILLIAM HOWARD TAFT
SPEAK I BROUGHT SOME VALENTINES.
GOT STUCK IN THE BATHTUB, I HAVE
ELLEN, SINCE WILLIAM HOWARD TAFT
TO BE HONEST, I TAFT TO BE
GOT STUCK IN THE BATHTUB, I HAVE
HONEST.
TO BE HONEST, I TAFT TO BE
I'M STUCK WITHOUT YOU.
HONEST.
I MAY HAVE DUMPED TEA BUT I WILL
I'M STUCK WITHOUT YOU.
NEVER DUMP YOU.
I MAY HAVE DUMPED TEA BUT I WILL
JOHN ADAMS WAS PRESIDENT DURING
NEVER DUMP YOU.
THE BOSTON TEA PARTY.
JOHN ADAMS WAS PRESIDENT DURING
>> Ellen: I LOVE IT.
THE BOSTON TEA PARTY.
>> THERE WERE A COUPLE OTHERS
>> Ellen: I LOVE IT.
LIKE YOU BARACK MY WORLD WITH
>> THERE WERE A COUPLE OTHERS
BARACK OBAMA.
LIKE YOU BARACK MY WORLD WITH
THERE WAS, ARE YOU IN THE
BARACK OBAMA.
WHITE HOUSE IN 1814?
THERE WAS, ARE YOU IN THE
BECAUSE YOU'RE HOT.
WHITE HOUSE IN 1814?
THAT'S WHEN THE WHITE HOUSE
BECAUSE YOU'RE HOT.
BURNED DOWN.
THAT'S WHEN THE WHITE HOUSE
THERE'S QUITE A FEW OTHERS.
BURNED DOWN.
>> Ellen: VERY CLEVER.
THERE'S QUITE A FEW OTHERS.
YOU PASSED THOSE OUT LAST WEEK
>> Ellen: VERY CLEVER.
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY?
YOU PASSED THOSE OUT LAST WEEK
I HEARD YOU LOVED MELISSA ON
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY?
"THE GREATEST NIGHT OF
I HEARD YOU LOVED MELISSA ON
GIVEAWAYS."
"THE GREATEST NIGHT OF
>> THANK YOU.
GIVEAWAYS."
IT WAS FUN TO DO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ME AND MY MOM ARE WATCHING
IT WAS FUN TO DO.
AND I WAS LIKE, I'D LIKE TO BE
>> ME AND MY MOM ARE WATCHING
ABLE TO DO THAT AND MY MOM WAS
AND I WAS LIKE, I'D LIKE TO BE
LIKE DO WHAT?
ABLE TO DO THAT AND MY MOM WAS
GET ALL THAT STUFF AND I SAID
LIKE DO WHAT?
NO, I'D LOVE TO BE ABLE TO GIVE
GET ALL THAT STUFF AND I SAID
ALL THAT STUFF WAY LIKE YOU DO.
NO, I'D LOVE TO BE ABLE TO GIVE
>> Ellen: IT IS SO FUN TO GIVE
ALL THAT STUFF WAY LIKE YOU DO.
STUFF AWAY.
>> Ellen: IT IS SO FUN TO GIVE
I HOPE YOU GET TO DO THAT ONE
STUFF AWAY.
DAY.
I HOPE YOU GET TO DO THAT ONE
ALL RIGHT.
DAY.
I HAVE TO ASK YOU, WHAT ARE YOUR
ALL RIGHT.
THOUGHTS ON WHAT'S HAPPENING IN
I HAVE TO ASK YOU, WHAT ARE YOUR
THE COUNTRY RIGHT NOW?
THOUGHTS ON WHAT'S HAPPENING IN
>> WELL, THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF.
THE COUNTRY RIGHT NOW?
I WISH THAT WE COULD ALL COME
>> WELL, THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF.
TOGETHER.
I WISH THAT WE COULD ALL COME
INCENTIVE REPUBLICANS AND
TOGETHER.
DEMOCRATS, COME TOGETHER AS
INCENTIVE REPUBLICANS AND
AMERICANS.
DEMOCRATS, COME TOGETHER AS
THERE SOME WAY EVERYONE COULD
AMERICANS.
SEE THE GOOD IN A REPUBLICAN AND
THERE SOME WAY EVERYONE COULD
THE GOOD IN A DEMOCRAT WHY
SEE THE GOOD IN A REPUBLICAN AND
COULDN'T COULDN'T THEY SEE THAT
THE GOOD IN A DEMOCRAT WHY
IN EACH OTHER?
COULDN'T COULDN'T THEY SEE THAT
>> Ellen: I HOPE WE CAN FIND
IN EACH OTHER?
SOMETHING THEY CAN BRING
>> Ellen: I HOPE WE CAN FIND
EVERYBODY TOGETHER.
SOMETHING THEY CAN BRING
WE ARE GOING TO PLAY A GAME.
EVERYBODY TOGETHER.
IT IS HAIL TO THE BLANK.
WE ARE GOING TO PLAY A GAME.
["HAIL TO THE CHIEF" PLAYS]
IT IS HAIL TO THE BLANK.
>> Ellen: WILL READ A QUESTION
["HAIL TO THE CHIEF" PLAYS]
AND THERE'S A BLANK AND WE WILL
>> Ellen: WILL READ A QUESTION
FILL IT IN AND SEE WHAT WE SAY.
AND THERE'S A BLANK AND WE WILL
GEORGE WH BUSH HAD BLANK BANNED
FILL IT IN AND SEE WHAT WE SAY.
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE DURING HIS
GEORGE WH BUSH HAD BLANK BANNED
TERM.
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE DURING HIS
OKAY?
TERM.
WHAT DO WE SAY?
OKAY?
>> FRENCH FRIES.
WHAT DO WE SAY?
>> BROCCOLI.
>> FRENCH FRIES.
>> IS THAT WHY YOU WERE STARING
>> BROCCOLI.
AT ME?
>> IS THAT WHY YOU WERE STARING
>> Ellen: IT WAS BROCCOLI.
AT ME?
>> YES.
>> Ellen: IT WAS BROCCOLI.
>> I THOUGHT THERE WAS A
>> YES.
FRENCH FRY THING.
>> I THOUGHT THERE WAS A
>> Ellen: HE DIDN'T LIKE
FRENCH FRY THING.
BROCCOLI?
>> Ellen: HE DIDN'T LIKE
LET'S SEE THE NEXT ONE.
BROCCOLI?
JAMES BUCHANAN LOVED CABBAGE AND
LET'S SEE THE NEXT ONE.
ENJOYED HAVING BLANK PARTIES.
JAMES BUCHANAN LOVED CABBAGE AND
[LAUGHTER]
ENJOYED HAVING BLANK PARTIES.
>> I CAN'T RIGHT THE FIRST THING
[LAUGHTER]
THAT COMES TO MY MIND.
>> I CAN'T RIGHT THE FIRST THING
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S
THAT COMES TO MY MIND.
SEE.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S
WHAT DO WE HAVE?
SEE.
>> SLAW PARTY.
WHAT DO WE HAVE?
>> SAUERKRAUT.
>> SLAW PARTY.
>> Ellen: SAUERKRAUT?
>> SAUERKRAUT.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> Ellen: SAUERKRAUT?
SAUERKRAUT PARTIES.
IS THAT RIGHT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
SAUERKRAUT PARTIES.
IS IT JUST SAUERKRAUT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
LITERALLY JUST SAUERKRAUT WITH
IS IT JUST SAUERKRAUT?
NO OTHER ADDITIONAL FOOD?
LITERALLY JUST SAUERKRAUT WITH
>> PROBABLY.
NO OTHER ADDITIONAL FOOD?
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE PARTY.
>> PROBABLY.
>> Ellen: STINKY PARTY.
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE PARTY.
MACEY, YOU ARE WINNING.
>> Ellen: STINKY PARTY.
LET'S SEE THE NEXT ONE.
MACEY, YOU ARE WINNING.
WARREN HARDING HAD THE LARGEST
LET'S SEE THE NEXT ONE.
BLANK OF ANY U.S. PRESIDENT.
WARREN HARDING HAD THE LARGEST
[LAUGHTER]
BLANK OF ANY U.S. PRESIDENT.
>> IT'S TOO EASY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S S
>> IT'S TOO EASY.
SEE.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S S
>> THEY WERE SIZE 14.
SEE.
>> Ellen: SIZE 14.
>> THEY WERE SIZE 14.
LARGE FEET.
>> Ellen: SIZE 14.
[LAUGHTER]
LARGE FEET.
>> MORE THAN ONE WAY TO BE RI
[LAUGHTER]
RIGHT.
>> MORE THAN ONE WAY TO BE RI
[LAUGHS]
RIGHT.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
[LAUGHS]
THE NEXT ONE.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
DONALD TRUMP IS THE FIRST
THE NEXT ONE.
PRESIDENT TO USE BLANK ON A
DONALD TRUMP IS THE FIRST
REGULAR BASIS.
PRESIDENT TO USE BLANK ON A
>> OH, BOY.
REGULAR BASIS.
>> Ellen: OKAY?
>> OH, BOY.
>> I AM FROZEN.
>> Ellen: OKAY?
OKAY.
>> I AM FROZEN.
>> Ellen: I HAVE TWO ANSWERS.
OKAY.
ONE OF THEM I THINK IS RIGHT.
>> Ellen: I HAVE TWO ANSWERS.
WHAT DO WE HAVE, MACEY?
ONE OF THEM I THINK IS RIGHT.
>> TWITTER.
WHAT DO WE HAVE, MACEY?
>> Ellen: I WROTE TWITTER AND
>> TWITTER.
FRIED CHICKEN.
>> Ellen: I WROTE TWITTER AND
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
FRIED CHICKEN.
>> NOT MUCH.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> Ellen: ON A REGULAR BASIS.
>> NOT MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ON A REGULAR BASIS.
ALL RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
I HAVE A POINT.
ALL RIGHT.
NO.
I HAVE A POINT.
I'M HAVING TOO MUCH FUN.
NO.
>> THIS IS WHERE I TURN IT
I'M HAVING TOO MUCH FUN.
AROUND.
>> THIS IS WHERE I TURN IT
>> Ellen: DURING JOHN ADAMS JOHS
AROUND.
PRESIDENCY, DURING LONG BLANK
>> Ellen: DURING JOHN ADAMS JOHS
BECAME A FAD.
PRESIDENCY, DURING LONG BLANK
OKAY.
BECAME A FAD.
[LAUGHTER]
OKAY.
>> THUMBNAILS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: THUMBNAILS?
>> THUMBNAILS.
NOT THE REST OF THE NAILS?
>> Ellen: THUMBNAILS?
>> I GUESS.
NOT THE REST OF THE NAILS?
>> SO IT IS SAUERKRAUT PARTIES
>> I GUESS.
AND LONG THUMBNAILS.
>> SO IT IS SAUERKRAUT PARTIES
I DON'T WANT IT.
AND LONG THUMBNAILS.
IF YOU GIVE IT TO ME, I WOULDN'T
I DON'T WANT IT.
TAKE IT.
IF YOU GIVE IT TO ME, I WOULDN'T
>> Ellen: MACEY, YOU ARE
TAKE IT.
OBVIOUSLY THE WINNER.
>> Ellen: MACEY, YOU ARE
I HEARD YOU'VE BEEN TO EVERY
OBVIOUSLY THE WINNER.
PRESIDENTIAL LIBRARY EXCEPT ONE.
I HEARD YOU'VE BEEN TO EVERY
FOR WINNING, WE ARE SENDING YOU
PRESIDENTIAL LIBRARY EXCEPT ONE.
TO THE FRANKLIN D. ROOSEVELT
FOR WINNING, WE ARE SENDING YOU
PRESIDENTIAL LIBRARY.
TO THE FRANKLIN D. ROOSEVELT
>> THANK YOU.
PRESIDENTIAL LIBRARY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
I HOPE I CAN MEET YOU ONE OF
THESE DAYS.
HOPE YOU HAVE A REALLY SPECIAL
DAY.
- I mean, another season?
- Yes!
[laughter]
ANNOUNCER: With Giant Delivers,
we'll do the shopping for you
so you can do more
of what you love.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OUR NEXT GUEST STARS
AS ARCHIE ON THE HUGELY POPULAR
SERIES "RIVERDALE."
TAKE A LOOK.
>> ARCHIE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S ALMOST 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
WHY ARE YOU IN YOUR BOXERS?
>> EVERYTHING IS OKAY, MOM.
I WAS JUST AT A PARTY AND WE
WENT SKINNY-DIPPING AND SOME
PREPPIES STOLE OUR CLOTHES AS A
PRANK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
>> I HAD INSOMNIA.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> EVERYTHING IS FINE.
I'M SORRY IT'S SO LATE.
I'M GOING TO GO TO BED.
>> Ellen: PLEASE WELCOME
KJ APA.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT IS SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU SENT A VERY FUNNY AND I'M
GOING TO SHARE IT.
YOU SENT A BIRTHDAY VIDEO TO ME.
>> IS IF THE ILLICIT VERSION?
>> Ellen: IT IS THE VERSION,
THE WHOLE VERSION.
IF IT'S ILLICIT, I LIKED IT.
>> GOOD.
THAT'S WHY I DID IT.
WHAT'S GOING ON, ELLEN?
I HEARD IT'S HER BIRTHDAY SO
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
HOPE I CAN MEET YOU ON ONE OF TE
DAYS.
HOPE YOU HAVE A REALLY SPECIAL
DAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I NEED TO TAN.
I GUTTED THEY BLURRED IT OUT.
I KNEW IMMEDIATELY AFTER I DID
THAT, I KNEW I HAD THE BEST
VIDEO.
IN MY MIND, I WAS THINKING I
DIDN'T WANT TO DO NORMAL VIDEO.
I REMEMBER BEING OUTSIDE ON MY
BALCONY NAKED AND I WAS FACING,
I SAW MY REFLECTION.
I SAW MY ASS AND I WAS LIKE
PERFECT, I SHOULD DO IT FOR
ELLEN.
THAT'S HOW IT CAME ABOUT.
>> Ellen: THAT'S WHEN MOST
PEOPLE THINK OF ME, WHEN THEY
ARE NAKED ON THEIR BALCONY.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
THIS IS YOUR FIRST TIME ON THE
SHOW.
WE HAVE A TRADITION OF SHOWING
SHIRTLESS PHOTOS OF ANYONE WHO'S
ON FOR THE FIRST TIME.
SO WE MUST SHOW THEM.
SO THE QUESTION TO YOU IS, HOW
OFTEN DO YOU WORK OUT?
>> I WORK OUT AS MUCH AS I CAN.
I LOVE TO WORK OUT.
IF I CAN, TWICE A DAY.
ONCE A DAY.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
DO YOU LOOK HEALTHY AND GOOD.
IT'S WEIRD BECAUSE YOUR ACCENT
ON THE SHOW IS AMERICAN AND I
DON'T THINK PEOPLE UNTIL THEY
HEAR YOU SPEAK, KNOW THAT YOU'RE
FROM NEW ZEALAND.
>> IT CAN BE A SHOCK TO PEOPLE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THINK I'M FROM
AUSTRALIA.
>> Ellen: IT'S A CLOSE ACCENT.
>> TWO VERY DIFFERENT PLACES.
ALL THE TIME AT LEAST ONCE A DAY
GET MISTAKEN TO BE AUSTRALIAN.
>> Ellen: YOU SOUND LIKE
YOU'RE ANGRY ABOUT THAT.
LIKE IT'S A COMPETITION, LIKE
YOU LIKE NEW ZEALAND BETTER THAN
AUSTRALIA.
>> I DO.
I DO.
>> Ellen: SETTLE DOWN.
MY WIFE IS FROM AUSTRALIA.
I WILL FIGHT YOU ON THIS.
ALTHOUGH I WOULD LOVE TO GO TO
NEW ZEALAND.
SEEMS BEAUTIFUL.
IT LOOKS INCREDIBLE.
>> IT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL PLACE
ON EARTH.
>> Ellen: WELL.
>> NOTHING CAN KILL YOU THERE.
>> Ellen: THERE ARE A LOT OF
SCARY THINGS.
>> IN AUSTRALIA, YOUR WIFE WILL
TELL YOU THERE'S A LOT OF
SPIDERS COME A LOT OF POISONOUS
CREATURES THAT WILL KILL YOU.
A NEW ZEALAND, THERE'S NOTHING
-- THERE'S NO PREDATORS.
NOTHING CAN KILL YOU.
>> Ellen: THAT IS NOT TRUE.
THERE ARE THINGS THAT CAN KILL
YOU ANYWHERE YOU GO.
>> NO.
[SCREAMING]
[BLEEP]
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: HE IS LUCKY.
HE'S LUCKY I DIDN'T GIVE THEM
ONE.
>> Ellen: IS GOING TO HAPPEN
SOMEDAY.
>> HOW LONG IS HE BEEN IN THERE?
THE WHOLE TIME.
>> Ellen: FOR A WEEK I THINK.
>> [BLEEP]
[LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: I THOUGHT THAT WATER
IS FLOWING IN MY FACE.
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE?
>> Ellen: THE TIMING.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
CHEERS TO THAT.
>> Ellen: WE'LL TAKE A BREAK
AND TALK MORE.
>> WHAT DO WE LOVE?
>> [CHEERING]
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO
BE IT.
Get to Kohl's
And take an extra 20 or 15% off!
Tek-Gear hoodies are
just $12.74
Save on Scott Living
And on this Power Air Fryer
Plus - take an extra 15% off
your $50 Home Sale purchase!
And - Kohl's takes your Amazon
returns too!
Shop Kohl's and Kohl's dot com.
[police siren]
Dispatch, we got a code bubly.
Are you going to get him down?
No.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
>>> MOMENTS AWAY.
"FIRST AT 4," ASSAULT-STYLE
WEAPONS HERE TO STAY IN
VIRGINIA.
WHY DEMOCRATS VOTED DOWN THE
PROPOSED BAN.
>>> AND A NEW TREND TO
STRAIGHTEN YOUR SMILE WITHOUT
BREAKING YOUR BANK.
DOUG?
>>> BEAUTIFUL DAY ACROSS YOUR
AREA, PRESIDENTS' DAY.
A CHANCE OF RAIN TOMORROW.
No, no, no, no,  this ain't no
sandwich.
Because on a sandwich,
they ask you if you want cheese.
But on a Papadia,
cheese is what's holding the
whole operation together.
Get one now for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
I bet you've never seen a
sandwich do yoga before.
Ommmmmmmmmmmmm.
Introducing the new Papadias,
for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
KJ APA.
WE JUST GAVE HIM A LITTLE
CARDIO.
YOU DID A MOVIE WITH SHANIA.
>> IT'S CALLED "I STILL
BELIEVE."
MARCH 13.
>> Ellen: FANTASTIC.
BECAUSE OF "RIVERDALE" YOU HAVE
AN INSANE AMOUNT OF FANS AND
EARLIER TODAY YOU SURPRISE SOME
OF THEM BACKSTAGE.
LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENED.
>> YOUR FAVORITE THING ABOUT KJ.
>> HE IS SO CUTE.
THAT'S THE NUMBER ONE THING.
>> HIS HEART.
I FEEL LIKE HE HAS SUCH GOOD
RELATIONSHIPS WITH EVERYONE.
HE TRIES TO BE A BAD GUY BUT
HE'S NOT AT ALL.
>> THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
>> [SCREAMING]
[LAUGHTER]
>> HOW IS IT GOING?
VERY FLATTERING, VERY
FLATTERING.
ARE YOU OKAY?
KEEP GOING.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
>> WE WERE SAYING HOW PERFECT
YOU ARE.
>> I'M OBSESSED WITH
"RIVERDALE."
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MY FAVORITE THING, ARCHIE AND
RIVERDALE.
I ACCIDENTALLY BLEACHED MY HAIR
TOO MUCH AND IT WAS BRIGHT RED.
>> [SCREAMING]
[LAUGHTER]
>> HE LIKES THE HAIR.
>> I DO LIKE THE HAIR.
>> HI.
I'M KJ.
>> WHO DO WE LOVE?
>> KJ!
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO
BE IT.
>> [CHEERING]
>> DID YOU SAY ABS?
SORRY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO FUN.
THAT'S SO FUN.
ALL RIGHT, "RIVERDALE" AIRS ON
THE CW WEDNESDAY NIGHTS AT 9:00.
I WANT TO THANK KJ APA, MELISSA
McCARTHY.
>>> "FIRST AT 4," NEW TWISTS IN
A FAMILY TRAGEDY.
>> A 17-YEAR-OLD MALE.
>> WHAT A RELATIVE TELLS US
ABOUT THE LOCAL TEEN ACCUSED OF
KILLING HIS MOTHER AND
6-YEAR-OLD BROTHER.
>>> ASSAULT WEAPONS HERE TO STAY
IN VIRGINIA.
WHY SOME DEMOCRATS DECIDED TO
REJECT THE BAN.
>>> AND PRESIDENTS' DAY, BUT BIG
CHANGES COMING IN THE FORECAST.
WHAT'S UP FOR YOUR FORECAST.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>>> PLUS, STREAMING YOUR SMILE
AND SAVE YOU BIG AT THE DENTIST
OFFICE.
>> NOW WE CAN REDUCE SOME OF THE
COSTS AND PAST SAVING ON TO
PATIENTS.
>> WORKING FOR YOU AND YOUR
WALLET.
>>> AND RETURN OF THE CHAMPS.
>> THE METS TAKE THE FIELD IN
FLORIDA.
FULL TRAINING IN FULL SWING.
>>> AND THE NATIONALS PREPARE TO
DEFEND THEIR TITLE, HOW THEY'VE
ALREADY GOT THE COMPETITIVE
JUICES FLOWING.
>> Announcer: NEWS 4 AT 4:00
STARTS NOW.
>>> WELCOME IN TO NEWS 4.
WE START THIS AFTERNOON WITH AN
UNFOLDING TRAGEDY IN NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
>> THE TEENAGER ACCUSED OF
MURDERS HIS MOTHER AND YOUNGER
BROTHER JUST APPEARED IN COURT.
POLICE SAID 17-YEAR-OLD LEVI
NORWOOD ALSO SHOT HIS FATHER AT
THEIR FAUQUIER COUNTY HOME
FRIDAY BEFORE STEALING A CAR AND
TAKING OFF.
ARRESTED IN NORTH CAROLINA
SATURDAY FOLLOWING A NEARLY
24-HOUR MANHUNT.
NORTHERN VIRGINIA REPORTER DREW
WILDER IS LIVE NEAR THE FAMILY'S
HOME IN THE MIDLAND AREA.
WE HAVE MORE ON THE STORY.
DREW?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
THE FAMILY'S NEIGHBOR GAVE US
PERMISSION TO BE HERE THIS
EVENING.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO GO ON CAMERA,
BUT OFF CAMERA HE COULDN'T
REALLY FIND THE