[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WOO!
HI, EVERYBODY!
HI!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
I FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HAVE A SEAT, EVERYBODY!
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE!
Y'ALL, IT IS A GOOD LOOKING
CROWD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YOU HAVE YOUR NICE CLOTHES ON.
YOU HAVE YOUR HAIR DID.
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S NICE.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE,
EVERYBODY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU SAW THIS,
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED OVER THE
WEEKEND ON AN AIRPLANE AND IT
WENT VIRAL.
NOW THE CORONAVIRUS.
[LAUGHTER]
ANYBODY HAVE THE CORONAVIRUS?
JUST CURIOUS.
[LAUGHTER]
IT IS A VIDEO OF A MAN, PUNCHING
THE BACK OF A WOMAN'S CHAIR
BECAUSE SHE RECLINED HER SEAT.
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS?
[AUDIENCE REACTION]
IF YOU HAVE NOT SEEN IT, I WILL
SHOW YOU AND THEN WE WILL
DISCUSS IT.
SHE STARTED RECORDING THIS
COMING AND HE NONSTOP PUNCHED
THE BACK OF HER CHAIR, GLANCINGP
MAKING SURE --
HE OBVIOUSLY SAID SOMETHING.
ANYWAY.
IT LOOKS UNCOMFORTABLE.
BUT BROOKSTONE CHARGES $600 FOR
A CHAIR LIKE THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
ANYWAY, THE VIDEO STARTED A
GREAT DEBATE OVER WHO IS RIGHT
IN THE SITUATION.
THE MAN OR THE WOMAN.
I CANNOT EVEN BELIEVE THAT THERE
IS A DEBATE OVER THIS.
BUT BEFORE WE TAKE SIDES, I WANT
YOU TO HAVE ALL THE INFORMATION
THAT I HAVE.
I WAS NOT THERE, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT THE MAN COULD NOT RECLINE
HIS OWN SEAT BECAUSE HE WAS IN
THE VERY LAST ROW BY THE
BATHROOMS.
WHICH IN MY OPINION SHOULD BE
FREE, BUT FOR SOME REASON THEY
COST THE SAME AS ALL THE OTHER
SEATS.
[LAUGHTER]
SO HE ASKED THE WOMAN TO PUT HER
SEAT UP WHILE HE ATE, BECAUSE HE
HAD VERY LITTLE ROOM.
WHICH THERE ARE ON PLANES LIKE
THAT.
SO SHE PUT HER SEAT UP, BUT WHEN
HE FINISHED, SHE RECLINED IT.
THEN HE STARTED A BOXING MATCH
WITH HER SEAT.
HOW MANY VOTE FOR THE WOMAN THAT
HE WAS IN THE WRONG?
OKAY.
[APPLAUSE]
HOW MANY PEOPLE VOTE FOR THE
MAN?
[LAUGHTER]
OKAY.
YOU RAISED HER HAND, I AM JUST
SO CURIOUS.
WHY DO YOU THINK IT WAS OKAY FOR
HIM TO PUNCH THE BACK OF HER
SEAT?
HE DID, HE ASKED HER TO PUT IT
UP WHEN HE ATE, AND THEN SHE PUT
IT BACK DOWN WHEN HE WAS DONE.
YOU STILL THINK IT'S OKAY THAT
HE PUNCHED?
YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND, OR ARE YOU
GETTING PEER PRESSURED?
[LAUGHTER]
I AM JUST CURIOUS.
THE WOMAN REPORTED IT TO THE
FLIGHT ATTENDANT, AND THE FLIGHT
ATTENDANT TOOK THE MAN'S SIDE --
ARE YOU THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT?
[LAUGHTER]
THE FLIGHT ATTENDANT TOOK THE
MAN'S SIDE.
AND HONESTLY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT THERE IS A DEBATE, BECAUSE
SPEAKING JUST FOR ME, I CAN'T
BELIEVE ANYBODY HAS TAKEN THE
MAN'S SIDE, BECAUS TO ME THE
ONLY TIME IT IS EVER OKAY TO
PUNCH SOMEONE SEAT IS IF THE
SEED TO PUNCH AS YOU FIRST.
[LAUGHTER]
THEN YOU CAN PUNCH THE SEAT
BACK.
OTHERWISE DON'T PUNCH SOMEONE
SEAT.
IT IS A FIRST CLUE THAT YOU
SHOULD NOT BE DOING SOMETHING IF
SOMEBODY PULLS OUT A PHONE AND
STARTS RECORDING YOU FOR
EVIDENCE.
AT THAT POINT YOU KNOW YOU WILL
BE A YOUTUBE STAR, AND OUT THE
ONE WHERE YOU MAKE A MILLION
DOLLARS FOR OPENING TOYS.
ALSO AIRLINE SEATS ARE MADE TO
RECLINE.
SHE HAS THE RIGHT TO RECLINE HER
CHAIR.
THERE IS NOT A LOT OF LEGROOM
COMING ARE FRUSTRATED AND HOT
BECAUSE OF THE BEARD.
[LAUGHTER]
BUT YOU ARE ALSO AN ADULT AND
YOU HAVE TO ACT LIKE AN ADULT.
YOU ARE ON A PLANE.
DON'T PICK ON HER LIKE A THIRD
GRADER PUNCHING THE BACK OF HER
SEAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEBODY WOULD
THINK THAT IS OKAY.
THERE ARE A LOTF ANGRY PEOEERE,N
MORE COMPASSION.
WE NEED TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
SOMEBODY ELSE MIGHT BE FEELING.
WHAT SHE COULD BE GOING THROUGH
IN HER LIFE.
MAYBE HE IS GOING THROUGH
SOMETHING, BUT HE DID NOT HAVE
TO PUNCH HER SEAT.
IF YOU'RE EVER UNSURE OF HOW TO
BEHAVE ON A PLAN.
I SAY THIS AT THE END OF EVERY
ONE OF MY SHOWS, RECLINE TO ONE
ANOTHER.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
FOR SOME REASON PEOPLE THINK BE
KIND TO ONE ANOTHER.
I SAY "RECLINE" TO ONE ANOTHER.
TWITCH IS NOT HERE, SO I WILL
PICK A SURPRISED ANSWER OF THE
DAY.
SO IF I COME INTO THE AUDIENCE
AND PUNCH THE BACK OF YOUR
CHAIR, YOU ARE GOING TO COME
DOWN HERE AND BE THAT DANCER OF
THE DAY.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: YES, INDEED!
[APPLAUSE]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT WAS FANTASTIC, WHAT IS YOUR
[APPLAUSE]
NAME?
THAT WAS FANTASTIC, WHAT IS YOUR
>> JANAE!
NAME?
>> Ellen: JANAE!
>> JANAE!
YOU ARE FANTASTIC FOR DOING
>> Ellen: JANAE!
THAT.
YOU ARE FANTASTIC FOR DOING
IF TWITCH WAS HERE, HE WOULD BE
THAT.
PROUD.
IF TWITCH WAS HERE, HE WOULD BE
THE DIRECTOR OF THE NEW "BATMAN"
PROUD.
MOVIE RELEASED A SNEAK PEEK OF
THE DIRECTOR OF THE NEW "BATMAN"
ROBERT PATTINSON'S BAT SUIT.
MOVIE RELEASED A SNEAK PEEK OF
AND THIS IS A BIG DEAL.
ROBERT PATTINSON'S BAT SUIT.
HERE IS THE BAT SUIT.
AND THIS IS A BIG DEAL.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: UH, SO DRAMATIC.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT SOMEONE WHO
GIVES YOU A LOT MORE THAN A
SNEAK PEEK.
KIM KARDASHIAN...
[LAUGHTER]
RECENTLY SHE POSTED.
SHE DOES.
SHE IS VERY GENEROUS WITH --
RECENTLY SHE POSTED A VIDEO OF
HER KIDS PLAY ROOM ON INSTAGRAM.
THIS IS HER KIDS PLAYROOM ON
INSTAGRAM, WHICH IS TOTALLY
NORMAL IF YOU LIVE IN SIDE A
SUPERCLEAN FAO SCHWARZ.
THOSE ARE REAL HORSES, BY THE
WAY!
I ASKED PEOPLE TO SEND ME
PICTURES OF THEIR PLAYROOMS.
AND THIS IS WHAT I GOT.
THE FIRST ONE, THIS IS MCKENNA
H.
SHE POSTED, I ASKED HER TO CLEAN
UP HER ROOM, SHE TOOK A NAP.
SHE IS EXHAUSTED FROM DESTROYING
YOUR HOUSE.
[LAUGHTER]
HERE IS THE NEXT ONE, NICOLE H.
PLAYROOM NEEDED DECORATING.
[LAUGHTER]
I SAW THAT ON AN EPISODE OF
"CSI," I THINK.
THAT MEANS SOMETHING.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
SAM S WROTE, IT COULD BE WORSE.
WELL, SHE PUT HERSELF AWAY.
THAT'S GOOD.
[LAUGHTER]
JACKIE G, MY SON DESTROYS HIS
BEDROOM IN MINUTES.
LOOK AT THAT.
AND IN THE MIDDLE, LOOK AT THE
CARTONS OF EMPTY PEPSI.
[LAUGHTER]
THAT IS CLUE NUMBER 1 WHY.
TOO MUCH SUGAR.
AND THE CAT IS ON THE TOP OF THE
STEP, CANNOT EVEN GET DOWN TH
THERE.
IT HAS BEEN STUCK THERE FOR D
DAYS.
AND LOOKING FOR THE CAT FOR A
MONTH.
THANK YOU FOR POSTING THOSE.
THEY MAKE ME SO HAPPY I DON'T
HAVE KIDS.
[LAUGHTER]
WHEN I AM NOT BUSY ENTERTAINING
AMERICA, I LIKE TO READ STUDIES.
AND I READ A STUDY TODAY.
THIS IS SURPRISING TO ME.
I KNOW EXERCISING IS GOOD FOR
YOU, IT SAYS EXERCISING MAKES
YOU HAPPIER THAN MONEY, YALE AND
OXFORD RESEARCH SUGGEST.
I LOVE EXERCISING, IT MAKES ME
VERY HAPPY.
BUT YOU KNOW, MONEY IS NICE.
I WANT TO SEE IF IT IS TRUE.
I'M STARTING A NEW SEGMENT WHICH
IS CALLED "ELLEN STUDIES THE
STUDIES."
♪ ♪
ALL RIGHT, IF YOU SEE YOUR NAME
ON THE SCREEN, COME ON DOWN.
I WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO YOU.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI!
HOW IS IT GOING!
>> AMAZING!
THANK YOU.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> MY NAME IS KATELYN.
>> Ellen: WHERE DO YOU LIVE,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I LIVE IN SAN DIEGO, I AM AN
ASSOCIATE MARRIAGE THERAPIST.
>> I AM BLINN.
I GO TO UCLA, I AM A STUDENT!
>> Ellen: SLOW DOWN, WE WILL
TALK TO YOU LIKE THIS.
>> I GO TO UCLA!
I AM A SECOND YEAR.
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE YOU
STUDYING?
>> I STUDY PUBLIC AFFAIRS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: GREAT, ALL RIGHT!
SO BLINN, WE WILL HAVE AN
EXPERIMENT, I WANT YOU TO DO TEN
JUMPING JACKS, GO.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
OKAY.
AND THEY WERE BIG ONES TOO!
THAT WAS GOOD!
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> I'M TIRED.
>> Ellen: ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> I'M HAPPY.
>> Ellen: THAT'S FANTASTIC.
OKAY, CAITLIN, I'M GOING TO GIVE
YOU $1,000!
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> [SCREAMS]
ALL RIGHT, SHE IS A LOT HAPPIER.
THAT SETTLES IT.
BACK TO YOUR SEATS, MONEY WINS,
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
YOU POSTED A PICTURE FROM YOUR
HONEYMOON, I BELIEVE THIS IS.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT, BECAUSE
IT LOOKS EXTREMELY PAINFUL.
>> YES.
>> Ellen: YOU HAD TO GIVE UP
YOUR JOBS BECAUSE YOU ARE TAKING
CARE OF EACH OTHER, AND YOU
WANTED TO BUY A HOME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> I LIKE YOUR STYLE.
STYLE.
>> Announcer: YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT YOU WILL FIND ON "ELLEN."
>> Ellen: THIS IS ANDY'S
JOURNAL THAT I BORROWED.
DEAR DIARY, I HAVE SOME EXCITING
NEWS TO SHARE WITH YOU.
TODAY I BECAME A MAN.
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN,"
KATE HUDSON AND OLIVER HUDSON.
PLUS A SURPRISED SUPERSTAR ONLY
TWO GUYS KNOW, AND THEY ARE NOT
TELLING.
>> Ellen: IS OKAY FOR ME TO
MAKE FUN OF THEM, WHAT ARE THEY
♪ ♪ ♪
Start Maxximizing Today
in store and online.
The good news?
Our protection lasts all day.
The bad news?
Your patience might not.
Depend® FIT-FLEX®
Underwear offers
Your Best Comfort
and Protection Guaranteed.
Because, perfect or not,
life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend®.
New Tide POWER PODS one up the
cleaning power of liquid.
Can it one up spaghetti night?
It sure can.
Really?
Can it one up breakfast in bed?
Yeah, for sure.
Thanks, boys.
What about that?
Uhh, yep!
It can?
Yeah, even that!
I would very much like to see
that.
Me too.
Introducing new Tide Power PODS.
One up the toughest stains with
50% more cleaning power
than liquid detergent. Any
further questions?
Uh uh!
Nope!
One up the power of liquid with
new Tide Power PODS.
♪♪
At Walgreens,
we love smart savers.
Like movie savers.
Tee-time savers.
And especially
Medicare Part D savers.
So you probably know
making Walgreens your
preferred pharmacy means
up to $5 off on copays
and 100 rewards points
on prescriptions.
Because you're smart like that.
Save smartly on Med D.
Walgreens.
Trusted since 1901.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUEST HAS
BECOME ONE OF THE BIGGEST MOVIE
STARS IN THE WORLD.
HIS NEW MOVIE IS CALLED "ON
"ONWARD."
PLEASE WELCOME CHRIS PRATT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> THANK YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI!
>> Ellen: HEY, CHRIS!
I HAVE NOT SEEN YOU IN A LONG
TIME.
>> IT FEELS TOO LONG.
>> Ellen: YOU LOOK GOOD.
ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> I'M VERY HAPPY.
>> Ellen: I'VE NOT SEEN YOU
SINCE YOU GOT MARRIED,
CONGRATULATIONS!
>> THANK YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: STILL MARRIED, STILL
HANGING IN THERE?
>> NO, UNFORTUNATELY IT IS OVER.
YES, STILL MARRIED, GOING
STRONG.
SPIT ON YOU POSTED A PICTURE
FROM YOUR HONEYMOON, I BELIEVE.
AND I WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE IT LOOKS EXTREMELY
PAINFUL.
>> YES.
[LAUGHTER]
YOU WILL NOTICE THE BUTT.
THAT'S THE COLOR I TYPICALLY AM.
[LAUGHTER]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
I THINK IT IS THIS.
OVER THE LAST FIVE YEARS I'VE
BEEN DOING ALL OF THESE MOVIES.
AND IN THOSE MOVIES I LOOK SO
TANNED.
BUT I FORGET THAT IT IS SPRAYED
ON, AND I THOUGHT I WOULD GET
MYSELF A LITTLE BIT OF COLOR AND
I LAID OUT, AND THAT TOOK NO
MORE THAN 9 MINUTES.
>> Ellen: NO.
YOU ARE NOT --
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> HERE'S WHAT I REMEMBER.
>> Ellen: WERE YOU ON THE SUN?
[LAUGHTER]
>> THAT IS WHERE WE VACATION,
GUEST.
WE WERE IN A TROPICAL LOCATION.
AND I REMEMBER CATHERINE SAYING,
YOU HAVE TO PUT ON SUNSCREEN.
AND I SAID I WANT A LITTLE BASE
GOING, AND THEN WE WILL THROW
SOME SPF ON, I LAID OUT, AND I
WAS LIKE, IS SOMEBODY COOKING
NORWEGIAN BACON?
[LAUGHTER]
IT HAPPENED SO FAST.
I FORGOT.
TRANSLUCENT TO MY SKIN IS.
>> Ellen: THAT MUST HAVE PUT A
DAMPER ON YOUR HONEYMOON?
>> IT DID.
>> Ellen: HOW LONG DID THAT
HURT?
>> A LONG TIME.
I STILL HAVE A WEIRD TAN LINE
FROM IT.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO END WELL.
>> Ellen: NEXT TIME JUST TAKE
YOUR PANTS OFF SO IT EVENS OUT.
>> IT WAS SHIRTS ON SWIMMING FOR
THE REST OF THE WEEK WHICH IS SO
SEXY ON A -- ALL OF OUR,
EVERYTHING SHIRT ON.
EVERY ACTIVITY THAT HAPPENS ON A
HONEYMOON, SHIRT ON.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE A LONG TIME
TOGETHER, SHE HAS TIME TO SEE
WITH YOUR SHIRT OFF.
YOU JUST TURNED 40.
>> I DID.
I AM 40.
OH, THANK YOU!
[APPLAUSE]
YEAH, I AM 40 NOW.
>> Ellen: HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> IT FEELS GOOD.
GOING UP I THOUGHT 40 WAS SO
OLD, AND I REALIZE NOW THAT IT
ONLY SEEMS OLD TO PEOPLE WHO
WERE THE AGE THAT I WAS WHEN I
THOUGHT THAT.
BUT IT FEELS FINE.
MY BODY MAKES A LOT MORE NOISES
NOW, I HAVE AN ANGLE THAT JUST,
EVERY THIRD STEP IS GOING TO
CRACK.
MY KNEES POP, IT'S LIKE I GOT A
LITTLE BRASS BAND LIVING IN MY
HIPS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: WOW.
>> MY BACK CAN SCOUT.
THERE IT IS.
OH, YEAH, THERE IT IS.
>> Ellen: DID YOU HEAR THAT?
>> YES.
>> Ellen: DON'T DO THAT.
>> THEY TELL YOU NOT TO DO IT.
IT'S SO HARD NOT TO DO.
IT'S A LITTLE TRICK.
>> Ellen: DON'T DO IT.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
KATHERINE GOT YOU.
WHAT KIND OF GIFT WAS THIS, A
BIRTHDAY GIFT?
>> THIS WAS A BIRTHDAY GIFT.
YES.
>> Ellen: LET'S SEE THEM WHEN
THEY WERE GIVEN TO YOU.
THE AGE THAT THEY WERE GIVEN TO
YOU, WHAT KIND OF PIGS ARE THEY?
>> THEY ARE COONEY COONEY PIGS.
THEY ARE PETS, THEY ARE CALLED
TIM AND FAITH.
AND TODAY ARE OBVIOUSLY BASED ON
THE FULL LOVE STORY OF THE TWO
COUNTRY ARTISTS TIM McGRAW AND
FAITH HILL.
AND IF YOU LOOK, YOU CAN SEE
THAT THERE IS A PALPABLE
CHEMISTRY, AND THEY ARE BROTHER
AND SISTER, BUT THAT DOES NOT
MATTER IN THE PIG WORLD.
[LAUGHTER]
THEY CAN DO THAT.
IT IS NOT ILLEGAL.
>> Ellen: OUT WITH PIGS.
LET'S SHOW THE SIZE, WHAT ARE
THEY NOW?
>> THEY ARE MASSIVE.
THEY ARE HUGE.
THERE WILL PROBABLY GET UPWARDS,
PROBABLY 250-300 POUNDS NOW, BUT
THEY WILL DOUBLE IN SIZE.
>> Ellen: PIGS JUST KEEP
GROWING.
>> GET BIG.
THEY EAT LIKE PIGS.
>> Ellen: THEY DON'T SWEAT
LIKE PIGS, PIGS DON'T SWEAT.
>> THEY ARE SO SMART, THEY
JUST -- WHICH MAKES THEM
TERRIBLE PETS FOR YOUR YARD,
BECAUSE IT WILL DIG GIANT HOLES
IN YOUR YARD TO TRY TO CREATE
SOME MUD HOLES.
>> Ellen: BECAUSE IT COOLS
THEM OFF, THAT'S WHY THEY DO IT.
THEY ARE SMART AS CAN BE.
I'M GOING TO GET SOME.
>> YOU ARE GOING TO GET SOME?
WANT SOME?
DO YOU WANT COONEY COONEYS.
>> Ellen: LET ME GET SOME
LAND.
>> NO, THEY ARE GOING TO LIVE
WITH YOU AND PORTIA.
>> Ellen: I WANT THEM TO LIVE
WITH US, BUT THE DOGS WOULD
CHASE THEM AROUND.
BUT I WANT PIGS, GOATS, AND
SHEEP.
ALL OF THEM.
>> DO IT.
IT IS SO NICE.
>> Ellen: DON'T YOU HAVE OTHER
THINGS?
>> I HAVE SHEEP AND GOATS.
IT IS LAMBING SEASON, SO WE HAVE
TWO AND A HALF YUS.
THEY ARE BEING BORN RIGHT NOW.
WE HAD TWO MORE BORN LAST NIGHT.
>> Ellen: A LA YEWS.
>> OH, I LOVE YEWS TOO.
>> Ellen: TOLD A STORY.
>> I AM WORKING ON "THE TOMORROW
WORLD."
I EXECUTIVE PRODUCED, AND ONE OF
THE IDEAS WAS TO MAKE IT FEEL
GLOBAL WE WILL SHOOT ON A
GLACIER.
WE WENT TO ICELAND, WE SHOT ON A
GLACIER THAT HAS NEVER BEEN SHOT
ON, IT IS UNBELIEVABLE, IT IS
REALLY HARD TO SHOOT THERE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU SHOOT THERE
IN WINTER AND THERE ARE FOUR
HOURS OF SUNLIGHT PER DAY, BUT
WHEN WE GOT OUT THERE, THEY HAD
JUST UNCOVERED, AND THIS IS
CRAZY, A COUPLE OF WEEKS BEFORE
A COUPLE HAD BEEN FOUND IN A
FISSURE THAT HAD BEEN IN THERE
FOR 80 YEARS.
AND SADLY THEY DID NOT MAKE IT.
THEY WERE FULLY PRESERVED IN
LIKE THEIR GLACIER HIKING
CLOTHES FROM WHATEVER THAT WOULD
BE, 1930 OR 1940.
THEY HAD THEIR SUPPLIES, THEIR
RATIONS, AND THEY WERE LOVERS
AND THEY FELL DOWN IN THE HOLE
AND JUST WENT MISSING AND
RECENTLY --
>> Ellen: NOW THE FAMILY HAS
COME OF THAT IS CRAZY.
>> ISN'T THAT WILD?
WE GOT OUT AND NOBODY FELL IN
ANY HOLES WHILE WE WERE
RECORDING.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: GOOD FOR YOU.
WE WILL TAKE A BREAK.
MORE WITH CHRIS AFTER THIS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
WHAT DO YOU SLEEP IN AT NIGHT?
>> "ELLEN" UNDERWEAR.
>> Ellen: YES, THAT IS RIGHT.
>> THE FIRST TIME WE WERE ON
HERE, WE JUST HAD A TREMENDOUS
RESPONSE.
>>> WE ALL WANT SOFT SKIN AND A
.
BEFORE YOU HIT THE BEAUTY AISLE,
WATCH THIS WARNING, NEX ON NEWS
4:.
Cheerios... Do I look like a
child to you?
Honey Nut Cheerios
are heart healthy
and can help lower
cholesterol.
That's why we introduced
heart shapes.
Get it?
Ummm
Did you just ummm?
No.
I'm pretty sure I heard a ummm.
♪ ♪
>> DON'T LET THE MAGIC SPOOK Y
YOU.
>> ELBOWS.
>> WHAT?
>> ELBOWS UP.
THAT'S TOO HIGH.
>> I'M TRYING TO FOCUS HERE.
>> YES, FOCUS.
FOCUS.
>> I GOT IT.
>> IT WORKED!
IT'S HUGE!
AND YOUR --
OH, NO!
>> Ellen: THAT IS CHRIS PRATT,
AND THAT IS "ONWARD"!
[APPLAUSE]
TELL EVERYONE ABOUT THIS THAT
EVERYONE CRIES WHEN THEY SEE IT.
>> IT IS TRUE.
IT IS VERY MOVING.
IT WILL MAKE YOU LAUGH AND CRY,
IT IS PIXAR, WHICH YOU KNOW,
THEY HAVE SUCH A GREAT TRACK
RECORD OF AMAZING MOVIES.
AND IT IS A STORY OF TWO
BROTHERS THAT GO ON A QUEST
THROUGH THIS FANTASY WORLD, AND
THEY ARE ON A QUEST TO BRING
BACK THEIR FATHER THAT THEY LOST
AT A YOUNG AGE.
IT IS SO MOVING.
I GET CHOKED UP EVERY TIME I
TALK ABOUT THIS.
OUR DIRECTOR, HE AND HIS BROTHER
LOST THEIR FATHER WHEN THEY WERE
VERY YOUNG.
HE DOES NOT REMEMBER MEETING HIS
DAD.
AND THERE WAS A MOMENT WHERE
THEY FOUND THE USE AUDIOTAPES,
THAT HAD HIS DAD'S VOICE, HE
NEVER HEARD HIS VOICE, SO THEY
KEPT MISSING HIS DAD AND TOWARDS
THE END THEY SAID, THEY FINALLY
GOT HIS VOICE, AND HIS DAD
SIMPLY SAID, HELLO, GOODBYE.
AND THOSE WERE THE TWO WORDS
THAT HE HEARD.
SO THAT BECAME THE SEED OF THIS
IDEA ABOUT THE BOYS THAT WERE
GIVEN AN OPPORTUNITY TO CAST A
SPELL TO BRING THEIR DAD BACK
FOR ONE DAY AND SCREW IT UP AND
ONLY GET FROM HIS FEET UP
BASICALLY A PAIR OF PANTS, AND
THEY HAVE TO TAKE THE PAIR OF
PANTS ON A QUEST IN AT 24 HOURS
TO GET ANOTHER PHOENIX GEM TO
COMPLETE THE QUEST AND MEET
THEIR DAD.
IT IS REALLY MOVING AND DEALS
WITH BROTHERHOOD AND THE LOSS OF
A FAMILY MEMBER.
IT IS VERY MODERN.
IT IS AN AWESOME --
>> Ellen: AND IT IS PIXAR.
YOU CAN'T GO WRONG.
AND YOU ARE ABOUT TO START
SHOOTING O "DRASTIC WORLD."
AND THIS IS THE END?
>> THIS FEELS LIKE IT.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO SAY ANYTHING,
BUT I WILL TELL YOU EVERYTHING!
IT HAS EVERYBODY.
IT FEELS KIND OF LIKE --
>> Ellen: THE ORIGINAL CAST?
>> IT HAS PRETTY MUCH EVERYBODY
IN IT.
MAYBE I JUST BLEW IT, BUT I
DON'T CARE.
I KNOW THAT ALL OF THE CAST FROM
THE ORIGINAL "JURASSIC PARK" IS
COMING BACK.
>> Ellen: WHEN YOU LEAVE TO DO
THAT?
>> I LEAVE TOMORROW AND WILL BE
SHOOTING FOR A LONG TIME.
THIS SCRIPT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
THE DIRECTOR FOR "JURASSIC
WORLD" IS DOING THIS ONE.
>> Ellen: HOW LONG WILL YOU
SHOOT THIS MOVIE?
>> I WILL SHOOT ON AND OFF UNTIL
JULY.
>> Ellen: WOW.
>> IT'S PROBABLY CLOSE TO 100
SHOOT DAYS, IT IS A MASSIVE
MOVIE.
IT WILL BE ALL OVER THE WORLD,
THE STORY IS REALLY ENGAGING.
REALLY COOL.
AND --
>> Ellen: THAT IS AMAZING.
I CAN'T WAIT.
WELL ARE WE GOING TO -- WE ARE
GOING TO PLAY A GAME AFTER THIS.
WE WILL PLAY A GAME...
AFTER THIS.
>> WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER
THIS.
>> Ellen: THERE WE GO.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
WHAT DO YOU SLEEP IN AT NIGHT?
>> "ELLEN" UNDERWEAR.
>> Ellen: YUP, THAT'S RIGHT.
[DING]
YOU HAVE HAD TO GIVE UP YOUR
JOBS BECAUSE YOU ARE TAKING CARE
OF EACH OTHER.
AND YOU WANTED TO BUY A HOME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN,"
KATE AND OLIVER HUDSON.
PLUS A SURPRISE SUPERSTAR.
ONLY TWO GUYS KNOW, AND THEY ARE
NOT TELLING.
>> Ellen: IT'S OKAY FOR ME TO
>>> I'M PAT L
A QUICK LOOK AT THE STORIES
WE'R
FIRST, FAMILY IS ONE STEP CLOSE.
A WOMAN PLEADS GUILTY TO FAKING
HER .
>>> THEN A POSSIBLE GROCERY
HOW IT COULD EFFECT YOUR NEXT
AND A CONSUMER ALERT ABOUT THE
's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz
the first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those with
moderate to
severe psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement
of their
psoriasis
plaques.
Some even saw
100% clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
CHRIS PRATT, AND NOW IT IS TIME
TO PLAY ONE OF OUR FAVORITE
GAMES "BURNING QUESTIONS."
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
I WILL ASK A QUESTION AND HE
WILL ANSWER HONESTLY.
AND THEN WE'LL HIT THAT RIGHT
AFTER YOU ANSWER THE QUESTION
FOR NO APPARENT REASON.
IT MAKES IT MORE FUN.
>> IT IS A BUTTON.
>> Ellen: IT SEEMS WEIRD TO
ANSWER OR NOT DO ANYTHING.
SO WE DO THAT AFTER.
WHAT ARE THREE WORDS THAT BEST
DESCRIBE YOU?
>> VERY PROUD FATHER.
[DING]
WEARING BORROWED CLOTHING.
NOT MY WATCH.
[DING]
BUT LIKE IT.
>> Ellen: WHO WAS THE LAST
[DING]
FAMOUS PERSON YOU ARE EXCITED TO
>> Ellen: WHO WAS THE LAST
MEET?
FAMOUS PERSON YOU ARE EXCITED TO
>> GARTH BROOKS.
MEET?
[DING]
>> GARTH BROOKS.
'S FEELING WOULD YOU NAME A PIG
[DING]
AFTER GARTH IF YOU GOT ANOTHER
'S FEELING WOULD YOU NAME A PIG
PIG?
AFTER GARTH IF YOU GOT ANOTHER
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU LIKE COUNTRY
PIG?
STARS.
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU LIKE COUNTRY
>> ABSOLUTELY.
STARS.
I WILL HAVE ALL OF NASHVILLE OF
>> ABSOLUTELY.
PIGS.
I WILL HAVE ALL OF NASHVILLE OF
>> Ellen: IT IS A GOOD IDEA.
PIGS.
IF YOU HAD TO CHANGE YOUR NAME,
>> Ellen: IT IS A GOOD IDEA.
WHAT WOULD YOU CHANGE IT TO?
IF YOU HAD TO CHANGE YOUR NAME,
>> CHRIS PRATT BUT SPELT WITH A
WHAT WOULD YOU CHANGE IT TO?
Q.
>> CHRIS PRATT BUT SPELT WITH A
QURIS.
Q.
WE HAVE TIME.
QURIS.
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU DO THAT
WE HAVE TIME.
MAKES YOUR SON LEFT?
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU DO THAT
>> I DO VOICES.
MAKES YOUR SON LEFT?
[DING]
>> I DO VOICES.
>> Ellen: FOR INSTANCE?
[DING]
>> IT IS AWESOME, I JUST RIP OFF
>> Ellen: FOR INSTANCE?
BAD IMPRESSIONS OF PEOPLE AND
>> IT IS AWESOME, I JUST RIP OFF
VOICE CHARACTERS IN HIS BOOKS
BAD IMPRESSIONS OF PEOPLE AND
THAT ARE READ TO THEM AT NIGHT.
VOICE CHARACTERS IN HIS BOOKS
SO WE ARE READING "NARNIA," AND
THAT ARE READ TO THEM AT NIGHT.
I WILL BE LIKE JUST DOING REALLY
SO WE ARE READING "NARNIA," AND
BAD VOICES FOR HIM.
I WILL BE LIKE JUST DOING REALLY
BUT IT MAKES HIM LAUGH.
BAD VOICES FOR HIM.
>> Ellen: THANK YOU FOR NOT
BUT IT MAKES HIM LAUGH.
EXPLAINING.
>> Ellen: THANK YOU FOR NOT
[LAUGHTER]
EXPLAINING.
[DING]
[LAUGHTER]
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT WHEN YOU
[DING]
SEE THIS PICTURE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT WHEN YOU
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SEE THIS PICTURE.
THERE IS HOTNESS AROUND IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> SPRAY TAN.
THERE IS HOTNESS AROUND IT.
[DING]
>> SPRAY TAN.
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE THREE
[DING]
THINGS THAT YOU SAY TO YOUR PET
>> Ellen: WHAT ARE THREE
PIGS?
THINGS THAT YOU SAY TO YOUR PET
>> SOOEY.
PIGS?
COME GET IT.
>> SOOEY.
AND I LOVE YOU.
COME GET IT.
[DING]
AND I LOVE YOU.
>> Ellen: I FEEL SEXY WHEN...
[DING]
>> WHEN I GET THE SPRAY TAN.
>> Ellen: I FEEL SEXY WHEN...
[DING]
>> WHEN I GET THE SPRAY TAN.
THIS EPISODE BROUGHT TO YOU BY
[DING]
A --
THIS EPISODE BROUGHT TO YOU BY
>> Ellen: SPRAY TAN.
A --
THE THING THAT SURPRISES ME MOST
>> Ellen: SPRAY TAN.
ABOUT MY SPOUSE IS?
THE THING THAT SURPRISES ME MOST
>> OH, MY GOSH, HER ABILITY TO
ABOUT MY SPOUSE IS?
JUST FILL IN MY MANY DEFICITS.
>> OH, MY GOSH, HER ABILITY TO
THAT'S IT.
JUST FILL IN MY MANY DEFICITS.
>> Ellen: AWE.
THAT'S IT.
>> I HAVE A LOT TOO.
>> Ellen: AWE.
THAT'S WHY IT IS SO SURPRISING.
>> I HAVE A LOT TOO.
SHE STEPS IN.
THAT'S WHY IT IS SO SURPRISING.
TO SPEED ON WHAT BODY PART ARE
SHE STEPS IN.
YOU MOST PROUD OF?
TO SPEED ON WHAT BODY PART ARE
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU MOST PROUD OF?
[LAUGHTER]
THINK ABOUT IT.
>> MY SCHOOL.
[LAUGHTER]
IT IS VERY THICK.
>> MY SCHOOL.
>> Ellen: THAT IS A GOOD ONE.
IT IS VERY THICK.
WHAT IS SOMETHING THAT YOU DO
>> Ellen: THAT IS A GOOD ONE.
THAT ANNOYS YOUR WIFE?
WHAT IS SOMETHING THAT YOU DO
>> I LEAVE NAPKINS FOLDED ALL
THAT ANNOYS YOUR WIFE?
OVER THE HOUSE.
>> I LEAVE NAPKINS FOLDED ALL
LIKE I WILL USE A NAPKIN, AND
OVER THE HOUSE.
INSTEAD OF TAKING THE EFFORT TO
LIKE I WILL USE A NAPKIN, AND
THROW IT AWAY, I WILL JUST
INSTEAD OF TAKING THE EFFORT TO
FOLDED UP AND SET IT DOWN AS IF,
THROW IT AWAY, I WILL JUST
THAT IS FOLDED, SO IT BELONGS
FOLDED UP AND SET IT DOWN AS IF,
THERE.
THAT IS FOLDED, SO IT BELONGS
SO THERE IS A TRAIL OF NAPKINS.
THERE.
>> Ellen: PORTIA FORGETS TO,
SO THERE IS A TRAIL OF NAPKINS.
WHEN I AM PICKING UP THE
>> Ellen: PORTIA FORGETS TO,
PLACE MAT OR THE PLATE, I WILL
WHEN I AM PICKING UP THE
COME BACK AND SHE IS HOLDING THE
PLACE MAT OR THE PLATE, I WILL
NAPKIN IN HER LAP, SHE NEVER
COME BACK AND SHE IS HOLDING THE
LETS GO OF THE NAPKIN.
NAPKIN IN HER LAP, SHE NEVER
MAYBE THE DAY AFTER SHE WILL BE
LETS GO OF THE NAPKIN.
HOLDING THE NAPKIN.
MAYBE THE DAY AFTER SHE WILL BE
WHAT DO YOU SLEEP IN AT NIGHT?
HOLDING THE NAPKIN.
>> "ELLEN" UNDERWEAR.
WHAT DO YOU SLEEP IN AT NIGHT?
>> Ellen: YUP, THAT'S RIGHT.
>> "ELLEN" UNDERWEAR.
[DING]
>> Ellen: YUP, THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Ellen: WHAT DID YOU THINK
[DING]
THAT YOU WOULD HAVE DONE THAT
>> Ellen: WHAT DID YOU THINK
YOU HAVE NOT DONE YET BY THIS
THAT YOU WOULD HAVE DONE THAT
AGE?
YOU HAVE NOT DONE YET BY THIS
>> BEEN IN JAIL.
AGE?
[DING]
>> BEEN IN JAIL.
THERE IS TIME.
[DING]
>> Ellen: "ONWARD" IS IN
THERE IS TIME.
THEATERS MARCH 6TH.
>> Ellen: "ONWARD" IS IN
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
THEATERS MARCH 6TH.
CHRIS PRATT, EVERYBODY!
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CHRIS PRATT, EVERYBODY!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> THE FIRST TIME WE WERE ON
♪ ♪
HERE, IT WAS JUST A TREMENDOUS
>> THE FIRST TIME WE WERE ON
RESPONSE.
HERE, IT WAS JUST A TREMENDOUS
WE HAVE HAD AN AMAZING
RESPONSE.
FOLLOWING.
WE HAVE HAD AN AMAZING
♪ ♪
FOLLOWING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
Ready.
When you sell with
a Redfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
The french girl's yogurt
is set in a glass spot for eight
whole hours.
For her,
it is more important to feel
special than to be practical.
Oui, the french style yogurt.
>> Announcer: NEXT "ELLEN,"
KATE AND OLIVER HUDSON.
PLUS A SURPRISE SUPERSTAR ONLY
TWO GUYS KNOW AND THEY ARE NOT
TELLING.
>> Ellen: IT'S OKAY FOR ME TO
MAKE FUN OF MIMES.
WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO SAY?
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
EARLIER THIS SEASON WE MEANT AN
INCREDIBLE COUPLE DEALING WITH
AN UNIMAGINABLE SITUATION.
TAKE A LOOK.
ERIC IS A FIREFIGHTER FOR THE
CITY OF LOS ANGELES.
THIS PAST SUMMER HE MARRIED HIS
COLLEGE SWEETHEART.
AND JUST ONE MONTH AFTER THE
WEDDING THEY RECEIVED THE NEWS
THAT AT AGE 29, ERIC HAD ALS.
>> I STARTED GOOGLING AND
CHECKING ALL OF THESE BOXES.
AND I WAS LIKE, THIS IS CRAZY.
ALS KEEPS POPPING UP.
>> IT STILL DOES NOT FEEL REAL
WHEN YOU ARE THERE AND THEY ARE
TELLING YOU, THIS IS WHAT YOU
HAVE.
HE IS 29, HEALTHY.
WE JUST GOT MARRIED.
>> Ellen: IT DOES NOT SEEM
FAIR OR REAL OR ANYTHING LIKE
THIS.
IT IS JUST -- I DON'T EVEN HAVE
WORDS.
I AM SO SORRY.
SO I CALLED YOUR FIRE STATION,
SO THEY ARE HERE.
COME ON OUT!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HE IS PROVING ONCE AGAIN THAT
YOU ARE REMAINING THE STRONGEST
GUY IN THE ROOM!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I LOVE YOU.
>> Ellen: FROM COSTA MESA,
CALIFORNIA, PLEASE WELCOME BACK
ERIC AND AMANDA STEVENS!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
IT IS GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>> Ellen: HOW ARE YOU FEELING,
ERIC?
>> I'M DOING GOOD.
I'M DEFINITELY PROGRESSING, BUT
I FEEL VERY FORTUNATE THAT I CAN
STILL WALK, AND STILL HAVE MY
VOICE.
AND EXTREMELY GRATEFUL TO BE
SITTING HERE.
AND SHARE WHAT WE HAVE BEEN
THROUGH.
>> Ellen: SINCE YOU HAVE BEEN
HERE, THAT WAS THE WHOLE POINT
WAS TO HELP SPREAD THE WORD AND
GET THE WORD OUT THERE.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED SINCE YOU HAVE
BEEN ON THE SHOW?
>> SINCE WE HAVE BEEN ON THE
SHOW WE HAVE BEEN ADVOCATING
LIKE CRAZY.
WE JUST WANT TO BRING MORE
AWARENESS TO THE DISEASE AND
REALLY TELL PEOPLE WHAT ALS
PATIENTS ARE GOING THROUGH.
WE HAVE TRAVELED TO
WASHINGTON, D.C., AND MET WITH
CONGRESSMAN AND SENATORS.
AND WE EXPLAINED TO THEM WHAT
ERIC IS GOING THROUGH, AND WHAT
ALL OF THESE 30,000 AMERICANS
ARE GOING THROUGH.
AND HOW WE CAN CREATE SOME
LEGISLATION TO REALLY ALLOW
PATIENTS ACCESS TO TREATMENTS TO
HELP THEM FIGHT FOR THEIR LIVES.
>> Ellen: AND FROM WHAT I
HEARD, THEY SOUNDED SHOCKED,
THEY WERE NOT REALLY AWARE OF
THIS, RIGHT?
>> NOT MANY PEOPLE ARE AWARE
THAT THERE IS FOR THE FIRST TIME
EVER PROMISING TREATMENT FOR A
ALS.
BUT IT IS STUCK IN THE FDA
TRIALS.
AND THOSE ARE REALLY LONG TRIALS
AND PROCESS.
AND IT CAN TAKE UP TO 10-12
YEARS FOR A TREATMENT TO BE
APPROVED.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT TIME, YOU
KNOW?
WHEN YOU ARE DIAGNOSED WITH ALS,
YOU GET A 2-FIVE-YEAR DIAGNOSIS.
AND PARALYSIS COMES A LOT SOONER
THAN THAT.
>> Ellen: RIGHT.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO?
I MEAN, THAT MUST BE SO
FRUSTRATING TO BE DIAGNOSED WITH
THE DISEASE KNOWING THAT THERE
IS A POSSIBLE CURE, OR AT LEAST
SOMETHING THAT CAN HELP YOU SLOW
IT DOWN.
AND YET IT IS JUST STUCK.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
>> I THINK HAVING US BACK ON THE
SHOW, AND THE FIRST TIME WE WERE
ON HERE, WE HAD A TREMENDOUS
RESPONSE.
AND THE "ELLEN" EFFECT IS REAL.
WE HAVE HAD AN AMAZING FOLL
FOLLOWING, AND BEING ABLE TO
SPREAD AWARENESS AND KEEP
SPREADING THE WORD, AND OUR
STORY, I MEAN, THIS PLATFORM IS
JUST AMAZING.
>> Ellen: THIS HAS CHANGED
THEIR LIVES.
OBVIOUSLY.
AND IN MANY, MANY WAYS.
BUT YOU ARE GOING TO WASHINGTON.
YOU ARE ADVOCATING FOR THIS.
IT IS SOMETHING THAT YOU THOUGHT
YOU WOULD NEVER DO TO GO SPEAK
TO CONGRESSMAN AND SENATORS AND
FIGHT FOR SOMETHING, WHICH
OBVIOUSLY YOU ARE GOING TO DO.
BUT HOW IS THE FAMILY TAKING
THIS?
>> THEY HAVE BEEN EXTREMELY
SUPPORTIVE.
HIS BROTHERS WERE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C., AGAIN TO
CONTINUE TO TALK WITH THE
CONGRESSMAN AND SENATORS, AND
TRY TO REALLY CREATE A DIFFERENT
PATHWAY FOR ALS TREATMENTS.
BECAUSE LIKE ERIC EXPLAINED, HE
DOES NOT HAVE YEARS.
THEY DON'T HAVE EARS TO WAIT.
THEY NEED SOMETHING NOW TO HELP
THEM.
AND IT IS THEY ARE.
SO WE'RE TRYING TO DO EVERYTHING
WE CAN BY TELLING THEM THAT, AND
THEY ARE REALLY WILLING TO HELP.
>> YES, MY BROTHERS HAVE JUST
BEEN INCREDIBLE.
REALLY OUR WHOLE FAMILY HAS JUST
BEEN SO SUPPORTIVE.
AND THEY FEEL THE FRUSTRATION
THAT WE FEEL.
AND THEY ARE DOING EVERYTHING
THEY CAN TO USE THEIR VOICE AND
JUST SOMEHOW TRY TO FIX THIS
BROKEN SYSTEM.
>> Ellen: WE WILL DO
EVERYTHING WE CAN DO.
AND I TOLD YOU THAT THE LAST
TIME YOU WERE ON, I JUST WANT TO
KEEP HAVING YOU ON AND DOING
EVERYTHING WE CAN.
WE WILL TAKE A BREAK.
AND WE WILL BE BACK.
MORE WITH AMANDA AND ERIC AFTER
THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
YOU HAVE HAD TO GIVE UP YOUR
JOBS BECAUSE YOU ARE TAKING CARE
OF EACH OTHER.
BUT YOU WANTED TO BUY A HOME.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
MUSICAL >> Ellen: WE ARE BACK
WITH MY FRIENDS ERIC AND AMANDA
STEVENS.
YOU JUST GAVE A TED TALK.
AND FOR SOME PEOPLE, THEY SPEAK
PUBLICLY FOR A LIVING AND THAT'S
WHAT THEY DO.
BUT FOR SOMEONE WHO HAS NEVER
DONE THAT BEFORE, I WOULD THINK
A TED TALK WOULD BE SOMETHING,
PUBLIC SPEAKING IS ONE OF THE
SCARIEST THINGS FOR ANYONE.
HOW DID YOU FEEL?
>> IT WAS EXTREMELY TERRIFYING.
I KEEP TELLING ERIC HE IS THE
ONLY PERSON I WOULD EVER DO THAT
FOR.
IT WAS DEFINITELY THE HARDEST
THING I'VE DONE IN MY LIFE.
BUT I THINK IT IS ALSO AN
AMAZING OPPORTUNITY TO SHARE OUR
STORY.
WE WERE JUST FIGHTING LIKE CRAZY
FOR THAT.
>> Ellen: WE WILL KEEP
FIGHTING LIKE CRAZY AND RAISING
AWARENESS AND DOING EVERYTHING
WE CAN.
IT IS CRAZY THAT THERE ARE
TREATMENTS SITTING THERE THAT
NEED TO BE -- SPEED THEM UP.
AND YOU MUST BE, YOU STARTED
FEELING THESE THINGS RIGHT
BEFORE YOU GOT MARRIED BUT DID
NOT WANT TO SAY ANYTHING BECAUSE
YOU DID NOT WANT TO MAKE ANYBODY
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING.
AND THEN YOU ARE NEWLY MARRIED,
AND YOU MUST BE SO GRATEFUL FOR
AMANDA.
>> YES, WORDS CAN'T EXPRESS HOW
THANKFUL I AM.
AND SHE IS AN ABSOLUTE
ROCK STAR.
SHE HAS TAKEN THE BULL BY THE
HORNS, AND HAS REALLY JUST BEEN
A ROCK.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
WITHOUT HER.
>> Ellen: WELL, YOU GOT TURK.
AND YOU HAVE ALL OF US.
YOU GOT ME.
BECAUSE
I WILL BE YOUR ADVOCATE FOR T
THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
WHILE COMING YOU HEAR PEOPLE SAY
YOU HAVE TO LIVE YOUR LIFE EVERY
SINGLE DAY LIKE IT IS YOUR LAST
TODAY, AND WE ALL JUST TAKE
THINGS FOR GRANTED, BUT WITH
THIS DIAGNOSIS, IT HAS BEEN SIX
MONTHS?
HOW IS YOUR PERSPECTIVE ON LIFE
CHANGED?
>> YEAH, LIKE YOU SAID, YOU TRY
TO LIVE EVERY DAY YOU CAN THE
BEST YOU CAN, BUT UNTIL YOU'RE
STRUCK WITH SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
YOU REALLY REALIZE WHAT THAT
MEANS.
AND YOU JUST, YOU HAVE TO TAKE
IT ONE DAY AT A TIME.
AND TODAY IS MY BEST DAY.
I GET TO SIT HERE WITH MY WIFE,
AND I GET TO SIT HERE WITH YOU.
AND WE GOT TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION.
AND YOU HOLD ONTO THAT.
AND I JUST FEEL SUPER FORTUNATE
TO STILL HAVE THAT.
BECAUSE NOT EVERYONE DOES.
>> Ellen: ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT YOU WERE GOING TO DO BEFORE
ALL OF THIS, AND YOU HAVE HAD TO
GIVE UP YOUR JOBS, BECAUSE YOU
ARE TAKING CARE OF EACH OTHER.
BUT YOU WANTED TO BUY A HOME.
AND MY FRIENDS AT SHUTTERFLY
SAID WHAT CAN WE DO TO HELP?
BECAUSE WE LOVE THEM.
AND I SAID I LOVE THEM TOO.
AND THEY SAID WHAT CAN WE DO TO
HELP, AND I SAID MAYBE IF YOU
GIVE THEM $100,000 FOR A DOWN
PAYMENT FOR A HOME, AND THEY
SAID OKAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Ellen: YOU ARE WELCOME.
GO TO OUR WEBSITE TO FIND OUT
HOW YOU CAN HELP AMANDA AND ERIC
FIGHT AGAINST ALS.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Awesome!
Quickly, get the big blue bag.
Here are your groceries.
Groceries!
Teamwork makes the dream work.
(Professor)
Sound power is defined as
thought a surface
the product of sound pressure
and a component of the partial
velocity at a point.
[Sounds]
Kazoo sound
♪
You don't want to just live,
you want to thrive.
That's why Alive! Multi-vitamins
give you more vitamins
and minerals
than leading brands.
Plus, delivers a full
complex of B-vitamins
to help convert food
into energy.
So every day you're
alive and thriving.
You know what?
The way you care
for your baby...
(phone ring-tone plays)
Is absolutely perfect.
And that inspired
our perfect diaper,
our softest yet
with trusted protection.
New Huggies Special Delivery®.
New Glade Tranquil Lavender
and Aloe plugin scented oil.
Experience a more authentic
lavender.
True fragrance crafted only
by Glade.
S.C. Johnson.
[police siren]
Dispatch, we got a code bubly.
Are you going to get him down?
No.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
♪
Find something incredible,
from somewhere amazing.
Unique selection,
unbelievable prices.
HomeGoods.
Go Finding.
.
>>> MOMENTS AWAY, FIRST AT 4:00,
THREATEN TO TO STRIKE.
SUSAN HOGAN DESCRIBES THE
BATTLES BETWEEN GROCERY STORES A
PHONY PSYCHIATRIST COMES CLEAN.
REACTION FROM ANGRY PARENTS YOU
WILL SEE ONLY ON NEWS 4.
DOUG.
>>> WE SAW PLENTY OF SUNSHINE,
W THE COLD SHARENO
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: I WANT TO THANK
CHRIS PRATT.
I ALSO WANT TO THANK EVERYONE
WHO IS FOLLOWING MY NEW
INSTAGRAM ACCOUNT PAWS UP.
WE HIT A MILLION FOLLOWERS OVER
THE WEEKEND, WHICH MAKES US THE
FASTEST NONJENNIFER ANISTON
ACCOUNT TO REACH A MELON.
IN HONOR OF THAT AND JENNIFER
ANISTON'S BIRTHDAY, HARRIS AND
AFGHAN WHO LOOKS LIKE JENNIFER
ANISTON.
WE CALL THAT JENNIFER
AFGHANISTAN.
HI, JEN.
IF YOU ARE NOT FOLLOWING PAWS
UP, I RECOMMEND YOU DO.
YOU SEE SO MANY GREAT VIDEOS,
THESE ARE THINGS THAT I FIND OR
PEOPLE SUBMIT THEM.
YOU CAN GO TO "ELLEN TUBE" AND
SUBMIT TO YOUR OWN PETS OR
THINGS YOU KNOW.
HERE'S THE FIRST ONE.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
♪ ♪
[LAUGHTER]
'S VIEW ON THE TINIEST PIG I
HAVE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
THESE ARE MY ANIMALS.
>> GOOD MORNING, DARLING.
[LAUGHTER]
NO.
THERE YOU GO.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
BE SURE TO FOLLOW PAWS UP, THE
ONLY PLACE THAT PORTIA AND I
POST OUR VIDEOS.
YOU CAN GO RIGHT NOW.
I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW!
RECLINE TO ONE ANOTHER.
.
>>> FIRST AT 4:00, THREATENING
TO STRIKE.
I'M SUSAN HOGAN WITH DEVELOPING
DETAILS ON THE BATTLE BETWEEN
WORKERS AND LOCAL GROCERY STORES
AND HOW IT COULD AFFECT YOUR
STORE.
>>> BREEZY.
A LITTLE CHILLY TODAY.
A LOT COLDER AIR MAKING ITS WAY
IN, EVEN A SMALL CHANCE FOR
SNOW.
>>> LIVE IN NEVADA, WHY WE
EXPECT THE DEMOCRATS TO BRING
THE HEAT AT TONIGHT'S DEBATE.
>> FIRST ONLY AT NEWS 4, LOCAL
FAMILIES ONE STEP CLOSER TO
BANKRUPTCY.
>>> JULIE CARRIE CONFRONTS HER
ABOUT IT.
YOU ARE PRE TENDING TO BE A
PSYCHOLOGY AND DIAGNOSING
CHILDREN.
>> WE ARE LIVE WITH NEW
REACTION.
>> AND WE START THIS AFTERNOON
WITH THAT NASSAU 4 EXCLUSIVE.
SHE CALLS HERSELF DR. AVERY,
CLAIMING SHE WAS A PSYCHOLOGIST
AND TREATED DOZENS OF NORTHERN
VIRGINIA CHILDREN.
>> IT TURNS OUT SHE NEVER EVEN
GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE.
NOW SHE IS ENTERING PLEAS TO
NINE FELONY COUNTS FACING
CHARGES SHE WAS A COMPLETE
FRAUD, DODGING OUR CAMERA,
REFUSING TO ANSWER QUESTIONS.
>>> ONLY ON NEWS 4, JULIE CARRIE
WAS IN THE COURTROOM PACKED WITH
ANGRY PARENTS.
>> Reporter: SHARONDA AVERY,
AFTER A HEARING THAT DISCLOSED
NEW DETAILS, NEWS 4 GETTING THE
CHANCE TO CONFRONT HER FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
>> Reporter: MS. AVERY, WHY DID
YOU DO THIS TO ALL THESE PEOPLE?
WHY DID YOU REPRESENT YOURSELF
AS A