Eargo, hear life to the fullest.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪♪ I KNOW THIS PAIN ♪
♪ WHY DO YOU LOCK YOURSELF UP IN
THESE CHAINS? ♪
♪ NO ONE CAN CHANGE YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ EXCEPT FOR YOU ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LET ANYONE STEP ALL
OVER YOU ♪
♪ JUST OPEN YOUR HEART ♪
♪ AND YOUR MIND ♪
♪ IS IT REALLY FAIR TO FEEL THIS
WAY INSIDE? ♪
♪ OH ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ SOMEDAY, SOMEBODY'S GONNA MAKE
YOU WANNA TURN AROUND ♪
♪ AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN, BABY ♪
♪ ARE YOU GONNA LET THEM HOLD
YOU DOWN ♪
♪ AND MAKE YOU CRY? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW THINGS CAN
CHANGE? ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE
DAY ♪
♪ CAN YOU HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE
DAY? ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: GIVE IT UP FOR
WILSON PHILLIPS!
♪ ♪
♪ SOMEDAY, SOMEBODY'S GONNA MAKE
YOU WANNA TURN AROUND ♪
♪ AND SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ UNTIL THEN, BABY ♪
♪ ARE YOU GONNA LET THEM HOLD
YOU DOWN ♪
♪ AND MAKE YOU CRY? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW? ♪
♪ DON'T YOU KNOW THINGS CAN
CHANGE? ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ IF YOU HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE
DAY ♪
♪ CAN YOU HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE
DAY? ♪
♪ THINGS'LL GO YOUR WAY ♪
♪ HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: GIVE IT UP FOR
WILSON PHILLIPS!
COME ON, COME ON!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WELCOME TO
"THE KELLY CLARKSON SHOW,"
EVERYBODY!
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE AN
EPIC SHOW WHEN IT WILL SEND A
FREAKING HERE!
THEY'LL BE HOLDING ON WITH US
ALL HOUR LONG.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES, TELL US WHAT
ELSE IS COMING UP.
>> FROM "VAMPIRE DIARIES" AND
THE NETFLIX HIT "V WARS" AT THE
SMOLDERING IAN SUMMON HOLDER IS
HERE!
THEN, KELLY HELPS TO WIPE OFF
THE VERY ROOM ROMANTIC SURPRISE
FOR HER POLICE OFFICER HUSBAND.
>> Kelly: DON'T FORGET, THAT
KELLY IS STILL BRINGING ALL THE
FIELDS FEBRUARY THIS MONTH.
SO I HAVE A SURPRISING LOVE BOMB
THAT COULD GO OFF AT ANY MOMENT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: BEFORE WE GET TO
CHATTING I WANT CHYNNA, WENDY,
AND KEARNY TO MEET THE FAN WHO
REQUESTED THEIR SON PULLED LOOK
AT THIS VIDEO SHE SENT US FROM
HER BACHELORETTE PARTY.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THAT'S MY FAVORITE
PART.
SO PEOPLE MAY HAVE BEEN DRINKIN
DRINKING.
WHERE IS SHE?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: CONGRATULATIONS ON A
PHENOMENAL PARTY.
WHEN IS THE WEDDING?
>> MARCH 28TH!
>> WHAT IS YOUR CONNECTION OTHER
THAN THAT IT'S FABULOUS?
>> IT'S FABULOUS BUT THESE ARE
SOME OF MY BEAUTIFUL BRIDESMAID
BRIDESMAIDS.
SHE HAS BEEN OBSESSED WITH
WILSON PHILLIPS AND THE SONG
EVER SINCE WE SAW "BRIDESMAIDS"
A LONG TIME AGO AND WE HAVE SANG
EVERY TIME WE GET TOGETHER.
MY FIANCE'S LAST NAME AS WELL
SEND SO WE THOUGHT THE THEME
COULD BE "HOLD ON" BY WILSON
PHILLIPS THAT WE'VE BELTED OUT A
LOT.
IT IS LOVE IT!
I LOVE THAT "BRIDESMAIDS, I GREW
UP, I LOVE THIS SONG.
I GREW UP WITH THIS SONG BUT
THAT MOVIE KIND OF REINVENTED
THE SONG AND KIND OF INTRODUCED
ITSELF TO A WHOLE NEW GENERATION
OF PEOPLE.
IS THAT CRAZY?
>> THE PHONE STARTED RINGING
AGAIN!
>> IT'S SUCH A GREAT SONG.
>> IT'S INSPIRING.
>> IT REALLY IS.
DID YOU ALL ENJOY DOING THAT
MOVIE?
>> I HATE ACTING.
BECAUSE WE HAD TO SING ABOUT 30
TIMES.
>> EVERYONE THERE LOVED IT.
I WASN'T THERE BUT I'M SURE IT
WAS AWESOME.
GETTING SOMEBODY THAT YOU LOVE
TO SING A SONG 30 TIMES AND
DIDN'T HAVE TO PAY FOR IT?
AND THE CAST.
>> SO GREAT!
>> SO FUNNY.
>> Kelly: SO ARE YOU GUYS UP
FOR SOME AUDIENCE QUESTIONS?
OKAY.
SO WHERE IS MICKEY AT?
HI, MICKEY!
OH, MY GOSH.
SO WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> FIRST OFF, CAN I SAY WHAT
HUGE FAN I AM OF YOU GUYS?
YOUR MUSIC WAS THE SOUNDTRACK TO
MY LIFE IN THE '90s AND I
HONESTLY WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT
THROUGH WITHOUT YOU.
>> Kelly: SO COOL.
>> MY QUESTION IS, IS THERE ANY
CHANCE FOR A REUNION COME UP
MAYBE AN ALBUM OR TO HER?
>> WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE DO ONE SHOW MONTH.
>> Kelly: YOU DO?
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> IT'S NOT REALLY UP TO HER
WITH SHOW MONTH.
SPEAK OUT THERE'S NINE CHILDREN.
BUT WILL COMP YOU.
YOU NEED TO BE OUR CHEERLEADER.
>> Kelly: WEARS JASON AT.
HEY, JASON!
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
SPEAK OUT SO LIKE YOU I GREW UP
LISTENING TO WILSON PHILLIPS AND
I HAVE TO ASK, FOR THE LEGIONS
OF FANS, WHY DID YOU BREAK UP
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO?
I KNOW IT'S A QUESTION, RIGHT?
BUT WHAT MADE YOU GUYS WANT TO
GET BACK TOGETHER?
>> OR DRAMA, BECAUSE I'M IN.
>> IT WASN'T QUITE A BREAKUP.
>> TELL THE REAL STORY, PLEASE.
>> WE WANT THE TEA, GIVE US THE
T!
>> I TALKED TO THE JONAS
BROTHERS BONNET AND THEY CAME
BACK, IT HAPPENS.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOUR FAMILY.
IT HAPPENS LIKE THAT BUT THEN
YOU COME BACK TOGETHER WHEN
YOU'RE OLDER, I THINK IT HAPPENS
A LOT.
>> IT WAS TRAGIC.
IT WAS REALLY SAD FOR ALL OF US,
IT REALLY WAS BUT IT WAS TIME.
WE WERE OVERLY BURNED OUT.
I NEEDED A BREAK.
I'LL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
I REALLY NEEDED A BREAK AND
WE'RE SINGING TOGETHER AGAIN AND
THAT'S WHAT MATTERS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THANK YOU, JASON!
HI SO WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
BOTH OF YOU GUYS, THE GROUP AND
YOU, BEING HERE.
YOU GUYS WERE THE FIRST FEMALE
GROUP TO GET NUMBER ONE, YOUR
NUMBER ONE ALBUM, HOW DID YOU
FEEL?
WHERE WERE YOU GUYS?
>> ARE WE IN JAPAN?
I THINK WE WERE IN JAPAN.
IT IS TO BE ONE OH, MY GOD, "WE
WERE IN JAPAN."
>> I WOKE UP TO HEARING
SCREAMING AND I KNEW SHE WAS AN
EXTRA TO ME AND I KNEW HER SON
HAD GOT NUMBER ONE BECAUSE WE
SET UP THE GHOST NUMBER ONE YOU
HAVE TO CALL US, WE DON'T CARE
WHAT TIME OF NIGHT IT IS, WAKE
US UP, AND I HEARD HER SCREAM,
AND I WAS LIKE, IT'S NUMBER ONE.
>> IT WAS 3:00 A.M.
>> SHE WAS ALWAYS THE FIRST TO
KNOW EVERYTHING, FOR SOME
REASON.
>> YOU GUYS HUGGED EACH OTHER,
IT WAS A SPECIAL MOMENT.
>> Kelly: WHO DID YOU KNOCK
OFF THAT NUMBER ONE SPOT?
IS THAT A TRIP?
NICE JOB QUEEN OF POP, HERE I
AM.
THAT'S AWESOME.
THERE WAS SO MUCH GREAT MUSIC
BACK THEN.
I LOVE MUSIC NOW, BUT THE
'90s?
LOVE IT.
SO GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE HAVE TO TAKE A QUICK
BREAK.
DO YOU MIND?
♪♪ HOLD ON FOR ONE MORE DAY ♪♪
[APPLAUSE]
Hey there!
Kelly Clarkson! What're
you doing on our sofa?
What're you doing on your sofa?
Try Wayfair. You got this!
Woah. Yeah!
Let me try!
All alright, get it!
Blow it up!
That's what I'm talking about.
Except that's my seat, so.
All right, so maybe
after the movie
let's talk about that
bedroom of yours!
When was she in our bedroom?
Ahoyy! (excited
squeal, giggling, panting)
Gotcha!
Ah!
Nooooo...
Noooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent than
the leading ordinary brand.
Ahoy! (laughing)
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT, Y'ALL,
WELCOME BACK.
I'M HANGING OUT WITH A NEW
GIRLFRIENDS, CHYNNA PHILLIPS AND
WENDY AND CARNIE IT WILSON, ALSO
KNOWN AS WILSON PHILLIPS.
IT'S BEEN 30 YEARS SINCE HOLD ON
WITH SONG OF THE YEAR.
WITH THEIR A TIME IN YOUR LIFE
THAT WAS KIND OF EXACTLY ON
POINT AND YOU NEEDED TO HEAR
THAT MESSAGE?
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
>> I WAS REALLY IN A DARK, DARK
SPACE WHEN THAT LYRIC WAS
WRITTEN.
I WAS REALLY AT A POINT IN MY
LIFE WHERE IT FELT LIKE, I WAS
AT A CROSSROADS AND I REALLY
FELT LIKE IF I DIDN'T GET MY
LIFE TOGETHER AND STOP DOING THE
DRUGS AND, YOU KNOW, I HAD A
REALLY BAD BOYFRIEND AT THE TIME
AND I JUST WAS IN A LOT OF PAIN
AND I SAID IF I DON'T CHANGE MY
COURSE I'M GOING TO BE IN A LOT
OF TROUBLE.
SO I KNEW THAT I WAS AT A
CROSSROADS AND I HAD TO HOLD ON
FOR ONE MORE DAY OR JUST DIE.
>> Kelly: CAN I SAY SOMETHING
HONEST ABOUT THAT, BECAUSE NOT
EVERYBODY IS HONEST ABOUT THAT.
>> I'M SOBER 15 YEARS.
AND I WAS SAYING, I NEED IT NOW
IN THIS WORLD IN THIS TIME.
WE NEED INSPIRATION LIKE THIS, A
SONG THAT CAN HELP GET YOU
THROUGH IT, YOU KNOW?
IT'S TRUE.
>> Kelly: SO WHATEVER YOUR
FAVORITE MEMORIES FROM THE TIME
IT HIT NUMBER ONE?
DID YOU SPLURGE OR DO ANYTHING?
>> THE FIRST TIME I HEARD IT WAS
ON MY BIRTHDAY ON THE RADIO.
IT WAS ON MY BIRTHDAY.
>> Kelly: WHAT A GREAT GIFT
THAT WAS.
>> I REMEMBER ALL THE DETAILS, I
SWEAR TO GOD.
>> HOW DO YOUR MEMBER THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS TERRIBLE IN SCHOOL, I HAVE
NO CLUE WHY.
BUT DATES, IT'S WEIRD.
BUT JUST KNOWING THAT WE WERE SO
YOUNG WHEN THIS HAPPENED, WE
WERE ON THE WHIRLWIND, ON TOUR,
WE DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING EXCEPT
THAT WE ARE GROUP THAT LOVED TO
SING AND WE WERE EMBRACED BY THE
WORLD AND WE WERE SO THANKFUL
FOR THAT.
>> Kelly: YOU JUST SAID
SOMETHING INTERESTING AND I
CONFESS THIS WHEN WE WERE
REHEARSING BUT I HAD NO IDEA,
EVERYONE MAKES FUN OF ME NOW, I
HAD NO IDEA WHO YOUR PARENTS
WERE.
>> RIGHT, NOT EVERYBODY DOES.
>> Kelly: UNTIL LAST NIGHT!
UNTIL LAST NIGHT.
I WAS WHY DO THEY KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THE MAMAS AND THE PAPAS
AND THE BEACH BOYS?
I WAS LIKE, I LOVE THAT, BUT
WHAT DOES THIS HAVE TO DO WITH
THAT?
AND THEN I WAS LIKE, WHAT?
I HAD NO IDEA.
ON YOUR OWN MERITS.
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
PARENTS OR ANYTHING.
I THINK THAT'S KIND OF
SOMETHING, BECAUSE TO GROW UP
AND I IMAGINE THAT WAS VERY
HARD, I'M GETTING THAT WITH MY
KIDS AND I'M SURE YOU HAVE TWO
AS WELL BUT BEING IN THE
PUBLIC EYE AND HAVING PARENTS SO
FAMOUS AND TRYING TO NAVIGATE
THAT AND WHAT IS NORMAL.
>> THERE WAS NO NORMAL.
THAT WAS OUR NORMAL.
IT WAS CHAOS.
>> Kelly: THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> WE ALSO HAVE A GREAT MOM,
MARILYN, WHO IS IN THE AUDIENCE.
BUT SHE WAS REALLY, SHE WAS
REALLY GREAT AT KEEPING IT
STEADY AND BEING REAL ABOUT
THINGS, YOU KNOW?
NOT EVERYTHING IS NORMAL, OR
WHAT IS NORMAL, AND BUILDING OUR
SELF-ESTEEM IS PEOPLE AND
SHOWING US LOVE AND THAT'S WHAT
WE INSTILLED IN OUR KIDS.
>> Kelly: IT'S A WEIRD THING
TO NAVIGATE.
SINCE FINDING THAT OUT, AND I
KIND OF RIDE, YOU WERE PUT TO
BED BY SIR ELTON JOHN?
AND I WAS LIKE, WHAT?
WHAT IS YOUR LIFE?
THAT'S INSANE.
SPEAK OUT DID HE SING YOU A
LULLABY?
>> HE REMINDED ME WHEN I WAS ON
THE TALK WITH HIM A COUPLE OF
YEARS AGO THAT, "DON'T YOU
REMEMBER I PUT YOU TO SLEEP" AND
I WAS LIKE WHAT?
I DON'T, BUT I'M TELLING YOU
EVERYONE.
HE WANTED TO BUY MY DAD'S PIANO
THAT HE WROTE "GOOD VIBRATIONS"
ON.
SOLID PIANO, LOT OF MEMORIES
THERE AND HE WANTED THIS PIANO.
HUGH CAME OVER AND HE IS
PROBABLY BEGGING FOR IT, MY MOM
SAID NO BUT I GUESS I CAME
DOWNSTAIRS AND THEY WERE
CHATTING AND DOING THEIR THING
AND HE SAID "TIME TO GO BACK TO
BED," PUT ME AT THE BED AND THAT
WAS IT.
>> THE BEST PART IT TURNS OUT OF
THE STORY IT'S NOT THAT, IT WAS
THE FACT THAT YOUR MOM WAS LIKE
NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE OUR PIANO, TO
ELTON JOHN.
>> GUESS WHAT, THAT PIANO IS
MINE NOW.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THANKS, MOM, GREAT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU WORKING ON NOW?
YOU SAID YOU DO ONE SHOW A
MONTH, BUT I KNOW YOU EACH HAVE
DIFFERENT THINGS YOU'RE INTO.
>> WE DO A SHOW A MONTH AND I'VE
GOT A YOUTUBE CHANNEL UP RIGHT
NOW WHICH I'M REALLY SUPER
EXCITED ABOUT CALLED "CALIFORNIA
PREACHING" AND IT'S ALL ABOUT, I
TALK A LOT ABOUT.
>> Kelly: SO THAT'S WHAT YOU
DO?
>> TRYING TO FILL UP THE
YOUTUBE.
>> I LOVE THAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
WHAT YOU LOVE US TO MARK >>
AMAZING FOUR BOYS.
>> Kelly: OH, GIRL, THAT'S A
HANDFUL.
>> TEENAGERS.
>> Kelly: I WILL BE GIVING YOU
A LOT OF WINE BACKSTAGE.
>> BUT I'M ALSO TRYING TO
DEVELOP MY OWN PERSONAL CARE
PRODUCTS, A LINE CARE.
>> Kelly: I NEVER CARED ABOUT
ME, BUT ONCE I HAD KIDS, I WAS
LIKE, WHAT'S IN THIS?
YOU FEEL RESPONSIBLE.
>> I WAS ALWAYS THAT WAY.
I WAS ALWAYS A HEALTH NUT, I
WANTED TO KNOW THE INGREDIENTS.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
>> Kelly: IT SHOULD BE
IMPORTANT TO ALL OF US.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT ELSE.
WE RECORDED "HOLD ON TODAY," YOU
CAN CHECK IT OUT ON SPOTIFY.
AND DOES FOR YOU WHAT POUND
CAKES AND CHEESECAKE STEW FOR ME
SO I FOLLOWED MY HEART, AND I
CREATED LOVE BITES BY CARNIE,
WERE LAUNCHING GROCERY THIS
YEAR, IT'S A DESERT LINE.
THERE'S A THING WITH WEIGHT AND
THE WHOLE IMAGE BUT THE TRUTH IS
I'M NOT GIVING UP SUGAR.
I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE A LITTLE
BIT AND THAT'S THE MESSAGE THAT
I THINK IS HEALTHY.
>> Kelly: I THINK THAT'S A
REALISTIC THING.
IT'S A REALISTIC THING TO
ACTUALLY SAY, LOOK, AND FOR ME
PERSONALLY, I'M GOING TO ALLOW A
LITTLE BIT.
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO GET THERE, I
BELIEVE.
>> IT'S REALISTIC.
>> Kelly: ANYWAY, I LOVE TAKE.
I WANT TO SHOW EVERYBODY THE
TAPE, THAT'S AWESOME.
>> IT'S THE NIGHT BEFORE THE
SHOW.
I MADE PEANUT BUTTER CAKES AND
THEN I HEARD THAT YOU DIDN'T
LIKE PEANUT BUTTER.
SO I RUSHED BACK IN THE KITCHEN
AND I MADE YOU 11 CAKES.
SO HERE ARE YOUR LEMON CAKES FOR
TOMORROW.
I GOT SOME BEAUTIFUL FROSTING
GOING FOR GLAZING THESE PUPPIES
AND BRING THEM IN TOMORROW.
>> HERE YOU GO, WOULD YOU ALL
LIKE ONE?
>> GO AHEAD.
I HAVE 5 MILLION OF THESE.
>> I DO THINK THAT THIS IS
AMAZING.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE GETTING IT BUT
IT'S NOT EXCESSIVE.
>> MY PROBLEM IS I GET THIS AT
HOME.
>> OH, MY GOD, THIS IS SO GOOD.
>> HELLO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WE ARE SISTERS FROM ANOTHER
MOTHER.
OH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IT'S A LOVE BOMB!
MARANDA HAS SOMETHING VERY
MEANINGFUL SHE WANTS TO SAY,
MELINDA, GO FOR IT!
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY
HEART.
THERE IS NO ONE BETTER IN THE
WORLD, AND WHAT YOU'VE DONE FOR
MY BROTHERS AND I COME UP FROM
THE TIME I WAS 12 WHEN YOU FIRST
PICKS ME UP FROM FOSTER CARE,
THAT WAS THE LAST TIME I HAD TO
WORRY ABOUT IF ANYBODY WANTED M
ME.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT, YOU
BEEN THERE FOR ME AND JONATHAN
AND JAMES AND THERE'S NOBODY IN
THE WORLD THAT I COULD IMAGINE
BEING BLESSED WITH THEN YOU AS A
FATHER.
YOU COULD'VE LEFT WHEN IT WAS IN
YOUR BEST INTEREST BUT YOU
DIDN'T.
YOU NEVER GAVE UP ON US AND
STILL DON'T.
I COULDN'T HAVE ASKED FOR A
BETTER PERSON, THANK YOU.
>> OH, GOSH.
THAT WAS SO SWEET.
I'D YOUR HEART IS SO BIG.
>> THANK YOU, GUYS.
>> Kelly: WHILE MATT, YOU ARE
AN AMAZING MAN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: WOW.
THAT WAS REALLY TOUCHING.
WE WANT TO HELP MELINDA AND TONY
CONTINUE TO BUILD AN AWESOME
FATHER DAUGHTER RELATIONSHIP SO
WE'RE SENDING THEM TO CABO'S IN
THE BAJA PENINSULA.
THEY'LL GET TO ENJOY LUXURIOUS
ALL-INCLUSIVE AMENITIES LIKE
OCEAN POOLS, HOT TUBS, AND IT'S
ALL INCLUDED.
IT'S GOING TO BTH.
COMING UP IS WHEN MY FAVORITE
VAMPIRES FROM ONE OF MY FAVORITE
SHOWS, IAN SOMERHALDER IS HERE
AFTER THE BREAK, Y'ALL!
You ever get the urge
to go a little crazy?
You know what I'm talking
about, right Karen?
Huh?
You wanna let yourself woah,
but you can't do it here.
Or here. It hurts more
when you fight it.
But totally cool here.
Woah!
And here.
Woaaaahh!
-Oh yeah.
Woah, kid.
She gets it.
[ roars ]
Woah!!
Get it all out.
So when you're ready
to let yourself woah,
there's only one
place to go.
Universal, baby!
HUMIRA patients...
this one's for you.
The heroes who won't let
your disease hold you back.
You inspired us to make your
HUMIRA experience even better
with HUMIRA Citrate-free.
It has the same effectiveness
you know and trust,
but we removed the
citrate buffers,
there's less liquid,
and a thinner needle,
with less pain immediately
following injection.
If you haven't yet,
talk to your doctor
about HUMIRA Citrate-free.
And you can use your co-pay card
to pay as little as $5 a month.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal
infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Ask your doctor about
HUMIRA Citrate-free.
The same HUMIRA you trust
with less pain
immediately following injection.
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK, I'M
HERE WITH CHYNNA, WENDY, AND
CARNIE OF WILSON PHILLIPS.
YOU ALL KNOW MY NEXT GUEST AS
JAME AND SALVATORE, ME TOO, ME
TOO COME UP THE WIDELY POPULAR
"VAMPIRE DIARIES" BUT TODAY HE
IS EXECUTIVE PRODUCER, DIRECTOR,
AND START OF ANOTHER VAMPIRE
HIT, "V WARS," ON NETFLIX.
WHAT CAN WE SAY, THE MAN LOVES
BLOOD.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THIS IS A VIRUS, CAUSING DNA
TRANSFORMATION.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT I BECOME?
THE MAN YOU KNEW IS GOING.
>> Kelly: PLEASE WELCOME IAN
SOMERHALDER!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> SUCH A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU
GUYS.
WHERE DO I GO?
HIGH MATT, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU.
>> AND I AM SUCH A FAN.
SERIOUSLY, SUCH A FAN.
>> SHE WROTE ME A HANDWRITTEN
NOTE.
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
WHAT DID YOU HAVE TIME TO DO
THAT?
>> I WRITE LETTERS FOR EVERY
GUEST ON MY SHOW.
WELL, IT'S IMPORTANT.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS TO MAKE THE
ROUNDS.
AND I'M ALSO SUPER FAN AND YOU
KNOW THIS BECAUSE...
>> YOU CAME TO OUR SET ! SHE
CAME TO OUR SET IN LIGHT, 2011
OR 12.
>> Kelly: I DON'T REMEMBER
THAT, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THAT
EARLIER.
>> WE WERE TATER TOTS, FOR SURE.
>> IT WAS AWESOME AND THE SHOW
IS SO GREAT.
>> NOW I'M STANDING ON A STAGE
WITH LEGENDS.
I'VE NEVER MET --
>> Kelly: IT'S THE
GRAVITATIONAL PULL.
>> I'VE NEVER MET THEM, BUT ANY
BOY AT THAT TIME COMPLETELY HAD
A CRUSH ON YOU GUYS.
>> OH, GOSH.
>> Kelly: AND ALL THE GIRLS
WANTED TO BE YOU.
>> YOU GUYS ARE HUGE.
>> Kelly: DID YOU GUYS EVER
GET INTO THE VAMPIRE STUFF?
I'M OBSESSED.
>> DOES "TWILIGHT" COUNT?
>> TWILIGHT COUNTS!
YOUR WIFE.
>> MY DIETER IS OBSESSED.
>> I READ ALL THE BOOKS BEFORE
THE MOVIE CAME OUT.
I LOVE ANYTHING KIND OF FANTASY.
I THINK BECAUSE SOMETIMES LIFE
CAN BE SO NOT GOOD THAT YOUR
LIGHT, I WANT TO ESCAPE AS THEM.
AND YOU DO IT SO WELL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Kelly: I LOVED VISITING
ONSETS, IT WAS SO COOL.
>> SO THE GUY THAT PLAYED MY
BROTHER ON THIS VERY
LONG-RUNNING TV SHOW, WE LOVE
EACH OTHER.
WE HAVE WANTED TO KILL EACH
OTHER ABOUT 800 TIMES.
>> Kelly: THAT MEANS BROTHERS.
>> THAT MEANS BROTHERS.
NOT ONLY WERE WE ON THE
TELEVISION SHOW EIGHT YEARS AGO
BUT NOW WE STARTED A COMPANY
TOGETHER.
AND IT'S REALLY SPECIAL, THE
SALVATORE BROTHERS BOURBON AND
IT'S GOOD TO BE A LOT OF FUN.
>> Kelly: HAVE YOU ANNOUNCED
THE NAME YET?
>> TRADEMARKING, COPYWRITING,
EVERYTHING.
>> Kelly: BUT YOU ARE NOW THE
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER, DIRECTOR,
AND YOUR STARRING IN "V WARS,"
RIGHT?
EXPLAIN TO PEOPLE BECAUSE IT'S
ABOUT VAMPIRES BUT NOT REALLY.
IT'S KIND OF DIFFERENT.
IT'S LIKE A DISEASE TAKES OVER,
RIGHT?
>> IS THE ONLY VAMPIRE SHOW
YOU'VE EVER SEEN THAT'S NOT
SUPERNATURAL, IT'S SCIENCE
BASED.
THIS IS ABOUT A DISEASE, A VIRUS
THAT'S FOUND BECAUSE OF MELTING
GLACIERS.
THINGS ARE STARTING TO BE
EXPOSED THAT ARE VERY HARMFUL TO
HUMANITY AND LIVESTOCK AND
WILDLIFE AND STUFF.
SO THESE ARE THINGS, IS THAT
EVEN POSSIBLE, IT'S PROBABLE
THAT THERE ARE GOING TO BE
THINGS THAT COME OUT.
>> Kelly: CAN I SAY SOMETHING
BECAUSE EVERYBODY GETS IN THIS
BATTLE ABOUT IF HUMANS CAUSED IT
OR WHATEVER, BUT WHO CARES WHAT
CAUSED IT, IT'S HAPPENING.
LET'S FIGURE IT OUT.
>> DO YOU EVER GET MISTAKEN FOR
ROB LOWE?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Kelly: I JUST HAD THEM ON
AS WELL.
YOU ARE NOT HARD ON THE EYES.
>> HE IS AWESOME.
HE WAS SO SWEET.
HE WALKED UP TO MY WIFE, HE
WALKED UP TO NIKKI REED, I THINK
IT WAS A GOLDEN GLOVES PARTY AND
HE WALKED UP TO HER AND SHE
NEVER MET HIM, HE WALKED UP TO
HER AND HE GRABBED HER FACE AND
HE JUST SAID, THIS IS WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO BE LOOKING AT IN
15 YEARS.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> HE WAS SO SWEET AND
RESPECTFUL ABOUT IT.
THE ANY WOMAN THAT IS THAT CLOSE
TO ROB LOWE IS SORT OF LIKE,
WHOA.
IT WAS VERY SWEET.
HE'S A REALLY SWEET MAN.
>> Kelly: BUT I THINK THAT'S
REALLY COOL, PEOPLE MIGHT SAY
THAT "V WARS" IS FAR-FETCHED BUT
I DO LOVE THAT IT'S BASED IN
SCIENCE AND A LOT OF THINGS
HAPPENING.
>> IT ALSO ATTACKS A LOT OF THE
BIG TEMPLE THINGS WERE DEALING
WITH RIGHT NOW IN SOCIETY.
WE WANT TO HAVE THIS FEEL OF THE
GENRE ENOUGH, LIKE OF "WALKING
DEAD BUT THE SOCIAL RELEVANCE
OF, LIKE, "I HANDMAID'S TALE.
>> Kelly: I LOVE YOU.
YOU ARE A HIGH FIBER, I LOVE IT.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE SURE TO
CATCH THE SERIES ON NETFLIX.
I CANNOT WAIT TO WATCH IT.
I'M EXCITED.
ESPECIALLY WITH ALL THE
BACKGROUND.
UP NEXT IS OUR FIRST EVER AMBUSH
LOVE SONG, AN UNSUSPECTING
HUSBAND HAS NO IDEA HE'S GOING
TO BE SERENADED BY PENTATONIX
AND MYSELF.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
(phone alarm beeps)
How do you become the YOU
you dream of being?
You just have to say yes.
Yes to finishing strong.
Yes to staying in the zone.
And yes to picture perfect
penguin cakes.
Yes.
Ugh, Yes.
And, oh boy, yes to that too,
I guess. I don't know.
More? Wow. I mean, yes...
seriously though.
Do you really want
to do all of this?
No.
(phone alarm beeps)
That's it.
No!
You NO girl!
Whoa! Someone could have
eaten that, but whatever.
Let them hear that no.
Because, no is beautiful.
At Pure Leaf, we believe
NO makes life better.
After all, it works
pretty well for our tea.
No Artificial Sweeteners.
No Artificial Flavors.
No Extra Stuff.
Pure Leaf.
No is beautiful.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT, I'M BACK
WITH WILSON PHILLIPS, CHYNNA,
WENDY, AND CARNIE AND IAN
SOMERHALDER.
AND IT'S PART OF ALL THE FIELDS
FEBRUARY.
WE'VE BEEN DROPPING LOVE BOMBS
LEFT AND RIGHT.
YOU SAW ONE EARLIER, PRETTY
POWERFUL STUFF.
WHILE SOMETIMES WE HAVE TO GET
OUT OF THE STUDIO AND GO EVEN
BIGGER AND BOLDER BECAUSE I'M
TEXAN SO WE GET LOUDER AS WELL.
SO TODAY WE LAUNCHED OUR FIRST
EVER AMBUSH LOVE SONG.
ALL RIGHT, MY NEXT GUEST REACHED
OUT TO US BECAUSE SHE WANTED TO
GO BIG IN LETTING HER HUSBAND, A
DECORATED POLICE OFFICER KNOW
JUST HOW MUCH HE MEANS TO HER.
LET'S START WITH THEIR LOVE
STORY.
MEET SHANNON AND TROY.
>> TROY AND I MET OUR SOPHOMORE
YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL BUT IT
WASN'T UNTIL THE BEGINNING OF
OUR SENIOR YEAR THAT I WAS LIKE,
HEY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD ASK ME OUT.
I'M DONE BEING FRIENDS.
ON JANUARY 1ST 2001, HE GOT DOWN
ON HIS KNEE AND SAID I WAS HIS
BEST FRIEND AND THAT HE WANTED
TO SPEND HIS LIFE WITH ME AND
HOW CAN I SAY NO TO THAT?
IN 2016 I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
BREAST CANCER.
TALK ABOUT NOT KNOWING WHAT TO
DO.
TROY HAS BEEN BY MY SIDE THROUGH
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
HE HAS CRIED WITH ME, TOOK CARE
OF OUR TWO BOYS, HE HAS HELD ME
UP.
THEN IN APRIL OF 2017 I WAS
DECLARED CANCER FREE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OUR HEARTS WERE SO FULL AND
EVERYBODY WAS SO HAPPY AND WE
DECIDED TO GO TO THE ROUTE 91
COUNTRY FESTIVAL IN VEGAS.
AT FIRST I HEARD WHAT I THOUGHT
WERE FIREWORKS.
TROY KNEW AT THAT TIME THAT
SOMEBODY WAS SHOOTING AT US.
TROY RUSHED OVER TO GET ME OUT
AND WE WERE HOLDING HANDS WHEN
HE GOT SHOT IN THE LEG.
HE NOT ONLY SAVED MY LIFE THAT
NIGHT BUT HE WAS CREDITED FOR
SAVING ANOTHER 20 PEOPLE.
HE WAS AWARDED HIS SECOND MEDAL
OF VALOR FOR WHAT HE DID THAT
NIGHT.
TROY IS AN AMAZING MAN AND I
LOVE HIM MORE THAN ANY WORDS
COULD EVER SAY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: WOW.
WELL, SHANNON IS JOINING US,
GIVE IT UP FOR SHANNON.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SO, IN MY TIME THAT I'VE GOT TO
SIT WITH YOU, THIS IS ONE OF MY
FAVORITE STORIES BUT HE WAS
ALMOST A MAN THAT GOT AWAY.
DO YOU WANT TO TELL EVERYONE
HOW?
>> SUGGEST BETWEEN US, I WILL
ADMIT IT WAS MY FAULT.
SO, WE WERE HIGH SCHOOL
SWEETHEARTS AND OUR FRESHMAN
YEAR IN COLLEGE I WAS SO
EXCITED, I'M AN ONLY CHILD FROM
A PRETTY STRICT FAMILY AND I WAS
LIKE, OH, MY GOSH, WERE GOING TO
GET OUT AND WERE GOING TO HAVE
FUN AND WERE GOING TO PARTY,
WERE GOING TO LET HER HAIR DOWN
AND HE WAS LIKE, NO, I WANT TO
BE A POLICE OFFICER.
I'VE GOT YOU.
YOU'RE MY LIFE, I'M GOOD.
AND I WAS LIKE OH, I DON'T THINK
I CAN HANDLE BEING MARRIED TO A
COP, WHICH WAS A GREAT, IT WAS
SO SILLY, 18-YEAR-OLD, I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT I WANTED.
IT WAS A BLESSING IN DISGUISE
BECAUSE I GOT TO GO DO WHAT I
WANTED AND NEEDED TO DO AND TROY
GOT TO FOLLOW HIS PATH IN
BECOMING A POLICE OFFICER AND
EVERYTHING.
AND HE'S TRULY MY BEST FRIEND.
>> Kelly: HAS HE ALWAYS BEEN
SENTIMENTAL?
IS HE MORE THE SENTIMENTAL WHEN
THE NEW?
>> WELL, YES.
I COULD INSTRUCT HOW TO BE
SENTIMENTAL BUT HE'S REALLY THE
ONE THAT DOES IT.
EVEN IN HIGH SCHOOL, HE WOULD
WRITE ME POEMS.
>> DID YOU WRITE POEMS, IAN?
>> MY WIFE WRITES ME KNOWS ALL
THE TIME AND LEAVES THEM,
BECAUSE I HAVE TO TRAVEL SO
MUCH.
BUT SHE WAITS NO LITTLE PICTURES
OF HER AND THE BABY.
AND I FIND THEM, LIKE, IN A
BOOT.
SHE HAS REALLY GOTTEN GOOD AT
HIDING THEM.
>> Kelly: MY HUSBAND WILL DO
THAT, HE'S REALLY GOOD WITH
THAT.
>> MY HUSBAND WRITE SONGS FOR M
ME.
>> I DON'T WRITE SONGS OR POEMS
WHICH IS WHY I'M HERE.
>> SO YOU WANTED TO GO BAG.
>> I HAVE NOT BEEN THAT
FABULOUS, I GUESS, ON EXPRESSING
TO HIM HOW MUCH HE HAS MEANT TO
ME THROUGH THE LAST THREE YEARS
THAT HAVE JUST BEEN, YOU KNOW,
ROLLER COASTERS UP AND DOWN AND
HE'S JUST MY KNIGHT IN SHINING
ARMOR.
I FELT LIKE REACHING OUT TO YOU
GUYS TO HELP ME GO ABOVE AND
BEYOND TO DO SOMETHING TO MAKE
HIM LAUGH AND HAVE FUN AND
REALLY FEEL HOW MUCH HE MEANS
NOT ONLY TO ME BUT TO EVERYONE
HE'S IN TOUCH WITH.
>> Kelly: WELL, SHANNON WANTED
TO GO BAG AND I WAS HAPPY TO
HELP BECAUSE I'M TEXAN.
I GOT TOGETHER WITH MY BAND AND
MY FRIEND, SCOTT, FROM
PENTATONIX AND WE HAD A MUSICAL
BRAINSTORM SESSION AND UP NEXT
YOU'LL SEE WHAT WE CAME UP WITH
AND JUST HOW SHOCKED TROY WAS.
WHEN HE WAS AMBUSH WITH THE LOVE
SONG.
[Crackling fire]
[Wood rolling]
Alexios, add toilet paper
to the shopping list.
[Chiseling on stone]
Oh, and camel milk.
And a chicken.
And moisturizer.
ALEXA: Thanks, guys.
I'll take it from here.
>> Kelly: I'M BACK WITH WILSON
PHILLIPS AND IAN SOMERHALDER.
AND SHE WANTED TO AMBUSH HER
HUSBAND WITH A CUSTOM LOVE SONG,
SO FIRST WE NEEDED TO WRITE THE
SONG.
SO I SET SHANNON UP WITH MY BAND
AND SURPRISE HER WITH MY GOOD
FRIEND, SCOTT, FROM PENTATONIX
AND HERE SAID THAT ALL WENT DOW
DOWN.
HELLO, THIS IS SCOTT FROM
PENTATONIX AND WE WANTED TO COME
HELP.
>> MY GOSH, KELLY CLARKSON AND
SCOTT FROM PENTATONIX JUST
WALKED INTO THIS ROOM.
I CAN'T EXPRESS HOW EXCITED I AM
WRITING A SONG FOR TROY WITH
CALLIE.
>> WE KNOW HE'S A GOOD DUDE BUT
WE WANTED TO GET SOME INPUT FROM
YOU ON HOW WE CAN KIND OF PULL
THINGS FROM REAL LIFE.
>> TO HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
SHARE LITTLE PARTS OF OUR LIFE
TOGETHER IS GOING TO BE SO MUCH
FUN.
>> Kelly: DOES YOUR HUSBAND
HAVE NICKNAMES WE COULD USE?
>> MY FAVORITE NICKNAME FOR HIM
HIS CABANA BOY TROY.
>> Kelly: THAT'S ALSO MY NEW
FAVORITE NAME.
>> I'VE WRITTEN SEVERAL SONGS
WITH KELLY AND MOST OF THE TIME
IT'S WITH THE RADIO IN MIND OR
FANS IN MIND SO THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME I'VE WRITTEN A SONG
WITH ONE PERSON IN MIND.
>> Kelly: I LOVE THIS SONG !
>> WATCHING THE BUILD TO THIS
SONG ABOUT TROY AND MY LIFE IS
MORE THAN INCREDIBLE.
>> Kelly: WILL MISS YOUR FIRST
KISS.
>> SPEAKING OF THAT, WHEN DID
YOU HAVE MORE THAN YOUR FIRST
KISS?
>> Kelly: GET IN THERE, GET IN
THERE.
>> LET ME JUST SAY THAT THE
MOVIE "THE LITTLE MERMAID THAT
SERVES UP SOME REALLY...
>> Kelly: THE LITTLE MERMAID?
>> CLEARLY I'M NOT HOLDING
ANYTHING BACK.
>> Kelly: WERE YOU WATCHING
WHEN YOU...
SPEAK OUT YEAH.
>> DO YOU GET A CERTAIN FEELING
WHEN...
[OPENING TO "UNDER THE SEA"]
>> YEAH.
>> I'M HAVING SO MUCH FUN WITH
EVERYBODY IN THIS ROOM.
A DUET.
>> I CAN'T WAIT BECAUSE HE IS
GOING TO CONNECTS TO EVERY PART
OF THIS SONG.
HE'S NOT GOING TO KNOW WHAT
HAPPENS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: OH, MY GOSH.
OKAY.
SO, SHANNON, CABANA BOY TROY,
FIRST OF ALL, THANK YOU FOR
THAT, THAT IS AWESOME.
SO HOW DID HE GET THAT NICKNAME?
>> SO, WHEN WE WERE YOUNGER, I
CONVINCED HIM TO START PARTYING
WITH ME, THANK GOODNESS, RIGHT?
AND HE IS A PARTY AND A HALF SO
ANY TIME THAT WE WOULD HAVE
PEOPLE OVER TO OUR HOUSE AND WE
WERE HOSTING HE WOULD MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY WAS HAVING A GREAT
TIME, HOW TO DRINK, HAD FOOD.
SO IT JUST CAME ABOUT, ONE TIME
HE WAS BRINGING A DRINK AND WE
ARE LIKE, THANKS CABANA BOY.
AND WE WERE LIKE, CABANA BOY
TROY, THAT'S WHAT HE HAS, AND
IT'S BEEN WITH HIM EVER SINCE.
>> Kelly: I LOVE IT.
WELL, NEXT WITH THE SONG ALL
WRITTEN THERE WAS JUST ONE THING
LEFT TO DO, AMBUSH TROY.
SO SHANNON INVITED TRY TO LUNCH
AT A PLACE THEY GO ALL THE TIME
AND HE HAD NO REASON TO SUSPECT
ANYTHING WAS GOING ON OTHER THAN
A NICE MEAL, SUGGEST LOOK.
♪ ♪
>> THERE'S THEM.
>> RIGHT.
>> GOT IT.
>> WE WERE SITTING THERE AND OF
COURSE HE'S GOT YODA IN HIS LAP
SO YODA SNORING.
>> Kelly: WERE GOING TO AMBUSH
THE OUT OF HIM, IT'S GOING TO BE
AWESOME.
ARE YOU TROY?
THIS IS FOR YOU.
HERE WE GO.
WE ARE COMING IN HOT, TROY.
>> GO CAMERA ONE.
>> APRIL AND JUNE OF THE TRIAL
DATES.
I THINK APRIL AND JUNE OF THE
TRIAL DATES.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> HI.
HELLO.
>> OH, BOY.
>> Kelly: HI.
OH, HEY, ARE YOU TROY?
>> YES?
>> HEY.
YOU GO.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE FOUR...
♪ ♪
♪♪ TO PUT ON THE UNIFORM, TURN
UP THE HEAT ♪
♪ IT'S ALL THAT YOU NEED ♪
♪ YOU MADE A SPLASH MOMENT WHEN
YOU KISS THE GIRL ♪
♪ IT WASN'T LONG UNTIL YOU ARE
PART OF HER WORLD ♪
♪ COME ON, BABY ♪
♪ SHE WON'T REMAIN SILENT WHEN
YOU SEE HER TONIGHT ♪
♪ CABANA BOY TROY ♪
♪ HE AIN'T AFRAID TO CRY ♪
♪ WENT TO COLLEGE, AND YOU'RE
LIKE, WE SHOULD GET MARRIED, I
LOVE YOU SO MUCH, AND HE WAS
LIKE, MAYBE WE SHOULD ENJOY OUR
LIVES, AND THAT IT WAS MAGICAL
AND WERE ALL HERE NOW TOGETHER.
IT'S GREAT.
♪♪ CABANA BOY TRY ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
>> CAN WE ALL PARTY WITH YOU?
IS THAT COOL?
♪♪ CABANA BOY, CABANA BOY
TROY ♪♪
>> YES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: THAT WAS OUR FIRST
OFFICIAL AMBUSH LOVE SONG AND
YOU ARE OUR FIRST, TROY.
WE HEARD YOU LIKE TO PARTY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, TROY IS JOINING US WHEN WE
COME BACK.
DON'T GO AWAY.
♪ ♪
Try Target's Same
Day Delivery.
At your door, so you
can get more.
♪ Feels so good ♪
Target Run & Done.
A lot of folks ask me why their
dishwasher
doesn't get everything clean.
I tell them, it may be your
detergent...
That's why more dishwasher
brands
recommend Cascade Platinum...
...with the soaking, scrubbing
and rinsing built right in.
For sparkling-clean dishes,
the first time.
Cascade Platinum.
Now, we know the Trump strategy-
try to win by attacking,
distorting, dividing.
Mr. President: It. Won't. Work.
Newspapers report Bloomberg is
the Democrat Trump fears most.
As president, universal
healthcare that lets people keep
their coverage if they like it.
A record on job creation.
A doable plan to combat climate
change.
I led a complex, diverse city
through 9-11 and I have
common sense plans to move
America away from chaos to
progress!
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
>> TO KELLY.
>> THE PLANNING FOR THIS WHOLE
AMBUSH, HUNDREDS OF EMAILS, TONS
OF PHONE CALLS AND THEN ALL OF A
SUDDEN IT'S HAPPENING.
♪ ♪
>> THAT SOUNDS AMAZING.
THAT'S GOING TO BE MY FAVORITE
SONG.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: I'M BACK WITH WILSON
PHILLIPS AND IAN SOMERHALDER
ALONG WITH SHANNON WHOSE
HUSBAND, TROY, IS A POLICE
OFFICER IN THE VERY FIRST LUCKY
RECIPIENTS OF OUR AMBUSH LOVE
SONG.
IT'S PART OF OUR CELEBRATION OF
ALL THE FIELDS FEBRUARY.
I MEAN, YOU WANT TO MEET TROY,
RIGHT?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT, COME ON OUT!
LET'S GO!
THAT WAS SO AWESOME.
>> YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING.
>> THANK YOU.
SPEAK A HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> WE USED TO DANCE TO YOUR
SONGS.
BECAUSE THAT WAS LIKE WHEN WE
WERE HIGH SCHOOL.
>> Kelly: I KNOW IT WAS A
SURPRISE BUT YOUR FACE LOOKS
AWESOME.
I FEEL A HUMOR ALMOST LIKE, NO,
I'M NOT TROY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THAT SURPRISE GIVE YOU ALL THE
FIELDS?
>> OH, YEAH, THAT WAS, I DON'T
KNOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR DOING
THIS.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT'S AN HONOR TO BE HERE WITH
YOU, WITH WILSON PHILLIPS, WITH
IAN, IT'S AMAZING THAT WERE EVEN
SITTING ON THIS COUCH.
>> Kelly: YOU'RE THE HERO,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAVES LIVES
AND GETS SHOT FOR US.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF HEROES OUT
THERE.
I THINK WERE ALL JUST HERE TO BE
THE BEST WE CAN COME OUT RIGHT?
>> Kelly: WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
DOING THAT.
>> IT WAS AN AMAZING PRICE.
I WAS SITTING THERE AND SHANNON
GETS ME TO COME TO LUNCH AT
12:30 WHICH IS RIDICULOUS
BECAUSE I HAVE LUNCH AT 11:00.
SOME STARVING.
AND I LOOK AND YOU COME OUT AND
I'M LIKE, OH, MY GOD, AND THEN
YOU HIT THIS LINE FROM THE
LITTLE MERMAID, "KISS THE GIRL,"
AND I WAS LIKE, OH, MY GOD.
>> AND FIRST OF ALL, WERE GOING
TO HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THIS
BACKSTAGE.
I'M TALKING, LITTLE MERMAID?
>> THAT WAS ME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Kelly: I FEEL CHALLENGED.
YOU'RE SOMETHING YOU WANT TO
TELL SHANNON, THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> SO, I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A PERSON
WHO IS THERE FOR PEOPLE AND
HELPING PEOPLE AND I LOVE MY
ROLE IN LIFE BUT WHEN THE PERSON
THAT...
>> Kelly: YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
FEEL LIKE THIS, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M LIKE A MAGICIAN.
YES.
>> BUT WHEN THE PERSON I CHERISH
THE MOST IN THE WORLD PUTS THAT
MUCH EFFORT AND HELPS ME THROUGH
ALL THIS STUFF, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
>> Kelly: YOU ALL ARE SO GOOD.
WE CAN SHARE.
I LOVE YOU!
>> I NEED A HUG FROM YOU.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Kelly: YOU ARE PRECIOUS.
GET IN THERE.
OH, MY GOSH, I LOVE IT.
WELL, WE HAVE ONE MORE SURPRISE
FOR THE BOTH OF YOU.
>> THIS ONE WON'T SCARE YOU.
>> Kelly: WE ARE SENDING YOU
TO PLAYA DEL CARMEN IS SET IN
THE RIVIERA MEYER REGION.
ALL NEW ADULTS ONLY RESORT IS A
PERFECT GETAWAY.
SO ENJOY ALL-INCLUSIVE AMENITIES
INCLUDING INTERNATIONAL DINING,
BOTTOMLESS CONTACTS, AND NIGHTLY
ENTERTAINMENT SET A LONG
SWEEPING OCEAN VIEWS.
IT'S TIME FOR A BREAK BUT I HOPE
YOU'LL HAVE SO MUCH FUN.
I WANT TO SERENADE YOU ALL.
STAY HERE, WE'LL BE BACK WITH
"WHAT I'M LIKING" ."
Young Man: Thanks for having
us this weekend Mrs. Garcy
Young Woman: Yeah, thanks Mom
Mother: Of course and
I love these flowers
Young Woman whispering: Hey, did
you bring the... the condoms?
Young Man whispering: What's up?
Young Woman whispering: Condoms
Young Man whispering: What?
Young Woman whispering: Condom
Father: Condoms Charlie.
She wants to know if
you brought any condoms.
Young Man: Yeah I brought some.
Announcer: Eargo, a virtually
invisible hearing loss
solution with high quality sound
and lifetime support.
If your a current or retired
federal employee
you could get Eargo at no cost
to you.
Simply call 800-EARGO-54
to hear more.
Eargo, hear life to the fullest.
Z3R4PZ Z16FZ
Y3R4PY Y16FY
>> Kelly: WELCOME BACK.
IT IS TIME FOR ME TO SHOW YOU
WHAT'S TAKING THE INTERNET BY
STORM.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
THIS IS "WHAT I'M LIKING" ."
SO, BALANCING RESPONSIBILITIES
CAN BE CHALLENGING FOR COUPLES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY HAVE KIDS,
OBVIOUS.
GENTRY NELSON FROM TENNESSEE
KNOWS THAT HER HUSBAND SPENDS A
LOT OF TIME HUNTING.
IT'S JUST THAT HER HUNTING TIME
IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
CHECK THIS OUT.
WHEN GENTRY NEEDS A BREAK SHE
GOES HUNTING FOR A HOT BATH OR
BOOK OR ANYTHING TO GET HERSELF
A MOMENT TO RELAX AND RECHARGE.
IN HER POST SHE RODE, "WE HAVE
LEARNED TO COMPROMISE.
WHAT REALLY HELPS IS THAT I'VE
STARTED HUNTING.
NOT WITH ADAM, NOT ACTUAL
HUNTING BUT ON THE WEEKENDS
AFTER HE GETS HOME I TELL HIM
IT'S MY TURN TO HUNT WHICH
REALLY MEANS I GO IN THE BEDROOM
AND READ A BOOK OR WATCH TV.
I GO OUT TO DINNER WITH A
GIRLFRIEND.
LADIES, TAKE THE TIME TO GO
HUNT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: 'S HUSBANDS, LET
YOUR WIVES HUNT, IT'S AWESOME.
LET'S CALL UP THE NELSONS AND
FIND OUT HOW HUNTING SEASON IS
GOING FOR BOTH OF THEM.
>> Kelly: WHAT'S UP, I'M KELLY
KELLY!
OKAY.
SO EXPLAIN HOW YOU CAME UP WITH
YOUR UNIQUE VERSION OF HUNTING
THAT I AM SERIOUSLY INTO?
>> HI, KELLY, FIRST OF ALL.
WELL COME UP BASICALLY WHEN WE
FIRST MET HE TOLD ME THAT HE
HUNTED A LOT AND THAT WAS
SOMETHING THAT WAS IMPORTANT TO
HIM, SO NOW I HAVE MY OWN
HUNTING SEASON.
>> Kelly: MY HUSBAND HUNTS AS
WELL AND HE IS HITTING THE
SEGMENT RIGHT NOW BECAUSE I'M TO
BE LIKE, WAIT, I WANT TO HUNT,
I'VE GOT THINGS I WANT TO DO.
SO HOW DOES THIS WORK AROUND
YOUR ACTUAL HUNTING?
>> THE PROBLEM SHE RAN INTO, THE
TIMES, DURING THE FALL, AND
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT WE HAVE
KIDS, AND THEN IT TRANSITIONS
INTO DEER AND DEER TRANSITIONS
INTO DOCS, I'LL BE OUT SOMETIMES
FOR A DAY OR TWO AND THEN WHEN I
GET HOME I JUST TAKE OVER THE
KIDS, HOPEFULLY SHE DOESN'T HAVE
TO SAY MUCH AND IF SHE DOES,
I'LL LISTEN.
SAW HANDLE EVERYTHING.
>> Kelly: THAT'S A GREAT
HUSBAND.
A REALLY COOL THING THAT YOU DO
FOR YOUR FAMILY BUT ALSO AS A
COOL THING THAT YOU RECOGNIZE
HOW EXHAUSTED SHE PROBABLY IS
WAKING UP WITH THE KIDS AND
DOING ALL THE THINGS AND GIVING
HER A MINUTE.
I THINK THAT'S HOW MARRIAGES
WORK.
IT'S GOT TO BE A PARTNERSHIP.
SO I'M GOING TO OFFICIALLY
"LIKED" THE RIGHT NOW.
THANK YOU TO ALL MY GUESTS.
WILSON PHILLIPS, AND SUMMER
HOLDER, SHANNON AND TROY.
HAVE A GREAT DAY, AND IF IT'S
NOT GREAT, JUST CHANGE IT.
♪ ♪
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: HERE SHE IS NOW,
ELLEN DEGENERES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]