[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THANK YOU SO MUCH!
I FEEL THE SAME WAY ABOUT YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
HAVE A SEAT, EVERYBODY!
THANKS FOR BEING HERE FOR THE
TELEVISION PROGRAM THAT WE ARE
ABOUT TO START SHOOTING.
HOW ARE YOU?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GOOD!
GLAD TO HEAR IT, ME TOO.
I AM VERY --
WOO.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THE
INTERNET.
YOU HAVE HEARD OF IT, RIGHT?
YOU SHOULD TRY IT IF YOU
HAVEN'T.
THE INTERNET CAN BE GREAT.
IT GAVE US JUSTIN BIEBER, CAN I
GET ALLELUIA?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IT'S ALSO THE REASON WE ARE ALL
STILL TRYING TO STAND OUR BROOMS
UP ON THEIR BRISTLES.
AND WHY THAT NIGERIAN PRINCES
GOING TO GIVE ME ALL OF THAT
MONEY.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE MORE AND MORE
THE INTERNET IS MEAN-SPIRITED.
WHAT I TRY TO DO ON MY INSTAGRAM
IS POST THINGS THAT MAKE PEOPLE
HAPPY AND SMILE.
THAT'S THE BEST OF THE INTERNET,
WE CAN ACTUALLY PASS ALONG GOOD
INFORMATION AND GOOD NEWS.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE THINGS TO
POST IS CUTE ANIMALS.
WHO DOES NOT WANT TO LOOK AT
CUTE ANIMALS, RIGHT?
I AM CREATING A BRAND-NEW
ACCOUNT CALLED PAWS UP FILLED
WITH MY FAVORITE ANIMAL VIDEOS.
YOU WILL SEE STUFF THAT YOU
WON'T SEE ANYWHERE ELSE.
IT IS EVERYTHING ADORABLE.
THIS VIDEO WILL BE ON THERE.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
OR YOU WILL SEE THIS.
[DOG PANTING]
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I WILL ALLOW CUTE
KIDS AS LONG AS THEY ARE
ALONGSIDE A CUTE ANIMAL.
I WILL ALSO SHARE ANIMALS UP FOR
ADOPTION, LIKE THESE ARE
AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW I WAGMOR
HERE IN TOWN.
LOOK AT THESE DOGS.
GO GET THEM SOMEBODY.
IT'S THE ONLY PLACE WILL I WILL
POST MY PICTURES OF MY ANIMALS.
THIS IS A VIDEO OF WALLY, SHE IS
ALL GROWN UP.
SHE IS EIGHT MONTHS OLD AND SHE
AND AUGIE ARE PLAYING ON THE
COUCH.
SHE DOES NOT KNOW HOW BIG SHE
IS.
>> THIS IS REALLY GREAT.
ONLY HERE.
>> Ellen: AUGIE SQUATS DOWN,
SO HE ATTACKS THE LEGS.
THE BOTTOMS AND THE LEGS.
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHTER]
>> WE CAN'T TAKE YOU ANYWHERE.
>> Ellen: WE HAVE COME A LONG
WAY.
THEY DID NOT GET ALONG AT FIRST.
NONE OF THEM ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
ON THE COUCH, INCLUDING PORTIA.
BUT IT WAS SO CUTE I LET HER
STAY UP THERE.
I'M EXCITED.
I WILL SHARE ALL KINDS OF VIDEOS
WITH YOU AND I WANT YOU TO SEND
ME YOUR FAVORITE VIDEOS AND
PICTURES OF ALL OF YOUR ANIMALS
OR ANY OTHER ANIMALS YOU KNOW
ABOUT.
SO FOLLOW ME ON PAWS UP ON
INSTAGRAM.
TO JUST SPELL IT OUT.
P IS FOR PETS, A IS FOR
ADOPTION, W IS FOR WOW.
S IS FOR STETHOSCOPE.
JUST LOOK AT.
PAWS UP, IT IS THAT.
NOW PUT YOUR PAWS UP FOR THIS
AUDIENCE DANCER OF THE DAY,
EVERYBODY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: YES!
WONDERFUL!
HI, WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
>> I AM MADDIE.
>> Ellen: THAT WAS WONDERFUL.
DID YOU ENJOY YOURSELF?
>> I DID ENJOY MYSELF.
>> Ellen: I AM AMAZED WITH HOW
MANY PEOPLE ARE COMFORTABLE
DANCING IN FRONT OF STRANGERS,
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU DO EVERY
DAY, UNLESS YOU DO DO THAT EVERY
DAY?
DO YOU DO THAT EVERY DAY?
>> I MIGHT, YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: YOU ARE A DANCER?
>> I AM PRETTY >> Ellen:
THAT'S WHY YOU ARE GOOD AND WHY
WE CHOSE YOU.
SO THE REST OF YOU GOING OUT
THERE EARLIER THINKING, WELL, I
WAS GOOD TOO.
SHE IS A DANCER.
USUALLY HERE'S WHAT I DO, I PICK
VIDEOS RIGHT NOW TO SHOW YOU
THINGS THAT I WANT TO SEE.
BUT TODAY I WILL DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT AND I WILL LET ONE OF
MY WRITERS CHOOSE, IT'S A
SEGMENT I AM CALLING "ALISON'S
CHOICE."
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: [ELLEN SINGING]
HELLO, ALLISON.
>> HI, ELLEN.
>> Ellen: SHE IS ONE OF THE
WRITERS DURING THE SHOW.
I WILL GIVE YOU TWO VIDEOS TO
CHOOSE FROM AND YOU CAN CHOOSE
THE ONE I SHOW.
I SHOULD TELL EVERYONE RIGHT NOW
THAT YOU DON'T LIKE SNAKES.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> Ellen: IS THERE A REASON?
>> I AM A HUMAN.
[LAUGHTER]
I DON'T LIKE THEM.
>> Ellen: WHAT IS WRONG WITH
THEM?
>> THEY ARE SNEAKY AND SLITHERY.
AND THEY ARE FAST.
>> Ellen: THEY ARE TRYING TO
MIND THEIR OWN BUSINESS.
THEY ARE NOT GOING TO SCARE YOU.
WE ARE GIVING YOU A SEGMENT
WHERE I SHOW YOU TWO VIDEOS TO
CHOOSE FROM AND YOU PICK ONE.
WHICH WOULD YOU RATHER WATCH?
VIDEO NUMBER ONE, A SNAKE GOING
UP A STAIRCASE.
THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING, OR A
VIDEO OF A NEWS REPORTER?
IT SEEMS OBVIOUS.
>> I'M GOING TO SAY NEWS
REPORTER.
>> Ellen: THERE IS NO SNAKE IN
THE TITLE.
WHAT COULD HAPPEN?
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT YOUR CH
CHOICE.
>> THE MICROPHONE!
>> I AM JUST NEXT HIM.
IT IS JUST BECAUSE IT IS RIGHT
IN FRONT OF HIS FACE.
>> NO!
>> HE IS RIGHT BY MY MICROPHONE!
>> WHAT IF HE SEES MY HAND?
>> Ellen: WELL, SHE SHOULD
NEVER HAVE DONE THAT.
THAT WOMAN.
I MEAN, THAT SEEMED LIKE IT WAS
A POISONOUS SNAKE, PLUS THEY
WERE IN AUSTRALIA, EVERYTHING IS
POISONOUS.
LET'S LOOK AT THE ONE THAT YOU
DID NOT WATCH.
>> OH!
I CAN'T!
OH, GOD.
IT IS STILL GOING ON.
>> Ellen: I THINK YOU MADE THE
RIGHT CHOICE.
ALLISON, YOU ARE DISMISSED.
WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NOW?
>> I'M GOING TO CRY AND TAKE MY
SHIRT OFF.
I'VE BEEN SWEATING.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, HAVE FUN.
SPEAKING OF MAKING CHOICES,
THERE IS AN IMPORTANT ONE COMING
UP, THE PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY.
THE DEADLINE TO REGISTER TO VOTE
IS FEBRUARY 17TH IN CALIFORNIA,
SO CHECK THE DATES IN YOUR
STATE.
IT IS DIFFERENT EVERYWHERE, AND
MAKE SURE THAT EVERYONE
REMEMBERS TO REGISTER.
I MADE THIS PSA WITH JULIA
LOUIS-DREYFUS.
IT IS ME, ELLEN.
>> AND IT IS ME AMERICA'S
SWEETHEART JULIA LOUIS-DREYFUS.
>> Ellen: WE ARE BOTH
REGISTERED VOTERS AS WELL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Ellen: IF YOU WANTED TO
VOTE FOR ME AND JULIA AS
PRESIDENT AND VICE PRESIDENT,
YOU WOULD HAVE TO REGISTER TO
VOTE.
>> NOT THAT WE ARE RUNNING, BUT
IF WE WERE, IT SEEMS MUCH MORE
LIKELY THAT I WOULD BE PRESIDENT
ANYWAY BE VICE PRESIDENT.
>> Ellen: YOU HAVE TO REGISTER
TO VOTE FIRST, THAT IS THE
POINT.
>> OF COURSE.
AND EACH STATE HAS THEIR OWN
DEADLINE.
IF YOU LIVE IN MONTANA, CHECK
YOUR DEADLINE TO REGISTER.
>> Ellen: ORMAN NEW MEXICO,
NEW YORK, MICHIGAN.
>> OREGON.
>> Ellen: I THINK IT IS ARE
AREGON.
>> OH, THAT IS INCORRECT.
IT IS ORGAN.
>> Ellen: THAT IS NOT OREGON.
THAT IS LIKE YOU ARE PLAYING A
ORGAN IN CHURCH.
NOBODY SAYS, WHERE YOU FROM?
>> IT IS OREGON.
>> Ellen: NO, OREGON.
AGAIN, WE ARE NOT RUNNING.
>> BUT WE WILL BE VOTING AND
REGISTERING.
>> Ellen: GO TO
EllenTube.com TO LEARN MORE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT SOMETHING THAT
IS ALMOST AS IMPORTANT AS
VOTING, DISHWASHING DETERGENT.
IT IS TIME FOR A LIFE COMMERCIAL
FOR CASCADE PLATINUM, EVERYBODY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
ALL RIGHTY THEN.
CASCADE IS THE NUMBER ONE
RECOMMENDED DISHWASHING
DETERGENT BRAND IN
NORTH AMERICA.
NOT JUST THE UNITED STATES, THAT
INCLUDES CANADA, MEXICO.
I'M SORRY, STOP THE MUSIC.
PEOPLE IN THE AUDIENCE ARE --
HEY, HEY.
EXCUSE ME.
SORRY, I AM IN THE MIDDLE OF
DOING A LIFE COMMERCIAL FOR
CASCADE PLATINUM.
>> WE LOVE CASCADE PLATINUM.
>> WE LOVE, LOVE, LOVE IT.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, I'M
TRYING TO TALK ABOUT CASCADE
PLATINUM, OKAY.
>> WE ARE SORRY, WE DON'T WANT
TO INTERRUPT.
WE ARE HUGE FANS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: LET'S GO BACK.
DID YOU KNOW THAT RUNNING YOUR
DISHWASHER ACTUALLY SAVES MORE
WATER THAN WASHING DISHES BY
HAND.
AND EVEN IF YOUR DISHWASHER IS
NOT FULL, YOU CAN DO IT EVERY
NIGHT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> DO IT.
DO IT.
>> DO IT EVERY NIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT SHE SAID.
>> Ellen: STOP THE MUSIC
AGAIN.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
>> I'M SORRY, WE JUST LOVE TO DO
IT EVERY NIGHT.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
I LOVE DOING IT WITH HER.
>> WE LOVE DOING IT EVERY NIGHT.
>> Ellen: I'M TALKING ABOUT
RUNNING THE DISHWASHER, THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
IT SOUNDED LIKE YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT SEX.
>> BARF.
>> ELLEN, WE RUN THE DISHWASHER
EVERY NIGHT BECAUSE IT SAVES 10.
>> AND SAVING WATER TURNS ME ON.
>> LOVE IT.
LOVE IT.
>> WE LOVE IT.
>> Ellen: THIS IS SO
RIDICULOUS.
YOU ARE BOTH GAY AND YOU ARE
BOTH MARRIED.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHY.
CASCADE WANTS YOU TO DO IT EVERY
NIGHT TOO, SO YOU ARE ALL GOING
HOME WITH A $150 TARGET
GIFT CARD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE BACK!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WAS THIS THE FIRST
♪ ♪
TIME YOU'VE HAD A PERFECT
>> Ellen: WAS THIS THE FIRST
ATTENDANCE PENCIL?
TIME YOU'VE HAD A PERFECT
>> NO, I GET ONE EVERY YEAR.
ATTENDANCE PENCIL?
>> Ellen: OH, YOU DO?
>> NO, I GET ONE EVERY YEAR.
>> YOU NEED ALL THREE.
>> Ellen: OH, YOU DO?
CHARLES, NAME THREE THINGS YOU
>> YOU NEED ALL THREE.
DO AFTER A GAME.
A lot of folks ask me why their
dishwasher
doesn't get everything clean.
I tell them, it may be your
detergent...
That's why more dishwasher
brands
recommend Cascade Platinum...
...with the soaking, scrubbing
and rinsing built right in.
For sparkling-clean dishes,
the first time.
Cascade Platinum.
Great parenting
needs great allies.
New Ziploc Grip n' Seal.
Easier to grip and open for the
world's greatest parents.
SC Johnson
[police siren]
Dispatch, we got a code bubly.
Are you going to get him down?
No.
bubly sparkling water.
Pack a smile.
♪♪
Free!
Free, free, free.
♪
That's right,
TurboTax Free is free.
Free, free free free.
I'm wondering how
you might respond
to me asking you for a drink.
So that was you asking me?
In my mind it wasn't
that forward.
[ laughing ]
What was he like?
I just think that
he's, special.
[ chuckle ]
I love the new myWW program,
because it's tailored to you!
...take the personal assessment
and get matched with a
proven weight loss plan.
Find out which customized plan
can make losing weight
easier for you!
myWW
Join for free
and get three months free!
>> Announcer: IT'S ALMOST
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> Ellen: I SEE A COUPLE OF
CONFUSED FACES.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW YOU'RE SINGLE,
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE.
>> Announcer: ALL NEW "ELLEN,"
LAUREN GRAHAM.
AND THIS HUSBAND THAT SINGS LOVE
SONGS TO HIS WIFE EVERY DAY.
ELLEN GETS READY FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY WITH EVERYTHING
BUT THE CARD.
>> Ellen: HERE IS A
VALENTINE'S DAY CARD.
A GIRLFRIEND IS A SISTER YOU
CHOOSE.
INSIDE THE CARD IT SAYS WAIT, I
CAN EXPLAIN.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OUR NEXT GUEST MAY HAVE PERFECT
ATTENDANCE, BUT ONE THING SHE
DOES NOT HAVE IS A PERFECT
ATTENDANCE PENCIL.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> YESTERDAY I PUT MY PENCIL, MY
PERFECT ATTENDANCE PENCIL IN THE
SHARPENED BOX.
BUT WHEN I UNPACKED, I WENT TO
GET MY PENCIL, GUESS WHAT I SAW?
NOTHING BUT YELLOW PLAIN OLD
PENCILS.
A SOMEBODY, AND I KNOW WHO STOLE
MY PERFECT ATTENDANCE PENCIL,
WHO DID NOT EVEN EARN ONE,
BECAUSE THEY WERE IN CANADA!
YEAH, SHE EARNED IT.
YOU DID NOT EARN IT.
YOU ARE IN CANADA!
AND THEN...
SHE DID NOT SAY IT LIKE THAT.
SHE SAID, YOU WERE IN CANADA.
>> Ellen: FROM PORTLAND,
TEXAS, PLEASE WELCOME 7-YEAR-OLD
TAYLOR!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
LOOK AT YOUR CUTE LITTLE OUTFIT
AND YOUR CUTE LITTLE BOWS IN
THEIR HAIR AND YOUR CUTE LITTLE
HAIR AND YOUR CUTE LITTLE SELF.
>>> THANK YOU, ELLEN.
>> Ellen: TELL ME ABOUT THIS.
IT SEEMS VERY UPSETTING.
YOU HAD THE PERFECT ATTENDANCE
PENCIL, AND THEN IT WAS GONE.
AND HOW ON A SCALE OF 1-10, HOW
MAD WHERE YOU?
>> I WOULD SAY 10, BECAUSE I
EARNED THE PENCIL, AND I REALLY
LIKE THAT PENCIL.
IT WAS PINK.
AND IT HAD A PINK ERASER.
AND IT WAS REALLY BIG, BECAUSE I
NEVER USED IT, THE ERASER.
AND IT HAD RAINBOWS.
AND IT SAID ATTENDANCE AWARD.
>> Ellen: YOU HAD NEVER USED
THE ERASER?
>> NO.
>> Ellen: YOU NEVER MADE A
MISTAKE?
THAT IS AMAZING!
ANYWAY.
[LAUGHTER]
SO IS THIS THE FIRST TIME YOU
HAVE HAD A PERFECT ATTENDANCE
PENCIL?
>> NO, I GET ONE EVERY YEAR.
>> Ellen: OH, YOU DO?
WOW.
THAT IS AMAZING.
[APPLAUSE]
SO TALK ME THROUGH THIS.
THAT IS AMAZING.
WHEN DID YOU REALIZE IT WAS
SO TALK ME THROUGH THIS.
MISSING?
WHEN DID YOU REALIZE IT WAS
>> SO WE SAT IN THE CAFETERIA.
MISSING?
WE WENT TO CLASS, AND I UNPACKED
>> SO WE SAT IN THE CAFETERIA.
AND GOT MY MORNING WORKOUT AND
WE WENT TO CLASS, AND I UNPACKED
THEN I WENT TO LOOK IN --
AND GOT MY MORNING WORKOUT AND
>> Ellen: MY MORNING WORK OUT.
THEN I WENT TO LOOK IN --
YOU GOT YOUR MORNING WORK OUT.
>> Ellen: MY MORNING WORK OUT.
>> I LOOKED IN THE SHARPENING
YOU GOT YOUR MORNING WORK OUT.
BACON WHERE THE PENCIL USUALLY
>> I LOOKED IN THE SHARPENING
IS COMING AND IT WAS GONE.
BACON WHERE THE PENCIL USUALLY
AND I WENT TO MY DESK TO USE A
IS COMING AND IT WAS GONE.
PLANE PENCIL, I LOOKED BEHIND
AND I WENT TO MY DESK TO USE A
ME, AND I SAW THAT LIZZIE HAD MY
PLANE PENCIL, I LOOKED BEHIND
PERFECT ATTENDANCE PENCIL.
ME, AND I SAW THAT LIZZIE HAD MY
>> Ellen: OKAY, DID YOU SAY,
PERFECT ATTENDANCE PENCIL.
LIZZY, CAN I HAVE MY PENCIL
>> Ellen: OKAY, DID YOU SAY,
BACK?
LIZZY, CAN I HAVE MY PENCIL
>> YES, I DID.
BACK?
BUT SHE SAID GO GET A REGULAR
>> YES, I DID.
PENCIL, IT'S JUST A PENCIL.
BUT SHE SAID GO GET A REGULAR
I FOUND IT IN THE PENCIL BEEN.
PENCIL, IT'S JUST A PENCIL.
>> Ellen: BUT IT WAS NOT A
I FOUND IT IN THE PENCIL BEEN.
REGULAR PENCIL TO YOU.
>> Ellen: BUT IT WAS NOT A
IT WAS A SPECIAL PENCIL.
REGULAR PENCIL TO YOU.
HOW DID YOU GET THE PENCIL BACK?
IT WAS A SPECIAL PENCIL.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HOW DID YOU GET THE PENCIL BACK?
>> I ASKED FOR IT BACK RIGHT
WHAT HAPPENED?
BEFORE LUNCH.
>> I ASKED FOR IT BACK RIGHT
SEE SHE WENT BACK -- SHE SAID
BEFORE LUNCH.
SURE, BUT SHE LOST THE PENCIL
SEE SHE WENT BACK -- SHE SAID
SOMEWHERE.
SURE, BUT SHE LOST THE PENCIL
AND THEN SHE SAID AFTER RECESS,
SOMEWHERE.
BUT I NEVER GOT IT BACK AFTER
AND THEN SHE SAID AFTER RECESS,
RECESS.
BUT I NEVER GOT IT BACK AFTER
AUTUMN FOUND AT THE NEXT DAY,
RECESS.
AND I SAID THAT IT WAS MINE AND
AUTUMN FOUND AT THE NEXT DAY,
SHE GAVE IT STRAIGHT TO ME.
AND I SAID THAT IT WAS MINE AND
>> Ellen: THAT IS REALLY NICE
SHE GAVE IT STRAIGHT TO ME.
OF ON-OFF.
>> Ellen: THAT IS REALLY NICE
>> AUTUMN.
OF ON-OFF.
>> Ellen: I'M SORRY.
>> AUTUMN.
I WAS THINKING OF ANNA, SHE IS
>> Ellen: I'M SORRY.
NO LONGER THERE.
I WAS THINKING OF ANNA, SHE IS
AUTUMN.
NO LONGER THERE.
I WAS VERY SWEET OF HER, RIGHT?
AUTUMN.
YOU ARE NOT THERE TODAY, TODAY
I WAS VERY SWEET OF HER, RIGHT?
IS WEDNESDAY AND YOU ARE
YOU ARE NOT THERE TODAY, TODAY
SUPPOSED TO BE IN SCHOOL.
IS WEDNESDAY AND YOU ARE
SO I GOT YOU A LETTER THAT YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE IN SCHOOL.
CAN BRING BACK.
SO I GOT YOU A LETTER THAT YOU
BECAUSE HE WANT PERFECT
CAN BRING BACK.
ATTENDANCE.
BECAUSE HE WANT PERFECT
SO I SIGNED A LETTER THAT TELLS
ATTENDANCE.
THEM WHY YOU WERE NOT THERE.
SO I SIGNED A LETTER THAT TELLS
BECAUSE I WANT YOU TO HAVE
THEM WHY YOU WERE NOT THERE.
PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
BECAUSE I WANT YOU TO HAVE
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOUR ENTIRE
PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
CLASS, BECAUSE IT WILL BE SO
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOUR ENTIRE
JEALOUS THAT YOU ARE HERE.
CLASS, BECAUSE IT WILL BE SO
BECAUSE EVERYBODY WILL BE LIKE
JEALOUS THAT YOU ARE HERE.
OH, TAYLOR IS ON "ELLEN."
BECAUSE EVERYBODY WILL BE LIKE
WE DID NOT GET TO GO.
OH, TAYLOR IS ON "ELLEN."
SO LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT I AM
WE DID NOT GET TO GO.
GOING TO GET FOR THE WHOLE
SO LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT I AM
CLASS, ALL KINDS OF SUPPLIES AND
GOING TO GET FOR THE WHOLE
PENCILS AND DIFFERENT THINGS FOR
CLASS, ALL KINDS OF SUPPLIES AND
EVERYBODY.
PENCILS AND DIFFERENT THINGS FOR
THEY WILL THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
EVERYBODY.
THAT.
THEY WILL THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
LIZZIE AND AUTUMN WILL BE LIKE,
THAT.
RIGHT ON!
LIZZIE AND AUTUMN WILL BE LIKE,
[LAUGHTER]
RIGHT ON!
AND THEN I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU
[LAUGHTER]
TOO, SOMETHING REALLY SPECIAL
AND THEN I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU
THAT YOU WILL LIKE!
TOO, SOMETHING REALLY SPECIAL
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT YOU WILL LIKE!
YEAH, LOOK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO LOSE THAT
YEAH, LOOK!
ONE, ARE YOU?
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO LOSE THAT
>> ?
ONE, ARE YOU?
>> NO.
>> ?
>> Ellen: THEY HAVE TO GET YOU
>> NO.
A BIG BACKPACK THOUGH.
>> Ellen: THEY HAVE TO GET YOU
ALL RIGHTS, WE WILL BE RIGHT
A BIG BACKPACK THOUGH.
BACK.
ALL RIGHTS, WE WILL BE RIGHT
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
BACK.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> YOU HAVE TO ALWAYS STAND UP
♪ ♪
AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
>> YOU HAVE TO ALWAYS STAND UP
AND I HAVE BEEN BLESSED, I'M
AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
NEVER GOING TO SIT BACK AND LET
AND I HAVE BEEN BLESSED, I'M
DISCRIMINATION HAPPEN ON MY
NEVER GOING TO SIT BACK AND LET
WATCH.
DISCRIMINATION HAPPEN ON MY
[APPLAUSE]
WATCH.
>> OR DO YOU THINK THEY ARE GAY?
Delicious Almond Breeze
almondmilk yogurt alternative.
Cut! Why did you eat that?
'Cause it tastes amazing.
Do you want to try it?
Delicious Almond Breeze
Almondmilk Yogurt Alternative.
Available now.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz.
The first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those
with moderate
to severe
psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement of
their psoriasis
plaques.
Some even
saw 100%
clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUEST IS
AN NBA HALL OF FAMER, A TWO TIME
OLYMPIC GOLD MEDALIST, A NINE
TIME NBA ALL-STAR, AND SOMEHOW
THIS IS HIS FIRST APPEARANCE ON
MY SHOW.
FROM TNT "INSIDE THE NBA" PLEASE
WELCOME CHARLES BARKLEY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
HI, CHARLES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IT IS COOL TO MEET YOU.
HI, CHARLES.
WE ALMOST MET A LONG TIME AGO.
>> IT IS COOL TO MEET YOU.
>> Ellen: WHERE?
WE ALMOST MET A LONG TIME AGO.
>> IS STAND UP FOR CANCER EVENT.
>> Ellen: WHERE?
AND I DID NOT KNOW IF YOU ARE IN
>> IS STAND UP FOR CANCER EVENT.
A GOOD MOOD OR BAD MOOD.
AND I DID NOT KNOW IF YOU ARE IN
SO I WAS SCARED TO GO  UP TO YO.
A GOOD MOOD OR BAD MOOD.
>> Ellen: I AM ALWAYS IN A
SO I WAS SCARED TO GO  UP TO YO.
GOOD MOOD.
>> Ellen: I AM ALWAYS IN A
>> OKAY.
GOOD MOOD.
THIS IS REALLY COOL.
>> OKAY.
I'VE BEEN A BIG FAN PRAYED WHEN
THIS IS REALLY COOL.
THEY SAID I WAS COMING ON HERE,
I'VE BEEN A BIG FAN PRAYED WHEN
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
THEY SAID I WAS COMING ON HERE,
>> Ellen: THANKS SO MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHY IT WAS THE
>> Ellen: THANKS SO MUCH.
FIRST TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHY IT WAS THE
>> THEY PUT ME ON ALL OF THE
FIRST TIME.
GUYS SHOWS.
>> THEY PUT ME ON ALL OF THE
I WANT TO BE ON THE SHOW WITH
GUYS SHOWS.
YOU.
I WANT TO BE ON THE SHOW WITH
YOU ARE A LOT SMARTER AND FUNNER
YOU.
THAN THOSE GUYS.
YOU ARE A LOT SMARTER AND FUNNER
>> Ellen: GUYS, I DON'T KNOW
THAN THOSE GUYS.
WHO YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, BUT
>> Ellen: GUYS, I DON'T KNOW
YEAH.
WHO YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, BUT
YOU KNOW WE HAVE A TRADITION
YEAH.
HERE, IT IS YOUR FIRST TIME ON
YOU KNOW WE HAVE A TRADITION
THE SHOW, WE MUST SHOW SHIRTLESS
HERE, IT IS YOUR FIRST TIME ON
PHOTOS OF YOU.
THE SHOW, WE MUST SHOW SHIRTLESS
IT'S JUST WHAT HAPPENS.
PHOTOS OF YOU.
>> PLEASE BE FROM THE '80s!
IT'S JUST WHAT HAPPENS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> PLEASE BE FROM THE '80s!
I MISS THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I MISS THE GOOD OLD DAYS WHEN
I MISS THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
YOU COULD TAKE YOUR SHIRT OFF IN
I MISS THE GOOD OLD DAYS WHEN
PUBLIC.
YOU COULD TAKE YOUR SHIRT OFF IN
[LAUGHTER]
PUBLIC.
I MISS THE '80s.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO TRUE,
I MISS THE '80s.
EVERYBODY WALKED AROUND WITH NO
>> Ellen: THAT IS SO TRUE,
SHIRTS.
EVERYBODY WALKED AROUND WITH NO
ESPECIALLY IN THE '60s.
SHIRTS.
>> I USED TO WALK AROUND WITHOUT
ESPECIALLY IN THE '60s.
A SHIRT.
>> I USED TO WALK AROUND WITHOUT
IT IS SO BAD NOW, I REALLY WANT
A SHIRT.
TO KEEP MY SHIRT ON.
IT IS SO BAD NOW, I REALLY WANT
>> Ellen: YOU ARE SO FUNNY.
TO KEEP MY SHIRT ON.
YOU HAVE STRONG OPINIONS, YOU
>> Ellen: YOU ARE SO FUNNY.
HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH
YOU HAVE STRONG OPINIONS, YOU
SHAQUILLE O'NEAL, SHAQ THAT IS
HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH
VERY INTERESTING.
SHAQUILLE O'NEAL, SHAQ THAT IS
SOMETIMES YOU LOVE HIM,
VERY INTERESTING.
SOMETIMES YOU DON'T, TODAY HOW
SOMETIMES YOU LOVE HIM,
DO YOU FEEL?
SOMETIMES YOU DON'T, TODAY HOW
>> HE IS ONE OF THOSE GUYS, HE
DO YOU FEEL?
WANT TO JAB YOU, BUT HE CAN'T
>> HE IS ONE OF THOSE GUYS, HE
TAKE THE JOB.
WANT TO JAB YOU, BUT HE CAN'T
SO HE HAS THIN SKIN AND FLY
TAKE THE JOB.
STYLE.
SO HE HAS THIN SKIN AND FLY
HE WANTS TO MAKE FUN OF YOU, BUT
STYLE.
YOU CANNOT MAKE FUN OF HIM.
HE WANTS TO MAKE FUN OF YOU, BUT
AND ONCE I KNOW THAT I GOT HIM,
YOU CANNOT MAKE FUN OF HIM.
I WILL KEEP DIGGING IN.
AND ONCE I KNOW THAT I GOT HIM,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, I LOVE THE
I WILL KEEP DIGGING IN.
BIG FELLA, HE IS FUN TO WORK
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, I LOVE THE
WITH.
BIG FELLA, HE IS FUN TO WORK
HIS MOM IS ONE OF THE MOST
WITH.
IMPORTANT PEOPLE IN MY LIFE.
HIS MOM IS ONE OF THE MOST
HIS MOM AND MY MOM AND ANOTHER
IMPORTANT PEOPLE IN MY LIFE.
WOMAN NAMED MARTHA WERE BEST
HIS MOM AND MY MOM AND ANOTHER
FRIENDS.
WOMAN NAMED MARTHA WERE BEST
WHEN MY MOM PASSED AWAY A COUPLE
FRIENDS.
OF YEARS AGO, THEY WERE BEST
WHEN MY MOM PASSED AWAY A COUPLE
FRIENDS FOR 30 YEARS.
OF YEARS AGO, THEY WERE BEST
WHEN MY MOM PASSED AWAY A COUPLE
FRIENDS FOR 30 YEARS.
OF YEARS AGO, HIS MOM SPENT THE
WHEN MY MOM PASSED AWAY A COUPLE
LAST FEW DAYS WITH MY MOM.
OF YEARS AGO, HIS MOM SPENT THE
THAT'S HOW LONG WE HAVE BEEN
LAST FEW DAYS WITH MY MOM.
FRIENDS.
THAT'S HOW LONG WE HAVE BEEN
BUT I LOVE GIVING HIM A HARD
FRIENDS.
TIME ON TELEVISION.
BUT I LOVE GIVING HIM A HARD
>> Ellen: HE LOVES GIVING YOU
TIME ON TELEVISION.
A HARD TIME TOO.
>> Ellen: HE LOVES GIVING YOU
SO HE SENT US THIS.
A HARD TIME TOO.
>> HEY, CHUCK, IT IS YOUR FRIEND
SO HE SENT US THIS.
SHAQ, HAVE FUN WITH THE
>> HEY, CHUCK, IT IS YOUR FRIEND
BEAUTIFUL ELLEN TODAY.
SHAQ, HAVE FUN WITH THE
DON'T WORRY SHE WILL STILL LOVE
BEAUTIFUL ELLEN TODAY.
ME MORE AFTER THE SHOW.
DON'T WORRY SHE WILL STILL LOVE
GIVE SPECIFIC WITH HIM A BIG HUG
ME MORE AFTER THE SHOW.
FOR ME AFTER THE SHOW!
GIVE SPECIFIC WITH HIM A BIG HUG
I LOVE YOU, ELLEN!
FOR ME AFTER THE SHOW!
I HATE YOU, CHUCK.
I LOVE YOU, ELLEN!
[LAUGHTER]
I HATE YOU, CHUCK.
>> HE IS A BIG TEDDY BEAR.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: EVERY TIME HE IS
>> HE IS A BIG TEDDY BEAR.
HERE HE IS SO MUCH FUN.
>> Ellen: EVERY TIME HE IS
WE LOVE HIM TOO.
HERE HE IS SO MUCH FUN.
YOU HAVE BEEN AN ADVOCATE FOR
WE LOVE HIM TOO.
LGBTQ RIGHTS FOR A LONG TIME!
YOU HAVE BEEN AN ADVOCATE FOR
LONG BEFORE MANY, MANY PEOPLE.
LGBTQ RIGHTS FOR A LONG TIME!
YEARS BACK YOU WERE GOING TO DO
LONG BEFORE MANY, MANY PEOPLE.
AN NBA ALL-STAR GAME --
YEARS BACK YOU WERE GOING TO DO
>> IN CHARLOTTE.
AN NBA ALL-STAR GAME --
>> Ellen: AND YOU ARE THINKING
>> IN CHARLOTTE.
THAT YOU SHOULD MOVE IT BECAUSE
>> Ellen: AND YOU ARE THINKING
OF THE BATHROOM BILLS.
THAT YOU SHOULD MOVE IT BECAUSE
>> I HATED THE BATHROOM BILL, SO
OF THE BATHROOM BILLS.
I WENT TO MY BOSS AND I SAID,
>> I HATED THE BATHROOM BILL, SO
HEY, BOSS, I WANT TO SIT OUT THE
I WENT TO MY BOSS AND I SAID,
ALL-STAR GAME.
HEY, BOSS, I WANT TO SIT OUT THE
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE, I DON'T
ALL-STAR GAME.
WANT TO TAKE AWAY FROM THE
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE, I DON'T
ALL-STAR GAME, BUT I SAID I'M
WANT TO TAKE AWAY FROM THE
GOING TO SIT OUT.
ALL-STAR GAME, BUT I SAID I'M
HE SAID YOU CAN'T SIT OUT THE
GOING TO SIT OUT.
ALL-STAR GAME.
HE SAID YOU CAN'T SIT OUT THE
YOU ARE OUR BIGGEST STAR.
ALL-STAR GAME.
I SAID, WELL, I HAVE TO MAKE A
YOU ARE OUR BIGGEST STAR.
STAND AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
I SAID, WELL, I HAVE TO MAKE A
HE SAID LET ME TALK TO THE NBA,
STAND AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
AND ADAM SIEBER WHO IS A GREAT
HE SAID LET ME TALK TO THE NBA,
COMMISSIONER MOVED THE GAME OUT
AND ADAM SIEBER WHO IS A GREAT
OF CHARLOTTE.
COMMISSIONER MOVED THE GAME OUT
IT WAS A REALLY NICE GESTURE FOR
OF CHARLOTTE.
THE NBA.
IT WAS A REALLY NICE GESTURE FOR
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I THINK ANY
THE NBA.
TIME YOU ARE BLACK, YOU HAVE TO
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I THINK ANY
STAND UP FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
TIME YOU ARE BLACK, YOU HAVE TO
BECAUSE BLACK PEOPLE KNOW WHAT
STAND UP FOR OTHER PEOPLE.
DISCRIMINATION IS LIKE.
BECAUSE BLACK PEOPLE KNOW WHAT
AND IF YOU ARE IN A POSITION OF
DISCRIMINATION IS LIKE.
POWER, YOU HAVE TO STAND UP
AND IF YOU ARE IN A POSITION OF
AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
POWER, YOU HAVE TO STAND UP
I AM BLESSED, MAN.
AGAINST DISCRIMINATION.
I'M NEVER GOING TO SIT BACK AND
I AM BLESSED, MAN.
LET DISCRIMINATION HAPPEN ON MY
I'M NEVER GOING TO SIT BACK AND
WATCH.
LET DISCRIMINATION HAPPEN ON MY
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WATCH.
>> Ellen: SO TRUE, I MEAN,
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT ANY
>> Ellen: SO TRUE, I MEAN,
DISCRIMINATION AT ALL.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT ANY
ANY INEQUALITY, I AM LIKE, FOR
DISCRIMINATION AT ALL.
YOU TO THINK THAT YOU SOMEHOW
ANY INEQUALITY, I AM LIKE, FOR
THEY WILL NEVER COME AFTER YOU
YOU TO THINK THAT YOU SOMEHOW
FOR SOMETHING, IT IS JUST WRONG.
THEY WILL NEVER COME AFTER YOU
I WANT TO ASK YOU YOUR OPINION
FOR SOMETHING, IT IS JUST WRONG.
ON THINGS, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
I WANT TO ASK YOU YOUR OPINION
STRONG OPINIONS AND I FOUND OUT
ON THINGS, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
SOME --
STRONG OPINIONS AND I FOUND OUT
FIRST OF ALL, I KNOW WHAT WOULD
SOME --
SURPRISE A LOT OF PEOPLE IS YOU
FIRST OF ALL, I KNOW WHAT WOULD
LOVE VACUUM CLEANERS.
SURPRISE A LOT OF PEOPLE IS YOU
[LAUGHTER]
LOVE VACUUM CLEANERS.
>> IT IS MORE LIKE I AM A SUCKER
[LAUGHTER]
FOR INFOMERCIALS.
>> IT IS MORE LIKE I AM A SUCKER
EVERY TIME I AM WATCHING
FOR INFOMERCIALS.
TELEVISION AND THERE IS A NEW
EVERY TIME I AM WATCHING
MORE POWERFUL VACUUM CLEANER
TELEVISION AND THERE IS A NEW
COMING OUT, I HAVE TO GO GET IT
MORE POWERFUL VACUUM CLEANER
TO.
COMING OUT, I HAVE TO GO GET IT
[LAUGHTER]
TO.
I HAVE TO HAVE IT.
[LAUGHTER]
THEY MAKE FUN OF ME AT THE
I HAVE TO HAVE IT.
HOME DEPOT AND LOWE'S.
THEY MAKE FUN OF ME AT THE
THEY ARE LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU
HOME DEPOT AND LOWE'S.
DOING?
THEY ARE LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU
AND I WAS LIKE, I DON'T WANT THE
DOING?
RINGS IN THE TOILET.
AND I WAS LIKE, I DON'T WANT THE
SO ANY TYPE OF CLEANING, I LOVE
RINGS IN THE TOILET.
TO CLEAN.
SO ANY TYPE OF CLEANING, I LOVE
>> Ellen: WE KNOW THAT IT IS A
TO CLEAN.
WILE BEFORE YOU RETIRE, BUT YOU
>> Ellen: WE KNOW THAT IT IS A
WILL NEED A LOT OF CLEANING
WILE BEFORE YOU RETIRE, BUT YOU
SUPPLIES ONCE YOU RETIRE TO
WILL NEED A LOT OF CLEANING
CLEAN.
SUPPLIES ONCE YOU RETIRE TO
SO WE GOT YOU, AND I'M SURE THAT
CLEAN.
THEY WILL BE UPDATED.
SO WE GOT YOU, AND I'M SURE THAT
LET'S BRING OUT WHAT WE HAVE FOR
THEY WILL BE UPDATED.
HIM NOW.
LET'S BRING OUT WHAT WE HAVE FOR
[LAUGHTER]
HIM NOW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHTER]
THIS IS EVERY VACUUM CLEANER WE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HAVE EVER GIVEN AWAY ON THE
THIS IS EVERY VACUUM CLEANER WE
SHOW.
HAVE EVER GIVEN AWAY ON THE
DO YOU ALREADY HAVE ALL OF
SHOW.
THESE?
DO YOU ALREADY HAVE ALL OF
>> I DON'T SEE THAT SHARK.
THESE?
>> Ellen: WE NEED TO GET YOU
>> I DON'T SEE THAT SHARK.
THE SHARK.
>> Ellen: WE NEED TO GET YOU
>> THAT THING AT THE END, THAT
THE SHARK.
LAZY VACUUM CLEANER.
>> THAT THING AT THE END, THAT
YOU ARE JUST LAZY.
LAZY VACUUM CLEANER.
>> Ellen: I AGREE.
YOU ARE JUST LAZY.
I AGREE.
>> Ellen: I AGREE.
AND IT IS BORING TO JUST LET
I AGREE.
THAT GO AROUND.
AND IT IS BORING TO JUST LET
>> I AGREE.
THAT GO AROUND.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
>> I AGREE.
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, THAT SHARK
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
IS PRETTY GOOD TOO.
>> I TELL YOU WHAT, THAT SHARK
>> Ellen: GOOD, WELL, THEY ARE
IS PRETTY GOOD TOO.
ALL YOURS.
>> Ellen: GOOD, WELL, THEY ARE
TO TAKE WHAT YOU WANT AND LEAVE
ALL YOURS.
WHAT YOU DON'T.
TO TAKE WHAT YOU WANT AND LEAVE
ONE OF THE COMMENTATORS ON
WHAT YOU DON'T.
"INSIDE THE NBA" SUGGESTED WE
ONE OF THE COMMENTATORS ON
WOULD SCARE YOU, BUT THIS IS NOT
"INSIDE THE NBA" SUGGESTED WE
THE TABLE WE SCARED.
WOULD SCARE YOU, BUT THIS IS NOT
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY WHO, BUT
THE TABLE WE SCARED.
SOMEBODY SAID WE SHOULD COULD
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY WHO, BUT
SCARE, WILL TELL YOU WHO LATER.
SOMEBODY SAID WE SHOULD COULD
WE'LL TAKE A BREAK AND  WE WILL
SCARE, WILL TELL YOU WHO LATER.
PLAY A GAME CALLED
WE'LL TAKE A BREAK AND  WE WILL
"5-SECOND RULE" WHEN WE COME
PLAY A GAME CALLED
BACK!
"5-SECOND RULE" WHEN WE COME
IT WILL BE FUN.
BACK!
>> NEXT QUESTION.
IT WILL BE FUN.
NAME THREE THINGS YOU DO AFTER A
>> NEXT QUESTION.
GAME.
NAME THREE THINGS YOU DO AFTER A
>> DRINK A BEER.
GAME.
>> [SCREAMS]
>> DRINK A BEER.
>> Ellen: I LOVE THAT YOU CARE
>> [SCREAMS]
ABOUT SCHOOL SO MUCH, AND
>> Ellen: I LOVE THAT YOU CARE
SHUTTERFLY LOVES THAT YOU HAVE
ABOUT SCHOOL SO MUCH, AND
PERFECT ATTENDANCE!
SHUTTERFLY LOVES THAT YOU HAVE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
PERFECT ATTENDANCE!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Announcer: ELLEN GETS READY
♪ ♪
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY WITH
>> Announcer: ELLEN GETS READY
LAUREN GRAHAM, AND EVERYTHING
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY WITH
BUT THE CARD.
LAUREN GRAHAM, AND EVERYTHING
>> Ellen: HERE IS A
BUT THE CARD.
VALENTINE'S DAY CARD, A
>> Ellen: HERE IS A
GIRLFRIEND IS A SISTER
>>> BREAKING NEXT ON NEWS 4 AT
4:00 A TERRIFYING SITUATION FOR
.
A SEARCH FOR HER 8-YEAR-OLD
SHE HASN'T SEEN HIM ALL DA
WHERE HE WAS LAST SPOTTED AT
1:30 IN THE MORN
>>> AND A MOTHER FOUND TODAY OUT
OF.
NEW REACTION FROM HER HUSB
>>> PLUS RAIN MOVING BACK IN ON
STORM TEAM RADAR.
EXPLAINS WHAT IT MEANS FOREK
WE'LL HAVE IT FOR
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
CHARLES BARKLEY!
IN THE NBA THERE IS A
5-SECOND RULE NAMED AFTER YOU,
SO OF COURSE WE HAVE TO PLAY
"5-SECOND RULE."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
ALL RIGHT, KEVIN WILL READ THE
CATEGORY, YOU WILL HAVE FIVE
SECONDS TO NAME THREE THINGS IN
THAT CATEGORY AND THEN HIT THE
BUZZER AFTER THAT TO SEE HOW
MUCH TIME IS ON THE CLOCK.
I WILL GO FIRST.
>> NAME THREE WORDS TO DESCRIBE
CHARLES.
>> Ellen: HANDSOME, FUNNY,
BRAVE.
[DING]
>> LOOK AT THAT.
CHARLES, YOUR TURN.
NAME THREE WORDS TO DESCRIBE
ELLEN.
>> PRETTY, SMART, AND
COURAGEOUS.
[DING]
>> ELLEN, TELL US YOUR THREE
FAVORITE SHOWS ON TELEVISION.
>> Ellen: "THE BACHELOR,"
"VEEP" "PARKS NUMBER."
>> YOUR THREE FAVORITE NBA TE
TEAMS.
>> 76ers, PHOENIX SUNS --
[BUZZER]
>> Ellen: OH, NO.
>> WHAT A DUMMY.
>> Ellen: HE DID NOT WANT TO
GIVE IT UP.
>> ELLEN, THREE THINGS HE WOULD
LIKE TO SEE CHARLES TRY TO DO.
>> AND I WOULD LIKE TO SEE HIM
DANCE AND DO PUSH-UPS, AND I
WOULD LIKE TO SEE HIM DRINK.
[DING]
AT THE BUZZER.
I JUST WAS GUESSING AT THAT.
>> CHARLES, THREE THINGS HE
WOULD NOT WANT TO SEE A GRANDMA
DO.
>> SUNBATHE.
--
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
THAT'S THE FIRST THING THAT
COMES TO MIND.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SE SEE THAT.
LISTEN, I AM A BASKETBALL
PLAYER, I AM NOT QUICK AND SMART
LIKE THAT.
I CAN RUN AND JUMP THOUGH.
WELL, USE TWO.
>> ELLEN, BESIDES PORTIA, NAME
THREE PEOPLE YOU WOULD LIKE TO
GO TO DINNER WITH.
>> Ellen: I WOULD LIKE TO GO
TO DINNER WITH CHARLES AND YOU
AND LAUREN.
[DING]
>> CHARLES, YOU CAN CATCH UP.
NAME THREE PEOPLE YOU WOULD NOT
WANT TO BE STUCK IN AN ELEVATOR
WITH.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP.
[APPLAUSE]
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
[BUZZER]
>> Ellen: DARN, I REALLY WANT
TO HEAR THE OTHER TWO.
>> IT WAS GOING TO BE O'CONNELL,
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
MITCH O'CONNELL, AND WHAT'S THE
OTHER DUDE'S NAME, LINDSEY
GRAHAM.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: OKAY.
>> WHAT'S YOUR LAST QUESTION?
>> Ellen: I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE THE SUNBATHING GRANDMA.
>> READY, ELLEN.
NAME THREE THINGS THAT MAKE YOU
LAUGH.
>> Ellen: PORTIA, ALICE
McCARTHY, AND MY DOGS PLAYING.
[DING]
>> LAST QUESTION.
CHARLES, NAME THREE THINGS YOU
DO AFTER A GAME.
>> DRINK A BEER.
>> [SCREAMS]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Ellen: [LAUGHS]
OH, I KNOW.
>> THAT WAS VERY SCARY, ELLEN.
>> Ellen: WE DID END UP
SCARING YOU.
SORRY.
>> THAT WAS PROBABLY ERNIE.
>> Ellen: "INSIDE THE NBA"
CELEBRATING ITS 30TH SEASON, AND
YOU CAN WATCH ALL OF THE
ALL-STAR EVENTS ON TNT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> OR DO YOU THINK THEY ARE GAY?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: OH, MY GOD.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
I'm a Big Kid Now
I'm a Big Kid now
Went from baby bottles to
drinking from sippy cups.
Went from wearing diapers,
to rocking these fresh Pull-Ups.
We're 50 million strong.
So, put on your Pull-Ups and
help us sing this song.
New size fits smaller trainers.
Our skin...
...tells a story
...that deserves...
—the best care.
Dove Body Wash's new formula
works with your skin...
...for lasting care.
So your skin...
...can keep telling stories...
...beautifully.
New Dove Body Wash proven
lasting care
for the skin you live
in.
New Dove Body Wash proven
lasting care
♪
It's no secret that a little
sweet,
is better with a little salty.
Nature Valley Sweet and Salty
Bars.
Also in Minis.
>> Announcer: ELLEN GETS READY
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY WITH
LAUREN GRAHAM AND EVERYTHING BUT
THE CARD.
>> Ellen: HERE IS A
VALENTINE'S DAY CARD.
A GIRLFRIEND IS A SISTER YOU
CHOOSE.
INSIDE THE CARD IT SAYS WAIT, I
CAN EXPLAIN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: A FEW WEEKS AGO I
TESTED THE JONAS BROTHERS ON
THEIR LISTENING SKILLS.
HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED.
LAST YEAR IN THEIR DOCUMENTARY
"HAPPINESS BEGINS" WE SAW THAT
THEY WORKED VERY HARD ON THEIR
RELATIONSHIP AND HOW THEY LISTEN
TO EACH OTHER.
I WANT TO SEE HOW WELL THEY CAN
HEAR EACH OTHER IN OUR GAME
CALLED "A WHAT."
IT IS THE GAME OF TELEPHONE LIKE
WE PLAYED AS KIDS.
YOU CAN ONLY ASK TO HEAR THE
SENTENCE TWICE.
I WILL READ THE SENTENCE AND YOU
WILL PASS IT DOWN THE LINE.
TO THE LAST PERSON WILL COME AND
TELL US WHAT THEY HEARD.
EVERYBODY PUT ON YOUR
HEADPHONES, PLEASE.
>> NO EXPLANATION OF WHY I AM
HERE?
>> Ellen: YOU ARE THE FIFTH
JONAS BROTHER.
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
[DING]
THERE IS NO --
WE DON'T CARE.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
JOE JONAS KNOWS WHICH BROTHER
WILL MAKE THEIR WIFE A MOTHER.
BECAUSE THEY ARE A REALLY GOOD
LOVER.
NOPE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> DO YOU THINK ALL THE JONAS
BROTHERS ARE MARRIED, AND WHICH
ONE IS YOUR FAVORITE?
>> OKAY, DO YOU THINK ALL THE
JONAS BROTHERS --
SLOW.
>> DO YOU THINK ALL THE JONAS
BROTHERS ARE MARRIED?
OR DO YOU THINK THEY HAVE
GIRLFRIENDS?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> DO YOU THINK THE JONAS
BROTHERS ARE MARRIED?
OR DO YOU THINK THEY ARE GAY?
>> Ellen: OH, MY GOD.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE THEM OFF.
[LAUGHTER]
ALL RIGHT, WHAT DID YOU HEAR J
JOE?
>> DO YOU THINK THE JONAS
BROTHERS ARE MARRIED, OR DO YOU
THINK THEY ARE GAY?
[LAUGHTER]
>> DID YOU GET IT RIGHT?
>> NO!
[LAUGHTER]
>> I SWEAR THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
>> THAT IS NOT WHAT I SAID.
>> Ellen: THAT IS NOT WHAT HE
SAID.
>> IS IT CLOSE?
>> Ellen: NO, IT WAS JOE JONAS
KNOWS WHICH BROTHER WILL MAKE
THEIR WIFE A MOTHER, BECAUSE
THEY ARE A REALLY GOOD LOVER.
>> YOU ARE NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> NICK WAS  SO FAR OFF.
>> Ellen: HE WAS VERY FAR OFF,
BUT HE DID NOT SAY ANYTHING
CLOSE TO GAY.
HE SAID OR DO THEY HAVE
GIRLFRIENDS.
>> OKAY, YEAH.
GO TO BREAK.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, THAT IS
IT.
WE WILL BE BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THE ENTIRE "12 DAYS
OF GIVEAWAYS" THAT WE GAVE AWAY
THIS YEAR!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
No, no, no, no,  this ain't no
sandwich.
Because on a sandwich,
they ask you if you want cheese.
But on a Papadia,
cheese is what's holding the
whole operation together.
Get one now for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
We don't need a ton of channels.
All we need is a fast internet
connection.
Fast internet. All the channels.
We need it all.
Verizon knows every home has
different internet and TV needs.
That's why now you can mix and
match on Fios.
Eso existe? Lo necesitamos.
So I can just do Internet?
I'm in.
Boom! Sign me up.
Internet plans start at just
$39.99 per month,
with no extra fees and no annual
contracts.
Plus, you can get up to $200 in
Visa Prepaid Cards.
Mix and match your perfect
Fios plan.
Only on Verizon.
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
I bet you've never seen a
sandwich do yoga before.
Ommmmmmmmmmmmm.
Introducing the new Papadias,
for just six bucks.
Better Ingredients.
Better Pizza.
Better Than a Sandwich.
Papa John's.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: LAST MONTH WE
SURPRISED A FAMILY AT THEIR HOME
IN RED BANK, NEW JERSEY.
I KNOW IT IS ONLY FEBRUARY, BUT
THIS WAS ONE OF MY FAVORITE
MOMENTS OF 2020.
IT WAS PREEMPTIVE AND A BUNCH OF
CITIES BECAUSE OF THE
IMPEACHMENT HEARINGS.
I WANT YOU TO SEE IT.
ENJOY.
EVERY MORNING -- NIGHT BEFORE I
GO TO BED, I WATCH THE NEWS.
I CANNOT BELIEVE WHAT I SAW.
>> THEY ALL SHARE THE SAME
BIRTHDAY.
>> DO YOU LIKE HAVING THE SAME
BIRTHDAY AS YOUR BROTHER AND
SISTER?
>> YES, AND I LIKE
ELLEN DeGENERES.
>> YOU LIKE ELLEN DeGENERES.
THEY SHARED THAT IN ADDITION TO
THEIR BIRTHDAY.
>> WHENEVER I GO TO MEET ELLEN?
>> YOU WANT TO MEET ELLEN TOO?
YOU GUYS LOVE ELLEN?
YOU WANT ELLEN DeGENERES, BUT
YOU ARE STUCK WITH ME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: THAT MADE ME HAPPY,
SO I HAD MY PRODUCERS FIND OUT
MORE ABOUT THE LOPEZ FAMILY, AND
IT TURNS OUT THEY COULD USE SOME
HOLIDAY CHEER.
SO I SENT MY RECEPTIONIST
JEANNIE TO THEIR HOME IN
NEW JERSEY.
HI, JEANNIE.
I WILL NOT CALL THEM, YOU SHOULD
JUST KNOCK ON THEIR DOOR.
IF THEY ARE NOT HOME, WE WILL
CALL THEM BACK.
YOU ARE OUT OF SHAPE.
YOU ARE BREATHING SO HARD
WALKING.
>> [LAUGHS]
HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO, ELLEN.
[KNOCK IN]
HELLO!
>> [SCREAMS]
ELLEN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: TELL ME WHO
EVERYBODY IS.
INTRODUCE YOURSELVES.
>> TELL HER YOUR NAME.
>> MY NAME IS JOSEPH, AND I AM
SEVEN YEARS OLD.
>> WHAT YOUR NAME?
>> AND I AM FOUR YEARS OLD.
>> I AM LAMAR.
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW OLD YOU ARE?
>> HOW OLD ARE YOU?
ARE YOU TWO?
>> TWO.
>> AND?
>> MY NAME IS RAUL.
>> Ellen: HI, EVERYBODY.
WHY DO THE KIDS KEEP MENTIONING
ME IN THE INTERVIEW?
>> WIDE WOULD THEY KEEP
MENTIONING HER IN THE INTERVIEW?
>> THEY HAD NEVER BEEN EXPOSED
TO INTERVIEWS LIKE THIS, ONLY
WHEN THEY ELLEN, SO THEY WERE
LIKE, THIS IS FOR ELLEN.
>> I'M GOING TO SAVE A GORILLA!
>> Ellen: I KNOW!
THAT'S WHY I AM THERE, I HEARD
THAT YOU ARE SAVING ALL OF YOUR
BIRTHDAY MONEY!
THAT'S AMAZING!
THAT IS SO SPECIAL.
>> IT'S GREAT THAT YOU THINK
ABOUT THE GORILLAS AND THE
WILDLIFE FUND.
>> Ellen: THE REASON YOU WERE
ON THE NEWS IS BECAUSE ALL OF
THE KIDS HAVE THE EXACT SAME
BIRTHDAY.
HOW DO YOU PLAN FOR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT?
[LAUGHTER]
THAT IS PRECISE.
>> IT WAS NOT PLANNED.
THEY HAD COMPLETE DIFFERENT TO
DUE DATES.
SHE WAS A WHOLE TWO WEEKS LATE.
SHE WAS NOT EVEN INDUCED.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M THINKING
THAT THEY WERE ALL A PRODUCT OF
VALENTINE'S DAY.
WE KNOW LONGER CELEBRATE
[LAUGHTER]
VALENTINE'S DAY.
WHAT IS VALENTINE'S DAY?
[LAUGHTER]
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS VALENTINE'S DAY?
>> Ellen: SO, JEANETTE, I KNOW
WHAT IS THAT?
THAT YOU ARE LIVING WITH YOUR
>> Ellen: SO, JEANETTE, I KNOW
PARENTS RIGHT NOW, YOU HAD TO
THAT YOU ARE LIVING WITH YOUR
MOVE BACK IN WITH THEIR PARENTS
PARENTS RIGHT NOW, YOU HAD TO
AND ARE SHARING ONE BEDROOM.
MOVE BACK IN WITH THEIR PARENTS
I KNOW THAT YOU WERE WORRIED
AND ARE SHARING ONE BEDROOM.
ABOUT CHRISTMAS, HOW DID IT GO
I KNOW THAT YOU WERE WORRIED
FOR YOUR KIDS?
ABOUT CHRISTMAS, HOW DID IT GO
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, AT THE END OF
FOR YOUR KIDS?
THE DAY CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, AT THE END OF
SPENDING TIME WITH THE FAMILY.
THE DAY CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT
AND THAT'S WHAT IT WAS, SO
SPENDING TIME WITH THE FAMILY.
CHRISTMAS WAS FINE.
AND THAT'S WHAT IT WAS, SO
AND I KNOW THAT MY KIDS, I WOULD
CHRISTMAS WAS FINE.
GRAB A BOX OF CEREAL AND WRAPPED
AND I KNOW THAT MY KIDS, I WOULD
IT, THEY WOULD'VE BEEN GRATEFUL
GRAB A BOX OF CEREAL AND WRAPPED
FOR THAT.
IT, THEY WOULD'VE BEEN GRATEFUL
RIGHT?
FOR THAT.
>> Ellen: WELL, LISTEN.
RIGHT?
FIRST OF ALL, I JUST WANT TO
>> Ellen: WELL, LISTEN.
SAY, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR WHAT
FIRST OF ALL, I JUST WANT TO
YOU'RE DOING!
SAY, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR WHAT
THAT MEAN SO MUCH TO ME THAT YOU
YOU'RE DOING!
ARE SAVING MONEY TO HELP THE
THAT MEAN SO MUCH TO ME THAT YOU
GORILLAS.
ARE SAVING MONEY TO HELP THE
THAT REALLY, REALLY MEANS A LOT
GORILLAS.
TO ME.
THAT REALLY, REALLY MEANS A LOT
SO I WANT TO DO SOMETHING FOR
TO ME.
YOUR FAMILY.
SO I WANT TO DO SOMETHING FOR
IT IS A LITTLE BIT LATE.
YOUR FAMILY.
BUT I HAVE SOME STUFF FOR
IT IS A LITTLE BIT LATE.
CHRISTMAS.
BUT I HAVE SOME STUFF FOR
YOU KNOW ABOUT MY "12 DAYS OF
CHRISTMAS.
GIVEAWAYS," RIGHT?
YOU KNOW ABOUT MY "12 DAYS OF
>> YES!
GIVEAWAYS," RIGHT?
YOU ALWAYS MAKE US CRY, RIGHT?
>> YES!
>> Ellen: I WANT YOU TO GET
YOU ALWAYS MAKE US CRY, RIGHT?
THE GIFTS FROM DAY 1 OF MY "12
>> Ellen: I WANT YOU TO GET
DAYS" AND DAY 2, AND DAILY 3,
THE GIFTS FROM DAY 1 OF MY "12
AND TO THE ENTIRE "12 DAYS" THAT
DAYS" AND DAY 2, AND DAILY 3,
WE GAVE AWAY THIS YEAR!
AND TO THE ENTIRE "12 DAYS" THAT
OVER $2500 IN VISA AND AMAZON IF
WE GAVE AWAY THIS YEAR!
CARDS, TCL ROKU TVs!
OVER $2500 IN VISA AND AMAZON IF
FIVE YEAR NETFLIX SUBSCRIPTION.
CARDS, TCL ROKU TVs!
APPLE AIR PODS, ROUND-TRIP
FIVE YEAR NETFLIX SUBSCRIPTION.
TICKETS ON JET BLUE.
APPLE AIR PODS, ROUND-TRIP
YOU ARE GOING TO JAMAICA,
TICKETS ON JET BLUE.
MEXICO.
YOU ARE GOING TO JAMAICA,
YOU ARE GOING TO -- YOU HAVE A
MEXICO.
LOT GOING ON!
YOU ARE GOING TO -- YOU HAVE A
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
LOT GOING ON!
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU ALL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVERYBODY!
MERRY CHRISTMAS TO YOU ALL!
>> THANK YOU, ELLEN!
THANK YOU SO MUCH, EVERYBODY!
>> Ellen: I LOVE YOU,
>> THANK YOU, ELLEN!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
>> Ellen: I LOVE YOU,
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HOW AWESOME IS THAT?
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HOW AWESOME IS THAT?
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: HERE'S WHAT I WANT
♪ ♪
TO DO.
>> Ellen: HERE'S WHAT I WANT
I LOVE THAT YOU CARE ABOUT
TO DO.
SCHOOL SO MUCH.
I LOVE THAT YOU CARE ABOUT
AND SHUTTERFLY LOVES THAT YOU
SCHOOL SO MUCH.
HAVE PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
AND SHUTTERFLY LOVES THAT YOU
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HAVE PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
♪ ♪
Cologuard: colon cancer
screening for people
45 plus at average risk.
I've heard a lot of excuses
to avoid screening
for colon cancer.
I'm not worried.
It doesn't run in my family.
I can do it next year.
No rush.
Cologuard is the
noninvasive option
that finds 92%
of colon cancers.
You just get the kit
in the mail,
go to the bathroom,
collect your sample,
then ship it to the lab.
There's no excuse for waiting.
Get screened.
Ask your healthcare provider
if Cologuard is right for you.
Most insured patients pay $0.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
Ask your(announcer) provider
if Once-weekly Ozempic® isyou.
helping many people
with type 2 diabetes like James
lower their blood sugar.
A majority of adults
who took Ozempic®
reached an A1C under 7
and maintained it.
Here's your A1C.
Oh!
My A1C is under 7!
(announcer)
And you may lose weight.
Adults who took Ozempic® lost
on average up to 12 pounds.
I lost
almost 12 pounds!
Oh!
(announcer)
Ozempic® does not increase
the risk of major
cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
There's no increased risk.
Oh!
And I only have
to take it once a week.
Oh!
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
Ozempic® should not be
the first medicine
for treating diabetes,
or for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump
or swelling in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase
low blood sugar risk.
Common side effects are
nausea, vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain,
and constipation.
Some side effects can lead
to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
Once-weekly Ozempic® is
helping me reach
my blood sugar goal.
♪ OH, OH, OH, OZEMPIC®! ♪
(announcer)
You may pay as little
as $25 per prescription.
Ask your health care
provider today
about once-weekly Ozempic®.
UP NEXT AT 4:00 A LOCAL MAN
REGAINS FREEDOM TODAY.
>> A NEW PIECE OF EVIDENCE THAT
MAY CHEER HIS NAME.
>>> AN URGENT SEARCH FOR AN
8-YEAR-OLD BOY IN D.C. WHERE HE
WAS LAST SEEN AT 1:30 IN THE
MORNING.
>>> AND DG IS TRACKINGOU
Delicious Almond Breeze
almondmilk yogurt alternative.
Cut! Why did you eat that?
'Cause it tastes amazing.
Do you want to try it?
Delicious Almond Breeze
Almondmilk Yogurt Alternative.
Available now.
When your psoriasis is bad,
it can be hard to
see what's possible.
But the possibilities
become clear with Taltz.
The first and only
treatment of its kind
offering a chance
at 100% clear skin.
With Taltz,
up to 90%
of those
with moderate
to severe
psoriasis
saw a significant
improvement of
their psoriasis
plaques.
Some even
saw 100%
clear skin.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Taltz.
Before starting,
get checked for
tuberculosis.
Increased risk
of infections
and lower ability to
fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor about
infections, symptoms,
or if inflammatory bowel disease
symptoms develop, worsen
or if you've had a
vaccine or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur.
See the possibilities.
Ask your doctor about Taltz.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: BEFORE WE GO I WANT
TO TALK TO TAYLOR ABOUT ONE MORE
THING.
WILL YOU COME BACK DOWN HERE?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I FORGOT I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO WHEN YOU GET
OLDER, DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
TO BE WHEN YOU GROW UP?
>> YES, I DO PRAY TO SPEED ON
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I WANT TO BE A SCIENCE
TEACHER.
I LIKE SCIENCE.
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU LIKE
ABOUT SCIENCE?
>> WE GET TO DO ALL OF THESE
COOL EXPER EXPERIMENTS.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN, BUT IT IS SOMETHING
COOL.
>> Ellen: HERE'S WHAT I AM
GOING TO DO.
I LOVE THAT YOU CARE ABOUT
SCHOOL SO MUCH.
AND SHUTTERFLY LOVES THAT YOU
HAVE PERFECT ATTENDANCE.
THEY WILL GIVE YOU A $10,000
SCHOLARSHIP TO MAKE SURE --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
YOU GO TO COLLEGE!
I WANT TO THANK CHARLES BARKLEY,
THE JONAS BROTHERS!
I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW!
BE KIND TO ONE ANOTHER!
BYE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 4:00, BUY YOUR
UMBRELLA, SOON YOU WILL NEED
COATS, TOO.
I'M TRACKING BIG TIME RAIN
HEADED OUR WAY.
>>> LOCAL NEWS, A LOCAL MAN
CLEARED FOR MURDER.
THE EVIDENCE THAT CLEARS HIS
NAME.
>>> A MOTHER CHARGED WITH
ABDUCTING HER FOUR CHILDREN
MONTHS AGO FOUND OUT OF STATE.
>> LOCATING MELANIE AND THE
CHILDREN SAFE IS A HUGE RELIEF.
>> WHAT'S NEXT FOR THE KIDS AND
NEW REACTION FROM THEIR FATHER.
>>> AND THE NEWS 4 I-TEAM
WORKING TO STOP UNDER AGE VAPING
AND GETTING ANSWERS FOR PARENTS.
>> THE IMPACT OF MY SON GETTING
CAUGHT UP IN VAPING WAS
DEVASTATING TO HIM.
>> Reporter: WE'LL SHOW YOU WHAT
HAPPENED WHEN WE WENT UNDER
COVER.
NEWS 4 AT 4:00 STARTS NOW.
>> AND FIRST AT 4:00, GET YOUR
EMBREL LA BACK OUT.
RAIN IS MOVING BACK IN ON THE
STORM TEAM 4 RADAR.
>> YOU CAN SEE IT ON THE RAIN
ALREADY COMING DOWN IN SOME
LOCAL NEIGHBORHOODS.
IT'S ALL A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE
WE ALL WANT THE UMBRELLAS AGAIN.
>> LET'S CHECK IT OFF.
DOUG, HOW IS IT LOOKING OUT
THERE?
>> WE ARE TRACKING THAT RAIN.
FAIRLY DRY AIR, THOUGH.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE ARE SEEING RAIN
AREA WIDE.
A LOT OF US FOUGHT HITTING THE
GROUND AROUND D.C. METRO AREA,
UP TOWARD BALTIMORE.
BUT BACK TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN,
BACK TOWARDS WINCHESTER, IT'S A
LITTLE HEAVIER.
WE ARE STARTING TO SEE THAT
HITTING THE GROUND.
STARTING TO SEE 66.
81 UP 270 AND 70.
IT WILL START TO GET WET OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE