♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WHEN YOU SEE ME FOR THE FIRST
TIME AND REACT LIKE THAT IT'S SO
SWEET OF YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
HAVE A SEAT, EVERYBODY, THANKS
FOR BEING HERE.
MAN, THERE WERE SOME GOOD
DANCERS JUST NOW THAT I WAS
WATCHING.
THAT WAS VERY IMPRESSIVE DANCIN
DANCING.
YOU'VE BEEN WATCHING
"THE BACHELOR" I ASSUME BECAUSE
I'VE BEEN WATCHING
"THE BACHELOR."
BECAUSE OF THE COURT ORDER.
YOU'RE GOING TO WATCH TONIGHT,
PROBABLY?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
EVERY YEAR I SAY I'M NOT GOING
TO WATCH AND THEN EVERY YEAR I
WATCH.
AND I DON'T LIKE TO ADMIT THAT I
WATCH HER THAT I'M A FAN, I SAY
WHAT MOST COUPLES SAY IS I WATCH
BECAUSE OF PORSCHE, AND I HAVE
TO TELL HER ABOUT IT.
THE VERY FIRST WAS IN 2002
ANALYSIS 24 SEASON.
MY TALK SHOW PREMIERED ONE YEAR
LATER AND WHERE ONLY IN OUR 17TH
SEASON.
I'M NOT THE GOODEST AT MATH OR
ENGLISH BUT EITHER MY SHOW
SKIPPED SEVEN SEASONS OR THE
BACHELOR IS GOING BY DOG YEARS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT'S IN ITS
24TH SEASON.
EACH YEAR THE CONTESTANTS CHANGE
BUT I'VE NOTICED IT DOESN'T
MATTER BECAUSE EVERY SEASON ENDS
UP EXACTLY THE SAME AND TO PROVE
IT I'VE TAKEN CLIPS FROM THE
LAST TWO SEASONS AND I PUT THEM
TOGETHER IN AN EDITING MACHINE,
WHEN I SAY I PUT THEM TOGETHER,
I MEAN MY EDITORS, YOU PROBABLY
FIGURED OUT, WHEN I CALL AN
EDITING MACHINE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THE FIRST THING YOU'LL NOTICE
FROM WATCHING "THE BACHELOR" IS
THAT IT'S REALLY HARD.
IT'S HARD TO FOR THE BACHELOR
AND IT'S HARD FOR THE WOMEN.
>> THIS HAS BEEN REALLY, REALLY
HARD.
>> IT SHOWS ME TRULY HOW HARD
THIS IS GETTING AND HOW MUCH
HARDER IT'S GOING TO GET.
>> IT SO HARD.
>> IT'S HARD TO SEE SOMEONE ELSE
GET THAT.
>> IT IS HARD TO SEE HIM HAVE A
CONNECTION WITH HER.
>> IT'S BEEN SO HARD.
>> FOR WHATEVER REASON IT'S JUST
BEEN HARD.
>> IT'S JUST BEEN REALLY, REALLY
DIFFICULT.
>> IT'S JUST HARD.
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD.
>> TONIGHT'S DECISION HAS BEEN
THE HARDEST.
>> LIKE, IT'S JUST SO HARD.
>> SEEING HOW DISAPPOINTED SHE
WAS IN THAT WAS HARD.
>> IT'S SO HARD.
>> Ellen: THAT'S WHAT SHE
SAID.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
ANOTHER THING THAT HAPPENS EVERY
SEASON IS EVERYONE ON THE SHOW
STARTS QUESTIONING EACH OTHER'S
MOTIVES.
>> LIKE WITH HANNAH, LAST
SEASON, SEEING HER FALL FOR
SOMEONE THAT WASN'T THERE FOR
THE RIGHT REASONS.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF GIRLS THAT
ARE HERE FOR THE RIGHT REASONS.
>> I WOULD HOPE FOR ALL THE
RIGHT REASONS.
>> HE REALLY NEEDS TO THINK
ABOUT WHO IS HERE FOR THE RIGHT
REASONS.
>> BEING HERE FOR COLTON IS HER
OPPORTUNITY TO GET OUT OF MIAMI
INSTEAD OF LIGHT, REALLY BEING
HERE FOR GENUINE REASONS.
>> I HAVE BEEN NOTHING BUT LIKE,
HONEST, UNLIKE, HERE FOR THE
RIGHT REASONS.
>> IF ANYONE IS HERE FOR THE
RIGHT REASONS IT IS TO ME.
>> SHE IS SHOW ME KNOW REASONS
THAT SHE'S HERE FOR THE RIGHT
REASONS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: SOME OF THEM ARE FOR
THE WRONG REASONS, NOT THE RIGHT
REASON, WHICH IS TO FALL IN LOVE
WITH A STRANGER INTO WEEKS AND
GET MARRIED.
THAT IS THE RIGHT REASON TO BE
THERE.
AND AS I'VE BEEN WATCHING THIS
SEASON I'VE NOTICED WOMEN GO ON
A DATE WITH PETER AND THEY SHOW
LOVE IN A VERY SPECIFIC WAY.
THESE ARE CLIPS FROM, THIS IS
ALL FROM THIS SEASON.
>> KELSEY ! >> HI.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> HELLO.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I MISS YOU!
>> OH!
>> WHAT'S UP, BEAUTIFUL.
>> HI!
>> HI.
[LAUGHTER]
>> YOU LOOK CUTE.
>> YOU LOOK ADORABLE.
>> I'VE MISSED YOU.
COME HERE.
I'M SO HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: WHY?
WHY?
WHY DO WOMEN LOVE TO BE PICKED
UP BY MEN?
I THOUGHT IT WAS A STRAIGHT
THING BECAUSE I NEVER RUN AND
JUMP IN TO PORTIA'S ARMS, ONCE,
BUT I WAS TRYING TO GET AWAY
FROM A SNAPPING TURTLE.
ACTUALLY, I HAVE JUMPED INTO A
MAN'S ARMS ONCE HERE ON THE SHOW
BUT YOU CAN'T BLAME ME BECAUSE
IT WAS RYAN GOSLING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: OH, OH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> COME ON!
>> Ellen: OH, OH!
♪ ♪
>> COME ON!
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
THREE TIMES.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS WHAT ONE MAN WE WOULD
THREE TIMES.
ALL LIKE TO GET AROSE FROM, THIS
THERE IS WHAT ONE MAN WE WOULD
IS tWITCH, EVERYBODY.
ALL LIKE TO GET AROSE FROM, THIS
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
IS tWITCH, EVERYBODY.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
>> IT'S LIKE, YEAH.
>> Ellen: I HAVE A BAG FULL OF
QUARTERS.
>> COOL.
>> Ellen: I CONTROL IT FROM
HERE, tWITCH X?
>> THAT'S COOL.
OH, [BLEEP]!
OH, THIS ACTUALLY, IT ACTUALLY
WORKS.
OKAY.
WOW.
>> Ellen: THAT'S NOT LONG
ENOUGH.
>> OKAY, YEAH.
YEAH.
THAT'LL WORK.
>> Ellen: OKAY?
IT WOULD BE COOL THE REST WERE
JUST A SECOND, OKAY.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: I'LL WAIT.
I'M GONNA SPREAD IT OUT THROUGH
THE SHOW.
IT'S MONDAY, IF YOU NEED A BOOST
HONEY NUT CHEERIOS ONCE TO MAKE
YOU FEEL THAT WITH THE SPECIAL
MOOD BOOSTER.
♪ ♪
>> WATCH THE GATE.
["FIGHT SONG" PLAYING]
>> Ellen: IT'S A SHAME.
THAT'S A SHAME.
SOMEBODY WORKING THAT THING
DIDN'T DO IT AT THE RIGHT TIME.
THANK YOU, HONEY NUT CHEERIOS.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE NEWS.
THERE IS A MAN IN FLORIDA.
HE BECAME THE OLDEST LICENSED
DRIVER IN AMERICA.
HE'S 107 YEARS SORRY.
I'M BEING TOLD HE'S OUTSIDE, HE
STILL PARKING?
WE HAVE A CAMERA?
OKAY, HE'S PARKING, LET'S SEE.
[AUDIENCE REACTING]
>> Ellen: WELL, OKAY, OKAY, HE
SHOULD BE HERE SHORTLY.
OKAY.
WHILE WE WAIT FOR HIM I WANT TO
TALK ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE THAT'S
IN THE NEWS.
ORLANDO BLOOM GOT A TATTOO WITH
HIS SON'S NAME IN MORSE CODE.
DID YOU SEE THIS?
BUT THERE WAS A MISTAKE.
IT'S A MUST A SAFE "FLYNN" BUT
IT SAYS "FRYNN" ."
THE TAXI WAS PERMANENT.
REMIND ME OF ONE OF MY FAVORITE
SEGMENTS I WANT TO DO RIGHT NOW.
IT'S TIME FOR "BAD IT PAID
TATTOOS."
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: YOU'RE GETTING GET
AT THAT.
>> GOT A RHYTHM GOING.
>> Ellen: JASON FROM AMSTERDAM
NEW YORK SAID YES, THESE ARE ALL
MY EXES.
[AUDIENCE REACTING]
>> Ellen: ALL THOSE LUCKY
LADIES THAT GOT AWAY.
FROM PHOENIX, ARIZONA, "I WAS A
BIT DRUNK WHEN I DECIDED TO GET
THIS TATTOO.
THE WORD "SOMETIMES" IS
MISSPELLED."
AT LEAST IT'S SMALL?
NERISSA FROM CAMBRIDGE,
CALIFORNIA, "SOMEONE CAME INTO
MY OFFICE WITH A TATTOO THAT
SAID "IT IS WHAT IT IS" AND I
THOUGHT IT SAID "TITS WITH TITS
TITS"."
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: THE OLD SLOGAN.
JAMES AND PORTLAND, OREGON,
"ELLEN, I SAW THIS ON LINE, SHE
WANTED REVENGE ON HIS WIFE SO HE
GOT A TATTOO OF HER SNORING.
>> OH!
>> Ellen: WOW.
THAT SEEMS LIKE A REALLY HEALTHY
RELATIONSHIP, DOESN'T IT?
IF YOU SEE A BAD PAID FOR
TATTOO, SEND IT TO ME.
HOW IS JOE DOING?
OH.
IT'S SNOWING OUTSIDE.
HE WENT TO A DIFFERENT
NEIGHBORHOOD.
OH, JOE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WHAT SOMETHING THAT
RHYMES WITH YUMMY?
>> GUMMY.
>> Ellen: THAT IS CORRECT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> YOU GOT TO THINK ABOUT THESE
THINGS SO THAT YOU HAVE THE BEST
POSSIBLE SLEEP ON THE ROAD.
>> Ellen: I'M SO GL
Big news America!
For a limited time, we've
changed the shape
of Honey Nut Cheerios.
Because we want people to know
they're delicious
AND can help lower cholesterol.
Heart healthy. Get it? A heart!
Can you believe they had one in
my size?!
Hi guys. This is the
Chevy Silverado,
with the world's
first invisible trailer.
Invisible trailer?
And it's not the
trailer right next to us?
This guy?
You don't
believe me?
Hop in.
Good lookin' pickup,
I will say that.
Oh wow.
Silverado offers an optional
technology package with
up to 15
different views -
including one
enhanced view
that makes your
trailer appear invisible.
Wow.
- That's pretty sweet.
- That's cool.
Oooohh!
That's awesome.
Where'd the trailer go?
I love it.
It's magic.
>> Ellen: I HAVE A PAIN IN MY
NECK THAT ALWAYS LETS ME KNOW
WHEN IT'S GOING TO RAIN.
HERE'S MY PRODUCER, ANDY, AND
RIGHT NOW HE'S TELLING ME IT'S
TIME TO PLAY "MAKE IT RAIN."
WHERE IS HE?
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT, JESSICA
COLEMAN AND AMBER HARTLEY, COME
ON DOWN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HI.
HELLO.
WHO ARE YOU?
HI.
>> I'M AMBER.
WHO ARE YOU?
>> Ellen: WHERE YOU LIVE, WHAT
>> I'M AMBER.
YOU DO QUESTION WORK >> I LIVE
>> Ellen: WHERE YOU LIVE, WHAT
IN FRESNO, CALIFORNIA, AND I'M A
YOU DO QUESTION WORK >> I LIVE
STAY-AT-HOME MOM OF TWO KIDS.
IN FRESNO, CALIFORNIA, AND I'M A
>> Ellen: HOW OLD?
STAY-AT-HOME MOM OF TWO KIDS.
>> FOUR AND ONE.
>> Ellen: HOW OLD?
>> Ellen: GOOD THING YOU'RE
>> FOUR AND ONE.
AWAY FROM THEM.
>> Ellen: GOOD THING YOU'RE
AND YOU ARE QUESTION MARKS
AWAY FROM THEM.
BECAUSE I'M JESSICA COLEMAN, AND
AND YOU ARE QUESTION MARKS
I'M FROM IRVINE, CALIFORNIA.
BECAUSE I'M JESSICA COLEMAN, AND
>> Ellen: HERE'S HOW THE GAME
I'M FROM IRVINE, CALIFORNIA.
WORKS.
>> Ellen: HERE'S HOW THE GAME
HIDDEN UNDERNEATH AN UMBRELLA
WORKS.
THERE THERE IS $5,000 CASH.
HIDDEN UNDERNEATH AN UMBRELLA
UNFORTUNATELY THERE'S ALSO A LOT
THERE THERE IS $5,000 CASH.
OF WATER.
UNFORTUNATELY THERE'S ALSO A LOT
I'LL ASK YOU A QUESTION READ AS
OF WATER.
SOON AS YOU KNOW THE ANSWER
I'LL ASK YOU A QUESTION READ AS
YOU'LL GRAB A WATER BOTTLE.
SOON AS YOU KNOW THE ANSWER
IF YOU ARE RIGHT YOU GET TO PICK
YOU'LL GRAB A WATER BOTTLE.
AN UMBRELLA.
IF YOU ARE RIGHT YOU GET TO PICK
READY?
AN UMBRELLA.
HEAD OVER THERE.
READY?
[APPLAUSE]
HEAD OVER THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU'LL START WITH YOUR HANDS
ALL RIGHT.
BEHIND YOUR BACKS.
YOU'LL START WITH YOUR HANDS
WHEN YOU KNOW THE ANSWER GRAB
BEHIND YOUR BACKS.
IT.
WHEN YOU KNOW THE ANSWER GRAB
MAKE SURE YOU KNOW THE ANSWER
IT.
BECAUSE OF IT'S NOT THE CORRECT
MAKE SURE YOU KNOW THE ANSWER
ONE YOUR OPPONENT CAN STEAL.
BECAUSE OF IT'S NOT THE CORRECT
THE MORE YOU GET RIGHT THE MORE
ONE YOUR OPPONENT CAN STEAL.
CHANCES, OBVIOUSLY.
THE MORE YOU GET RIGHT THE MORE
JUSTIN BIEBER'S NEW HIT SONG IS
CHANCES, OBVIOUSLY.
CALLED "YUMMY."
JUSTIN BIEBER'S NEW HIT SONG IS
>> SORRY!
CALLED "YUMMY."
>> Ellen: WHAT SOMETHING THAT
>> SORRY!
RHYMES WITH "YUMMY?"
>> Ellen: WHAT SOMETHING THAT
>> GUMMY.
RHYMES WITH "YUMMY?"
>> Ellen: THAT A SCRATCH.
>> GUMMY.
PICK ONE.
>> Ellen: THAT A SCRATCH.
THAT ONE?
PICK ONE.
GOOD LUCK.
THAT ONE?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GOOD LUCK.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OH, MY GOD, .
♪ ♪
WOW.
>> Ellen: OH, MY GOD, .
THAT IS CRAZY.
WOW.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME THAT IS
THAT IS CRAZY.
EVER HAPPENED AND UNFORTUNATELY
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME THAT IS
DUE TO MY LEGAL TEAM I NEED TO
EVER HAPPENED AND UNFORTUNATELY
PROVE THAT THERE IS WATER UNDER
DUE TO MY LEGAL TEAM I NEED TO
THE OTHER UMBRELLAS.
PROVE THAT THERE IS WATER UNDER
SO PULL ANY OTHER UMBRELLA,
THE OTHER UMBRELLAS.
PLEASE.
SO PULL ANY OTHER UMBRELLA,
[SCREAMING]
PLEASE.
>> THERE IS WATER!
[SCREAMING]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE IS WATER!
THAT COULD BE A FLUKE.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
PULL ANOTHER ONE.
THAT COULD BE A FLUKE.
>> NO!
PULL ANOTHER ONE.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
>> NO!
IT'S REALLY GOOD FOR YOU.
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME
IT'S REALLY GOOD FOR YOU.
EMPTY ENDED, YOU'RE GETTING A 6E
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE NOT GOING HOME
GETTING $5,000.
EMPTY ENDED, YOU'RE GETTING A 6E
WE'LL BE BACK!
GETTING $5,000.
♪ ♪
WE'LL BE BACK!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> HE'S LIKE COME UP BUT YOU'RE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
PLAYING IN TWO MONTHS.
>> HE'S LIKE COME UP BUT YOU'RE
AND I'M LIKE YEAH.
PLAYING IN TWO MONTHS.
HE'S LIKE, THIS IS BIG PROBLEM
AND I'M LIKE YEAH.
FOR YOU.
HE'S LIKE, THIS IS BIG PROBLEM
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
FOR YOU.
[chuckles]
Beat you home.
Uh yeah, but I got dinner.
Cheers!
ANNOUNCER:
With Giant same-day pickup,
we'll do the shopping
for you
so you can do more
of what you love.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to everything
from helpful reminders...
to presorted
prescription packs.
CVS customers are better...
Thanks to free
prescription savings reviews...
home delivery...
and more.
No wonder CVS customers
are better...than most
at staying on
their prescriptions...
Which tends to
make you healthier.
And what could
be better than that?
Treat yourself well at CVS.
And what could
be better than that?
With Redfin, when you see a home
you love,
you can book a tour on demand.
So you can see homes first.
And with your local Redfin Agent
guiding you,
the right home is closer than
you think.
I'm Amy Klobuchar and I approve
this message.
We live in a country of shared
dreams.
That no matter where you come
from.
No matter the color of your
skin.
No matter who you love.
That you can make it in the
United States of America.
So I stand before you today
as the grandaughter of an iron
ore miner.
As the daughter of a teacher and
a newspaperman.
As the first woman elected to
the U.S. Senate from the state
of Minnesota.
And a candidate for president of
the United States.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OUR FIRST GUEST IS A
VERY FUNNY HOST OF
"THE DAILY SHOW," TAKE A LOOK.
>> THE DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY
CAMPAIGN.
AND WHEN IT STARTED IT WAS ALL
KUMBAYA, LEFT SPEECH TRUMPED
TOGETHER.
BUT NOW IT'S TURNED INTO A
SEASON OF "GAME OF THRONES."
EVERYONE BACKSTABBING PRICK THE
HOUSE OF BERNIE HAS GROWN IN
STRENGTH AND SIZE WHILE FACING A
CHALLENGE FROM THAT KINGDOM OF
PETE BUTTIGIEG.
MEANWHILE THE ONCE POWERFUL LORD
BIDEN IS SLOWLY WATCHING HIS
INFLUENCE SLIP AWAY.
AND DON'T FORGET, ONCE THEY'RE
ALL DONE FIGHTING EACH OTHER,
THEY WILL HAVE TO FACE OFF
AGAINST THE ULTIMATE ENEMY, THE
WHITE KING.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Ellen: PLEASE WELCOME
TREVOR NOAH.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: HELLO, TREVOR.
>> OH, HELLO, ELLEN.
HELLO EVERYBODY.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> Ellen: YOU'RE A FUNNY MAN.
YOU'RE A FUNNY MAN AND I SAW YOU
AT THE GRAMMYS, WE WERE BOTH
NOMINATED.
>> FOR A GRAMMY.
WE WERE BOTH GRAMMY NOMINEES FOR
COMEDY ALBUM.
>> Ellen: AND THEN GRAMMY
LOSERS.
>> I DON'T THINK OF IT AS
I THINK EVERYBODY WAS A NOMINEE
LOSERS.
AND ONE PERSON WILL WIN THE
I THINK EVERYBODY WAS A NOMINEE
AWARD AND THAT PERSON WAS DAVE
AND ONE PERSON WILL WIN THE
CHAPELLE.
AWARD AND THAT PERSON WAS DAVE
DAVE CHAPELLE, I'M NOT OFFENDED
CHAPELLE.
BY THAT.
DAVE CHAPELLE, I'M NOT OFFENDED
>> Ellen: I'M NOT EITHER.
BY THAT.
>> BUT HE WASN'T THERE TO GET
>> Ellen: I'M NOT EITHER.
THE AWARD, AND I THINK, WE WERE
>> BUT HE WASN'T THERE TO GET
BOTH IN OUR SEATS.
THE AWARD, AND I THINK, WE WERE
>> Ellen: I THOUGHT BACKSTAGE
BOTH IN OUR SEATS.
BUT HE GOT THERE LATE AND I
>> Ellen: I THOUGHT BACKSTAGE
SAID, YOU DON'T DESERVE IT.
BUT HE GOT THERE LATE AND I
>> I AGREE, BECAUSE HE WAS AT
SAID, YOU DON'T DESERVE IT.
THE BAR AND THEN HE MISSED THE
>> I AGREE, BECAUSE HE WAS AT
AWARD AND I WAS LIKE, THAT
THE BAR AND THEN HE MISSED THE
SHOULD BE A RULE.
AWARD AND I WAS LIKE, THAT
WHOEVER GETS TO THE AWARD FIRST
SHOULD BE A RULE.
SHOULD GET IT.
WHOEVER GETS TO THE AWARD FIRST
AND THAT WOULD'VE BEEN ME AND
SHOULD GET IT.
YOU.
AND THAT WOULD'VE BEEN ME AND
>> Ellen: YES, WE BOTH WOULD
YOU.
HAVE RUN.
>> Ellen: YES, WE BOTH WOULD
ANYWAY, CONGRATULATIONS FOR YOUR
HAVE RUN.
NOMINATION.
ANYWAY, CONGRATULATIONS FOR YOUR
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
NOMINATION.
CAN VENTILATIONS FOR YOURS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Ellen: YOU'RE A FUNNY MAN.
CAN VENTILATIONS FOR YOURS.
I LEARNED THIS TODAY WHICH I
>> Ellen: YOU'RE A FUNNY MAN.
NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I LEARNED THIS TODAY WHICH I
FOR SMALL, DO YOU PLAY TENNIS?
NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
>> I DO NOW.
FOR SMALL, DO YOU PLAY TENNIS?
>> Ellen: THIS IS THE CRAZIEST
>> I DO NOW.
THING.
>> Ellen: THIS IS THE CRAZIEST
YOU PLAYED WITH RAPHAEL AND THE
THING.
DOLL.
YOU PLAYED WITH RAPHAEL AND THE
SPEAK OUT RAPHAEL AND ADELE,
DOLL.
ROGER FEDERAL, AND BILL GATES IN
SPEAK OUT RAPHAEL AND ADELE,
THE BIGGEST TENNIS MATCH THAT'SR
ROGER FEDERAL, AND BILL GATES IN
BEEN ATTENDED.
THE BIGGEST TENNIS MATCH THAT'SR
THE LARGEST TENNIS MATCH OF ALL
BEEN ATTENDED.
TIME.
THE LARGEST TENNIS MATCH OF ALL
52,000 PEOPLE IN CAPE TOWN,
TIME.
SOUTH AFRICA.
52,000 PEOPLE IN CAPE TOWN,
SPEWING JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE A
SOUTH AFRICA.
BIG CELEBRITY?
SPEWING JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE A
HOW DID YOU GET INTO THAT?
BIG CELEBRITY?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS
HOW DID YOU GET INTO THAT?
HAPPENED BUT I THINK I BECAME A
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS
FAN TO MY FRIENDS WITH
HAPPENED BUT I THINK I BECAME A
BILL GATES.
FAN TO MY FRIENDS WITH
WE ADMITTED MANY TIMES AND WE
BILL GATES.
HAVE CONVERSATIONS AND WANT TO
WE ADMITTED MANY TIMES AND WE
HEAVE PHONE AND HE WAS LIKE A
HAVE CONVERSATIONS AND WANT TO
JAUNT TO ME.
HEAVE PHONE AND HE WAS LIKE A
IT IS LIKE A BUTTON CAPE TOWN,
JAUNT TO ME.
AND I WAS LIKE, THAT'S A LONG
IT IS LIKE A BUTTON CAPE TOWN,
WAY TO GO TO PLAY TENNIS ANY
AND I WAS LIKE, THAT'S A LONG
SITE, WITH ROGER FEDERAL?
WAY TO GO TO PLAY TENNIS ANY
AND I WAS LIKE, THAT'S A STRANGE
SITE, WITH ROGER FEDERAL?
REQUEST.
AND I WAS LIKE, THAT'S A STRANGE
BUT THEY HAD WANTED ME TO PLAY
REQUEST.
TENNIS WITH THEM AND I WAS LIKE,
BUT THEY HAD WANTED ME TO PLAY
I MEANT.
TENNIS WITH THEM AND I WAS LIKE,
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY
I MEANT.
TENNIS, THOUGH, BUT I DIDN'T
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY
WANT TO TELL THEM THIS BECAUSE
TENNIS, THOUGH, BUT I DIDN'T
WHEN COOL PEOPLE INVITE YOU TO
WANT TO TELL THEM THIS BECAUSE
THINGS YOU LIKE YEAH, I'M IN.
WHEN COOL PEOPLE INVITE YOU TO
SO I WAS LIKE, I'M IN.
THINGS YOU LIKE YEAH, I'M IN.
AND THEN THERE WERE LIKE, DO YOU
SO I WAS LIKE, I'M IN.
KNOW HOW TO PLAY TENNIS?
AND THEN THERE WERE LIKE, DO YOU
AND I WAS LIKE, YEAH.
KNOW HOW TO PLAY TENNIS?
YOU KNOW, THE THING.
AND I WAS LIKE, YEAH.
AND THEN TWO MONTHS BEFORE THE
YOU KNOW, THE THING.
EVENT ROGER'S PEOPLE CALLED AND
AND THEN TWO MONTHS BEFORE THE
THEY WERE LIKE, CAN WE SEE A
EVENT ROGER'S PEOPLE CALLED AND
VIDEO OF YOU PLAYING TENNIS?
THEY WERE LIKE, CAN WE SEE A
SO I CALLED MY FRIEND AND I WAS
VIDEO OF YOU PLAYING TENNIS?
LIKE HEY, LET'S GO PLAY SOME
SO I CALLED MY FRIEND AND I WAS
TENNIS AND WILL VIDEO THIS AND
LIKE HEY, LET'S GO PLAY SOME
SEND IT TO THEM AND THEN WE GOT
TENNIS AND WILL VIDEO THIS AND
THERE AND I COULD NOT, PEOPLE
SEND IT TO THEM AND THEN WE GOT
THINK TENNIS IS EASY.
THERE AND I COULD NOT, PEOPLE
I COULD NOT HIT THE BALL TO
THINK TENNIS IS EASY.
WHERE I WAS TRYING TO HIT THE
I COULD NOT HIT THE BALL TO
BALL.
WHERE I WAS TRYING TO HIT THE
I COULD HIT THE BALL BUT NOT IN
BALL.
THE DIRECTION THAT I WAS TRYING
I COULD HIT THE BALL BUT NOT IN
TO GET IT TO GO AND THEN I
THE DIRECTION THAT I WAS TRYING
PANICKED.
TO GET IT TO GO AND THEN I
AND THEN I WAS JUST LIKE, I'M
PANICKED.
SCREWED.
AND THEN I WAS JUST LIKE, I'M
AND THEN I GOT A COACH AND I
SCREWED.
TOLD HIM MY PHONE DOESN'T WORK,
AND THEN I GOT A COACH AND I
IT CAN'T SEND VIDEOS RIGHT NOW.
TOLD HIM MY PHONE DOESN'T WORK,
SO I'VE GOT A TENNIS COACH AND
IT CAN'T SEND VIDEOS RIGHT NOW.
THEN IN TWO MONTHS I HAD TO
SO I'VE GOT A TENNIS COACH AND
LEARN TENNIS FROM SCRATCH, WITH
THEN IN TWO MONTHS I HAD TO
THE CRAZIEST THINGS I DID IT IN
LEARN TENNIS FROM SCRATCH, WITH
MY LIFE.
THE CRAZIEST THINGS I DID IT IN
EVERY SINGLE DAY, TWO AND A
MY LIFE.
HALF-3 HOURS JUST LEARNING HOW
EVERY SINGLE DAY, TWO AND A
TO PLAY TENNIS.
HALF-3 HOURS JUST LEARNING HOW
THAT'S TWO MONTHS OF ME
TO PLAY TENNIS.
LEARNING.
THAT'S TWO MONTHS OF ME
THIS YEAR, PANICKING RIGHT NOW.
LEARNING.
I WAS LIKE, I'M THE PERSON IS
THIS YEAR, PANICKING RIGHT NOW.
PANICKING THERE.
I WAS LIKE, I'M THE PERSON IS
>> Ellen: LOOK AT THAT.
PANICKING THERE.
>> PANIC.
>> Ellen: LOOK AT THAT.
PANIC.
>> PANIC.
AND WHAT WAS WILD, WHAT WAS
PANIC.
WILD, THIS IS CRAZY.
AND WHAT WAS WILD, WHAT WAS
SO I GET THE TENNIS COACH, BUT
WILD, THIS IS CRAZY.
NOW THERE'S CONFUSION BECAUSE
SO I GET THE TENNIS COACH, BUT
THE ROGER FEDERAL OR PEOPLE
NOW THERE'S CONFUSION BECAUSE
PHONED THE TENNIS COACH AND THEY
THE ROGER FEDERAL OR PEOPLE
GO HEY COME OUT THIS GUY NEEDS A
PHONED THE TENNIS COACH AND THEY
COACH IN THE TENNIS COACHING
GO HEY COME OUT THIS GUY NEEDS A
PLACES LIKE, WHAT DOES HE NEED A
COACH IN THE TENNIS COACHING
COACH FOR QUESTION WORK AND
PLACES LIKE, WHAT DOES HE NEED A
THEY'RE LIKE, HE'S PLAYING
COACH FOR QUESTION WORK AND
TENNIS AGAINST ME NIGHT SO THEY
THEY'RE LIKE, HE'S PLAYING
THINK I'M A PROFESSIONAL SO THEY
TENNIS AGAINST ME NIGHT SO THEY
GO, WE GOT THE RIGHT PERSON, THE
THINK I'M A PROFESSIONAL SO THEY
SKY TRAIN'S PROFESSIONALS.
GO, WE GOT THE RIGHT PERSON, THE
I NEED TO BE TAUGHT LIKE A
SKY TRAIN'S PROFESSIONALS.
CHILD.
I NEED TO BE TAUGHT LIKE A
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY THE
CHILD.
GAME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY THE
SO I GET THERE AND HE'S FROM
GAME.
EASTERN EUROPE AND HE'S LIKE,
SO I GET THERE AND HE'S FROM
"OKAY, YOU READY TO PLAY SOME
EASTERN EUROPE AND HE'S LIKE,
TENNIS" AND HE'S LIKE, "HOW MUCH
"OKAY, YOU READY TO PLAY SOME
OF YOU PLAYED BEFORE?"
TENNIS" AND HE'S LIKE, "HOW MUCH
AND I'M LIKE, NOTHING.
OF YOU PLAYED BEFORE?"
AND HE'S LIKE, "FUNNY GUY."
AND I'M LIKE, NOTHING.
AND THEY DO THE THING IN MY BALL
AND HE'S LIKE, "FUNNY GUY."
GOES.
AND THEY DO THE THING IN MY BALL
AND HE GOES, YOU HAVEN'T PLAYED
GOES.
IN A WHILE?
AND HE GOES, YOU HAVEN'T PLAYED
AND I'M LIKE, IF A WHILE IS
IN A WHILE?
LIFE, YES, A WHILE.
AND I'M LIKE, IF A WHILE IS
AND HE SAYS, HIT AGAIN, AFTER
LIFE, YES, A WHILE.
FIVE OR SIX HE LOOKS AT ME AND
AND HE SAYS, HIT AGAIN, AFTER
HE'S LIKE, HOW MUCH YOU PLAY
FIVE OR SIX HE LOOKS AT ME AND
TENNIS?
HE'S LIKE, HOW MUCH YOU PLAY
MUCH OF YOU PLAYED?
TENNIS?
BUT YOU'RE PLAYING ROGER FEDERER
MUCH OF YOU PLAYED?
IN TWO MONTHS.
BUT YOU'RE PLAYING ROGER FEDERER
AND I'M LIKE, YEAH.
IN TWO MONTHS.
AND HE SAYS, "THIS IS BIG
AND I'M LIKE, YEAH.
PROBLEM FOR YOU."
AND HE SAYS, "THIS IS BIG
SO HE DOESN'T REALLY KNOW HOW TO
PROBLEM FOR YOU."
COACH ME, SO THIS IS THE MOST
SO HE DOESN'T REALLY KNOW HOW TO
AMAZING THING, HE HITS THE BALL
COACH ME, SO THIS IS THE MOST
TO ME AND HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO
AMAZING THING, HE HITS THE BALL
TEACH ME BECAUSE I'M USELESS SO
TO ME AND HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO
JUST KEEPS GOING GREAT HE'S LIKE
TEACH ME BECAUSE I'M USELESS SO
JUST BRUSH THE BALL.
JUST KEEPS GOING GREAT HE'S LIKE
BRUSH THE BALL.
JUST BRUSH THE BALL.
SO I'M TRYING.
BRUSH THE BALL.
HE'S LIKE NO, BRUSH THE BALL.
SO I'M TRYING.
HE DOESN'T CHANGE HIS
HE'S LIKE NO, BRUSH THE BALL.
INSTRUCTION BUT HE'S LIKE,
HE DOESN'T CHANGE HIS
BRUSH.
INSTRUCTION BUT HE'S LIKE,
NOW BASH IT.
BRUSH.
BRUSH IT.
NOW BASH IT.
NO, BRUSH IT.
BRUSH IT.
BRUSH THE BALL.
NO, BRUSH IT.
YOU GOT TO BRUSH IT.
AND MIGHT, BRUSH IT.
AND HE'S LIKE, BRUSH IT.
DON'T HIT, BRUSH.
TRY TO BRUSH THE BALL.
AND I AM TRYING MY ASS OFF.
BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH, LIKE
A WEEK AND HALF A BRUSH IN, THE
BALL DOES NOT GO TO THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE NET AND I'M
PANICKING.
I SAID COME ON BOARD TO LOOK
LIKE AN IDIOT IN FRONT OF 52,000
PEOPLE.
THEN, I MOVED TO ANOTHER PLACE
WHERE GOT TO GET ANOTHER COACH
BECAUSE I'M COACHING IN EVERY
CITY WHERE I'M DOING COMEDY
ENTERING AND THEN I GET ANOTHER
COACH AND SHE'S ALSO FROM
EASTERN EUROPE, THIS IS
HILARIOUS.
I MEET HER ON DAY ONE AND SHE'S
LIKE, SO YOUR PEOPLE TELL ME YOU
NEED COACH.
AND I'M LIKE, YES.
SHE'S LIKE, YOU PLAY TENNIS?
SHE'S LIKE, A LITTLE BIT.
SHE'S LIKE, HIT THE BALL.
YOU DON'T PLAY TENNIS BRITS WE
PRACTICED FOR ABOUT AN HOUR AND
FINALLY, WE'RE GETTING THERE AND
THEN SHE COMES TO ME AND SHE'S
LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM
IS?
SHE'S LIKE, YOU BRUSH THE BALL
TOO MUCH.
YOU NEED TO HIT THE BALL.
HIT THE BALL.
SO THAT WAS MY JOURNEY.
SO NOW I CAN PLAY.
>> Ellen: WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> YOU LIKE TO THINK OF ALL
THESE THINGS SO YOU HAVE THE
BEST POSSIBLE SLEEP ON THE ROAD.
>> Ellen: I'M SO GLAD I ASKED
THAT QUESTION.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen:
Great parenting
needs great allies.
New Ziploc Grip n' Seal.
Easier to grip and open for the
world's greatest parents.
SC Johnson
[Crackling fire]
[Wood rolling]
Alexios, add toilet paper
to the shopping list.
[Chiseling on stone]
Oh, and camel milk.
And a chicken.
And moisturizer.
ALEXA: Thanks, guys.
I'll take it from here.
So Bryan and I were thinking
about holding off
'til next year, you know?
But, the kids aren't getting
any younger,
so maybe we should go?
Then we saw this offer
they have, and I was thinking
Is this finally the year?
So guess what?
That's right! We're going!
You know, you're really
a great listener.
Must be the ears.
Stop dreaming about
a Walt Disney World vacation.
With our 4-park magic ticket,
a lifetime of memories
is closer than you think.
Your dry skin story changes
from one day to the next.
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
and switch.
It doubles your skin's moisture
And repairs dry skin over time.
So tomorrow
can be a different story.
Eucerin —
Recommended
and used by dermatologists.
Eucerin —
Ariana's not just going to
school...
She's going to school with a
lunch she helped pack herself.
Because she's becoming
an independent child.
Yoplait, for
fueling independence.
For big
little wins.
>>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M PAT LAWSON WITH A QUICK LOOK
AT THE STORIES.
HARVEY WEINSTEIN CONVICTED ON
RAPE BUT ACQUITTED OF THE MOST
SERIOUS CHARGES.
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT TO THE
DISGRACED MOVIE MOGUL.
>>> AND FEARS CORONAVIRUS WILL
TANK THE ECONOMY.
WE'RE MONITORING THE DOW'S
PLUNGE AND TAKING A LOOK AT THE
IMPACT TO LOCAL BUSINESS.
>>> AND A SNEAK PEEK AT THE
LATEST TOY TRENDS OF 2020.
>> Ellen: WE ARE BACK WITH
TREVOR NOAH.
SO, HAVE YOU INTERVIEWED EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF THESE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES RIGHT NOW?
>> ALMOST ALL 125 OF THEM.
I THINK THE ONLY PEOPLE WE
HAVEN'T HAD ON THE SHOW IS
ELIZABETH WARREN AND JOE BIDEN.
AND MIKE BLOOMBERG BECAUSE NOW
IT'S IN THE RACE.
BUT EVERYONE ELSE HAS COME TO
"THE DAILY SHOW" AND WE HAD FUN
TALKING ALL THE CANDIDATES.
>> Ellen: YOU'RE DOING, I
DON'T KNOW HOW YOU MAKE IT
FUNNY, AND THEY USE YOU A LOT ON
CBS MORNING NEWS LIKE BUMPING
IN.
BUT I MEAN, IT'S A SAD, SCARY
PLACE RIGHT NOW AND SOMEHOW YOU
MAKE IT REALLY FUNNY.
DO YOU GET DEPRESSED GOING TO
WORK?
HOW DO YOU MAKE THIS FUNNY?
>> HERE'S THE THING.
I THINK WHEN PROCESSING POLITICS
THE ONE THING WE HAVE TO LEARN
TO DO AS PEOPLE, IN MY OPINION,
IS YOUR MEMBER THAT THERE WAS A
TIME BEFORE AND THERE WILL
ALWAYS BE A TIME AFTER AND A LOT
OF THE TIME PEOPLE TELL US TO
LIVE IN THE PRESENT BUT IF
YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL YOU ONLY LIVE
IN THE PRESENT AND THEN YOU ACT
AS IF THE PRESENT WILL BE
FOREVER AND THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
THAT'S WHAT I TRY TO DO IS I TRY
TO REMEMBER THAT, FOR ME,
POLITICS IS WHAT IS SUPPOSED TO
BE HAPPENING, SO I CAN'T BE
ANGRY AT POLITICS AND THEN WHAT
I'M TRYING TO DO IS ENGAGE IN
DIALOGUE THAT EDUCATES PEOPLE
AND INFORMS PEOPLE, INCLUDING
MYSELF, AND GETS US TO A PLACE
WHERE WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
SO ONE OF THE BEST COMPONENTS
EVER GOT, NO JOKE, IT WAS ON THE
FLIGHT COMING OUT HERE TO L.A.
THERE WAS A GUY ON THE PLANE AND
HE CAME UP TO BE ANY SAID HEY.
MY SON SAID I SHOULDN'T BOTHER
YOU BUT I WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
I'M A BIG CONSERVATIVE GUY AND I
DON'T AGREE WITH A LOT OF THE
THINGS YOU SAY BUT YOU ARE A
FUNNY GUY.
YOU'RE A COOL GUY AND YOU'RE
FUNNY AND I LIKE THAT ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT, MY SON SAID YOU WOULD
HATE ME BUT THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND I SHOOK HIS HAND AND I WAS
LIKE HEY, THANK YOU FOR SEEING
ME AS A HUMAN BEING.
I SEE YOU AS A HUMAN BEING AND
WE DON'T AGREE ON MANY THINGS
BUT WE STILL AGREE THAT WE ARE
HUMAN BEINGS AND I THINK IF WE
CAN FIND THAT PLACE WE CAN GO
FROM THERE.
>> Ellen: WE HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THAT RIGHT NOW.
WE NEED TO GET BACK TO THAT.
IT'S LIKE, YOU COULD BE TALKING
TO SOMEBODY AND REALLY GETTING
ALONG WITH THEM AND HAVING A
GREAT, WAS SOME STRANGER AND
THEN YOU FIND OUT THAT THEY ARE
NOT THE SAME POLITICAL PARTY,
AND THEN YOU SUDDENLY HAVE AN
OPINION ABOUT THEM AND IT'S
REALLY A FRIGHTENING TIME RIGHT
NOW.
I DON'T THINK WE ALL HAVE TO BE
EXACTLY ALIKE.
I THINK WE CAN LET EACH OTHER
HAVE OTHER OPINIONS AND OTHER
THINGS AND LIKES AND DISLIKES.
I JUST DON'T LIKE PEOPLE THAT
HURT PEOPLE.
I DRAW THE LINE THERE.
DON'T HURT SOMEBODY.
DO YOU THINK, HOW DO YOU FEEL,
WITH TRUMP AS PRESIDENT, IS THAT
A GOOD THING FOR YOU FOR COMEDY
OR HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> I WAS DOING COMEDY BEFORE
TRUMP.
THERE WERE STAND-UP SHOWS BEFORE
THERE WERE LATE-NIGHT SHOWS
TRUMP.
BEFORE TRUMP.
THERE WERE LATE-NIGHT SHOWS
I DON'T EVER THINK TRUMP IS GOOD
BEFORE TRUMP.
FOR US, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T EVER THINK TRUMP IS GOOD
IF ANYTHING SOMETIMES I WISH HE
FOR US, YOU KNOW?
WOULD MAKE US WORK A LITTLE BIT
IF ANYTHING SOMETIMES I WISH HE
HARDER BECAUSE NOW AS A COMEDIAN
WOULD MAKE US WORK A LITTLE BIT
I'M LIKE, HE DID THIS.
HARDER BECAUSE NOW AS A COMEDIAN
AND PEOPLE ARE LIKE, THAT'S
I'M LIKE, HE DID THIS.
CRAZY.
AND PEOPLE ARE LIKE, THAT'S
OF THAT I MIGHT, THEN HE DID
CRAZY.
THIS.
OF THAT I MIGHT, THEN HE DID
I'M NOT DOING MUCH.
THIS.
I'M JUST SHOWING YOU WHAT HE
I'M NOT DOING MUCH.
DID.
I'M JUST SHOWING YOU WHAT HE
>> Ellen: SO ANYWAY, I WANT TO
DID.
TALK TO YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE
>> Ellen: SO ANYWAY, I WANT TO
TRAVELING STILL.
TALK TO YOU BECAUSE YOU'RE
YOU SOLD OUT
TRAVELING STILL.
MADISON SQUARE GARDEN, STAPLE
YOU SOLD OUT
CENTER, YOU'RE DOING SO WELL AND
MADISON SQUARE GARDEN, STAPLE
YOU'RE DOING "THE DAILY SHOW"
CENTER, YOU'RE DOING SO WELL AND
AND TOURING AND DOING STAND UP,
YOU'RE DOING "THE DAILY SHOW"
HOW IS THAT TO BE IN A HOTEL ALL
AND TOURING AND DOING STAND UP,
THE TIME AND TRAVELING AS MUCH
HOW IS THAT TO BE IN A HOTEL ALL
IS YOUR TRAVELING?
THE TIME AND TRAVELING AS MUCH
>> IT'S NOT BAD BECAUSE, I USED
IS YOUR TRAVELING?
TO TOUR ALL THE TIME,
>> IT'S NOT BAD BECAUSE, I USED
MONDAY-SUNDAY AND NOW I TOUR ON
TO TOUR ALL THE TIME,
THE WEEKENDS.
MONDAY-SUNDAY AND NOW I TOUR ON
YOU GET USED TO TRAVELING.
THE WEEKENDS.
I'M A VERY GOOD TRAVELER.
YOU GET USED TO TRAVELING.
I NEVER PACK MORE THAN I NEED
I'M A VERY GOOD TRAVELER.
AND I NEVER PACK LESS THAN I
I NEVER PACK MORE THAN I NEED
NEED.
AND I NEVER PACK LESS THAN I
I'VE LEARNED, YOU ALWAYS PACK
NEED.
THE EXACT AMOUNT OF UNDERWEAR
I'VE LEARNED, YOU ALWAYS PACK
PLUS ONE IN CASE OF EMERGENCY.
THE EXACT AMOUNT OF UNDERWEAR
DON'T ASK ME THAT WHAT THAT
PLUS ONE IN CASE OF EMERGENCY.
EMERGENCY MIGHT BE.
DON'T ASK ME THAT WHAT THAT
AND THEN I PACKED THINGS IN THE
EMERGENCY MIGHT BE.
ORDER I'M GOING TO NEED THEM IN
AND THEN I PACKED THINGS IN THE
THE BACK.
ORDER I'M GOING TO NEED THEM IN
SO SOMETIMES I'VE SEEN PEOPLE
THE BACK.
WHEN THEY FLY AND THEN THEY GET
SO SOMETIMES I'VE SEEN PEOPLE
SOMETHING OUT OF THE OVERHEAD
WHEN THEY FLY AND THEN THEY GET
AND THEY HAVE TO DIG THROUGH THE
SOMETHING OUT OF THE OVERHEAD
BAG OR THE TSA PRAYED I KNOW
AND THEY HAVE TO DIG THROUGH THE
WHAT THE TSA WILL LOOK FOR.
BAG OR THE TSA PRAYED I KNOW
THEY ALWAYS THINK MY NAIL
WHAT THE TSA WILL LOOK FOR.
CLIPPERS ARE A RAMBO KNIFE SO
THEY ALWAYS THINK MY NAIL
HOT THAT ON TOP.
CLIPPERS ARE A RAMBO KNIFE SO
HAVE THINGS IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
HOT THAT ON TOP.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE HOTEL YOU
HAVE THINGS IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
GOT YOUR ROUTINE.
WHEN YOU GET TO THE HOTEL YOU
I ROUTINE AS YOU GO TO THE BAR,
GOT YOUR ROUTINE.
TURN ON THE WATER, SEE HOW LONG
I ROUTINE AS YOU GO TO THE BAR,
IT TAKES FOR THINGS TO GET HOT,
TURN ON THE WATER, SEE HOW LONG
FIGURE OUT WHAT'S GOING ON SEEN
IT TAKES FOR THINGS TO GET HOT,
ON THE MORNING WHAT'S CAN HAPPEN
FIGURE OUT WHAT'S GOING ON SEEN
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
ON THE MORNING WHAT'S CAN HAPPEN
THAN HAVING TO GO SOMEWHERE IN
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
THE TIME FOR THE SHOWER AND
THAN HAVING TO GO SOMEWHERE IN
YOU'RE LIKE, AND THEN YOU'RE
THE TIME FOR THE SHOWER AND
LOOKING AT YOUR WATCH, AND ALL
YOU'RE LIKE, AND THEN YOU'RE
YOUR DAY STARTS HORRIBLY, YOU
LOOKING AT YOUR WATCH, AND ALL
GOT TO PLAN FOR IT.
YOUR DAY STARTS HORRIBLY, YOU
SO FOR ME, I KNOW EVERYTHING FOR
GOT TO PLAN FOR IT.
IT SIDE OF THE BED I SLEEP ON,
SO FOR ME, I KNOW EVERYTHING FOR
WHERE THE OUTLETS.
IT SIDE OF THE BED I SLEEP ON,
PEOPLE GET TOO COMFORTABLE
WHERE THE OUTLETS.
PLANNING FOR A BED AS IT IT'S
PEOPLE GET TOO COMFORTABLE
THEIR BED FROM HOME.
PLANNING FOR A BED AS IT IT'S
IT'S NOT YOUR BED.
THEIR BED FROM HOME.
YOUR TRAVELING.
IT'S NOT YOUR BED.
SO WHEN YOU GET IN, IT'S NOT
YOUR TRAVELING.
YOUR BED.
SO WHEN YOU GET IN, IT'S NOT
IT'S A HOTEL BED.
YOUR BED.
LOOK FOR THE DRAFT COMES IN.
IT'S A HOTEL BED.
SOMETIMES THERE IS LIKE A BOAT
LOOK FOR THE DRAFT COMES IN.
WHEN GOING THROUGH A DOOR.
SOMETIMES THERE IS LIKE A BOAT
YOU GOT TO THINK OF ALL THESE
WHEN GOING THROUGH A DOOR.
THINGS SO THAT YOU HAVE THE BEST
YOU GOT TO THINK OF ALL THESE
POSSIBLE SLEEP ON THE ROAD.
THINGS SO THAT YOU HAVE THE BEST
>> Ellen: I AM SO GLAD I ASKED
POSSIBLE SLEEP ON THE ROAD.
THAT QUESTION.
>> Ellen: I AM SO GLAD I ASKED
THAT WAS WONDERFUL.
THAT QUESTION.
WONDERFUL.
THAT WAS WONDERFUL.
YOU HAVE NOT MADE ME MISS TWO OR
WONDERFUL.
A GOT ALL.
YOU HAVE NOT MADE ME MISS TWO OR
YOU'VE JUST MADE ME SO HAPPY
A GOT ALL.
THAT I'M STAYING HOME NOW.
YOU'VE JUST MADE ME SO HAPPY
"THE DAILY SHOW," YOU'RE SO
THAT I'M STAYING HOME NOW.
GREAT ON IT, IT AIRS EVERY NIGHT
"THE DAILY SHOW," YOU'RE SO
AT 11:00 ON COMEDY CENTRAL.
GREAT ON IT, IT AIRS EVERY NIGHT
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, TREVOR
AT 11:00 ON COMEDY CENTRAL.
NOAH.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, TREVOR
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
NOAH.
>> Ellen: HOW MANY PUSH-UPS
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CAN YOU DO?
>> Ellen: HOW MANY PUSH-UPS
>> I USED TO DO 200 STRAIGHT BUT
CAN YOU DO?
NOW BECAUSE I'VE BEEN EATING A
>> I USED TO DO 200 STRAIGHT BUT
LOT WITH THE STRESS AND
NOW BECAUSE I'VE BEEN EATING A
EVERYTHING, I CAN ONLY 230.
LOT WITH THE STRESS AND
>> Ellen: OH, ONLY 130.
EVERYTHING, I CAN ONLY 230.
OH.
Big news America!
For a limited time, we've
changed the shape
of Honey Nut Cheerios.
Because we want people to know
they're delicious
AND can help lower cholesterol.
Heart healthy. Get it? A heart!
Can you believe they had one in
my size?!
Hi guys. This is the
Chevy Silverado,
with the world's
first invisible trailer.
Invisible trailer?
And it's not the
trailer right next to us?
This guy?
You don't
believe me?
Hop in.
Good lookin' pickup,
I will say that.
Oh wow.
Silverado offers an optional
technology package with
up to 15
different views -
including one
enhanced view
that makes your
trailer appear invisible.
Wow.
- That's pretty sweet.
- That's cool.
Oooohh!
That's awesome.
Where'd the trailer go?
I love it.
It's magic.
So, you bought those "good
enough" paper towels?
[daughter laughs]
Not such a bargain.
There's Only One Quicker Picker
Upper.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
To be their best kids
need good nutrition,
and practice.
Lots of practice.
Get them started right
with Carnation
Breakfast Essentials.
Now with probiotics
and key nutrients
for digestive and
immune support
to help kids be their best.
Carnation Breakfast Essentials.
Wow!
I know right? Walmart.com
has a lot of great stuff.
And now get 5% back
on the things you buy there,
with the new Capital
One Walmart Rewards Card.
Say what?
5% back.
Say that again!?
Yes!
What's in your wallet?
Yup. Nailed it!
TIME FOR IT.
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: A COUPLE OF WEEKS
AGO WE INTRODUCED A NEW SEGMENT
CALLED "CAN YOU DO THAT," A
THING WHERE tWITCH AND I HAVE
TO GUESS WHETHERE
MEMBER CAN ACTUALLY DO WHAT THEY
SAY THEY CAN DO.
WE MET A YOUNG MAN WITH A TALENT
THAT BLEW US AWAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY NAME IS CHRISTOPHER JOYCE,
I'M FROM THE BRONX AND I'M A
CARETAKER FOR MY]
>> Ellen: WOW!
OH, MY GOD, !
>> Ellen: I WAS SO IMPRESSED I
WANTED TO LEARN MORE ABOUT HIM.
PLEASE WELCOME CHRISTOPHER
JOYCE!
♪ ♪
>> Ellen: THAT WAS AMAZING.
WHEN YOU SAID YOU COULD DO THAT
I DIDN'T PICTURE THAT AT ALL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
PICTURING.
HAVE YOU ALWAYS BEEN THIS
NATURALLY STRONG?
>> WELL, WHEN I WAS YOUNGER I
WANTED TO BE REALLY STRONG.
I'M FROM THE BRONX SO IT'S TOUGH
THERE.
SO THEY HAVE THESE COMPETITION
WORDS LIKE BRONX VERSUS BROOKLYN
VERSUS QUEENS, STATEN ISLAND,
AND THEY DO, WHO CAN DO THE MOST
PULL-UPS, PUSH-UPS, HANDSTAND,
AND I WANTED TO BE DIFFERENT AND
ORIGINALS I WENT TO THE GYM AND
STARTED PRACTICING ON DUMBBELLS
AND BARBELLS.
I DID EVERY DAY.
>> Ellen: WOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT COULD BE
BETTER THAN THAT.
SO HOW OFTEN DO YOU TRAIN AND
WORK OUT?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I TRAIN MONDAY THROUGH
FRIDAYS AND REST ON SATURDAYS
AND SUNDAYS AND I TRAIN AT 5:00
5:00 A.M. EVERY DAY BECAUSE
THERE'S MORE FREEDOM AND I CAN
GRAB MORE WEIGHTS WITHOUT NO ONE
HAVING A PROBLEM.
AND MY DAD, YOU KNOW, HE'S SICK
AND EVERYTHING, SO I LIKE TO
COME BACK BEFORE HE WAKES UP, SO
IT'S BETTER FOR ME TO GO EARLY
IN THEM WHEN I COME BACK
EVERYTHING IS GOOD.
I TAKE CARE OF HIM AND THEN I
TAKE A NAP AND I TRAIN AGAIN.
AS I TRAIN TWICE A DAY. SLACKINH
YOUR DAD?
>> MY DAD HAS A RARE SPINAL
PROBLEM.
SO, IT'S KIND OF FORCING HIM TO
BE PARALYZED.
SO THE DOCTORS RECOMMENDED A
SURGERY TO TRY TO HELP AND WE'VE
JUST BEEN TAKING CARE OF HIM AND
IT'S PRETTY TOUGH BECAUSE THAT'S
THE PERSON I FIRST IN MY
PUSH-UPS WITH.
IF THE PERSON I RACED WITH WHEN
I WAS YOUNGER AND ALWAYS LOOKED
UP TO AND TO NOW SEE HIM WEAK
AND STUFF, IT MAKES ME SAD.
BUT MY MOM ALWAYS TELLS ME,
LIKE, CHRIS, USE YOUR PAIN AS
MOTIVATION.
SO I'VE BEEN TRYING TO LIGHT, GO
FOR MY GOALS MORE AND TRAIN MORE
AGAIN AND, YEAH.
>> Ellen: BECAUSE YOU'RE A
FULL-TIME CARETAKER?
WHAT YOUR ULTIMATE GOAL?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> MY ULTIMATE GOAL IS TO BE IN
COMMERCIALS.
AND TO INSPIRE PEOPLE WHO ARE
LIKE ME WHO COME FROM SIMILAR
BACKGROUNDS WHO HAVE HAD IT
HARD, WHO DON'T HAVE ALL THE
RESOURCES AND I WANT TO SHOWCASE
MY TALENT IN COMMERCIALS AND
OTHER PLACES TO LET THEM KNOW
THEY CAN DO IT TOO.
>> Ellen: YOU SHOULD DO THAT
FOR SURE.
WERE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK AND
YOU'RE GOING TO PERFORM WHEN WE
COME BACK.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL BE BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]s!
[laughter]
I remember thinking,
'please God, I hope I don't
meet the Mayor today.'
And in walked Mayor Bloomberg.
Soon as I saw him,
I knew what that meant.
I'm Margaret Brick, and my son
Tommy Brick was the
first firefighter to be killed
in a fire after 9/11.
I said what is going to
happen to his children?
Without even skipping a beat,
Mike said to me,
'the fire department will take
good care of those kids,
but if they don't,
I will do it myself.'
Every year around the
anniversary, Mike calls me.
It's sixteen years later,
to just say I want you to know
I'm thinking about you.
It's just amazing.
He doesn't have to do that.
The Mike I know said
he would never forget Tommy,
and he has not.
I'm Mike Bloomberg
and I approve this message.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE BACK WITH A VERY, VERY
STRONG CHRISTOPHER JOYCE AND,
ALL RIGHT.
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT.
BUT DO SOMETHING.
OH, START WITH THE STAIRS.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: WHAT!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: OH, MY GOD, !
OH, MY GOD.
SO HERE'S THE THING.
YOU SAID IT WAS YOUR DREAM TO BE
IN A COMMERCIAL.
SO PURE PROTEIN LOVES YOUR STORY
AND THEY'REUTTING YOU IN THEIR
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO HANG
OUT AFTER THIS?
>> WE'LL BE AT THE BAR.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU AND ME BOTH, SISTER.
>>
Great parenting
needs great allies.
New Ziploc Grip n' Seal.
Easier to grip and open for the
world's greatest parents.
SC Johnson
[Crackling fire]
[Wood rolling]
Alexios, add toilet paper
to the shopping list.
[Chiseling on stone]
Oh, and camel milk.
And a chicken.
And moisturizer.
ALEXA: Thanks, guys.
I'll take it from here.
So Bryan and I were thinking
about holding off
'til next year, you know?
But, the kids aren't getting
any younger,
so maybe we should go?
Then we saw this offer
they have, and I was thinking
Is this finally the year?
So guess what?
That's right! We're going!
You know, you're really
a great listener.
Must be the ears.
Stop dreaming about
a Walt Disney World vacation.
With our 4-park magic ticket,
a lifetime of memories
is closer than you think.
Your dry skin story changes
from one day to the next.
Try Eucerin Advanced Repair
and switch.
It doubles your skin's moisture
And repairs dry skin over time.
So tomorrow
can be a different story.
Eucerin —
Recommended
and used by dermatologists.
Eucerin —
Ariana's not just going to
school...
She's going to school with a
lunch she helped pack herself.
Because she's becoming
an independent child.
Yoplait, for
fueling independence.
For big
littin
>>> FIRST AT 4:00, A
STAR-STUDDED TRIBUTE.
>> WE'LL TAKE YOU INSIDE THE
CELEBRATION OF LIFE FOR KOBE
BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER, GEE
JANUAR
dfin Agent,
more people see your home.
That's because more people visit
Redfin.com
than any other brokerage site.
So, the right buyers
come to you.
And you sell for more than the
home next door...
all for a 1% listing fee when
you buy and sell.
THOUSANDS OF FANS CAME TO SEE ME
SO I HAD ADAM GO TALK TO SOME OF
THEM BEFORE THE SHOW AND HERE'S
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> I'M HERE AT THE HARD ROCK
HOTEL IN FLORIDA WHERE ELLEN IS
ABOUT TO DO HER Q&A AT LIVE.
>> THE ONE, THE ONLY, ELLEN!
>> SHOW US WHAT YOU HAVE HERE.
>> THAT'S MY>> NO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
PROBABLY FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE I'M FROM THE
SHOW.
THERE ARE STARSTRUCK, CLEARLY,
THEY CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> WERE GREAT FANS BUT WE LOVE
YOU.
YOU'RE SO HANDSOME.
>> TO SPEAK UP THANK MUCH.
>> YOUR WONDERFUL, REALLY.
>> I LOVE HOW YOU WRAP PRESENTS.
>> AND YOU'RE SO SERIOUS WHEN
YOU DO IT.
SHE'S THE BEST, THE BEST IN THE
WHOLE WORLD.
GOD BLESS HER.
>> I SAID YEAH, OF COURSE, IT
ELLEN.
SPEAK ARE YOU GOING TO HANG OUT
AFTER THIS?
>> I'LL BE AT THE BAR, I DON'T
KNOW.
>> YOU ANDISR.
>> I'LL SEE YOU THERE, BLUE EYE
EYES.
>> LISTEN.
I LOVE YOU.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I'M FROM MIAMI.
I SAW YOU.
>> THAT'S HOW SHE WALKS.
>> SHE DOES.
>> HOW SHE WALKS TO THE OFFICE,
A LOT OF ATTITUDE.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> THEY'RE PUSHING ME.
>> HERE'S MORE PEOPLE.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> I'M SHAKING.
>> BECAUSE OF ELINOR BECAUSE OF
ME?
>> BOTH.
I SHAKE LIKE A CHIHUAHUA, I'M
SORRY.
>> DOES THAT HAPPEN A LOT?
>> NO.
>> WHAT YOU GUYS HOPING TO HEAR
HER TALK ABOUT?
>> ANYTHING.
I WOULD WATCH HER BREATHE, I
DON'T CARE.
>> I WENT THROUGH BREAST CANCER
AND I USED TO WATCH HER ON THE
SHOW AND I USED TO MAKE JOKES
ABOUT HOW SHE WAS MY BEST FRIEN
FRIEND.
SORRY.
>> NOT AT ALL!
NOT AT ALL.
WE LOVE TO HEAR STORIES LIKE
THAT.
>> NO ONE'S EVER SEEN ME BALLS.
I SAID YES, I AM DOING THAT.
HE SAID HOLY, WHATEVER.
>> HOLY WHAT?
>> LISTEN, I'VE GOT ENOUGH.
I KEEP IT CLEAN.
HOLY [BLEEP].
HE SAID YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR
[BLEEP] MIND.
>> I'M GLAD YOU CAN MAKE IT
TONIGHT.
WILL THIS BE YOUR FIRST TIME
SEEING HER LIFE?
>> I GET TO SHARE OXYGEN WITH
HER, THAT'S FINE.
>> WE'VE GOT CROCS WITH STOCKS
HERE.
>> MAKING THE WORLD A BETTER
PLACE, WERE SO GLAD TO HEAR
STORIES LIKE YOURS.
AND YOU'RE MAKING KNOCKOFF ELLEN
ITEMS.
YOU'LL BE HEARING FROM OUR
LAWYER.
>> WE LOVE YOU, ELLEN!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ellen: I>> Ellen: I WANT TO K
'LSEE YOUOM KIND TO ONE ANHER,
ACQUITTED ON OTHER CHARGES.
>>> CORONAVIRUS FEARS SEND
STOCKS PLUNGING.
THE IMPACT TO OUR WALLETS HERE
AT HOME.
>>> PLUS I'M TRACKING RAIN ON
STORM TEAM 4 RADAR, I'LL SHOW
YOU WHEN YOU WILL NEED THE
UMBRELLAS AND THOSE PUFFY COATS.
>> FIRST, BIGGER THAN
BASEBALL --
♪♪
>> A SEA OF PURPLE AND GOLD
CELEBRATES THE LIVES OF KOBE
BRYANT AND HIS DAUGHTER GIANNA.
>> EVERYWHERE YOU GO YOU SEE HIS
FACE, HIS NUMBER.
>> AND KOBE BRYANT'S WIDOW SHOWS
STRENGTH AND GRACE IN A MOVING
MESSAGE.
>> GOD KNEW THEY COULDN'T BE ON
THIS EARTH WITHOUT EACH OTHER.
BABE, YOU TAKE CARE OF OUR GIGI.
>> LIVE COVERAGE FROM MAMBA'S
MEMORIAL STARTS NOW.
>> SO MANY TEARS, SO MUCH LOVE.
BRYANT'S WIFE, VANESSA.
>> HERE NOW, JUST SOME OF THE
MOST POWERL