2018 SHE SAID IN AN INTERVIEW
THAT THERE ARE NO LONGER FRIENDS
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THAT'S NOT
TRUE BECAUSE SHE WAS THERE UNTIL
5:00 PARTYING, DANCING, SMILING,
HAVING A GREAT TIME AND THEY
FINISHED OFF THE NIGHT WITH THE
DRAKE BUYING EVERYONE
McDONALD'S.
BUT HERE'S THE THING.
>> Wendy: WAS THERE A MICK RIB
IN THERE?
>> MAYBE, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT YOU KNOW, SHE JUST CAME OUT
AND SAID IN AN EXCLUSIVE
RELATIONSHIP AND SHE'S VERY
HAPPY WITH A SAUDI BILLIONAIRE.
SHE SEEMS REALLY HAPPY ABOUT IT,
YOU KNOW?
I WANT TO UPDATE YOU ON RIHANNA
AND CHRIS BROWN.
RIHANNA PUT UP A VIDEO OF HER
SHOWING HER NEW LIP GLOSSES IN
THE BACKGROUND SHE PLAYED CHRIS
BROWN SONG, SO A LOT OF FANS ARE
LIKE, WAIT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
ARE WE FORGIVING HIM?
I THOUGHT WE WEREN'T FORGIVING
HIM.
WHAT'S YOUR WHOLE THING ON THAT?
THE ONE I THINK SHE PLAYS WITH
HER EXES BUT I THINK SHE'S
PROBABLY ONE OF THOSE COOL GIRLS
WHO ASSURES THE BILLIONAIRE,
LOOK, BY, I'M YOURS.
I DON'T WANT ANY OF THESE
CLOWNS.
BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
NOW YOU'RE OVER THERE MAKING
BILLIONS AND I'M HERE IN THE
STATES AND I'M A YOUNG GIRL AND
I'M PART OF ENTERTAINMENT AND
I'VE GOT TO KEEP MY SOCIAL MEDIA
GOING SO I'M GOING TO DRAKE'S
PARTY BUT I WILL CALL YOU EVERY
HOUR OR FACETIME YOU, YOU WILL
NOT SEE PICTURES OF ME KISSING
HIM IN THE SAME THING WITH CHRIS
BROWN.
SHE'S ONE OF THOSE COOL GIRLS.
AND THE BOYFRIEND IS PROBABLY SO
SECURE.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU.
WE ARE NOW MOVING ON TO DENNIS
QUAID WHO IS ENGAGED TO A
YOUNGER WOMAN.
GUYS, DENNIS QUAID IS 65 YEARS
OLD.
HIS NEW FIANCE IS 26 YEARS OLD.
THAT IS ALMOST 40 YEARS YOUNGER,
OKAY?
THAT YOU WERE VACATIONING IN
HAWAII, THEY WERE TAKING A
SELFIE AND HE'S LIKE, I'M GOING
TO PROPOSE SO HE GOT ON ONE KNEE
AND PROPOSED TO HER AND SHE'S
GETTING HER PhD AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS.
SHE'S 26 YEARS OLD.
SHE'S DATING THIS MAN.
THIS IS HIS FOURTH MARRIAGE.
HE WAS WITH MEG RYAN FOR TEN
YEARS, HE JUST DIVORCED FROM HIS
LAST WIFE, HE HAS THREE KIDS AND
HIS OLDEST SON IS 27 WHICH IS
JUST A YEAR OLDER THAN HIS NEW
FIANCE.
SO A LITTLE CREEPY, A LITTLE
WEIRD.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THIS?
>> Wendy: MY TAKE ON IT IS IF
I WAS 26 YEARS OLD I WOULDN'T
WANT ANYTHING WITH IT BEING A
STEPMOM.
YOU KEEP YOUR KIDS OVER THERE.
SHE'S BETTER THAN A LOT OF
26-YEAR-OLDS AND THAT SHE'S
FOCUSED AND GETTING HER PhD.
THAT IS NOT AN EASY FEAT.
SO HER 26 IS PROBABLY LIKE 36 IN
TERMS OF HER MIND.
SHE'S YOUNG ENOUGH TO HAVE KIDS
AND START HER OWN FAMILY.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A STEPMOM.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THESE KIDS.
I'M TOO YOUNG FOR THAT.
IFOU Y STILL ACTING QUESTION
WHAT DOES HE HAVE MONEY?
>> YES, HE STILL ACTING.
MAN HAS MONEY.
>> Wendy: I'M NOT HATING ON
IT.
>> HE HAS A GOOD BODY, HE IS
LOOKING PRETTY GOOD.
BUT 65 IS A LITTLE...
>> Wendy: IT'S A LITTLE
CREEPY.
BUT MEN CAN HAVE KIDS ALL THEIR
LIVES.
BUT THE OLDER YOU GET THE MORE
TICS IT HAS, IF YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING.
>> WERE MOVING ON TO SOMEONE
YOUNGER.
BROOKLYN BECKHAM IS THE
OFFSPRING OF VICTORIA AND DAVID
BECKHAM.
HE'S A CUTIE.
THE PEOPLE IN SOCIAL MEDIA ARE
GOING A LITTLE CRAZY BECAUSE HIS
CURRENT NEW GIRLFRIEND IS A
MODEL NAMED STEVIE TORRENCE, IT
LOOKS A LOT LIKE VICTORIA
BECKHAM AND FUN FACTS, GUYS, SHE
USED TO BE A VICTORIA BECKHAM
LOOK ALIKE BACK IN THE DAY TO
PAY FOR COLLEGE.
THIS IS SIDE-BY-SIDE, THEY LOOK
KIND OF A LIKE AND ALSO HIS LAST
GIRLFRIEND HANNAH ALSO LOOKS
LIKE VICTORIA.
THERE SHE IS AGAIN.
>> Wendy: IN THE NAME OF LAMAR
ODOM...
>> YEAH, YEAH, CREEPY?
A LITTLE.
>> Wendy: AS A MOM I GUESS,
SOME MOMS WOULD BE VERY
FLATTERED.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL ENOUGH AND
WHOLESOME ENOUGH, BUT THE BIGGER
PICTURE IS THAT IT'S KIND OF
CREEPY BUT I GUESS HE HAS A TYP
TYPE?
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> GOOD FOR YOU, KEEP DOING YOU.
HE WANTS A MONICA IS OFFICIALLY
SINGLE?
>> SHE'S OFFICIALLY SINGLE AND
IS FINALIZED HER DIVORCE.
SO HERE'S THE THING.
THE TWO OF THEM MET NINE YEARS
AGO WHEN SHE NEEDED A LOVE
INTEREST FOR A DANCE VIDEO AND
THEN FIVE MONTHS LATER THEY GOT
SECRETLY MARRIED WHICH IS SUPER
CUTE BUT SHE FILED FOR DIVORCE
IN MARCH AND THERE HAS BEEN NO
INFORMATION ON WHY SHE IS
DIVORCING THIS MAN.
THE ONLY THING SHE SAID WAS THAT
INFIDELITY IS NOT THE REASON.
>> Wendy: SHE TOLD US HERE
THAT COMMUNICATION BASICALLY
SHE SAID IT WAS STARTING TO
STAGGER.
THEY WERE JUST TWO ADULTS LIVING
IN A HOUSE.
NOW, WHEN SHE WAS ALSO HERE, IT
SEEMS LIKE THEY ARE STILL LIVING
IN THE SAME HOUSE WITH THE KIDS
AND WHEN WE ASKED HER ABOUT IT
SHE DIDN'T ANSWER.
SO I DON'T KNOW WHETHER THEY ARE
LIVING TOGETHER OR NOT BUT SHE
DID SAY HE'S A VERY GOOD
COPARENTS.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
HE ACTUALLY FOLLOWED HER AND
SHANNON WAS A NO-SHOW, SO SHE
WAS IN AND OUT 10 MINUTES, GOT
THE DIVCE AND SHE HAS HER
MAIDEN LAST NAME NOW.
SHE'S BACK TO ARNOLD'S.
SO IT'S REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
HE WAS A NO-SHOW BUT HE
DEFINITELY SHOWED UP ON
INSTAGRAM BECAUSE SHE POSTED A
PICTURE OF HER LOOKING AMAZING
AND HE WROTE, WHAT HE RIGHT, HE
WROTE THAT DOES SOMETHING TO ME
AND IT POSTED 27 HEART IMO JEEZ.
IS HE SHOOTING HIS SHOT AGAIN
CUSTOMER IT DOES HE WANT ANOTHER
CHANCE?
>> Wendy: MEN ARE SO STUPID.
CONGRATULATIONS, MONICA, BE
HAPPY.
MAKE YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING HERE.
ELLIE LEE, EVERYBODY PRAYED UP
NEXT, WE'RE MAKING
>> Wendy: OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THE BEST PART OF HALLOWEEN IS
THE CANDY AND HERE TO HELP US
WITH SOME SPECIAL RECIPES IS OUR
FRIEND, GEORGE DURRANT.
WELCOME BACK.
GEORGE, WHAT ARE WE DOING?
>> THE THINGS YOU CAN DO WITH
CANDY AND DESSERTS IS FANTASTIC
CLOSING THIS INCREDIBLE
CHOCOLATE BARK OR BRITTLE.
ALL YOU'RE GOING TO DO IS MELT
SOME CHOCOLATE INTO A PAN AND
DIFFERENT COLORS ARE GOING TO
MAKE DIFFERENT, COOL LITTLE
DESIGNS LIKE THIS.
IT'S MELTED CHOCOLATE AND ONCE
YOU'VE MELTED IT INSIDE THE PAN
YOU'RE GOING TO GET YOUR
CHOPSTICK AND KIND OF JUST SWIRL
IT AROUND ALL THROUGHOUT.
YOU SEE THIS COOL DESIGN THAT I
MADE?
ONCE YOU PUT THAT IN THERE
YOU'RE GOING TO GO AHEAD AND PUT
YOUR WORMS, PUT YOUR EYEBALLS IN
THE BONES AND THE LITTLE THINGS.
THE WORMS ARE THE BEST, AND SEE
HOW CUTE THAT LOOKS QUESTIONABLE
ONCE YOU REFRIGERATE THIS YOU
GOT YOUR CANDY BAR GREAT OVER
HERE.
ISN'T THAT CUTE?
FANTASTIC.
MY NEXT ONE IS MY FAVORITE ONE.
STAINED GLASS COOKIES.
IT WORKS GREAT FOR HALLOWEEN AND
PRETTY MUCH WHAT YOU'RE DOING
HERE IS TAKING THE
JOLLY RANCHERS, LIFESAVERS WORK
AS WELL, JOLLY RANCHERS, SORRY,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO CRUSH IT AND
PRETTY MUCH GET A ROLLING PIN.
YOURS IS OVER HERE IF YOU WANT
TO HELP ME.
B1 NO.
>> AND YOU'RE GOING TO GO AHEAD
AND CRUSH THEM.
IT LOOKS ALMOST LIKE GLASS BUT
IT'S NOT.
IT'S CRUSHED JOLLY RANCHERS,
YOU'RE GOING TO GO AHEAD AND
TAKE YOUR COOKIE-CUTTER THAT ALL
READY HAS THE HOLES INSIDE OF I
IT.
ALL YOU DO IS YOU CRUSH THEM UP
AND THEN YOU PUT THEM INSIDE THE
COOKIE-CUTTER, MAKE SURE YOU GET
IN THE NEXT AND CRANNIES.
THEN YOU POP IT INTO THE OVEN
AND IT BAKES BUT THE
JOLLY RANCHERS COOK AND WHAT YOU
GET IS THIS AMAZING STAINED
GLASS KIND OF LOOKING COOKIE
OVER HERE.
>> AND IT'S NOT TOO SUGARY.
>> IS CALLED A SUGAR COOKIE BUT
NOT TOO SUGARY.
NEVER GOING TO GO TO THE
CEMETERY A LITTLE BIT.
WE WANT YOU, BLACK LICORICE, I'M
GROSSED OUT.
>> THEN FORGET IT.
WERE NOT GOING TO USE IT.
BUT WE ARE GOING TO USE CUPCAKE
CUPCAKES.
A GREAT TRICK IF YOU DON'T HAVE
TIME AT HOME, YOU'RE GOING TO
GET STORE-BOUGHT CUPCAKES AND
YOU'RE GOING TO SPREAD THIS
ACROSS WITH YOUR HANDS IF YOU
HAVE THE TIME AND IF IT'S ROOM
TEMPERATURE EVEN BETTER COME UP
WITH YOU SPREAD IT ACROSS IT'S
GOING TO BE ONE BIG CEMETERY
LOOK TO IT.
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL FLAT.
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TAKE
THEM OF THE OREO COOKIE CRUMBS
AND YOU TURN IT INTO SOIL.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS, THE SOIL.
AND THEN COME UP MY FAVORITE,
YOU TAKE ONE OF THESE COOKIES,
YOU'RE JUST EATING MY WHOLE
SITE, THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU CUT IT IN HALF AND NOW YOU
HAVE A TOMBSTONE WHERE YOU CAN
WRITE THE NAME OF THE PERSON
THAT YOU HATE THE MOST.
OR JUST R.I.P. IS FINE.
NOT VERY GOOD.
B1 EN.
>> THAT'S FINE.
THEN YOU PUT A TOMBSTONE THERE
AND YOU DECORATE WITH MORE OF
THESE PUMPKINS AND LOOK AT THIS
BEAUTIFUL SITE OVER HERE.
THE PUMPKINS DO NOT TASTE LIKE
PUMPKINS, THERE CANDY CORN
PUMPKINS.
>> Wendy: YOU.
>> WELL, IF YOU LIKE WAX...
SPEW ON THE WORST PART OF
HALLOWEEN FOR ME.
SHAKE IT UP.
>> LET'S GET GOING.
>> Wendy: WOW.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE SEEN A GHOST.
THERE YOU GO.
VERY NICE.
I'M REALLY, REALLY, REALLY
SCARED NOW.
HERE WE GO, OF PEANUT BUTTER
BALL VERY SIMPLE.
PEANUT BUTTER, CREAM CHEESE,
VANILLA, POWDERED SUGAR.
MIX IT UP, YOU HAVE REESE'S
PEANUT BUTTER CUPS, MOLD IT INTO
A BALL, THIS IS PEANUT BUTTER.
ADD SOME MORE OF THE REESE'S
PIECES AND GO AHEAD AND GRAB ONE
OF THESE COOKIES COME OUT RIGHT.
>> IS IT LIKE ROCK COOKIE DOUGH?
>> IT'S NOT, IT'S PEANUT BUTTER
AND CREAM CHEESE.
THIS WOULD LOOK GREAT ON YOUR
HAIR, TOO.
IT WOULD FIT NICELY.
CANDY CORN MILK SHAKES, MY IN
THE WORLD.
THESE MANGOES IN DIFFERENT TYPES
OF FRUITS AND THEN OF COURSE,
HAVE YOU USED A WHIP CREAM THING
BEFORE?
YOU KNOW HOW IT WORKS?
I HOPE YOU DO.
AND THEN IT GRAB SOME CRUSHED
CANDY CORN AND PUT IT ON TOP AND
I'M TELLING YOU COME OUT THE
COLORS ARE BEAUTIFUL.
YOU PUT THIS IN THE FREEZER AND
SERVE IT.
IT'S VERY NICE, YOU USE FROZEN
YOGURT IF YOU WANT TO MAKE IT
NICE AND HEALTHY BUT THE KIDS
THINK THEY'RE EATING CANDY AND
THEY'RE NOT UP THERE DRINKING
FRUIT JUICE.
IT'S FANTASTIC.
>> Wendy: THIS IS GEORGE
DURRANT.
HE'S BEEN HERE BEFORE.
FOR THESE RECIPES, GO TO
WendyShow.com.
"ASK WENDY" IS NEXT.
>> Wendy: YOU KNOW THE BEST
WAY TO START YOUR MONDAY.
MONDAYS AND YOU THAT INSIDER
INFORMATION.
GIVE US A SNEAK PEEK OF THEIR
NEW SHOW.HOW.
>> MONDAY, ON A NEW "WENDY"!
I'm LáDeia, and there's
more to me than HIV.
There's my career...
my cause...
and creating my dream home.
I'm a work in progress.
So much goes into who I am.
HIV medicine is one part of it.
Prescription DOVATO is for
adults who are starting
HIV-1 treatment and who aren't
resistant to either
of the medicines dolutegravir
or lamivudine.
DOVATO has 2 medicines
in 1 pill
to help you reach and
then stay undetectable.
So your HIV can be controlled
with fewer medicines
while taking DOVATO.
You can take DOVATO
anytime of day
with food
or without.
Don't take DOVATO if you're
allergic to any of its
ingredients or if you
take dofetilide.
If you have hepatitis B,
it can change during
treatment with DOVATO
and become harder to treat.
Your hepatitis B may get worse
or become life-threatening
if you stop taking DOVATO.
So do not stop DOVATO
without talking to your doctor.
Serious side effects can occur,
including allergic reactions,
liver problems, and
liver failure.
Life-threatening side effects
include lactic acid buildup
and severe liver problems.
If you have a rash and
other symptoms
of an allergic reaction,
stop taking DOVATO and get
medical help right away.
Tell your doctor if you have
kidney or liver problems,
including hepatitis B or C.
Don't use DOVATO if you plan
to become pregnant
or during the first 12
weeks of pregnancy
since one of its ingredients may
harm your unborn baby.
Your doctor should do a
pregnancy test
before starting DOVATO.
Use effective birth control
while taking DOVATO.
The most common side effects
are headache,
diarrhea, nausea, trouble
sleeping, and tiredness.
So much goes into who I am
and hope to be.
Ask your doctor if starting
HIV treatment
with DOVATO is right
for you.
Narrator: STILL, DELEGATE
TIM HUGO STANDS WITH THE NRA.
TIM HUGO LED
THE REPUBLICAN EFFORT
TO BLOCK ANY
GUN SAFETY LAWS
EVEN UNIVERSAL
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
THE WASHINGTON POST
SAYS
TIM HUGO'S EXTREME
RECORD ON FIREARMS
SUGGEST HE'S NOT GOTTEN
THE MESSAGE THAT
GUN VIOLENCE IS A
MORTAL THREAT
TO THE
PUBLIC.
Dan: I'M DAN HELMER.
I SERVED IN IRAQ,
AFGHANISTAN AND KOREA
TO KEEP OUR FAMILIES SAFE.
I'M RUNNING FOR
DELEGATE AND SPONSORED THIS AD,
BECAUSE NOTHING
IS MORE IMPORTANT.
♪ ♪
>> Wendy: WE ARE BACK.
EVERYBODY HAVE A SEAT EXCEPT
FOR, HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> IT'S P23 MY NAME IS JAMES,
I'M 19.
I'M A SOPHOMORE IN COLLEGE.
>> Wendy: WHERE'D YOU GO?
>> I GO TO NOTRE DAME, YOU KNOW.
AND SO A LOT OF MY GUY FRIENDS
THERE, I WAS TALKING ABOUT MY
MOM, HOW HOT SHE IS, ALL THESE
VERY INAPPROPRIATE THINGS AND SO
FOR ME, I THINK IT'S VERY
INAPPROPRIATE AND WRONG BUT MY
MOM THINKS IT'S FUNNY AND SHE
ENCOURAGES IT WHEN SHE COMES TO
VISIT.
MOM IS HERE.
SO MY QUESTION FOR YOU IS, HOW
DO I TELL MY FRIENDS IT'S NOT
OKAY AND TELL MY MOM IT'S NOT
FUNNY?
US TO BE ONE YOU JUST HAVE.
I THINK A LOT OF MOMS LOOK GREAT
TO THEIR SONS FRIENDS.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FOR US TO
ENTICE THEM VERBALLY OR WEAKLY,
IF YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE ON A TIGHT
DRESS, THAT'S ONE THING.
AND FOR YOU, TALK TO YOUR
FRIENDS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET UPSET
ABOUT IT.
I'VE ALL READY TALKED TO HER,
DON'T HIT BACK, IT'S
UNCOMFORTABLE.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD LUCK.
ARE YOU THE COUSIN OF JANET
JACKSON?
I SEE SOMETHING.
GO AHEAD, YOU WEREN'T.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
>> I'M FROM PITTSBURGH, RECENTLY
A DAY CARE OWNER.
I'M ONLY 26.
A BOYFRIEND IS 40.
WE'VE BEEN DATING FOR ABOUT
THREE YEARS.
AND HE'S PRESSURING ME TO HAVE
KIDS.
IN MY BEING INCONSIDERATE, AM I
BEING SELFISH?
>> Wendy: DO YOU WANT KIDS?
>> LATER.
I FEEL LIKE WITH 26, I   I HAVE
TIME.
>> Wendy: YOU CERTAINLY DO BUT
THAT'S YOUR FAULT BEING WITH A
20-YEAR-OLD MAN.
BECAUSE THIS WOULD BE A
DEAL BREAKER.
>> Wendy: GOOD LUCK BEING
SINGLE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK BACK.
(AVO)
Do you push through migraine?
(MAN)
You ok to watch a movie?
(WOMAN)
Yes. I'll pick.
(AVO)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(WOMAN)
Here, catch!
(AVO)
When you're not fighting through
migraine,
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is a
preventive treatment
for migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you more
migraine-free days.
With Emgality, about 60% of
people had their migraine
days cut in half or more.
Don't use if allergic to
Emgality.
Allergic reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing can occur
even days after using.
Common side effects include
injection site reactions.
(WOMAN)
What should we watch tomorrow?
(AVO)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
And imagine more migraine-free
days.
WE WENT GET EXCLUSIVE CONTENT
AND MORE.
IT'S ALL GOING DOWN ON INSTAGRA
INSTAGRAM.
>> Wendy: TODAY'S AUDIENCE EYE
CANDY IS A BREAST CANCER
SURVIVOR.
IT'S OCTOBER AND THAT'S WHY
WE'RE CELEBRATING YOUR LIFE,
CHRISTINA.
WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
>> NEW YORK CITY.
>> Wendy: WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M IN REAL ESTATE.
>> Wendy: HOW YOU DOIN'?
TELL US WHERE YOU WERE WHEN HE
FOUND OUT AND WHAT WENT THROUGH
YOUR MIND AND THE HOW LONG YOU
BEEN CANCER FREE?
>> I WAS DOING SELF EXAM ON MY
COUCH AND THAT I WAS
MISDIAGNOSED FOR TWO YEARS BY
DOCTORS BECAUSE OF MY YOUNG AGE.
I WAS 30 WHEN I FOUND IT I WAS
32 WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED SO I
FOUND I HAD STAGE TWO
BREAST CANCER.
THEN I KNEW THAT SOMETHING WAS
DEFINITELY WRONG.
>> Wendy: WAS THEIR PAIN?
>> THERE WAS, ACTUALLY.
IT FELT LIKE A LITTLE BIT OF A
BRUISE.
>> Wendy: DID IT GET BIGGER?
>> IT DID, IT GOT BIGGER.
I FOUND ANOTHER ONE UNDER MY ARM
ALSO AND I KNEW MY INTUITION WAS
CORRECT AND I HAD TO FOLLOW THAT
AND I DEMANDED AN MRI WHICH THEN
DID FIND IT AND THEN I WAS
DIAGNOSED A WEEK LATER AFTER THE
MRI.
I HAVE BEEN CANCER FREE R 14
YEARS.
I'M VERY HAPPY AND I ALSO, I
HADN'T TOLD ABOUT 98% OF THE
PEOPLE THAT I'M FRIENDS WITH
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT ANYBODY TO
FEEL BAD FOR ME.
BECAUSE IT DIDN'T BREAK ME AND I
BETTER THAN I WAS BEFORE AND I
WROTE THIS BOOK TO JUST TELL
WOMEN TO LISTEN TO THEIR BODIES,
TO LISTEN TO YOUR INTUITION, AND
IT SAVED MY LIFE.
>> Wendy: YOU LOOK ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFUL.
I LOVE YOUR DRESS AND YOUR BELT
AND YOUR SHOES AND OBVIOUSLY
YOU'RE DOING BETTER THAN AFRICA,
BUT WE ALSO WANT TO GIVE YOU
$300 GIFT CARD TO SPEND WHEREVER
YOU WANT.
SO, HAPPY LIFE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
WE WILL BE RIG
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
ALL
(VO) If you live in Northern
Virginia
and you're eligible for
Medicare,
Anthem HealthKeepers can
help you
get a great plan at a great
rate!
Our Medicare Advantage plans
pay for many of the costs
original Medicare doesn't.
So you can focus on
other important decisions.
Anthem plans help protect you
from high medical costs.
Included this year, an allowance
for health items at Walmart.
Plus get dental coverage, vision
benefits,
prescription drug coverage
and access to over 15,000
fitness locations nationwide.
Now's the time to switch.
If you live in one of
the following counties,
you can get a plan with zero
dollar monthly premiums.
Call now.
The Medicare enrollment deadline
for Northern Virginia
is December 7th.
So call Anthem today at
1-855-626-1342
to learn more or to schedule
an in-person meeting.
FOR TICKETS, GO TO
WendyShow.com.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[♪♪]
Indulge Your Home.
The uplifting scent
of Tuscan fields
could only mean one thing
the powerful clean of Scentiva.
From Clorox.
Now, New York inspired shades.
Super Stay Matte Ink
from Maybelline New York.
Bold color.
Urban edge.
Liquid matte
formula.
Up to 16
hour wear.
Super Stay Matte Ink.
Only from Maybelline New York.
Get to Kohl's...
50% Off Sale this weekend!...
Plus - take an extra 20% off!...
Plus - take an extra $10 off
when you spend $50 or more!...
Plus - everyone gets $10 Kohl's
Cash for every $50 spent!
Stack the savings!...
This weekend - at Kohl's.