>>> A GAME 2 BLOWOUT IN
HOUSTON.
>> ROCKING IT OUT TO WRITE!
>> HAS NOT SPANS THINKING THEY
HAVE A CHANCE OF SWEEPING THEIR
WAY TO WORLD SERIES
CHAMPIONSHIP.
>>> ELIJAH CUMMINGS LIES IN
STATE OF THE CAPITAL THIS
AFTERNOON.
>>> I WAS REALLY SCARED.
>> IT IS SUPPOSED TO BE A NICE
WAY TO SURPRISED NEIGHBORS FOR
HALLOWEEN BUT THIS WOULD BE
TREAT COULD TURN INTO A VERY
SCARY TRICK.
>>> WE ARE GOING ON THAT'S ALL
NATS  TO CELEBRATE THIS DAY.
THE NATIONALS ARE HEADED HOME
TO CELEBRATE AT 2 GAME WIN IN
THE WASHINGTON WORLD SERIES.
THEY WERE TIED A 2 WHEN THE
INNING STARTED.
WHEN IT WAS OVER, THE NATIONALS
LED 8-2 WITH A 12-3 WIN.
WASHINGTON FANS WENT CRAZY
KNOWING THEIR TEAM MIGHT WIN
THE CHAMPIONSHIP THIS WEEKEND.
AS NICOLE TELLS US, THEY ARE
HOPING FOR ANOTHER WIN.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHERE YOU
CAN COME TO SHOW OFF YOUR DANCE
MOVES, YOUR BABY SHOCK AND JUST
HAVE FUN WITH ALL OF US.
THAT IS THE GOAL OF THIS EVENT.
WE ARE GOING TO BE HERE EVERY
SINGLE HOME GAME FROM 4:00 TO
8:00.
WE NOT ONLY HAVE THE DUGOUT BUT
WE ALSO HAVE THE STAGE THAT WAS
JUST SET UP WHERE OUR CREW HAS
BEEN WORKING LONG HOURS GETTING
THE LIGHTS UP, THE STAGE AND
THEY ARE EXCITED FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
THAT IS WHAT THE ENERGY HAS
BEEN LIKE HERE.
THERE HAS BEEN EXCELLENT
ENTHUSIASM, EXCITEMENT AND A
LOT OF PEOPLE SHOWED ENTHUSIASM
IN THEIR DANCE MOVES.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> WE WANTED SEE PEOPLE'S BEST
DUGOUT DANCE.
LET'S SEE WHAT THEY'VE GOT.
>> ♪ DUGOUT ♪
>> WE'VE BEEN ASKING EVERYONE
TO SEE THEIR DUGOUT DANCE.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>> --
>> OKAY.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> -- HE IS POINTING.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE A HOME
RUN.
>> ♪ DUGOUT ♪
>> THE BABY SHARK MOVE WORKS
EVERY SINGLE TIME.
>> LET'S SEE YOUR BABY SHARK.
>> GO, NATS !
>>> WE DO WANT TO KEEP A GOOD
LUCK GOING.
BEEN
>>
>> Reporter: THE SONG WAS
WRITTEN SPECIFICALLY BY SHIVA
FOR WUSA SO WE ARE  SO EXCITED
ABOUT THAT.
THIS IS THE PLACE YOU WANT TO
BE.
WE WILL BE HERE EVERY SINGLE
HOME GAME FROM 4:00 UNTIL 8:00.
THERE WILL BE GIVEAWAYS AND
MOST IMPORTANT, DUGOUT DANCING.
SO IF YOU WANT TO JOIN IN,
THERE WILL BE A PHOTO BOOTH AND
A BABY SHARK.
>> THAT WILL BE A LOT OF FUN.
NATS PARK IS GOING TO BE PACKED
TOMORROW.
COMING OUT WITH US, WE WILL BE
OUT THERE AGAIN, FOR ALL THE
HOME  GAMES AND THAT NATS
POSTGAME 3, 4 AND IF NEEDED, 5
TOMORROW NIGHT THROUGH SUNDAY
NIGHT.
YOU CAN CHECK OUT MORE ON THE
TEAM ANYTIME ON OUR WUSA9 APP
AND OF COURSE ON OUR WEBSITE,
WUSA.COM.
>>> THERE IS ANOTHER BIG D.C.
SPORTING EVENT TONIGHT.
THE REDSKINS ARE IN MINNESOTA
FOR THURSDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL.
THEY ARE FACING THEIR OLD
STARTING QUARTERBACK BUT NOT
ONLY THAT, ADRIAN PETERSON SAYS
DESPITE BEING BANGED UP, HE
WILL TAKE THE FIELD TONIGHT,
TOO AGAINST HIS OLD TEAM, AND
WASHINGTON IS IN SEARCH FOR A
SECOND WIN THIS WEEKEND AND THE
VIKINGS ARE 5 AND 2 PICS
>>> HEADING OUTSIDE THIS
AFTERNOON, A NICE FALL DAY
SHAPING UP.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
REALLY NICE OUT THERE.
60s AREA WHITE, 65 IN
GAITHERSBURG, 65 IN WALDORF AND
62 IN D.C. AT THIS HOUR.
THE NEXT FEW HOURS LOOK LIKE
THIS.
PLENTY OF SUNSHINE HANG AROUND,
UP TO 68 BY 4 AM  -- 4 PM, 65
BY 6 PM AND OVERNIGHT, FALL
THROUGH THE 50s.
THE HIGH IS 65 THROUGH 70 UNDER
SUNNY SKIES.
IT A NICE OUT THERE.
WE KNOW THAT THE NUTS GAME, THE
WORLD SERIES, I SHOULD SAY,
GAME 3 IS COMING HERE IN OUR
BACKYARD ON FRIDAY.
YOU MAY BE WONDERING WHAT THE
WEATHER WILL BE LIKE FOR YOUR
WATCH PARTY OR IF YOU'RE GOING
OUT TO THE BAR TO WATCH THE
GAME OR GOING TO THE GAME SO
HERE'S WHAT WE'VE GOT.
WE ARE THINKING THE SAME ON
FRIDAY IS GOING TO BE DRIVE.
THERE IS GOING TO BE A COLD
FRONT PASSING THROUGH ON FRIDAY
BUT WE WILL HAVE DRIER AIR IN
PLACE AND NOT ANTICIPATING A
LOT OF SHOWERS WITH THIS FRONT.
YOU WILL HAVE A FEW MORE
CLOUDS.
FRIDAY AT 7:30 PM, THERE ARE
CLOUDS THERE.
WE ARE LOOKING AT THE POTENTIAL
FOR A FEW SHOWERS ON SATURDAY
AND PAST SUNDAY MORNING, WE
WILL SEE HOW THAT COULD IMPACT
THE GAMES BUT SO FAR, FRIDAY,
IF YOU'RE HEADING OUT THERE,
LOOK FOR TEMPERATURES TO BE IN
THE 60s AS THE GAME IS STARTING
AND FALLING TO THE 50s AS THE
GAME WRAPS UP.
>>> RIGHT NOW, FINAL
PREPARATIONS ARE UNDERWAY AT
THE U.S. CAPITOL BEFORE ALL OF
US CAN PAY OUR RESPECTS TO
ELIJAH CUMMINGS.
STARTING AT 1:00, PEOPLE WILL
BE ALLOWED TO FILE PAST THE
CASKET.
THE VIEWING RUNS UNTIL 7 PM.
THE HEARSE CARRYING THE
MARYLAND DEMOCRATS BODY ARRIVED
THIS MORNING ALONG WITH FAMILY
AND FRIENDS INCLUDING
CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS FOR A
PRIVATE CEREMONY.
CUMMINGS DIED A WEEK AGO AT 68.
HIS FUNERAL WILL BE TOMORROW AT
HIS HOME CHURCH IN BALTIMORE.
FORMER PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA
IS EXPECTED TO DELIVER PART OF
THE EULOGY.
>>> BECAUSE REPRESENTATIVE
CUMMINGS IS LYING IN STATE,
THERE ARE ROAD CLOSURES THAT
MAY IMPACT YOU.
HERE'S WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW.
FIRST STREET FROM CONSTITUTION
AVENUE TO INDEPENDENCE AVENUE
WILL BE CLOSED AND EAST CAPITOL
STREET FROM FIRST STREET TO
SECOND IS SHUTDOWN AS WELL.
>>> SERVICES FOR ELIJAH
CUMMINGS HAVE PUT THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY ON HOLD.
COMMITTEE CHAIRS HAVE CANCELED
HEARINGS ON WITNESSES
APPEARANCES FOR TODAY AND
TOMORROW.
MEANWHILE, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
TURNING TO FELLOW REPUBLICANS
TO PUSH BACK AGAINST THE
INQUIRY.
THE GOP CONTROLLED THE SENATE
WHERE ACTION IS PLANT TODAY.
>> Reporter: SENATE REPUBLICANS
ARE INTRODUCING A RESOLUTION
CONDEMNING HOUSE DEMOCRATS FOR
CONNECTING CLOSED DOOR
DEPOSITIONS AS PART OF THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY.
>> TO URGE THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS
TO GIVE THE SAME RIGHTS TO THE
PRESENT TIME TRUMP AS CLINTON
AND NIXON HAD AND NOT DO THIS
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS.
>> Reporter: HOUSE REPUBLICANS
STAGED A PROTEST YESTERDAY,
SWARMING THE SECURE BRIEFING
ROOM WHERE INTERVIEWS WERE
HAPPENING AND REFUSED TO LEAVE
FOR 5 HOURS.
>> WHAT ARE THEY TRYING TO HIDE
FROM THE AMERICAN PEOPLE THAT
THEY WON'T ALLOW VOTING MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS TO HEAR WHAT IS
GOING ON IN THAT MOOD ROOM?
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY THAT
CLOSE HEARINGS ARE STANDARD TO
KEEP WITNESSES FROM SHARING
TESTIMONY.
>> THAT IS HOW IT HAS ALWAYS
BEEN DONE.
>> Reporter: WHILE LAWMAKERS
SQUABBLE OVER IMPEACHMENT
INQUIRY PROCESS, CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING INTO
WHETHER PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY
HAVE PRESSURED UKRAINE'S NEW
PRESIDENT EVEN BEFORE HE WAS
SWORN IN.
CBS NEWS HAS LEARNED UKRAINIAN
PRESIDENT ZELENSKY MET WITH HIS
TOP AIDE BACK IN MAY FOR 3
HOURS TO DISCUSS HOW TO AVOID
GETTING INVOLVED IN AMERICAN
POLITICS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND HIS
PERSONAL ATTORNEY, RUDY
GIULIANI WANTED UKRAINE TO
INVESTIGATE AN ENERGY COMPANY
THAT 4 VICE PRESIDENT JOE
BIDEN'S SON HUNTER WORK FOR AND
LOOKING INTO CONSPIRACY
THEORIES ABOUT THE DMC COMPUTER
SERVER TAPPED IN 2016.
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS A
INSTIGATE CITED A
CONGRATULATORY PHONE CALL WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> THEY DID NOT TELL ANY OF US
--
>> Reporter: PRESLEY --
PRESIDENT TRUMP INSISTS HE WAS
NEVER PRESSURING UKRAINE AND
THERE WAS NEVER A QUID PRO QUO.
>>> THE WASHINGTON POST IS
REPORTING DEMOCRATS COULD BEGIN
PUBLIC HEARINGS AS PART OF THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY AS SOON AS
MID-NOVEMBER.
>>> NOT TO THE LATEST
INFORMATION ON A METRO STRIKE
THAT COULD IMPACT YOUR RIDE
HOME ESPECIALLY IF YOU ARE IN
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
METROWEST PUTTER ACCOUNT FIRST
ANNOUNCED THAT SOME LINES ARE
RUNNING ON A SUNDAY SCHEDULED
DUE TO A STRIKE IN AND TWEETED
THERE WAS NO SERVICE ON THOSE
LINES.
A STRIKE BY WORKERS AT A
METROWEST GARAGE IN HORTON,
VIRGINIA WAS RECENTLY
PRIVATIZED.
THE UNION AND OPERATORS ARE
WORKING TO WORK OUT A DEAL OF
THE NEW COLLECTIVE BARGAINING
AGREEMENT.
>>> THE LATEST CALIFORNIA
WELFARE IS IN THE STATES FAMOUS
WINE COUNTRY AND THIS
AFTERNOON, IT SPARKED EMERGENCY
EVACUATION ORDERS.
MORE ON THAT COMING UP.
>>> PLUS FEAR THAT A HOLLOWING
SURPRISE WHICH WAS INTENDED AS
A TREAT COULD LEAD TO SOMEONE
GETTING HURT.
>>> AND IT IS A NICE FALL DAY
ACROSS THE DMV BUT WILL THE
She wanted a roommate to help
with the cooking.
But she wanted someone who loves
cats.
So, we got Griswalda.
Dinner's almost ready.
But one thing we could both
agree on
was getting GEICO to help with
our renters insurance.
Yeah, switching and saving
was really easy!
Drink it all up. Good!
Could have used a little salt.
Visit geico.com
and see how easy saving on
renters insurance can be.
Narrator: STILL, DELEGATE
TIM HUGO STANDS WITH THE NRA.
TIM HUGO LED
THE REPUBLICAN EFFORT
TO BLOCK ANY
GUN SAFETY LAWS
EVEN UNIVERSAL
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
THE WASHINGTON POST
SAYS
TIM HUGO'S EXTREME
RECORD ON FIREARMS
SUGGEST HE'S NOT GOTTEN
THE MESSAGE THAT
GUN VIOLENCE IS A
MORTAL THREAT
TO THE
PUBLIC.
Dan: I'M DAN HELMER.
I SERVED IN IRAQ,
AFGHANISTAN AND KOREA
TO KEEP OUR FAMILIES SAFE.
I'M RUNNING FOR
DELEGATE AND SPONSORED THIS AD,
BECAUSE NOTHING
IS MORE IMPORTANT.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
LET'S GET TO THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENTS FROM ENGLAND.
TODAY, BRITISH POLICE CONFIRMED
39 PEOPLE FOUND DEAD IN A
CONTAINER TRUCK WERE CHINESE
CITIZENS.
THE BODIES OF 31 MEN AND 8
WOMEN WERE IN THE CONTAINER.
IT PASSED THROUGH A PORT IN
BELGIUM TUESDAY BEFORE BEING
DISCOVERED YESTERDAY NEAR
LONDON.
POLICE ARE QUESTIONING THE 25-
YEAR-OLD TRUCK DRIVER AND
SEARCHED SEVERAL SPOTS NEAR HIS
HOME IN NORTHERN IRELAND.
>>> THE LATEST BIG CALIFORNIA
WILDFIRE HAS TORCHED MORE THAN
15 SQUARE MILES AND IS
PROMPTING EVACUATIONS IN SONOMA
COUNTY, PART OF ONE COUNTRY
JUST NORTH OF SAN FRANCISCO.
FIREFIGHTERS ARE BATTLING MORE
THAN JUST THE FLAMES.
WINDS IN THE AREA HAVE GUSTED
UP TO 70 MILES PER HOUR.
>> THAT IS THE BIGGEST
CHALLENGE IS BEING ABLE TO
ACTUALLY DO SOME FIREFIGHTING
WITHOUT IT JUMPING OVER OUR
LINES SO WE REALLY NEED THE
WINDS TO COOPERATE.
>> EVEN IN THE AREA NOT
DIRECTLY EVACUATED BY THE FIRE,
WINDS ARE HITTING SPACE BETWEEN
30 AND 50 MILES PER HOUR AND
THE FORECAST FOR THOSE HIGH
WINDS HAS LED TO ANOTHER
MASSIVE BLACK UP.
PG&E SHUT OFF HIS LINES TO TRY
TO PREVENT A LIVE WIRE FROM
CAUSING A WILDFIRE.
>>> THE NEW YORK CITY POLICE
OFFICER WHO WAS FIRED FOR
PUTTING ERIC GARNER IN A
CHOKEHOLD IS SUING TO GET HIS
JOB BACK.
DANIEL PANTALEO FILED THE SUIT
WEDNESDAY.
HE WAS FIRED IN AUGUST WITH IN
FIVE YEARS AFTER GARNER'S
DEATH.
WAS PUT IN A CHOKEHOLD AFTER
BEING ARRESTED FOR SELLING
LOOSE AND UNPACKED CIGARETTES.
GARNER SAID, "I CAN'T BREATHE.
" OVER AND OVER AGAIN BEFORE HE
DIED.
>>> HARVEY WEINSTEIN IS
ACCUSING LAWYERS OF
RACKETEERING TO -- BEFORE SHE
WENT PUBLIC WITH CLAIMS THAT
WEINSTEIN HER.
McGOWAN HAS WRITTEN TWO BOOKS --
ABOUT THE ALLEGATIONS.
>>> SHARES FELL 20% BEFORE
TODAY'S OPENING BELL OF 20
BECAUSE IT REPORTED A NET
QUARTER INCOME OF $37 MILLION,
NEARLY $70 MILLION LESS IN THE
SAME PERIOD LAST YEAR.
DESPITE GROWTH IN USERS,
TWITTER HAS ALREADY LOWERED ITS
OUTLOOK FOR THE FOURTH QUARTER.
>>> HALLOWEEN IS ONE WEEK FROM
TODAY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
WHEN KIDS IN COSTUMES SHOW UP
AT YOUR DOOR AND ASK, TRICK OR
TREAT, BUT ONE EFFORT TO HAVE
SOME FUN WITH NEIGHBORS COULD
BE SO TRICKY THAT IT IS REALLY
NOT SAFE.
REPORTER, LAUREN TELLER IN
CHECKS OUT WHAT HAPPENED TO ONE
WOMAN IN HOUSTON.
>> Reporter: THESE ARE THE
SCARES YOU EXPECT AROUND
HALLOWEEN.
BUT IT IS THIS THAT HAD CAMELLIA
TRULY FREAKED.
>> IT COULD BE JUST SO
DANGEROUS.
>> Reporter: IT HAPPENED LAST
WEEK WHEN THIS MOTHER OF 4 WAS
SPENDING TIME WITH HER FAMILY
AT NIGHT.
>> WE WERE JUST ALL SITTING,
WATCHING TV.
THE DOORBELL RANG.
AND WHEN I LOOKED AT MY PHONE,
THERE WAS JUST AN IMAGE OF A
PERSON WITH A PAPER BAG OVER
THEIR HEAD.
I WAS REALLY SCARED.
>> Reporter: THE MYSTERY GUEST
LEFT THE PAPER BAG ON THE FRONT
STOOP AND LEFT.
CAMELLIA POSTED ON NEXT DOOR
ASKING IF ANYONE KNEW WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
>> IMMEDIATELY I STARTED
GETTING FEEDBACK FROM NEIGHBORS
SAYING OH, YOU PROBABLY HAVE
BEEN BOOED.
>> GETTING BOOED IS WHEN
SOMEBODY ANONYMOUSLY LEISURE
LAKE HALLOWEEN TREAT ALONG WITH
A POEM AND SIGN TO PUT IN YOUR
WINDOW AND THEN YOU ARE
INSTRUCTED TO BOO TO OTHERS.
>> I WASN'T AWARE THIS IS
SOMETHING PEOPLE DO.
>> Reporter: SOME NEIGHBORS
LOVE THE IDEA BUT OTHERS, NOT
SO MUCH.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE SAYING,
IF YOU CAME TO MY DOORBELL, I
WOULD HAVE, YOU COULD HAVE
GOTTEN SHOT.
YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU REALLY
SHOULD NOT BE DOING.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHAT WAS
LEFT ON CAMELLIAS DOORSTEP,
INNOCENT TREATS FROM A
NEIGHBOR.
BUT SHE WORRIES THAT OTHERS WHO
DON'T LIKE TO BE TRICKED COULD
MAKE A VERY SCARY MISTAKE.
>> ALL OF THESE THINGS
HAPPENING IN THE WORLD TODAY,
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW.
IT IS KIND OF A DANGEROUS IDEA.
IT IS A GREAT GESTURE BUT
SOMEONE CAN GET HURT IF YOU
RING THE WRONG DOORBELL.
>>> NOW, YOUR WUSA  WEATHER
FORECAST, SPONSORED BY COX.
>>> SO I KNOW EVERYONE HAS GAME
3 AND 4 AND MAYBE 5 ON THEIR
MINDS TODAY.
>> I KNOW.
WHAT'S THE WEATHER LOOKING
LIKE?
>> I HOPE IT DOESN'T GO TO A 5.
WE WANT A SWEEP.
LET'S SWEEP THIS THING.
>>> WEATHER IS COOPERATING
NICELY FOR THE FIRST -- THE
THIRD MAKE GAME AND PERHAPS
EVEN THROUGH THE FOURTH GAME.
IT IS GORGEOUS OUTSIDE.
THE CALL FALL COLORS ARE NOT
OUT YET BUT WE WILL GET THERE
EVENTUALLY BUT I HAVE 60
AREAWIDE, 61 INDIANAPOLIS RIGHT
NOW.
THE NEXT FEW HOURS WE WILL
CONTINUE TO SEE THE SUNSHINE
AND TEMPERATURES STAYING IN THE
60s UNDER THE ABUNDANCE OF
SUNSHINE.
57 BY 10:00 TONIGHT.
THE 50s EVENTUALLY WILL COME.
THE HIGHS TODAY 65 TO 70.
THE PERFECT FALL DAY.
WE STARTED COLD THIS MORNING
WITH 30s AND 40s AND NOW WE
WILL SEE 60s AND 70s THIS
AFTERNOON.
WHAT WE WILL BE WATCHING FOR
FRIDAY IS A COLD FRONT TO MAKE
ITS WAY THROUGH THE AREA.
HERE IS THE DEAL.
DRY AIR IN PLACE, NOT EXPECTING
ANY SHOWERS OUT OF IT AND
HARDLY A BIG TEMPERATURE
CHANGE.
FRIDAY WE NOTICED A FEW MORE
CLOUDS OUT THERE BUT FRIDAY
NIGHT IS LOOKING DRY SO GAME 3
GOES OFF WITHOUT A HITCH.
THIS IS SATURDAY AT 3 PM, SOME
CLOUDS, TEMPERATURES IN THE 60s
AND PERHAPS ABOUT 5 DEGREES
COOLER THAN FRIDAY.
THIS IS WHAT 8:00, NOT PICKING
UP ON SHOWERS DURING THIS
SCENARIO BUT THE POSSIBILITY IS
THERE IS THE LOW PRESSURE
SYSTEM APPROACHES.
I DO THINK THAT THE BULK OF
THOSE SHOWERS WILL NOT COME
UNTIL LATER ON SATURDAY NIGHT
SO WITH ANY LUCK, WE ARE JUST
HAVING CLOUDS DURING THE GAME
AND SHOWERS STARTING AFTER THE
GAME.
SO FRIDAY, I WATCH PARTY YOU
ARE GOING TO?
TEMPERATURES AROUND 63 TO START
THE GAME AND THEN WILL BE IN
THE UPPER 50s AS THE GAME
BEGINS TO WRAP UP.
TO BRING THE JACKET OUT THERE
TO STAY COMFORTABLE.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE FORECAST.
60s FOR GAME 3. GAME FOUR, 50s,
A BIT COOLER DURING GAME TIME
SATURDAY AND THERE IS THAT
SLIGHT CHANCE FOR A SHOWER.
IF IT HAS TO GO ALL THE WAY TO
GAME 5, 60 TO 65, I DON'T THINK
WE WILL SEE SHOWERS ON SUNDAY
IF WE DO HAVE TO HAVE A GAME 5.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE NEXT
SYSTEM COMING IN.
NEXT WEEK, NOT ONLY ARE WE
LOOKING AT MORE RAIN BUT ALSO
THE POTENTIAL FOR VERY CHILLY
TEMPERATURES AS WE HEAD INTO
HALLOWING AND AS WE CALL CLOSE
OUT OCTOBER AND WELCOME IN
NOVEMBER.
TUESDAY AT 5:30, I DO THINK WE
GO DRY AT THIS POINT WITH
CLOUDS WEDNESDAY, SOME SHOWERS
AS THE CLOUDS APPROACH THE
AREA, THE COLD AIR BEHIND IT
THURSDAY INTO FRIDAY.
WEDNESDAY AT 9 AM, SHOWERS AND
BY WEDNESDAY AT 530 IN THE
AFTERNOON, WE WOULD BE LOOKING
AT RAIN AT SOME POINT.
THEN TEMPERATURE START TO TRAIL
OFF.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE DROP
FOR A MOMENT.
THERE HAS BEEN AN IMPROVEMENT
WITH ALL OF THE RAIN THAT WE
SEE.
SO FAR, MORE THAN 3 FEET INCHES
OF RAIN IN THE MONTH OF OCTOBER
AND THAT HAS HELPED TO MAKE UP
THE DEFICIT THAT WE HAD IN
SEPTEMBER.
FOR NOW, A MODERATE DROUGHT
GOING ON IN D.C. BUT  THE
FORECAST IS FOR THAT START TO
IMPROVE AS WE HAVE MORE RAIN
CHANCES AS I JUST MENTIONED.
SOMEONE SATURDAY HEADING INTO
SUNDAY AND EVEN SOME COMING IN
NEXT WEEK ON WEDNESDAY.
WE DO STILL HAVE A SEVERE
DROUGHT IN PARTS OF FAUQUIER
AND LOVING COUNTY, A SMALL AREA
THERE.
OTHER AREAS ARE ABNORMAL DRIVE.
HERE'S THE 7-DAY FORECAST, HIGH
TEMPERATURES DARE 70, UPPER 60s
FRIDAY, 6570, NEAR 70 SUNDAY
AND WE ARE EXPECTING THE BULK
OF THE SHOWERS IN THE MORNING
AND NOT MUCH COOLING BEHIND
THAT SYSTEM.
STILL IN THE LOW 70s ON MONDAY.
>>> NUTS FANS HOPE THEIR TEAM
WILL GET OUT FOR A WORLD SERIES
SWEEP.
(VO)
This is Annie.
And this is Annie paying back
her friend for the tickets with
Zelle® before the previews
start.
And this is Annie getting ready
to enjoy the show.
[whispers]
This is your right here,
right now bank.
This Is Wells Fargo.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO.
THE NATIONALS ARE COMING HOME
TODAY FOR GAMES 3, 4 AND 5
STARTING TOMORROW NIGHT.
THOUSANDS OF FANS WILL BE AT
THE PARK IN SOUTHEAST WHICH
BACKS UP TO THE RIVER BUT THAT
LIMITS THE NUMBER OF LAND
ENTRANCES.
THERE IS ANOTHER WAY.
>> Reporter: I STEPPED ON BOARD
WHAT IS ABOUT TO BE A NATIONALS
PARTY BOAT.
LANDS FANS WILL FLOAT RIGHT TO
THE DOORSTEP OF THE WORLD
SERIES.
DAVE LANGA, CAPTAIN OF THESE
RIVERBOATS IS ADDING EXTRA
SERVICE FROM THE CITY MARINA.
3 BOATS WILL GO TO HOME DAYS
GAMES ON FRIDAY, SATURDAY AND
SUNDAY.
>> WE ARE THE EASIEST WAY TO
TRAVEL TO THE NATS GAMES.
>> Reporter: THE ENTIRE RIDE
TAKES A HALF AN HOUR.
THE HOPE IS IT RUN SMOOTHLY.
>> IT WILL START RIGHT AWAY
BEFORE WE EVEN DEPART.
>> Reporter: BOAT OWNERS WILL
DOCKET NEARBY YARDS AT THE
ARENA.
LIPS FILL UP QUICKLY.
THE MARINA SAYS THERE IS
ALREADY A WAITING LIST.
NOW IT IS ON THESE YELLOW BOATS
TO TURN NATS PARK INTO A SEA OF
RED.
>> IT IS A GOOD PRO NATS PARTY
AND WE ARE HOPING TO GET A GOOD
WIN.
>> Reporter: AND ALEXANDER,
PETE FONTAINE,  WUSA9.
>>> TACKLE YOUR  TAILGATE IS
SPONSORED BY XFINITY.
>>> THIS IS YOUR TACKLE YOUR
TAILGATE FORECAST SPONSORED BY
>>> WELCOME BACK.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE IS MORE
TORN ABOUT THIS WORLD SERIES
THAN HOUSTON POLICE OFFICER,
RONALD BRADBURY.
YOU SEE HE COACHED BASEMENT
ANTHONY RODON IN LITTLE LEAGUE
AND THE TWO UNITED THIS WEEK.
COACH RON SAYS HE IS ROOTING
FOR HIS FORMER PLAYER AND
HOMETOWN TEAM SO HE WILL BE
HAPPY NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
A WIN-WIN FOR EVERYONE.
>> THAT IS THE SITUATION TO BE
IN.
>>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE 7-DAY
FORECAST.
TEMPERATURES AROUND 70 TODAY,
UPPER 60s FRIDAY, SHOWER
SATURDAY AND I DO THINK THEY
HOLD OFF UNTIL LIKELY AFTER THE
GAME OR TOWARD THE END OF THE
GAME.
THERE WILL BE SHOWERS SUNDAY
MORNING. IF THERE IS A GAME 5,
I BELIEVE AT THAT POINT THE
SHOWERS WILL HAVE PASSED.
SO EVEN THEN IT WILL BE DRY.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
THAT'S IT
Stay safe man.
See you when you get back.
Count on it.
Hey babygirl, Daddy's gotta go
for a bit.
I'll be back.
I promise.
Come here.
Goodnight sweetie.
Goodnight mommy.
Can we try without the hat?
At Dominion Energy, one in every
five new hires is a veteran.
We're grateful for the many
sacrifices you make.